下來
In the middle of the river,
I saw the sunrise
I dropped my love stone
Then I jumped to my shoe
I wonder if I'm going to be a tycoon who was a jokin
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is a Katsushika Kameari
There is no change in my yawn
The cityscape is so kind
From the fountain of the Tongari Boshi
To the Taishakuten
The sunset falls
I'll wake up tomorrow and finish it
Hey, Katsushika Shibamata
I've lost my happiness again
I've noticed it
Because I'm an idiot
What should I do?
Ryo-san
I'll give it to you
If I don't get it now, I won't get it again
Please put it on
No.
It's been accumulated for the last year
Only cash
If you are annoying, go home
There are people who want to get it
I looked at people's feet
If it becomes like this
Take the thief
Thief!
There you go!
Haha! I did it!
I should have just used half of it.
I spent all my money.
I don't know how I'm going to get my payday.
For now, I'm going to pass this time.
Hmm?
Iyan旅行, huh?
Alright!
What?
Senpai is going to do the kanji for the next Iyan旅行?
Are you serious, Ryo?
Yeah, I'm serious.
I've decided to take the volunteer spirit and do it for everyone.
As expected of you, Ryo-sama. You're great.
But...
You were so arrogant last year that you said you had a high budget.
That's right.
You said you could only drink half of the kanji.
Senpai, you're thinking of something that doesn't make sense.
I'm not.
No!
Remember last year's Iyan旅行!
The time when the chief did the kanji!
So you're going to the amusement park on a Sunday day?
After all, you got on the bus in the middle of the night.
There's no other option but the bus.
I suppose.
The time when you can't go to the amusement park and the bus stops and starts to run.
Yes, I got it.
Well, you seem to have forgotten the signs.
Well, we'll go for a walk.
We won't.
As I expected.
Why aren't you here?
Well, it's kind of sad.
Pack everything you need.
But why is Oto gonna be the only one who gets to go?
Remember.
I'm sure.
I'm sure he knew the kanji for "Mee Kanji"
just by shouting out loud.
Normally, he wouldn't know that.
Eh?
You're too sweet!
You're too sweet, Nakagawa!
You can say "Mee Kanji"
only if you think of all the situations.
Oh, I see.
The mistake is that you usually leave the kanji
to the leader.
Eating at an amusement park, karaoke?
The typical course is also a good place.
I can't feel any sense.
I don't think I can say kanji
to that stupid, honest stone head.
I can't even say kanji to him.
Well, I...
I...
Chief!
Now I know what you're trying to say.
You're saying you're the best
at this trip, right?
No, I'm not!
I'm saying that I can speak kanji!
You think you can do it?
I can!
I'll show you how to enjoy
a trip that's 100 times more enjoyable
than the chief's trip with a budget of 5,000 yen per person!
You can do it!
Ryo, you can do it!
If you can do it, try it!
If this is a trip that's a little boring,
you're going to pay for it!
Okay.
But, if you're good at it,
please keep my instruction manual for a while.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, that's fine.
This is the price of everyone's fame.
I got it.
Cruising with a cruiser?
Is that budget okay?
Leave it to me.
I have a good reputation in various places.
Well, that's just a sample.
Then I'll go get it right away.
If you give me 1,000 yen, it's 4,000 yen each.
That's my profit.
You're smart, Ryo.
You're eating while listening to a live band on a cruiser.
This year's trip is really cool.
It's true.
It's like a little beret.
I wanted to ride a cruiser once.
I don't want to get seasick.
It's okay.
I can't shake a cruiser.
Good morning.
Good morning, chief.
Good morning, Ohara.
Chief, thank you for your busy schedule.
Good morning.
No, no.
This trip is quite luxurious.
Isn't it a good plan for a 10,000-year-old Ryotsu?
Well, yeah.
But I'm sure you're really okay, Ohara.
I'm fine.
Maybe.
But you're late, Ryotsu.
I can already see that.
I thought they said they're meeting at 10:00.
Yeah.
But I'm curious.
Can a cruiser make a live band with only a 5,000-yen budget?
Yeah.
Hi, guys.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh, you're finally here.
Wow!
Look, that's the ship!
Wow, that's great.
Awesome, senpai.
What a wonderful cruiser!
It's more than I imagined!
Wow!
It went too far.
Hey! This way!
Everyone!
This is it!
What is that?
You can tell by looking at it.
It's a yacht.
Isn't that a cruiser?
That's right! That's right!
You're talking about the wrong thing!
This is a great Japanese cruiser.
Now, don't complain.
Get on!
How is it?
The Japanese is in full swing, right?
The roof is full of holes.
That's right!
That's why you can swim in the sun
and have a natural encounter.
The tatami mats are also very painful.
Hey, chief!
Don't put too much weight on it.
It's rotten.
What?
Well, well, don't look so scared.
Let's enjoy the trip.
Ryozu, this is 5,000 yen.
Chief, instead, the food is...
That's right, Ohara.
Even if the ship is shabby,
the food should be delicious.
Fresh fish can be eaten, right?
That's right!
Fresh fish are the best.
That's right.
Well, then, please enjoy the fishing.
What are you doing?
What is this?
I told you.
We're going to have a grand fishing.
Oh, that's right.
The chief, Nakagawa, Honda,
Reiko and the girls
are going to the sea.
Hey, Ryo.
We don't go fishing.
That's right!
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
What?
The fish we caught today
will be the main dish of the day.
Then you're not going to go.
What?
We don't go fishing.
We'll go fishing ourselves.
This is the new way of the Ian trip.
If we don't go fishing,
everyone will be eating fresh sashimi.
So we're going to try it.
It's okay.
We'll help you.
I'll help you.
Oh, thank you.
That's wonderful.
It's different from you.
What do you mean?
It feels good
just to be in the sea.
It's good to be in the sea.
Oh, it smells.
This is the chief's fish.
It smells.
Look, I did it.
As expected of the chief.
Ryo, I came here too.
Oh, me too.
Oh, it's a professional.
Don't do it, Mario.
I'll do it, too.
Okay.
Everyone, please enjoy.
Honda,
you're always fishing for sea bream.
I'm fishing for this.
Well, it's okay.
Sea bream tempura is delicious.
What's wrong, chief?
You're not fishing at all.
Shut up.
It's just the beginning.
I'm fishing for sea bream and mini puffer fish.
When I become the chief,
I have to catch tuna or whale.
It hurts.
Don't say tuna or whale.
Anyway, Ryo,
you don't have to fish for yourself?
I'm a kanji.
I'll eat while everyone's fishing.
If I become a kanji,
I'll have a lot of trouble.
Ryo,
I'll do my best
to fish for you.
Yeah.
More importantly,
I don't have to do it for the chief if I don't have any fish.
You have to pay 5,000 yen
and fish for yourself.
Oh, here it comes again.
Ohara is really fun.
Here it comes.
This is a big one.
Ohara, you can do it.
You got this!
You can do it!
You do it!
You did it!
Help me.
You're awesome, chief.
You're doing well.
I'm not gonna let you get away!
Yes sir!
Bujo!
Ye-... Get away!
I-I-!
So, it's like the fire engine of a ship...
What are you doing, Bujo?
You should be fishing instead of the fire engine!
But Senpai,
doesn't that fire engine
belong to this boat?
Don't you dare touch it!
Please continue fishing!
I can't believe I'm fishing in this boat.
I should hide this one somewhere.
Oh no!
I can't laugh.
It was pretty fun.
Fishing is easy.
Everyone, good job.
Everyone sit down.
Sit down, sit down.
The chief is here.
Hey, I'm the chief.
I'm not going to sit down.
Don't say that.
Today is break day.
And the chief is a guest.
The chief is in charge of this trip.
But...
Ohara, you don't have to say no to me.
But something is wrong with the boat.
What?
Don't worry.
Listen to me, chief.
No matter what happens,
you must not move.
Everyone, give the chief a round of applause!
It's delicious.
You can eat the tempura with your teeth.
Hey, I really want to eat.
If you want, I can...
Everyone, give the chief a round of applause.
Hey, I can eat the tempura with my teeth.
Please, give him a round of applause.
I think there is a lot of alcohol.
Now, welcome to the Karaoke competition
by a fancy live band playing.
Karaoke competition by a fancy live band playing.
What is this?
Isn't it a war ship?
That's right.
Back then,
they used to do a comedy show on Asakusa Rock.
I know, but what's the boat like?
Don't worry.
It is a self-propelled ship.
Self-propelled?
Is this the latest equipment for this ship?
I'm a bit worried.
I'll go check it out.
Chief, you can't move.
Get out of the way.
What's this?
Chief, you can't move.
I told you not to move.
Ryo!
Senpai!
Ryo again!
Senpai, you'll sink if you keep going.
What?
Ryo!
Get the key out of the package!
What do you mean?
Take this!
I can't do this.
Stop it.
If you keep going,
Ryo will hit you.
Make them happy!
Thank you very much.
You have my respect.
I am sorry.
The ship has come home.
The ship was such a soon dessert.
Its why we need a closest one for them.
This ship has a strong shaking.
Ame brought this for us.
I don't think this will change the fact that I'm outside.
What's going on, Ryozu?
Yes, yes. I've prepared a proper umbrella for this time.
Oh, don't get too excited.
However, it's a rental, so one person will get 200 yen.
What did you say?
I don't need that!
It's starting to rain.
I don't like this.
Seriously? I don't like this.
Senpai, you should go back to the ship.
Don't say unnecessary things.
It's natural for the ship to shake.
What's wrong?
I... I'm lost. I feel bad.
That's because you don't have enough to drink.
If you drink alcohol, you won't feel lost.
This is ridiculous.
Yes, it's karaoke.
The Karaoke Tournament of Forgetting Storms.
First, the first person to leave the boat is me.
I'm Yujirou Irihara.
I'm Yuyabooishinbo.
That sounds amazing.
This is really bad, Ryo.
Huh? I'm coming too!
I've found a
Help me.
That's right.
Baloo, you're being a big hit.
You're such a big hit.
You idiot.
If Sendou gets drunk, who will be the winner?
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
This is when you get to use your hobbies.
Come on.
You idiot!
Ryo, you did something again.
I don't want to imagine it.
The boat is going up the river.
Sintell the boat.
The river shrank.
Oh, no!
It's gone from Sumida River to Kanda River.
What?
We're being pushed out like a Swan.
This boat is more serious than a regular boat.
Right?
The roof has been peeled off!
Sorry to you, but it's dangerous.
Let's call for help from Nakagawa Taibatsu.
Hello? It's me.
I can't do this anymore.
What's going to happen now? What will be our fate?
I don't want to!
It's not that you don't want to!
It's because you don't know what's going to happen!
This is the joy of traveling.
It's truly a new Iyan Trip!
If we keep going like this, we'll be in for a storm!
Get some water!
Get your balance!
Reiko, stay in the middle!
Nakagawa and the chief, to the left!
The others, split into two groups!
Get some water!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
It's strange that we don't have to do anything.
If we can get home alive, we'll remember this, Ryo.
I'm getting dizzy!
Watch out!
It can't be!
Do something, Ryo!
Mister, the signal's pretty good!
I understand!
That was aane.
How'd get this one done so fast?
That's impossible!
Take a look!
The shaft of the screw is broken.
The train is moving faster than before.
It seems to be sucked in.
What?
It's the entrance of the subway.
It's on the train!
Min-chan! Ryo-chan!
The train is coming!
Stop it!
I'm saved!
It's not that bad!
Good job!
What are you doing?
Don't be scared!
Enjoy it!
This is not fun!
It's not!
It's not fun!
You did it!
That's it!
It hurts!
Stop it!
They fight a lot in this situation.
It hurts!
There they are!
They went to the tea fountain!
To be continued.
Wh-what do you think, chief?
You didn't feel bored for a second, did you?
I-I'm an idiot.
Hey, Ryo. You're the only one with money.
One of you isn't worth a dime.
R-Ryo!
Senpai.
Ryo!
Y-you know what...
What's the matter?
Well, it's...
Well...
Ryosu!
I thought you were acting weird, but you were really just fooling around!
Wait a minute!
My money!
Hey, Ryosu!
My money! My money!
You idiot!
I'll give you three minutes to cool your head!
Please stop, chief! My money!
To be continued
Hey, Eigo!
You finally got married after looking at the wedding photos and sighing?
What?
Do you want me to destroy this wedding?
If you go with your usual style, I'll refuse!
There's no doubt about it!
Next time, I'll show you the strategy to reverse the ball!
See you then!
There's a rumor that a woman who can't fall in love
has a lot of things she wants to do
I want to ride a bike through the vast desert
I want to be freer than a bird
A lady's dream that changes with the speed of a full moon
My love, I'm sorry, wait
The future of the panorama is a dazzling light
You know that, right?
I'm sorry, wait
It's the way I want to be
I still don't know what happened
To be continued
It's not that I can't say anything