"When you're watching TV, light up your room and look away!"
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
It'll be alright eventually
I have no job
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds and the burning clouds
It'll be alright eventually
You know what to do, right?
If you do, then come to me!
It's been a year since I entered the 21st century
But crimes don't go away at once
On the contrary, they increase
My special detective also pays full attention to the increasing crime every day
and the ability to deal with them.
However, our ability to deal with them is also reaching its limit.
That's why, this time, we're going to be adding a new special system.
That name is...
"The Transparent Giant Appears!"
The Transparent Giant Appears!
And so, I have appointed you to become a special detective!
So, I told you I don't want to be a member of the pervert group!
What?
My...
Where are you calling me a pervert?!
That's what I'm talking about!
Why are you so sad? You're the chief of the council and the chief of the council,
and you're acting like a weirdo!
Then, don't worry.
This time, you don't even need to wear a suit.
What kind of pose are you going to do? That's your choice.
Huh? Really?!
Yeah.
Why? Because you're going to be a transparent person.
Transparent person?!
What is this?!
Kurokuro! Kurokuro! Kurokuro! Kurokuro! Kuro-suke!
Kei-koro! Kei-koro!
Yu-oh!
Professor Ezaki...
Ryo-san, is this...
It might be Pink Lady!
When you hear "transparent human," the first thing a Japanese thinks of is Pink Lady!
But isn't that song "Yu-oh"?
Gink!
Y-Yes, it is!
Actually, I can't help but remember the intro of "Transparent Human."
What are you here for?
Invisible Liquid!
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa!
By drinking this liquid, you can become a transparent human!
And become a special detective, Transparent Deka.
That's a no!
Did you really do the experiment?
You don't have to worry about the details.
In short, I'm the experiment team, right?
Every time, they're all ridiculous!
Ehem...
Hehehe.
Handsome, you seem to no longer perform as Transparent Deka.
What?
Aah!
What's lying here!?
Huh?
I-it's so transparent!
What?
Oh...
Ah...
Ah!
While you were outside...
Huh?
I thought it was Seen in the Water.
Professor Ezaki gave it to you.
I put the invisible liquid in there.
What an excellent collaboration play.
You guys are dirty!
I'm doing this to destroy crime.
You guys are like criminals!
Your body is...
It disappeared!
I've never seen a transparent human before.
I can't see it though.
It's my body!
Are you that happy?
I can see your happy face!
I can't see it because it's transparent.
What?
Ryotsu, when you're officially assigned to the Special Investigation Department, your salary will be three times as much as before.
In addition, you'll receive special treatment for all your travel.
I don't want to be fooled by such a sweet word.
He's definitely smiling.
There's no mistake.
What?
You guys can't see my face, can you?
I can see it even if I can't see it.
It's decided.
Then take off your clothes.
What?
If you wear clothes, there's no point in being a transparent human.
R-right.
I understand.
Take it off.
It's transparent inside.
Don't stare at it.
I can't see anything.
Hey, do I have to take this off?
Of course.
Even if you know that you can't see, it's hard to take off your pants in front of people.
How about this?
Oh!
When the transparent department carries out its missions, it must always be in line.
That's why you were chosen, a person who can never catch a cold even in the morning.
I knew you would say that.
Yes.
Hmm...
It's me.
I understand. I'll be right back.
I've got a job.
I'm Tomoe Deka Ryo-tsuwa.
Until I'm officially assigned to the Special Police Department, I will continue my work as I have been.
Well then...
I should get going now.
Wait a minute!
How am I supposed to get back to normal?
You're still a transparent human being.
You don't have to worry about getting back to normal.
I'm worried about what you've made!
"A place where the winter comes and the spring comes."
"There's a beginning and an end to everything."
"Any great invention can eventually be destroyed."
So you're saying we have to wait for the destruction to be over and we can get back to normal?
That's...
God knows.
What?
When you get back to normal, you'll be able to contact me.
Well then, goodbye!
Ugh...
What's going on?
Are you laughing?
I'm frustrated.
You guys have been dating me for years.
Don't you know whether you're angry or crying?
I can't see your face.
What kind of face did you have?
You're all so annoying.
You're so annoying.
This is the face.
I see.
Not "I see".
Try to see with your eyes.
Yes, sir.
Listen up.
I'm standing in front of you.
Look at me closely.
You're going to laugh.
You see?
How's this?
Do you see anything?
So what do you mean, "how's this"?
Is it possible for me to see with my imagination?
I think you can see, now.
Eh?
Are you sure you think I can see, Reiko?
S-s-s-sry.
This is a bit...
Let's go!
We're going to get you on in time.
How is this?
Well...
Now, you see?
Y-yeah.
W-well, guess who I guess this is?
Guess what it is.
Huh?
Um...
How should I put it?
Well...
It has eyes, a nose, a mouth, and ears.
See? You can see the nose. You're smiling, right?
Ouch!
I'm behind you, young man.
That's unfair.
Good morning.
Oh, Chief.
What?
Ryo-tsu, you're skipping again?
No...
Well, Ryo-san...
Shut up.
I'll pour you some tea.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ryo-tsu, you're a pain in the ass.
Huh?
Oh, and before that, let's go to the bathroom.
Chief, you're so lucky.
Ryo-san, you're lucky.
Don't do that.
Now that I'm an invisible man, I'll make a little fun of the Chief.
When he comes back, I'll get him to walk on his feet.
Senior, you'd better not do that.
Shut up!
I'm telling you, you two.
Be quiet!
I don't know.
Ah, I feel refreshed.
My body feels lighter.
Ouch!
I heard something strange.
What's that sound?
Is there a rat?
No, chief. Actually...
Get rid of it with my spirit.
Oh, that's...
Ouch!
Please stop!
I felt like I heard Ryotsu's voice.
It must be my imagination.
Ouch!
It's not my imagination!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm the one you're hitting!
I became a transparent human!
Is that true, chief?
Senpai became a special detective, a special detective!
I knew it.
I got a call from you, too.
That's terrible!
If you knew, why did you do that?
I knew it!
I tried to pull the chair and make it hang on the ground,
or I tried to make it fall down!
Did you notice?
Ouch!
I can imagine what you're going to do.
Please don't pull my ears!
I can see where your ears are.
I've seen all Ryotsu's behavior patterns.
I've been a boss for more than 20 years.
As expected of Chief Ohara.
Chief, the tea is here.
Ouch!
Be careful, Reiko!
Oh!
I can't see, so I can't help it.
Damn it!
That's why I said I don't like transparent people!
Oh, no!
It's late again!
My face is gone!
It's gone!
What's going on?
My body is gone, too!
Did I die?
Ouch!
Oh, I see!
I forgot I became a transparent big man.
You moron!
Ouch!
You're late again, Ryotsu!
I'm sorry!
If you skip work here because you're so transparent,
you'll be in trouble!
Chief, the tea is here!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I told you to be careful!
I told you to run away!
But I can't see it.
It can't be helped.
Damn, it's no good to be a transparent giant.
That's right.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Ryotsu!
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
Ryotsu disappeared before I knew it.
You must have been beaten up by your senior.
Damn, Ryotsu.
What's with the mountain of boiled eggs?
A lot of eggs came from the next farm.
I got a lot of eggs.
This is it.
No, no, I forgot my wallet.
I can't get a pachinko with this.
Is the chief still here?
Close the door.
There's no one here.
Ryotsu!
Where did you go?
Chief, can you see me?
You can't see me at all.
This is it.
You can see it from this egg's shell.
I'm going to get out of here.
If you want to get out of here, I'll let you go.
Send this document to the office.
Okay, okay.
I got it.
I'm going.
Chief, you don't have to get so angry.
Move!
What? Is that a remote-controlled bicycle?
Move, move.
Don't stare at me.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'm going to kill you!
I played dirty to the end.
Uh, where is it?
It broke, but it can't be helped.
Let's walk.
I'm gonna get you!
Hey, what was that?
What was that?
I don't know.
But I'm sure we're all tired.
You work too much.
Take a break.
That was close.
He's getting in my way.
I can't see the other side.
Ouch!
I think I heard someone.
Get out of the way!
Whatever.
Damn it. The road is dangerous.
Let's go the back way.
I think this way is safe.
Ouch! I stepped on a nail.
I can't walk on my own.
You...
I'm out of the way.
Ouch!
What?
Can you see me?
Oh, right. Dogs smell.
Do you know that?
Go away!
Ouch!
Don't bite my butt!
Shut up, you stupid dog!
Damn it.
I stepped on it.
Ouch!
Damn it.
I told you I'm not playing soccer in the street.
I'm sorry.
The back way is dangerous.
Ouch!
A women's room?
I'm glad I became a transparent person.
Emergency! Emergency!
At the Katsushika-cho office,
-Hitojichi-Tatakiya-Buchi-ken... -Nako, let's go!
Huh? What's wrong?
I think we ran into something.
Just in case. Let's go.
Okay.
Damn it, you suddenly opened it.
I almost had a nosebleed.
It's your turn, Transparent Deka.
Why are you here?
A man who became a transparent person
would want to be here at least once.
Gifu, you're being read.
Why are you coming out of the room?
Don't worry about the details.
Ryo-tsu, the chief inspector,
if you successfully solve this case
and get officially hired by the Special Prosecutor's Office,
your pay will be tripled.
I-I see.
Okay, I'll do it.
Today,
the man who went to the Katsushika financial company
is running to the security and police station
where he ran into an emergency call
and running towards a female employee.
He's currently hiding in this new building.
The scene is in a mess.
Hey, you, get up!
Hurry up and bring the cash and the car!
I don't care what happens to this woman!
Help me!
I can't get any closer.
If Ryo-tsu, the transparent person, were here,
I'd be able to get close to the culprit.
He said he went to the Katsushika financial company
with Chief Inspector Kaipan,
but he's already here.
Chief Inspector Kaipan?
I'm here, too.
You're here?
How do you know that?
I said you saw through my actions!
It's not the time to play around!
I'm sorry.
How's the situation?
The culprit is a young man with a rifle.
He's holding a young woman,
and he's asking for 500 million yen in cash
and a car for the robbery.
The building is just completed,
and there's nothing in it yet.
There's not much of an obstacle,
and it's hard to get in.
The entrance is just that one place
in front of the front door.
All right, you're all clear.
You can get close without the culprit noticing.
Get close and rescue the host first.
Yes, sir!
Once you've been rescued,
the police force will rush in
and secure the culprit.
I'll make sure the culprit's safe.
No, you can't.
You just need to think about rescuing the host.
You're going to be in trouble
when you get in trouble.
Yes, sir.
Sir,
when the culprit enters the building,
he's locked in from the inside.
This is the key.
I borrowed it from the owner of the building.
All right, I got it.
Then the operation begins.
Clear and clear.
Roger that.
I'm on my way.
I don't think I can see him.
Here I go.
I can't see him.
He's dressed like this,
and he's showing his butt hole.
I can't even notice him.
Both of them
haven't reached the entrance yet.
Yes, sir.
It looks like they've entered the building.
Yes, they've entered successfully.
It's the second floor.
First,
we need to rescue the host.
Hey,
hurry up.
The car and the pipe.
Don't be so nervous.
I'm the police.
I'll save you.
What's that?
I see something important
at an important moment.
Even if I hide it with my hands,
my hands are transparent.
Hey,
don't move.
Damn it.
If I do,
I'll burn.
What's that?
What are you doing?
It's a big transparent thing.
I'll arrest you.
Hey,
don't do it.
All right.
I'll get you.
Hey,
what are you doing?
Pull it.
Okay.
I'll go first.
It's over.
The case is solved.
Ryochi!
Hey,
Ryochi's figure.
The power of the medicine
must have run out.
Hey,
move.
Oh.
The culprit is arrested.
The poison scoop.
This is the arrest site.
Huh?
What was that?
The culprit is a pervert.
Something's wrong.
What was that?
The culprit's figure is...
A gentleman.
It's Ryochi.
A certain incident
has made him look weak.
No more night in his hypocritical face.
He hasn't been sent off
to the special police department,
nor to see anyone.
Amazing.
Hey,
don't get depressed,
Gorilla.
Everyone makes small mistakes.
Hey,
Hey Ezagi! I know it's your fault, but you made such a half-baked medicine!
Nin!
Invisible Liquid Market!
It's a supplement. This time it's perfect. Try it.
I'm never going to drink what you made!
It's already in the tea.
What?!
You idiot! You drank it!
This one's quick-release. It should work right away.
Re... Re... Re...
Nakagawa! How do I look? Am I gone?
No, you're not.
That's too bad.
You scared me!
I have to go back and do my Mark III research.
I don't want to!
Well, everyone, good luck!
Damn it. What a mad scientist.
What's wrong, Senior?
I feel dizzy.
I... I...
What's wrong, Ryo?
This time, only the key points are transparent!
Everyone, look!
No! Don't show it!
I said, you can't see it anymore!
It's true!
It's weird.
Damn it! Ezaki!
Ezaki, come back!
What are you doing to me?!
Damn it!
I feel dizzy now that I'm a transparent human!
"Residue"
I don't want to be a fool
If I go down the wrong path
The moon will run away
Because now is not everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat a little
You are sometimes helping someone
Baby do you know me
I'm going to tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't get sick
I'll do what I have to do
Cute breathing
It's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than looking down
Na na na na