Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the passing seasons ♩
♪ The brightest, the best parlor ♩
♪ Cross the new era lightly ♩
♪ Hero, diving in the yellow bird ♩
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♩
♪ Rather than wearing only the trendy things ♩
♪ The more you're honest, the more you'll be decided ♩
♪ Let it ring ♩
♪ Everybody can do it! ♩
♪ Let's start running ♩
♪ Dreams can't always stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the future without regret ♩
♪ Let it ring ♩
♪ Everybody can do it! ♩
♪ Even if you're a little bit out of it, it doesn't hurt ♩
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♩
♪ And fly high and strong ♩
♪ You have to set these ships apart ♩
♪ Run, Honda, for love's sake ♩
♪ For love's sake ♩
Move!
The Garga is not running.
Huh?
Humph.
Hey, Nakagawa, you're getting hungry, aren't you?
Why don't we have fried lebanese and gyoza for lunch today?
Chinese food? Sounds good.
Honda, you're in danger!
Don't get so angry, Ryo-chan's husband.
Whatever.
Anyway, let's go buy lunch.
I'll go with you.
I'm going on a business trip today.
Can I say I'll treat you?
Honda, why don't you say that first?
I'll have a special dish of fried lebanese and gyoza.
I'll have some tonjiru for the first time in a while.
He's a very energetic old man.
Nakagawa, you're...
What? Me too?
Yeah, just in case.
Hey, Nakagawa, this is your treat.
Then, I'll have a fried chicken lunch.
Okay.
Well then, Nakagawa-san, I'm off!
It's rare to see someone with such a different personality.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
H-hello.
Oh, welcome.
You're having lunch today, too?
Yeah.
This place has the best lunches.
I'm so happy.
What are you having today?
I'll have a special dish of fried lebanese and gyoza.
I'll have nori and two more tonjiru please.
Okay!
I'll have a special dish of fried lebanese and gyoza,
and two more fried lebanese and nori, please.
What?
Oh, am I wrong?
Ah...
It's okay.
I'll have some tonjiru.
Oh, six kinds of tonjiru!
Yes, ma'am.
Boss, we'll have two types of tonjiru: Toku-hire, Kara-age, Nori-ben, and Tonjiru.
Here we go!
Two types of tonjiru, please.
Sorry to bother you.
Well, we're always on your side.
That's what we should be thinking about.
It's a big difference from someone else's.
That's what the boss says. Someone else's.
It's about you! You!
Isn't this place a little dry?
You're right.
No, it's not.
I'm using the best light.
Your ass is a little salty, too.
This is just right.
This lunch box is the best.
I'm in love with it no matter what.
I can read it.
You're making a mistake by taking a lot of lunch boxes.
You're a lunch box salesman, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I know.
You must like the girl from the lunch box store.
No, that's not...
I see. That shopkeeper is cute.
How do you know?
Look at her face.
I can tell who she is by looking at her face.
She's so sweet.
So? What's the name of the shopkeeper?
Megumi Hoshino.
Well, I'll tell you the answer.
Give up on her.
Why?
Ryo, are you still friends?
Please help her.
Reiko, how many times do you think she's been out of love?
It's not once or twice.
It's a hundred times.
To be exact, it's a hundred and one times.
Really?
Then you should try to stop her from seeing you.
But...
Reiko, stop it.
You can't do anything about love without a reason.
You don't know that, do you?
Uncle!
What?
You're rude to me, who is called the nice middle of a woman killer.
What do you mean, the nice middle of a woman killer?
Stop joking around!
Right this is how it works.
I'm going to make it real, 1.
2.
3.
4.
See?
Why are you here?
I thought you were a guy, 1.
I'm going to do it, too.
All right.
I'm sorry.
What do you think, senpai?
No, no. There's a man I like.
No way.
What kind of man do you think he is?
You said you wanted to be a white-collar employee who passes by at 9:00 every morning.
That's not true.
You should give up, Megumi.
I'm also a white-collar employee.
I also pass by the store at 9:00 every morning.
What did you just say?
Come on, Honda!
Hey, Megumi.
Yes?
This is the white-collar man I told you about.
He always comes to buy things.
Hello.
What do you think?
No, they don't look like him at all.
Oh, I see.
He looks a little slim, but he has a tight face.
He always wears a lot of arms and wears a muffler.
He's really manly and cool.
It's me, after all.
Don't listen to him! Senpai!
He's a man.
He does look different.
You can't believe it.
If you take a look at this bike,
your face and your personality will be completely different.
You can't believe it.
This Honda is number one with his white-collar employees.
That's my number one strength.
You're right.
If you're a white-collar employee,
you know who passes by every morning.
You probably don't.
Yes, I do.
Leave it to me.
What?
Then, if you know the person,
Please let me know if you know anything.
Yes.
You made an extra promise.
I'm sorry.
I see. It's getting complicated.
Megumi likes Honda when she rides a motorcycle.
So, she can't ride the current Honda?
Honda, there's only one way.
What should we do?
You'll be riding a motorcycle in front of Megumi forever.
What?
That's impossible.
I know it's impossible.
But if you go on a date with a motorcycle,
you'll definitely get a "yes" for sure.
That might be true, but...
That's a little too much.
A man and a woman are important at first.
If you decide right away,
everything will be fine.
Is that so?
A nice middle man who killed a woman says so,
so there's no doubt.
I'm going to do it.
Mr. Honda!
I like her.
If I can go on a date with someone as wonderful as her,
I don't mind what happens after that.
Okay, it's settled.
Now we just need to attack.
Yes, sir.
Good morning.
Mr. Honda, you're here.
Oh, yes.
Oh, sorry.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Megumi Hoshino.
What's your name?
I'm Honda.
Are you Mr. Honda, too?
Oh, no.
I'm Suzuki, the son of Honda.
Mr. Suzuki?
It's a custom for a woman to ride a motorcycle,
but...
How about you entrust your life to me
and feel the wind with me?
I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I'll be here at 9:00 on Sunday morning.
I'll be here at 9:00 on Sunday morning.
Okay.
See you later.
I'll pay you back with this.
How's it going, sir?
I did it.
I'm going on a date on Sunday.
I see.
You did it.
Listen, don't get off your bike
during a date.
Okay.
Mr. Suzuki.
What is it?
I'm so cold.
My heart can't beat this.
I'm just kidding.
You're going anywhere.
How's the taste?
It's good, sir.
I'm sure you'll have it.
Let's drive it.
You know what?
I hate it when it gets cold.
You're just a piece of crap!
Mr. Honda!
It's not Mr. Honda! It's that stupid Suzuki!
I'm so sorry.
I didn't think it was Mr. Honda.
It's Suzuki, you idiot!
Please forgive us, Mr. Suzuki!
I hope you understand.
We'll forgive you for today,
but if you do that again, we won't let you off!
Yes, sir!
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm not scared if Mr. Suzuki is with me.
Okay, hold on tight.
Yes, sir!
That's strange.
It's Mr. Honda, but...
I don't feel any left.
We should have found him a while ago.
Where is Suzuki?
Suzuki-san, you're really strong.
I'm so touched.
Are you going to watch a movie?
Yes!
The seats are already open.
Good night!
I always look at it this way. Don't worry about it.
You've changed.
...
Wow, you really like bikes, don't you?
Yeah, they're the best you've ever had.
.......
The bike and I are one.
You're the best partner.
What's wrong?
Actually, he's going to America with me.
He has a girlfriend?
He's going to America?
Yes.
Megumi, you're going to America with me?
No, it's nothing.
Two years is too short. We can meet again.
That's all you want to say?
You can go anywhere in America.
Goodbye.
Megumi!
But it's fine.
It's over.
I'm going to beg that man.
A man has to be as manly as you.
I see.
Let's go home.
Yes.
Um...
Welcome.
What are you doing?
Well, what are you doing?
I did it!
I can play!
How was the date?
As you said, I was riding the bike for a long time, so it was perfect.
I see.
You're good.
"She really is very good"
Megumi-san!
Yamamoto-san!
Senpai, please don't interrupt my birthday party, okay?
Who did you think you could date by, right?
"Wrong"
Who is that guy?
Actually, today, he is going to America.
"Wrong"
Hey, Honda, explain who is he?
Wait, you bastard!
"Wrong"
Before we go, I want to tell you my feelings.
Megumi, I like you. I want to marry you.
"Wrong"
This is a ticket for your flight.
I want you to come with me.
"Wrong"
You said it suddenly.
I know. I can't do it.
I always do this.
"Wrong"
Take care.
Dad.
Dad?
"Wrong"
Dad.
Dad?
What happened to you?
Actually, I saw your image in the newspapers.
"Wrong"
Damn it! I'll arrest you if you do it again!
Hey Honda! Why are you like that?
You like Yamamoto, don't you?
A man's personality is not only his appearance.
I think it's also manly to keep thinking about the woman you like.
Mr. Suzuki.
Mr. Suzuki!
Damn it! I can't believe I'm stuck here.
What time is the departure time of the plane?
7 o'clock.
Damn it! I can't make it in time.
Hold on tight!
What?
Here.
Darn it!
Thank you everyone.
Hey, don't make a terrible face.
I'm going to Los Angeles, bro.
It means you're on the right track.
Let's go.
We'll be back.
Yeah.
Take care.
Call me if you need me.
Good luck!
M-Megumi-san!
Go on.
I-I decided to...
I decided to go with you.
Take me with you, too.
Ah...
Megumi-san...
How long are you going to be like this?
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
Suzuki-san, what can I say?
Don't worry about me.
Let's go.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Honda, it was you.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Mr. Honda!
Thanks, Mr. Honda!
Thank you, Mr. Honda!
Good-bye, Ms. Megumi.
Ms. Megumi.
I was a good boy, but I fell in love for the second time.
I know. Stop crying.
I was in the police station for six months.
I can't help it.
But you're too good at acting as Cupid.
You're like Ryo when he was young.
He was drunk as soon as he fell in love with you.
How about you, Ryo?
Don't talk nonsense.
Well, it's okay.
You fell in love with me 102 times.
You've fallen in love with me over 300 times.
Really?
I feel better.
Let's drink.
We'll get a lot of praise from the chief in two days.
I'm sure.
What?
Damn it.
Let's get drunk.
I'll drink up all the sake in the store.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your help.
Do you only serve tea?
I'm glad you came all the way to the mountain.
Please, give us something.
Next time, to the familyoria of Ohara.
Please.
Slept well
Time passes
Don't look around
Don't cry, laugh and live on
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye, let's wash our hands
Goodbye for the things we don't like
Oh yeah, let's live the way we like
There are good things
The sun is calling outside the door
Thank you for watching!