Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♩
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♩
♪ Overcoming the rough times lightly ♩
♪ The hero is diving to the city on his own ♩
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♩
♪ Rather than wearing only trendy things ♩
♪ The face is 100 times more decided ♩
♪ Let it bleed ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Start running ♩
♪ Dreams never stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow as well ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Even if you get a little bit out of it ♩
♪ It doesn't hurt ♩
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♩
♪ And fly high and strong ♩
♪ Be the hero and keep the spirit ♩
♪ It doesn't matter if the sky is dark or the sky is blue ♩
♪ So fly high and strong ♩
♪ Fly high and strong ♩
♪ Let's fly high and strong ♩
Oh, you're about to get in.
This bastard is dangerous!
Bastard!
Senior!
This guy...
He's the gourmet commentator who's been on TV and magazines lately.
It's you, Chogoro.
This taste is not just any ordinary taste.
As usual, the store is not just any ordinary taste.
Is there a chef?
Oh, this is the teacher.
Please come in.
Oh, it's a split, you bastard!
Well, well, senior.
Here you are.
This is not just any ordinary taste.
You're so great.
I've been waiting for three hours under the cold sky.
Do you know the taste of the
the best
the
best
of
the
best
I found something that's not your specialty, Maeda-sensei.
I knew it. This soba is the best!
It doesn't matter if it's your specialty.
When you're done eating, get out of the seat.
My lord, I want to sell this soba to my acquaintances.
I want 200 soba.
200 soba is more than 100,000 yen.
My lord, I'm the best gourmet of Japan,
and you're the best gourmet of Japan.
Of course, I don't need any of that.
Please, everyone, enjoy your meal.
I'll be more diligent from now on.
Thank you very much.
Ah, finally it's gone.
Well, it's our turn next.
W-what?
Hey, old man! What's with the closed store?
We've been waiting for three hours under this cold weather
because we want to eat warm soba!
Oh, Maeda-sensei took all the soba.
What?
No way!
I'm the one who wants to cry!
I shouldn't have been put on this magazine!
Damn it!
I see.
Because it was introduced on this magazine,
suddenly there are more customers.
So they're selling it for free.
They're really something.
Damn it.
If this continues, it'll be a little bit of a disaster.
Is there any restaurant that can make us eat warm soba?
Senior, how about this soba restaurant?
What?
I'm sorry.
It's as if there's no customers here.
This place is dangerous!
Let's get out of here.
Eh? Why?
You don't know?
It's not normal for this place to be so popular.
If we eat a lot,
we'll have to make a bad soba that we can never eat again.
Are you a customer?
I was going to say that.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Actually, you are the fifth customer.
The fifth customer today?
Well, I guess that's it.
No, it's the fifth since the restaurant started.
What?
Wait a minute!
When did the restaurant start?
Three years ago.
Three years ago?
I'll make it right away.
What should I do?
Actually, I suddenly feel a little hungry.
Senior, I feel sorry for you.
Let's eat it.
What should we do if we eat soba here and really feel hungry?
If something happens,
we'll do something with Nakagawa Zaibatsu's medical team.
Let's be the fifth customer.
Please.
I understand.
I'll be the fifth victim.
Thank you for waiting.
It's a bad soba.
Let's eat it quickly and go back to the delivery.
What?
Don't look at me!
I'm sorry.
The customer's reaction is a little...
You're worried about the soba, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll tell you after I finish eating.
So go over there while I'm eating.
Yes.
It's a soba with no weirdness.
It's not that bad that you can't eat it.
What's this?
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
Master, I have something to ask you.
Yes, what is it?
Is this soba made from the soba flour made at Yamada Farm?
Yes, it is.
What's Yamada Farm?
You know it.
It's the farm of the soba maker,
Dengoro Yamada.
It's said that the soba made here is the best in Japan.
It's difficult to get,
so even the Nakagawa group's cooking department
uses it only in a few shops.
I've known the Yamada grandpa for a long time,
so I've been using it cheaply at home.
I knew it.
And the soba made from the soba broth,
isn't it the one made by Sato Jozo?
Yes.
Sato Jozo has been making handmade soba for years.
It's said to be the birthplace of soba.
It's a traditional taste of Kishu.
The soba made here is called "soba in soba".
No, it's called "soba".
It's not just soba.
It's also called "katsuobushi" and "konbu".
It's a must-have for this rich broth.
The green onions are well-cooked,
and it's a great, glossy dish.
And the chili peppers,
the 7 flavors bring out the perfect harmony.
The spiciness is just right,
and it's a very well-chosen ingredient.
Hey, hey, why do you use such a great ingredient
to make only ordinary soba?
Ordinary?
Senior, please have a look at your bowl.
When did you find it?
This is what it means to be delicious.
It goes into your body naturally.
Old man, that's for you!
One more, please!
Yes!
It is true that it tastes good when you chew it.
Right?
You're putting out such a great flavor.
You should promote it more!
I'm not good at making flashy things.
But even so,
It's strange to think about it.
If it tastes like this, it seems like it's going to attract customers.
But there's a deep reason for it not to attract customers.
Deep reason?
Three years ago, I won't forget.
On a day when the snow was falling, this store opened.
I was nervous, waiting for the first customer.
Then...
Sorry.
What? You're Mr. Oomaeda?
You're Mr. Oomaeda. Did you come here to eat?
No, I came to borrow the bathroom.
So this was a soba restaurant.
I didn't realize it was so ordinary.
But it's just right. Let's have lunch here.
Yes, I'll make it right away.
It was my first customer, so I made it with my own hands.
Here you go.
Thank you.
How was it?
It's just an ordinary taste.
Is that so?
Oh, it will be 700 yen, but...
Sir, I don't think you know me.
I'm Chogoro Omaeda, a food critic.
Yes, so it will be 700 yen for a bowl of kakesoba.
I'm Chogoro Omaeda, a food critic from Nippon-ishi!
So, 700 yen for a bowl of kakesoba.
I said I'm Omaeda!
700 yen...
I'm sorry, but I don't have any cash.
I'll have to pay you back later.
I'm sure it'll be 20,000 or 30,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Sir, what's the name of this shop?
Tanaka Soba.
I'll remember that.
In the end, the full-year room was a complete fake.
What a sad story.
I was surprised a week later.
They were so mean to our shop.
It's not a human's fault.
Even if the world forgives me, I won't forgive it.
-7 times.
That's terrible.
Don't put this on display.
But our shop is introduced.
It's just a negative image.
It's a terrible article.
It's full of criticism.
I can't forgive you for bringing soba that I was supposed to eat.
You're so good at this.
It's strange that a person who doesn't know the taste is a gourmet critic.
Okay.
I'll get angry, and then tell you what's going to happen.
All right?
Yes, if it's possible.
Leave it to me.
I have a good idea.
Wash your head and wait.
Hey, you!
I need a sacrifice to make a fool of you.
Are you prepared?
Yes.
Well, now, we'll start the strategy to make a fool of you.
I'm starting a strategy to make you laugh, Chogoro.
What are you doing?
You can't let a regular store like this be accepted by a gourmet critic.
We need to have a tradition and a style!
I see.
You're trying to fight back the feelings that have been with you for many years.
That's right.
You can't let a regular store like this be accepted by a gourmet critic.
My store...
Senior, do you need any help?
Yes, anything.
Bring me something that has a tradition and a style.
I understand!
Next...
Hey, Ryo! What are you doing?
Hey, I'm here at a good place.
I remember you saying you made some rice balls during the school's school lunch break.
Yeah, but they're covered in dust and have cracks.
It's a good thing.
Bring that here.
And borrow some for your friends.
Okay, Ryo!
You've made it, haven't you?
An abandoned happening at a news conference.
I borrowed this from the museums around the world.
All of these mucus are storytelling the history of mankind.
Hello, hello.
Uh...
there's a thing like this in this toy shop.
It looks very natural.
No, it isn't.
I should have told you.
Oh, right.
I'll call this a celebration of the rotation of the Cleopatra.
It's so messy.
I wonder if it's this big.
I'll leave one pillar here.
Please don't.
If you cut this, the building will break.
That's true.
Ryo!
I'm waiting for you!
Good.
Good job.
The restaurant is ready.
Now...
No way!
Please stop!
Stop it!
The one who will be the judge is the owner!
Don't speak like that!
Huh?
That bicycle is...
It's a forfeit.
You're not sure about this, are you, Kankichi?
Huh?
Mr. Nakagawa!
You finished it.
Come here.
But...
Don't be shy.
I'm sure you're not sure about this.
I'll tell Chief Ohara.
Hey!
I... I'm retired...
I... I... I'm retired...
I'm so happy...
Oh, you're that happy?
I'm lamenting my own misfortune.
Now the stage is set.
Nakagawa, prepare the cherry blossoms.
Yes.
Now we just have to drive in the prey.
Is there really a good soba restaurant that can line up in a place like this?
Yes.
According to the viewers,
you can line up two kilometers a day.
Oh, isn't that it?
Wow!
So this is the line that goes to the soba restaurant?
I wonder what this current line looks like.
Today we are interviewing the best gourmet actress in Japan,
Omaeda Chomoro.
With her, we will try to find out who is the best Tak Ent,
I am Omaeda Chomoro!
What are you two?
I heard you want us to interview a restaurant,
would you mind?
Would you like to join us?
Yes, please do not disturb us.
Sir, what is your first impression of the shop?
Do you know? This shop has been open for 20 years.
It is said that it is a very important cultural asset of the country.
A very important cultural asset of the country?
This shop is probably the one that has been around since the beginning of the world.
This shop must have been a place where fierce battles were fought between the Ishin and the Bakufu armies.
Even though it is a shop made by a senior, it is easy to be deceived.
This is a great treasure that has been kept for a long time.
This shop is not just a treasure.
This shop is a treasure.
This is a treasure that is not just a treasure.
This is a treasure that is likely to be popular with the public.
Hello.
You are stupid. Get out of my way.
This shop is a shop where chili peppers are sold once.
Please use it twice.
Please tell the store manager to open the shop.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and come out.
Are you really going out in this costume?
Of course.
Don't be too hard on me.
Because of the article he wrote, only five customers came in in the last three years.
Just remember that.
Come on, let's go.
I'm sorry, store manager.
The one who doesn't keep the style of the shop is a customer.
Don't come back.
Wow! It's a shop for craftsmen!
What do you think, Mr. Maeda?
Oh, man!
He must have kicked out the people of the Royal Court of Britain with that attitude!
But now, he's back and enjoying himself here,
and he's serving water to the Buckingham Palace every week!
Royal Court of Britain...
He's just trying to keep the taste of soba,
and his way of being an angel!
He's wearing a traditional coat,
but he doesn't fall for the tradition,
and he's actively taking on Western styles!
He's experiencing the western fusion of the West and the West!
The owner of the shop...
is not an ordinary person!
He's not an ordinary person again!
Why? Why, you guys?
Don't you know me?
I'm the gourmet commentator, Maeda Chogoro!
I came for a TV interview!
What? A TV interview?
You idiot!
Don't do interviews!
If you do a TV interview,
the people who don't know the taste of soba will come and push you!
If there's any more customers,
I'll be too busy to take care of them!
Hey, don't shoot!
There's no customers!
We just serve the usual soba!
Yes, of course!
Wonderful!
I've tried all the dishes in the world,
but this is the first time I've ever eaten so delicious soba!
I'll leave the food here!
Here it is!
As expected, the chief of staff of the United Nations is a regular customer.
People who say this is bad are not human!
The chief of staff of the United Nations!
Wait!
Well, how about the taste of the soba?
How about the taste of the soba?
The way the soba is kneaded,
the way the soup is made,
the way the leeks are cut,
and even more,
this artistic bowl!
I made it!
Whichever you take is good!
It's really not a normal one!
I'll give you the proof that this Omaeda Chogoro's
top-notch is not a normal one!
Seven stars!
You must be happy, too!
Hey, you!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
You're a rude guy!
Shut up!
Look at him!
Tanaka Soba?
You still don't remember me?
What's this place?
You finally remember me.
You're the Tanaka Soba
who made the -7-star soba
three years ago!
What?
What's going on?
This place has been making soba
for three years,
and it's still the same!
It's been using the best ingredients
from the first class for a long time!
It's been using the best ingredients from the first class for a long time!
I wonder if that's true.
You saw yourself belittling him yourself!
It really means you can't understand the taste of soba!
Oh no!
You can't call yourself anаче
or a gourmet两聖子,
it's just a loss of one flavor!
that's all.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Are you serious?!
Just make it clear to me!
N-No comment!
Tanaka Soba,
We did it!
The plan was a success!
The magic soba restaurant was built, but Oomaeda's was a disaster.
Tanaka-san's soba restaurant has been in good shape since then.
Yeah.
But since then, Oomaeda-sensei has been very quiet.
What?
What's wrong?
A mysterious home cooking critic has appeared.
Recently, a person who is known as a home cooking critic has appeared in the city,
and has been eating with his family in the city.
Is this Oomaeda-sensei?
He's such a guy!
He's not just a normal person.
If you want to study,
you can't make a living by only memorizing ideas.
Having a quality life is what makes a life meaningful.
Learning style through your body.
I'll teach you the practical ways for studying!
Next time, the preposition test in the preparation ritual.
Take care and look forward to it!
Sengoku Jikoku
Band
Stop the clock and look to the sky
Sengoku Jikoku
will pass by
Don't stare at me
Let's laugh and live
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
Let's wash our hands
Goodbye for the things we hate
Oh yeah
Let's live the way we like
There are good things
The sun is calling me outside the door
Let's live the way we like
♪
♬
"The