English Translation:
When he was looking over the river twice
He burned a love stone and the shoes
From the main line of the Tungari hat to the taishakuten, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end already, won't it?
If I win, I'll lose happiness again
I realized, I'm such an idiot
What's wrong, chief?
You've been sighing since morning
That's right
I heard he had a fight with Hiromi
Really?
He said he didn't want to see her, and he wouldn't let Daisuke, his grandson, see her
Chief, which way?
I'm going to patrol. Please take care of Luce
Yes, sir
He seems to be pretty stubborn
Yeah
Wow!
He's got three, four, and one!
He's really good
Yeah!
I'm going to beat you all
Yay!
I don't think we can win 351-2 in a video game, but crane games are Nash
By the way, I want to teach you all the tricks of the crane
What are you doing while you're working?
Chief, this is...
I never skipped any work
I'm preparing for the region...
A hectare's owner?
Hey, you must be a rich chief, right?
You look like a real man.
Don't scare me.
But it's rare to see Mr. Ryo.
He's not even in a competition outside the shopping mall.
Competition? What's that?
You don't know?
It's a crane that takes a super luxurious product.
Really?
If I don't hurry, it's about time I got married.
Oh, you're already gone.
Luxurious product, grab it!
I did it!
The Asumoto-Sakaguchi group is the top in the price of luxury products.
Oh, no.
Two of them in one group.
Hey, you.
Why don't you join me in the crane game?
You don't have to run away.
Hey, you.
Join me.
A gorilla!
Damn it.
Hey, you with long hair.
No way.
Damn it.
Don't come there.
You're so bad.
Join me in the crane game.
Mr. Ryo!
That's strange.
Do you always do this?
Don't show your face to illegals.
I'm just kidding.
This is strange.
I hope it's not the front of the entire branch.
Um, chief.
What's wrong?
You look like you had a fight with Hiromi-san.
How did you know?
What? Are you really fighting?
It's not that serious.
I just called her and she hung up.
I even visited her house and she didn't show me Daisuke's face.
That's a good fight.
What's the reason?
I think she spilled tea on the idol's autograph paper when she visited Hiromi's house.
What idol?
I think it's a group called Smappi.
What? Smappi?
You know them?
Of course I do!
Smappi is a popular idol group that 99.999% of the Japanese population knows.
They are the most popular idol group in Japan.
The only idol group that I don't know is the leader.
I see.
That's why Hiromi was so angry.
It's probably the product of this event.
What?
Smappi's autograph paper.
I see.
I'm impressed by the Kameari Shopping Association.
It's time.
I'd like to give the last one to the next participant.
Does anyone want to participate?
Let's participate, chief.
What?
Let's participate in the crane game.
This is a chance to get back together with Hiromi.
What?
The name of the sign is on the sign.
The heavens are ordering you to take the sign and give it to Hiromi.
But...
It's hard for me to skip work.
But if you miss this chance,
you may not be able to get back together with Hiromi.
It's too much.
Parent-child relationship is a little thing that collapses.
My friend has a father and daughter who haven't spoken to him for 20 years.
What's the cause?
It's because his father's fart was smelly.
I have to take this chance to restore the good relationship.
I'll do my best!
But...
It's not good if someone sees me.
Is there anyone else who has the courage to challenge?
If you don't do it quickly, other people will come out.
Go!
Hey!
Thank you!
Now, the last challenger is here!
What's your name?
My name is Ryo...
If you call me by my real name, there's no reason to take the side.
That's right.
We are the "Fukumen Brothers".
I'm No.1 and you're No.2.
What?
You don't have to come out with your real name.
But...
Then, explain the rules quickly.
Yes!
One person is a crane, and the other person controls it.
Within three minutes of the time limit,
you can get as many items as you like.
But you can only return to the starting point once.
The total amount of the winning item,
the top five groups,
can enter the final that will be held soon after this.
What?
There's a final?
Yes.
If you win there,
you can challenge the special stage,
"10,000 yen ticket, grab it, human crane".
What?
"10,000 yen ticket, grab it, human crane"?
Alright!
I'm getting more and more motivated!
Get ready for the crane!
I'm not good at this.
Don't worry.
If you do as I say,
everything will be fine.
Then, "Fukumen Brothers" team,
start!
First, let me climb.
Yes.
Stop!
Move forward!
Roger!
As expected from the president of the Kameari Shopping Association.
It's like they've taken out the prize as long as anything is fine.
That's the signature of the Kameari Shopping Association.
Stop, stop!
Did you find it?
Good job, Ryo...
No, Ichigo!
Wait a minute.
If I take the signature of the Kameari Shopping Association here,
I'll be in trouble!
Alright, your honor.
Then, I'll go back to work.
The final is "10,000 yen ticket, grab it, human crane"!
I'll pretend I didn't see it.
I'll take the crane!
No, it was a mistake.
Let me move forward.
I see.
Oh, that's...
The first lot of the Parastepan Doki Doki Memorial!
Stop, stop!
Please take it down!
I already gave up because I couldn't get it,
but I can't believe I'm here.
Oh, that's the modern model 48 series that was a hit 20 years ago!
And it's No. 10!
It's the Tiger II with the 13th-year-old Rommel doll!
No. 2!
To the left!
Good job!
The premium price is 100,000 yen!
Ichigo!
The price of all the products is calculated at a low price!
What?
Then, is this only 500 yen?
No, no.
I can't go to the final without taking a more expensive product!
Forward, forward!
Right, right!
Now, go back to the left!
What is that guy taking from a while ago?
No, no, no!
It's the Fukumen Brothers No. 1!
Our goal is to get the signature of the Smappi!
Look for it!
I'm looking for it!
I'm sure he's trying to get rid of something that might get in the way!
I can only see that he's choosing a more expensive product and taking it.
Oh?
That's it!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
It's the No. 2, not the 2nd one!
That's it!
There's a signature underneath it!
Isn't it the Smappi's signature?
Huh?
No, it's not!
It's the signature of another idol!
Really?
That's strange.
I'm sure the signature is only for the Smappi.
No, it's not!
You!
Hey, that was Smappi!
But it's not in good condition, so I can't get it.
You'll get it if you stretch your legs!
Oh no!
I got it!
You're such a troublemaker!
Now, take it!
Oh no!
I got it again!
It's broken!
You're such a troublemaker!
I got it!
I got it again!
Huh?
Now, you'll get it this time!
I'm sorry!
I can't take it anymore!
You should throw it away somewhere!
I can't do such a wasteful thing!
Then, take it with your mouth!
Damn it!
What's wrong with him?
What?
What's this?
What are you doing?
Take the signature now!
This is the legendary Toyota 2000GT!
I can't believe it's here!
I don't care about cars!
I'm signing it!
If you take this, you'll definitely get into the finals!
What's the finals?
I want to sign it!
If this happens...
That's not it!
I'm signing it!
Amazing!
I'm supporting the car with my teeth!
This is a great 10th anniversary!
Oh, no!
It's time!
Oh!
I'm supporting the car with my teeth!
Is this the end?
The final score is...
272,000,000 yen and 95,000 yen!
The total cost is...
A total cost of...
2,720,000,000 yen and 95,000 yen!
It's not over yet!
I'm going home.
Wait, it's the finals!
I just wanted the signature!
It's the final!
You can't even take a picture of the sign in front of you.
I really couldn't take it.
You're so stubborn.
I don't want to hear any excuses.
After all, you used me and Hiromi's fight to get into this game.
Oh no, he's looking at me.
Come on, let's go back to work.
Wait a minute.
We can take a picture of the sign of Smoppy even in the finals.
What?
That's right.
The prize for the finals is something else.
I don't mind if you give me one more.
Oh, yes.
Do you have a signature of Smoppy?
I'll take it for sure this time.
I want to get back together with Hiromi.
You're trying to get into the weakness of people.
Well, let's do our best in the finals.
Mr. Uemura, the finals has begun.
I'm sorry we kept you waiting.
The Himeari Shopping Association is going to host the finals of the Himeari Human Crane Tournament.
There are five to ten athletes who have won the qualifying.
It's pretty tough to come out of the finals.
It's going to be fine this time.
Leave it to me.
I'll win the finals for sure.
I'll show you.
It's a signature.
Of course.
It's a signature of the Smappi.
No one will forget it for a moment.
How suspicious.
Now, for today's day,
we have a special guest.
He's the local police chief of the local police station,
Mr. Gomes Tonda.
Hello, hello.
The first stage of the final round
is the Piranha Stage
in the water.
In this water tank,
there are luxurious products
that have been purified.
However,
there is a Piranha in the water tank.
If you dive for too long,
you will be attacked by Piranha.
So please be careful.
Let's start.
The top battle is
the Atsumi Buying Team.
I thought my heart would stop.
When the chief came...
It's okay.
We have this mask.
You can't get caught.
But,
if you want,
you can't get caught.
Chief,
in the case my acquaintance handled,
my daughter made fun of my father.
The cause was
that my father used my daughter's towel
without any hesitation.
No way.
It's just a towel.
That's dangerous.
If you don't do it when you can get along with each other,
you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
On the other hand,
you will have hatred for each other,
and you may have to take a period of life.
Is that okay?
Chief,
please don't worry about the chief.
If you don't think about it,
you'll be caught.
Is that okay?
I,
I understand.
Next,
the next challenger
to the Piranha Stage
is the top of the qualifying team,
the Fukumen Brothers Team.
Chief,
don't be nervous.
We'll find out.
Okay,
we're ready.
Then,
the game starts.
The game starts.
We're going to the Name and state not the time.
Then,
I'm sorry,
sorry.
Oh,
oh,
it's hot.
The surface is reflected,
so it'sЛ
It's quite ugly.
I don't care.
I have no choice.
You can call a break.
ah
Yeah!
Ah! Did you invite Piranha with a flashy landing?
They are noisy.
I won't make Piranha a problem at all.
I was off the schedule.
There's nothing good.
If this happens, I'll win the game.
What?
What's that?
That's right!
Why didn't you take it? You should have noticed.
No, I mean number one!
Here's the time!
What's the total amount of the prize money?
128,721 yen.
The total is...
They won't pay me.
Here's the point.
Ah!
I have one!
What?
I'll sell it all here.
Excuse me.
The Main Brothers' team won the top spot.
Of course.
Why didn't you take the sign?
You should have seen me.
You didn't notice?
What delighted me?
No oxygen bombs.
I can't wait to die.
I don't have time to decide.
I'll talk about that later.
Hey, you guys.
You didn't see me?
Idiot!
Move as you're told, No. 2!
What do you want, Ryotsu?
We have to talk about the president's suspicions.
If he knows our true identity, he won't think I'll hit the president.
That's possible, but...
Our goal is to win, so don't lose your temper.
Sorry!
Don't apologize!
We won't do it seriously.
If you don't do it, the president will find out.
If he finds out, you're fired.
You don't get promotion or bonus.
Do you get it?
I get it.
You have to do it properly next time.
Oh!
He's so powerful!
I thought I'd stop him from playing the piano.
But he didn't seem to be very talkative.
It's the final stage.
Up to now, the top team is...
The X-Men Brothers team, 397,5527 yen.
Only the cost is included.
And the winning team is...
The 10,000-yen crane.
This is a challenge for the 10,000-yen crane.
Oh!
I get the prize!
I can't trust him anymore.
This is it.
It's a big deal, Ryotsu.
We're about to take off our masks.
What?
Oh, it's true!
It's a big deal if the president finds out.
The promotion doesn't matter, but you won't get bonuses.
I'll be back!
- - You
're late, Ichigo. You
're so slow. Come
on, get to your position. Wait,
wait, wait. I'll
get the Smutpy sign for sure. The final
stage of the final match is the Battle Royale Balloon Bomb Stage! The balloons
have bombs on them, and they explode when they touch them.
The white powder is the bomb, right?
It's a common thing on TV.
Now, watch this.
Which team will be able to win the battle and win 10,000 yen?
The final stage...
Start!
What's wrong, Ichigo? Why aren't you moving?
I can't do it. Let's switch.
I can take at least one of the sign sign.
I said I can't win.
Don't say anything. Just move.
I can't do it.
If you're really not going to move...
What?
How dare you!
Let me go!
It's for the bond between father and daughter.
I'm sorry, but can you help me?
It's dirty. Let go of that hand and come back.
If you get a sign...
You're so arrogant.
Then, how about this!
Stop!
Igo, switch with me.
I'll get a sign this time.
Can you trust me?
Come on.
I'm not feeling well.
Igo!
You're so tough.
What's wrong?
You're not doing it right!
Give up!
I won't take your orders!
Where is Sai Nishikishi?
Stop the nonsense!
Don't get in my way!
Where is Sai Nishikishi?
Sai Nishikishi...
Where is the sign of Smuppi?
There it is!
We did it!
Now we can make up with Hiromi!
That's...
It can't be!
Everyone, get in the car!
The End
I'm so nervous about the memorial...
The Toyota 2000 GT...
Too bad, you know,
Mr. Ichigawa of the Fukumen Brothers.
What?
No, Mr. Ryozu Kankichi!
S-S-Sire!
You did it again, didn't you?
Not really...
There are good news and bad news,
but which do you want to hear first?
Well, the bad news first...
You're so brave.
This time,
you'll pay for all the damage, Ryozu-kun!
No way!
It's all because of No. 2...
No, it's all because of Chief Ohara!
He's doing this because he's so annoying!
Ohara-kun?
Sign...
Smuppi's sign...
Where is the Smuppi's sign?
Where is it?
It's...
Smuppi's sign...
The Smuppi's sign...
See? Chief Ohara, right?
No, it's someone else's sign.
There's no way a serious man like Ohara-kun
would be here.
That's right, there's no mistake!
No way!
Chief, what about the good news?
You don't have to work anymore, Ryozu-kun.
You're fired!
Please, let me finish this properly!
There's a serious problem!
You're fired!
Nagagawa!
What do you mean by quitting the police?
What?
Did your father decide it?
I'm not joking!
It's the job you chose, right?
Are youсть throw away your heart?
I have no choice but to be with you, either!
Next time on "The Fiery President: The Father of Nakagawa"
I look forward to working with you!
"The Father of Nakagawa"
I'm surprised
I'm startled
Bia Bia!
Solving it!
Do-ka Do-ka!
And then quickly
Uwaaaaaa!
"The