Timing and Subtitles brought to you by 中買いvesic
中川に浮かぶ春日を目かけ Bwinding along the river In the water of a summer
小石を蹴ったら靴まで飛んで If one kicks the tenоп wrote, possibly even a shoe
From the street to the taishakuten, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost the happiness of being a Katsushika Shiba
I realized, because I'm such an idiot
I'll give you a blow!
Damn it, it's burning!
That was close!
What's wrong Ryo-chan?
I'll make you a hot pot with hot tempura!
Ryo-chan, that's enough.
You really want to eat it?
You should stop eating it.
That's right, Ryo-san.
You're not going to lend me money, right?
But you're the one who ordered me to stop.
You're such a coward.
If you don't lend me money, you'll have to pay for what I do.
You're pretty good at this.
This guy is...
He's a tough guy.
I can't eat this!
B-Bujou!
Ryotsu!
Your working hours are over!
Stop doing stupid things and go back to the dorm!
This is...
Sukiyaki!
Who is it?
Who's this guy who is working hard before the holiday?
It's here!
It's my room.
Ryo-sama?
Welcome back!
It's Maria!
You said it was before the holiday!
What happened to this Sukiyaki?
I wanted to eat it with you.
Oh!
This is what it's like to be a Buddha in hell and Maria in hell!
Well, Indra!
Can you still see the meat?
I don't care if it's raw.
It's food!
Here!
Yum!
I ate it.
What happened all of a sudden?
Were you kicked out of the dorm?
No, it's...
It's my fault that I live in the dorm.
My father found out that I live in the dorm.
Your father?
Yes.
I told you I won't force you anymore.
You have no choice but to follow the Hon-dara-kenpo.
I absolutely don't want to!
Before the treatment,
my father's students were waiting for me to go home.
My father was finally here.
Hey, hey, hey, honey.
There's a delicious fried rice restaurant in Odaiba.
Would you like to go with me?
Hey! Hey!
I thought you wouldn't look at me recently.
If I stay here, everyone will be in trouble.
I thought I'd hide away from you.
If Maria is here, the food will be better.
It can't be helped.
I understand.
You can live in this room for a while.
Really?
I'm so happy!
Hey, stop it.
Don't get close to me.
I'm so happy to live with you.
Stop it.
Hey, senpai.
Hey, everyone.
Good work.
Good evening, everyone.
What are you surprised about?
Maria is a man.
Even if you say so...
Look at this.
Hey!
No!
Senpai...
In the end, while Maria was in the bath,
Honda was completely exhausted and everyone climbed and lay down.
I can't help it.
Maria is an annoying person.
Ryo, hurry up and get married!
Don't say stupid things.
How can a man get married?
Episode 2
He's not here!
Where's he going?!
No!
As expected of Rin! You're the best!
Thank you. But you should stop, Rin.
I'm fine with Marilyn, Director.
Really? Marilyn, the next film of the Women's Spy No. 5 series is definitely the best!
I'm looking forward to it, Director.
Marilyn, good job.
Thank you.
By the way, Marilyn, it will take about two hours to prepare for the next scene.
Is that so bad?
What should we do? Should we take a break at the location bus? Or...
Yes, that's right. Which one would you like?
Oh, I'm going to call Marilyn. She's my father.
What?
Hello, Dad?
I saw you at the show. Why didn't you call me when you came back to Japan, Rin?
I'm so sad, Dad.
What's the matter? I'm in the middle of shooting.
That's right. You're the one who gave me the ultimate Hon-dara-kenpo, Rin.
What are you talking about? I'm a woman. You have love, don't you?
That's right.
I've become a woman.
What? You?
And I've become a criminal.
You're the only one I have.
I know you don't want to, but I don't like it.
Please, you're next.
I'm going to see Ai.
Ai? Oh, the twin brother?
Yes.
Please come back in two hours.
Okay.
Take this.
Thank you.
See you.
I'll make Ai responsible for being a boy.
Hello.
Ai said she's in the girls' dorm. Why did she go to the boys' dorm?
Welcome back, Ai.
What?
You're just in time. Go take a bath.
No one's back yet.
Um...
Hurry up.
You don't want to be with them again, do you?
Oh, I see.
Ai made a mistake because you're dressed like this.
But it's okay.
I'll take a bath.
Maria, I'm back.
Huh?
You're not back yet?
Oh, Ryo, welcome back.
Ai wants a bath.
A bath?
Oh, really?
Ah, I'll take a bath before dinner.
Hey, Maria, I'm coming in, too.
What?
Ai!
What's wrong with you?
You!
You've completely turned into a woman!
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Bats!
Ouch!
It's okay, it's okay.
Just one bit, and you'll be ok.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a bath!
And more importantly, do you have a dryer?
Huh?
Hey, you're hungry.
If you're hungry, you can prepare dinner.
Why would I prepare dinner for you?
You're acting different than usual.
Hey, where's the bathroom?
It's on the right side of the corridor.
Oh, I see.
He should know about the bathroom.
Ryo, I'm sorry I'm late.
I'll prepare dinner for you right away.
Huh?
I said you're not going to do it!
I don't want to, Ryo.
I love cooking for you and washing dishes,
but why would I say that?
I don't want to, Ryo. I love cooking for you and washing dishes,
I don't like cooking for you and washing dishes,
Right...
Do you want some?
It is your chest.
Did something happen to my chest?
Um, well...
Please let me touch it.
What are you doing?
It's just a cheap lift.
The inside of the box is wishful thinking.
Please.
Well...
Hmm...
I can't do it.
Huh?
I forgot to buy soy sauce. I'll borrow some from Ryo's aunt.
If you say "here you go", it's hard to touch.
You're pretty fast. Bye.
What are you doing?!
Ouch! I told you to touch it!
Rin!
Ai?!
Wh-wh-what?! Why is Maria with them?!
She looks just like me!
W-what's going on?!
Ryo, Rin is my twin sister.
She's an actress in Hong Kong.
Your twin sister?
I see. So that's why she has real boobs.
Rin, why are you here?
We're here for the movie shoot in Tokyo.
If I come to see you, she'll peek in the back and touch the bus.
I'm so pissed!
What? I-I can't help it. I didn't know.
But still, if we're together, we're like clone humans.
You're right.
I even copied her hairstyle.
Why did you become a woman?
Well...
My father called me.
What if I'm the leader of that disgusting Hong Kong gang?
I don't want to be a dancer like that.
You should become a singer.
I'm an actress.
You can do it while you're an actress.
You can do it while you're a police officer.
What? You're the eldest, right?
It doesn't matter!
Hey, hey! Stop fighting!
You're the one who seduced Ai, right?
You're the one who turned Ai into a woman.
No, I'm not!
Ryo, stop being so mean!
You did it!
Don't copy my voice!
Stop talking like that!
I can't fix it! I'm too late!
Wait, you two!
Don't fight with the same voice!
It's messy!
Maria, calm down!
I'm Rin, and Ai is over there.
Oh, I see.
I can't believe you're so determined.
Yes, this is Rin.
Oh, it's already that late?
Ai, I'll take care of this after the shoot.
Good!
I'll do what I want!
Honey, I made cookies.
Try them.
Oh? Isn't that Rin?
A Japanese star actress from Hong Kong,
Marilyn, and Rin Asato,
came to Japan for a movie shoot.
How is it?
It's been a while since you've been to Japan...
Oh, Dad!
I'm not going to go to the Hon-dara-kenpo!
Why, Rin?
Honey, I'm going to see Rin.
Darling!
Oh, my!
You really are a man, aren't you?
Yes, but I'm a man.
I know that a sister like you
is a real nuisance to me,
but please be nice to me.
Oh, no, thanks.
Now, director, let's shoot.
Shoot.
Oh, yeah.
Ouch!
Come on, come on, come on.
I'm going to hit you from here,
so you have to dodge and kick.
Okay.
As expected from a popular actress,
the staff is also careful.
Rin is selfish, so...
Alright, let's take the test.
Ready...
Action!
Ouch!
Ouch...
What's wrong, Marilyn?
What?
You guys are so bad at dancing,
that your legs are broken, aren't they?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Kishima!
Yes?
Bring me a chair.
Yes.
She's also a popular actress,
even if she's selfish.
Once Rin starts to nag,
she won't listen to anything I say.
Hey, Marilyn,
can't you do anything?
My legs hurt, so I can't help it.
Then, take a break for a while.
What?
You're trying to force me,
I really can't believe it.
Oh, I can't do this.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
Oh,
I see.
Hey,
please play the role of Marilyn.
What?
It's okay, it's okay.
There's no line.
It's just an action.
I can't do that.
Ai,
if you play the role,
I can take over the role of the head of Hondara Prefecture.
Really?
Okay, I'll do it.
Will you do it?
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Then, let's start filming.
Let's go.
Hey,
you know the story.
No way.
Huh?
I'll do anything if you say so.
You're like a big actress, aren't you?
Ready,
action!
You have great power!
Got it.
Okay, fine.
Very good.
Director,
Uh?
Oh,
By the way,
I can't use this anymore.
What can I do about this?
I took it too seriously.
Oh,
I'm sorry.
الب coils
It's over.
You!
Those three guys...
Father...
Rin, I'm begging you.
I'll have to get you to take care of this mess.
What's this?
I don't like it, Father.
It's a bad idea!
What?
What happened to that flimsy, flimsy F cup?
Father, you have to take care of that one.
I'm going to take care of this one.
I think I messed up because it's too similar.
My F cup is just like this.
Okay, fine, fine.
You're not going to let me touch it, are you?
You're just as stubborn as ever.
Ryo, what are you doing here?
You're not even bothering Rin, are you?
I'm just taking a look around the studio.
Then hurry up and get out of here!
Father, please forgive Ryo.
Shut up, you idiot son of a bitch.
You're being fooled by a pervert gorilla like this.
Shut up!
Didn't you hear what Uncle Kappa said?
Hmph.
Listen, Ryo.
Touch my successor just a little bit.
I won't forgive you for nothing.
Who's your successor?
You're the only one I have, not anyone else!
I'm not joking.
I definitely don't want to!
Then who's going to get the Hondara sword?
I'm going to get my father's love!
I'm going to be happy with Ryo, so I'm definitely going to say it!
What?
I'm going to be a global actress, so I'm definitely going to say it!
I'm definitely going to say it!
What?
I thought you were going to say this, but I'm going to say it clearly, Ai.
You can't fall for a gorilla like this!
What did you say?
I can bear it if you want to have me, but I can't forgive you for all the insults you've made to Ryo!
Are you stupid?
You're a man.
No matter how much you love him, you can never marry him!
You should give up on your father and follow him!
I can't forgive you!
Hoooray!
The battle begins.
I did it!
It's a turn of events.
No, this is a good chance.
3, 5, Din, listen carefully.
The loser of this battle will be the successor of the Hondara Sword.
Huh? What did you say?
Hey, hey, don't you think it's better to win?
Shut up! That way, you won't be a burden!
I got it! Ai! I'm going for it!
I'm going for it!
Let's go!
Yeah!
That was amazing.
Hey! Turn the camera!
But we're still filming.
It's okay!
You can't win a battle this strong!
Yes, sir!
The next game of Spy #5 is...
Spy #5 vs. Clone Man!
Start!
Of course, the power of the man's love is at its highest!
For posterity, even!
Don't be coming here!
My every price is 1,000 yen!
This is for you.
This is for you, Sister.
No, this is for you, Brother.
It looks like he's talking about this holy battle!
Huh?
No way.
What the...?
You can take that!
Hey!
Huh?
I owe you a million.
Don't bet on me!
Fine. I bet on you.
Ryo!
What?
Move a little.
I'll crush this guy's balls.
Dad, stop!
Rin, I'm sorry.
Take this chance.
You're so dirty!
Shut up!
Ai, I'm sorry, but I want to continue being an actress!
I'm sorry.
Stop!
Darling, what are you doing?
What?
Let go of my hand!
Kyoko, you saved me.
Honey, don't be so mean.
Shut up.
I won't let you have your children fight for the sake of the successor.
But who's going to take care of the whole family?
If you want to have your own child, why don't you have another child?
Huh?
What?
You have that kind of a hand?
Let's go, honey!
Ouch!
Stop!
Stop, you bastard!
If you let the child carry the Honda-raken, it will only bring misfortune to the child!
What did you say?
The world's most powerful Honda-raken...
Don't make fun of me!
Ouch!
Damn it!
You're so mean, you idiot!
What are you doing, you pervert gorilla?
What?
Ouch!
Oh, my!
Ryo, you're like a child's sword.
Ai, Rin, this Honda-raken is the first child's sword.
The only child's sword is the best!
Really?
As expected of Mother!
Then we don't have to fight.
Yes.
Ai, I'm sorry for saying the bad things.
No, I'm sorry.
It's been a long time, so let's have a meal together.
Yes, Mother.
Let's go! Let's go!
Ai, Rin!
Kota-raken, ear pulling!
Ear pulling!
Hitsuba's front!
That's terrible.
Director, what should we do?
The film is waiting.
Stop it.
I'm tired of this battle.
Let's retreat!
Aeogappa!
Sentai Gorilla!
Thank you!
What?
The chief is moving to the third address?
Great!
I'm so lucky!
I didn't have to see the eyes of the leader every day!
You're the leader.
Now, I made my choice.
It's time for the book.
Next time, the leader!
Take care!
♪ I can't fall in love with you ♩
♪ You'm not my friend ♩
♪ But there are rumors ♩
I'm tired, but there's so much I want to do
I want to run through the wild desert on my bike
I want to be more free than a bird
With the speed of a full moon, I change into a lady's dream
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait
I dive into the future of the panorama
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait