Alien
You will lose your sight to the stars beyond time!
Found the culprit's car!
Roger!
Let's lower the altitude further!
There's no need for that!
I'll leave the rest to you, Ryo!
The helicopter just now hit the tires!
Right. If this happens, we'll run away on foot.
But this is a highway.
S- Special Security Team!
Sorry to keep you waiting, villains!
Everyone, be quiet!
-S- -S-
-S-
- -S
- -s
-
-Hyaa! -Hyaa!
-Don't shoot me!
Now, stand up!
-He's a small one. -H- help me!
-Hyaa! -Hyaa!
-Hyaa! -I'm throwing the gun!
-I'm gonna kill him if I can't do it!
-Did you hate the other one?
-Help me!
-What should we do, Ryo?
-Leave this to me!
-Hey! -Senpai!
-Ryo!
-Hey!
-Can't you hear me saying to throw the gun?
-Yeah, I can't hear you at all.
-What?
-Is it okay for him to die?
-Don't look at me or do anything.
-No way!
-Don't come near me!
-Oh, I see.
-You!
-You're still a special security!
-Yah!
-Hyaa!
-You did it!
-Now, stand up!
-Nice, Nakagawa!
-We both are the arrested!
-You, too!
-Amazing!
-All of us!
-I definitely think he's telling the truth.
-I know that all of them would get the dirty eye
-due to his decision of Ryo and Kikichi.
I think so.
Next, the 9th member, Reiko Akimoto.
She's a member of the Katsushika-sha.
You did it, director!
Four members were chosen from our department!
My department has excellent staff.
And the last member, the number 10,
Ryozu Kankichi, a member of the Katsushika-sha.
Why Ryozu?
It can't be!
That's all for now.
Special Security, known as the SS team,
who has just been established,
is now a member of the Katsushika-sha.
Now, let's have Captain Keppel,
who is the captain of the world-famous SGS-9,
who will lead the team.
It's international now.
With the high-tech development of Tokyo,
there will be a terrorist attack and terror
like other international cities in the near future.
For that, we have to build a special unit
like our country's SGS-9 as soon as possible.
Captain Keppel, I have a question.
What is it?
The last member chosen from our department
is a former Green Belly,
and Asato is a former kickboxing champ,
and Nakagawa Akimoto is a shooting skill
that fights with the police,
so it's obvious that he will be chosen by the members.
But why did you choose Ryozu?
I can't choose Ryozu?
Ryozu Kankichi is a member of the Shima-tachi.
He draws more than 100 cards a year.
It's impossible to do such an important mission.
Tch, tch, tch, tch.
Ryozu is good at shooting,
and he has a lot of vitality and vitality.
And he is a man who is needed
as a vitamin for the SS team
so that there are no more Ukkari and Hachibai
He is quite a Japanese 2.
Yes.
You may give us an opportunity to throw an 181-yen howitzer,
Good idea, Nakagawa!
You are good at shooting,
I want to join your club.
I?
Yes, that's right!
What did you do for 10 years?
and who caught my club?
I was a newbie.
That's strange.
Is it for been in our club for so long?
Next!
Ryo-tsu and Kankichi! Here I go!
One, two, three!
R-Ryo-sama!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
I forgot to tighten the belt.
You're a little under 8 meters, Ryo-tsu.
Be careful. There's a saying that a gorilla falls from a tree.
Captain, if you say that, the monkey will also fall from a tree.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
President Hashimoto.
Oh, it's so cold!
Captain, I don't mind the heat of Japan, but your joke is like Dave Spector.
Is that so?
Next, I'll tell you about the tactic when the culprit got stuck in the high-rise building...
Ryo!
I'm counting on you!
What's with the tactic? It's a very important training!
You should learn from Ryo-tsu.
Don't blink. Stretch your back and listen carefully.
Yes!
What's going on?
He's always sleeping in the high-rise building.
That's strange.
Ryo-tsu.
In this case, how will you arrest the culprit?
Hmm?
Ryo-tsu.
Please answer the question.
Ryo-sama.
Can't you hear me?
Ryo-sama, what happened?
Ryo-chan.
This is a doll.
It was made by a toy manufacturer last year.
It's a one-in-one figure that was sold out.
What? Then, what about Ryo-tsu?
Get rid of that doll.
Yes, sir.
Ryo-tsu!
Idiot!
Stand in the corridor!
What?
I'm not a doll, and I'm not a student.
Captain Keppel.
Please listen to me.
What?
What did you say?
Everyone.
The lecture is canceled.
Ryo-tsu.
Nakagawa.
Akimoto.
Volvo.
The five of you.
Gather in my room in thirty minutes.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
What happened?
Captain Keppel's face was blushing.
Maybe he's watching a disgusting video.
That's not true.
Captain Keppel is a Japanese-style, so he's a Japanese-style police officer.
I see.
But I'll recommend a stupid lord from Shibura Prefecture.
There was a big guy among the criminals arrested last night.
What?
This man, Adayada, is the younger brother of the boss of the Dark Syndicate, Abudara Kadabra.
Abudara Kadabra?
Do you know him?
Yes.
He's a master of darkness who sells weapons and ammunition at a high price
when there's a war or a conflict.
He's a master of darkness who sells weapons and ammunition at a high price when there's a war or a conflict.
He's known internationally, but he hasn't been caught yet.
He's a super duper big guy.
Abudara Kadabra.
Why do you call me "big guy" when my name sounds like a magician?
Don't underestimate him!
He already knows what happened last night and sent us a letter of challenge.
A letter of challenge.
Captain Keppel, you were so good to arrest him, didn't you?
Yes.
I'll let you know what will happen if you challenge me!
I'll definitely take back my brother and revenge on you and the SS team!
Prepare yourself!
You're so brave to challenge us!
Look at this.
Who are those scary people?
These are the photos of the terrorists that Avdala sent from the SGS headquarters just now to avenge them.
Jackal Henders, the leader who takes the name of the destroyer.
He's a special unit of the Oni army that has a strong presence in the foreign forces.
Next is the former pro wrestler Atomic Thunder.
He's the special unit of the close combat line that has been incorporated into all martial arts.
The special unit of the close combat line that has been incorporated into all martial arts.
Well, these two are Mr. Suke and Mr. Kaku, if you say so.
Next is Lily Francis.
There's a woman too?
I don't think you can underestimate me because I think you're a woman.
Lily is a shooting specialist who won the world shooting tournament, including the Olympics.
If you say it as a high school teacher, it's the position of the Shadow Old Silver.
Yumekaru looks more colorful than him.
And the last one is the high school teacher, Mr. Sato.
Let's go, Mr. Sato.
What is this?
And who were you to ask?
I was wondering because you weren't the one who should know.
Your father is a Mongolian.
Russia and America are half.
Your mother is an English Chinese.
No, well, it's just not explained at all.
My lord is...
Wearing a 63-year-old velcro.
Hey, hey, don't say it first.
Oh yeah, whatever you guys, do anything for the money.
Tiger.
There is no information that they have landed in Japan yet.
For now, Avdara's brother will be transferred to another place secretly from the base.
While the others are searching for their brother, we will make the mission a success.
You guys also prepare for an emergency and wait!
Roger!
Hmm?
It's under construction.
What a terrible thing to do!
It's unbelievable that they have already been landing in Tokyo!
Hey, the route is wrong. The airport is in the opposite direction.
That's enough.
Don't you dare say that!
Hey, the route is wrong. The airport is in the opposite direction.
We were hired by your brother. We don't accept your orders.
But, the SGS-9 Kepler has the grudge of sending many of its friends to the prison.
Until we make him pay, we won't be able to say goodbye to Japan.
Oh, my.
Oh, I see the military uniform.
That's it.
Captain Kepler!
Mr. Ryuichiro Nakagawa is being arrested.
We will broadcast this from the scene.
Mr. Kasai on the scene.
How could the Japanese police and SS team be silent about such a big thing?
That's our aim.
What?
The news that we are involved will be spread all over the world.
Everyone's eyes will be on this Odaiba building.
It's already happening.
More than 10 mass media helicopters are flying around.
I see.
We will show you the best show in that.
The best show?
Mr. Musou, I set up all the traps.
Especially, I set up a lot of explosives on the first floor.
Good job.
Then I'll show you a real show.
What do you think about the amount of this bomb?
Perfect.
Then I'll tell Keppel what I want to ask.
How much do you want for the Minoshiro Gold?
One million million yen.
What? One million yen?
We can make the money with Nakagawa's tax.
It's too much for one million yen, no matter how much you ask.
Who said it was expensive?
100 billion yen is too cheap!
What?
I earn 100 billion yen per second.
If you get released from the hostages with such a cheap money, you'll be a laughing stock!
1 trillion yen, no, 10 trillion yen!
What?
10 trillion yen!
10 trillion yen and an overseas flight to escape?
Is that what the terrorists are asking for?
That's right.
They said if we don't prepare by 3:00 p.m., we'll kill Nakagawa Ryuichiro.
Let's prepare for now.
Hey, hey, wait a minute!
If we say 10 trillion yen, it's 100 times, 1000 times, 10,000 times my salary!
It's too much that I don't understand!
As expected of Nakagawa's wealth!
In the old days, they called it Kinokuni and Bunzaemon.
You don't understand!
You guys, get in through the back door.
Roger!
The rest of you, go straight ahead!
The rat got caught right away.
This is the direct route to the president's office.
Wait, Ryo!
Everyone, step back!
Hey, what are you doing, Reiko?
Damn!
Even this trap!
If Reiko hadn't stopped me, everyone would have been killed!
Damn it!
We have no choice but to climb the stairs!
There are also stone walls here!
If we don't go down the stairs, we won't be able to get to the president's office.
Don't worry.
The eye is an eye, and the bomb is an bomb.
Here, there is a walking bomb-like Volvo.
Yeah! Leave the bomb to me!
The Bomb
I'm sorry.
I can't move from here.
What? There's an enemy?
No. I used all the grenades I had.
Raku! Think before you use them!
This time, it's fine. I brought as many as I could.
Are you Mr. Gombe?
If I get shot from behind, I'll blow up the entire building.
Oniwa Soto!
Aqua-uchi!
Let's go, Poli-ball!
Oniwa Soto!
You idiot! What are you going to do with the broken stairs?
There are too many of them!
But, just in case, I need to think about safety.
Don't use 10 shots at once!
Are you doing a leaf-building job?
I'm sorry.
I'll be more modest.
Be more modest. Be more modest.
S-sure!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Are you trying to eliminate your allies?
I have to do it quickly or else I won't be able to keep up.
Whatever!
Nagaga, do it!
Y-yes!
Just like Gunso,
there was a bomb-man.
I didn't expect half of them to come up.
Sander, Gosha, it's your turn.
Ouch!
Nagaga is so excited!
Father wants to save him with his own hands.
Oh!
Good! Don't be late, Nagaga!
Father, I'll definitely save him.
I'll save him!
Hey!
Hey, Nagaga!
senses
P-Pu study
Ryosuke!
I'm here, dolbe!
ha ha!
kept
ha ha ha!
ha!
Damn it! Don't let me do it!
It's no good.
How could he attack Mr. Wolff with a single blow?
You guys have to stop here.
I'm going to the president's office.
Please stop them somehow.
I got it.
Wait!
I won't let you get away!
I'll be your opponent here.
Alright.
If you keep this up...
I'll kill you!
Hey, stop it!
If you don't stop, I'm going to kill this woman!
Kei!
Reiko!
Is this the end?
That means...
this is the president's office.
It seems that only two of you have cleaned it up.
Keiichi...
What?
Be quiet!
Mr. Ryozu!
Mr. Nakagawa!
Are you alright?
You!
If you have a match, raise your hands!
You're the one who should raise your hands!
You!
What?
Senior!
Nakagawa!
Keiichi...
Father!
You got caught!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
What?
All of you?
I'm sorry.
It seems that it's the other way around.
Is this the level of the Japanese SS?
It's pathetic that only four of us can't win.
Shut up!
These guys are a reserve force!
I'll bring the real one, so wait for me!
Everyone, I'll definitely save you!
Don't be silly!
This is the 100th floor of the building!
I forgot that it was the 100th floor!
That's a foolish guy.
The only thing left is Keppel.
He's not a senior who's going to die just like this!
That's right!
Ryo's life force is more than a cockroach!
Oh, no.
Do you really think this is gonna end?
Do you really think this is going to end?
The SS team has gone to capture the culprit,
but, on the contrary, we got all of them killed,
and now only Ryo is left and we're at a disadvantage.
Nnngh...
As I thought, it's impossible for Japan to have a special force.
What a shame...
I'll contact the SGS9 of the country and ask for their support.
Hm?
The competition hasn't started yet!
I'm still left!
Impossible!
Just by being careless, Hachibey can't defeat the enemy!
As I thought, there must be someone like the Cazaguruma's Yashichi and Kagero Ogin!
Fufufufufufufufufufufufufufufufu!
Ahhhhh!
What?
It's a windmill.
It's not a piece of wood.
When an accident happens on land,
it can be solved with one pan.
One of the special police officer, Sanbagaras.
Big pan.
I'm back, Sanjiro.
There's a door.
Don't come in by opening the wall.
What's that voice?
It's a flying monkey!
I love the sea and protect justice.
Who read this?
Poseidon.
I'll put it in my tank.
I'm the captain of the police force on land.
I'm the leader of the sea.
The
Oh, these two are...
They are, too.
Is this the high Scholar's strange ointment?
No.
What?
I saw a woman's silhouette on the window.
And they're dressed properly.
How naive. They're the most perverted.
What?
Moonlight Power!
Are you transforming?
You'll laugh if you watch.
This is...
Wake up!
They're... they're changing.
It's not just a fancy transformation.
They're wearing the moon energy on their backs,
and they're breaking the stick of justice.
Leave the other cases to me.
The Moonlight Magician, Gekkou Deka!
I'm also the Venus Deka!
I'm back!
You guys are taking too long!
It's been a while, Ryo-tsu.
We're special police officers,
Samba-Galas,
and I can easily arrest terrorists.
Hmm.
Ryo-tsu, these guys are reliable.
Hey, hey, are they reliable?
Hmm...
Here it comes!
It's a pre-battle hunger strike.
Oh.
I knew it!
Hmm...
They're quite strong,
to let Hachibie fall.
Don't you get impressed, too!
You guys, support Ryo-tsu,
and rescue the hostages.
Yes, sir!
The peace in Japan is on your shoulders.
Hmm...
I don't care what happens.
The building on the 100th floor is the neck.
Well,
I'll burn the energy before I reach the top floor.
If it's at least 10 times,
I can arrest myself.
No way.
You can't do that.
You can't make the 100th floor into 10.
Make the 100th floor into 10?
No.
It's not like I can.
Huh?
I have an idea.
Cheers!
In an hour,
I'll get 10 trillion yen of cash,
and we'll be in Japan.
The weird guy who ran away from the window,
didn't show up to rescue us.
He ran away because of our terror.
He truly6
really6
really8
really9
really10
really11
really12
really14
really21
really24
All the members inside, move quickly!
What did you say?
Okay! Let's start the wire lock operation!
-Roger! -Roger!
Fire the wires!
Fire!
Alright! Good! Pull out!
Roger!
Come on! Let's escape quickly!
Kawashima, Kisa, Tsukui!
Don't let them get away!
Protect them with your life!
Alright! Good! Keep it up!
Terrorists! Look!
What is that?
Captain Kepelle?
What on earth is he planning to do?
Alright! Put the helicopter on the side!
Fire!
Special 9 wire!
Alright!
Alright! Go!
It's a mythic fall!
No way out.
Go away!
Oh...
It's going anywhere!
This is the kind of thing I would do.
Okay! One more!
...
Okay! Good, everyone!
Low the building down at this rate!
Understood!
...
What's going on?
Damn it! What have they done?
The building is getting lower!
What's going on?
To do such a reckless thing...
Ryo! Ryo is here!
What's going on?
Ryo!
Good! We can get in easily if we pull this much.
You terrorists! Wait!
Kaipan Deka and I will get in.
Dolphin Deka and Moon Deka, follow me to the base.
Roger!
Good! Let's go, Kaipan Deka!
Wait.
What?
When you combine with me, you must wear these.
That again?
If you don't wear them, I won't talk about this.
I got it. I just have to wear them, right?
Is it okay to let them do as it is?
This is the time. Leave it to me.
Let's go!
The SS guy is coming in with another one.
And he's naked.
What?
Thunder, Gosha, let's fight back.
Roger!
Ryo is here to help us.
But what does it mean to be naked with another one?
Maybe, maybe...
Don't say that! I don't want to hear that name.
How is it? This outfit is easier, right?
Shut up! Run!
Look! There are 95 stairs on the 5th floor.
It's wonderful.
Wonderful.
Alright, let's go!
That's it.
I won't let you go any further.
You're stupid to stand with a rifle and a hand.
What are you doing?
I don't need any equipment.
Don't panic.
Hey, hey!
Excuse me, it's time to get some nutrition.
I told you to stop eating that banana!
Mugumugu.
Gokkun.
I don't like to fight.
Let's get naked and talk.
What?
Now, let's get naked and talk.
Isn't he crazy?
He is.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Everyone was barefoot when humans were born.
Let's talk in a pure heart like a baby.
Don't get too close!
Ryotsu, you should take off your pants.
What?
You're lying!
If you take them off, they'll take them off, too.
I don't know the basis at all.
In order to make the other person naked, I must be naked first.
That's your own logic!
Take them off!
I got it.
I'll take them off.
You're a useless assistant.
What are you doing?
You're already a middle-aged man.
You don't have to hide it.
Don't raise the level on your own.
Damn it!
I don't like this anymore.
How is it?
Now, you don't have to be embarrassed anymore.
Don't get too close!
We don't have that kind of hobby!
Don't be so embarrassed.
If you make us move, you'll be free both physically and mentally.
I'm hungry.
Now!
Choryo!
It's a little more than we expected.
As usual, it's a terrible method.
Senpai!
Ryo!
I knew they'd come.
What's wrong with the terrorists?
They're planning on running away.
Take your father to the roof!
Tadayada's little brother, Abdara, is coming on a helicopter to fetch us.
Did Abdara come to Japan?
You got it? Kaipan, leave it to us!
Ryo-sama, be careful!
Dolphin, start the second operation!
Roger!
Hey, move it!
You made us work so hard.
I'm sorry, brother.
It's alright. Get on the boat.
Oh, Mr. Ryo.
I won't let you get away!
Dolphin Digger!
What?
Nobody knows the South Sea...
Joe, it's not the time to sing!
Hurry up!
What a tough guy.
Welcome, Mr. Sokkuri!
The one in the South Sea is Ryuichiro!
I'm the one in the South Sea!
Shut up!
I'm not that kind of a man!
I'm not that kind of a man either!
Which one is the real one?
Then, you all get on the boat!
Hurry up!
I'll kill you!
Oh, no!
Can't believe he's taking all of us!
Gekko, come here!
Roger!
Alright! Go chase the helicopter!
Idiot! Why are you coming down?
What are you doing? Go chase the helicopter!
Now, change into this.
Eh? Again?
With such a shabby outfit, I will be laughed at.
I will also transform, so change quickly.
I don't care, so hurry up!
Moonlight Power!
Hey, hurry up!
What is that outfit?
Let me explain.
When Gekko Deka wears the bunny girl costume,
his sense of taste changes.
And he becomes ten times more powerful.
I can hear it.
Their helicopter is...
It's over there!
Right.
You can see it, can't you?
Why don't you transform and chase it?
Then, let's go with the costume for the chase.
Stop it!
Yeah!
Leave it to you.
I will drive.
They are chasing us.
I'll help you.
You are way too fast.
These are coming, so hurry up!
Instead of the training over, I won't be faster.
I will change the car тотem.
You'll take care of them.
I will!
You move a bit.
Hey!
I'll shoot them!
Hey, it's dangerous!
Their arms have the power of Nagagawa or Reiko!
Reiko?
panelists
Yeah!
Aim the engine next time.
OK!
What's going on?
What's wrong?
It's a living thing, even though it just shot out its spine!
That's not going to happen.
Aim once more!
lt's a monster!
Hissing! Hissing! Hissing!
I- I'm out of bullets...
Ha ha! I'm out of bullets at last!
They were all my figures!
You tricked me!
Let's go! Now it's my turn!
Go, Bazooka!
Take this!
Let me explain.
If you transform into this costume,
you can do some crazy acrobatic controls!
Let's go!
How's that?
It's the full 30 Udinmai!
I got it!
I got it, so please stop!
I feel so bad!
You're still going to shoot me?
That's right.
I'm going to shoot you!
I feel so bad!
He's so good at controlling that I can't believe it!
All right! Let's go!
I can't control the machine!
What?
Damn it!
Let's get out of here!
Yes, sir!
Wow!
What's going to happen to us?
Help!
Getto, you guys!
Go rescue the old man and the children!
Roger!
Yes, sir!
Help!
I'll save them now!
Voilà!
OK, we rescued the old man!
And those guys won't let us out!
What?
Dammit!
Get off the ship.
What's happening?
What's going on?
I'm going to take the ship!
Take this, Asuka!
How dare you escape!
Y- yes!
W- what's that?
Nobody knows.
It's him again!
Damn!
The sea of waves.
We can't escape anymore!
Shut up!
Don't underestimate the special security!
Dolphin Dagger, counterattack!
OK!
Hey, Dolphin!
Come on!
I'm the only one in pink!
No, no, no!
Today, Pinka, the dolphin,
has come to cheer us on.
You know, the one who comes out at midnight!
A- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a-
You idiot!
You shouldn't make the enemy happy!
This is a promise, by the way.
I'm serious about the next one.
That's it!
What are you going to do?
Go for it!
Wow!
Bней Hauring
-Get out of the way! -Damn it...
Are you still trying to run away, Dolphin Digger?
Don't you have any stronger weapons?
Of course, but I don't have any responsibility.
What? Tomahawk?
Go koo!
No, don't make a noise!
We did it!
We'll arrest everyone.
We're here.
Captain Keppel, the operation is over.
Mr. Ryozu, thank you. Thank you so much.
We broke the building, but it's not a problem compared to the 10 trillion yen.
I don't care about the money.
He's here on behalf of Fuji TV.
Mr. Tsuyuki.
Our company's car.
I'll have it insured.
20 billion yen?
Are you kidding me?
We don't have that kind of money.
Oh, right. Where's Nakagawa's father?
Goodbye. We'll meet again in 10 years.
Father, goodbye.
Hey, don't send me off without permission.
Captain Keppel, please do something.
I didn't say to do this. I don't care.
No! Hey, Kaipan!
What?
What? An incident?
All right, I'll be right there.
See you later.
Hey, I didn't call you.
Don't run away!
Damn it!
Captain Keppel!
Take one!
Florence Joyner!
I don't care, but you guys are too old-fashioned.
Let me explain.
Captain Keppel, if you wear this costume, you'll run away faster.
Hey, you're dirty!
You're a dolphin!
Nobody knows!
Hey!
Come on!
Let's pay him!
Hehehe.
I don't like the Special Security team!
I hate him!
You say it like that,irrelevant to our company!
Eh?
Damn it.
Let's get in here.
I Ai-kun will goく!
Do I need to lean this equipment this much?
I'm fine!
Ah, really.
Thank you very much.
What a pity.
Listen to what I have to say.
I'll pay you later if you get it.
Mr. Kawasaki, your ticket is in a neat way.
Say, how was your trip from in Japan?
It was great.
It's the best in Japan.
♪ It's bouncing, it's tumbling, it's bouncing, it's bouncing ♩
♪ It's moving, it's moving, it's flying ♩
♪ It's the most amazing power ♩
♪ If everyone gathers here ♩
♪ It's like a dream, the final energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, yesterday, believe in it, draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ The world will be a rainbow, a rainbow ♩
♪ This is good, right? ♩
♪ There's no reason to say it's not good ♩