I don't believe in hell
when you're watching TV,
how about you try and
make this room your own?
This cloudy evening,
like someone's calling me,
I walked while looking back at the day after the rain
"Mom, please hold my hand"
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked only in the dark place of the Akegogai Tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone is forgetting
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Bonus Battle
Fight!
This is...
The first CI castle!
It's a treasure in the Hot Dog Gang!
And it's...
A box with a beautiful item!
I didn't know there was such a thing in this store!
A friend's toy closed the store
I was able to get the item there
It was in there
How much is it?
I don't intend to sell it
I'll display it in the store
Please! Sell it!
Well, if you insist...
Is it like this?
It's too expensive!
At least...
It's like this, right?
Then, how about this?
A little more!
Then, like this!
I won't buy anything more than this!
Alright! I bought it!
Thank you!
Hm?
What's this hand for?
It's not "what", it's a coin!
Unfortunately, I don't have any money
I'll pay later
We're a cash transaction
I said I'll pay later!
Can I trust you?
I can't!
You don't have to be so honest
I'm wondering how much you've been through so far
I didn't know that
I had a lot!
It's not just me!
We have a bar, a bar, a bar, a bar, a bar, a bar!
How much do you think we, the people of the shopping street, have suffered?
I knew it wouldn't sell
Please! Sell it!
I'll pay later!
If you don't have any money, leave the store
It's a bonus soon!
Then I'll pay!
I heard there's someone who likes this kind of thing around the 3rd store
Please! I'll pay for real!
This time for sure!
You say that every year
This year is for real!
Look at my eyes!
It's cloudy
Please, Bram!
Promise me!
I'll make sure to pay for sure!
That's not a promise
It's a pledge!
I'll write anything in the contract!
Then, let's sign this.
What is this?
It's like a contract.
Come on, sign here.
I got it!
Don't forget the coin.
I did it! I finally got it!
Thank you!
I did it!
Please, Dad.
Oh, Ryo-san, how are you?
I got a nice figure.
I'm going to give it to you as a blessing tonight.
That's good.
Well, then, see you later.
See you later.
Hey, Ryo-san, I haven't paid the bill yet.
It's a bonus.
I'll pay you with a bonus.
I'm always fooled by those words.
If you really want to get it,
let's ask him to sign it.
It's cheap if you just sign it.
My darling!
Wow!
W-what is this?
When I got my first CI,
I wanted something to decorate my surroundings.
I was just...
He's surprised.
You're making a lot of money, aren't you?
Well, yeah.
You've got a lot of money.
Even though it's a bonus.
Well,
I'll give you a bonus.
Ryo-chan,
if you keep saying that every year,
you'll end up being a rich man.
You're bothering the people in the shopping district.
I'll pay you this year.
Yes, yes.
You're such a noisy woman.
That's why I got a bride.
Did you say something?
Nothing.
Hello!
I'm from Tsurukame prefecture.
Oh, you're here.
Leave it there.
Yes.
Here.
It'll be 750 yen.
Please put it on.
Ryo-chan!
I don't have a date now.
I can't help it.
Then I have to ask for a date.
I can't help it if you ask for it.
Oh, you're so ridiculous.
Should I change the date?
No, no, it's fine.
When you get married,
I'm told to have this document signed.
Sign?
Okay.
Okay, sure.
Thank you!
What was that?
I don't know.
When I shop in the shopping district recently,
I get signed all the time.
Haven't you checked?
It's like a contract.
"Pay with a bonus!"
Hmm.
Oh, by the way,
I just got an email with a draft.
Where is it?
I found it somewhere and threw it away.
I see.
I wonder?
Yes, I think so.
Oh, the one next to it.
Oh, right.
"Pay with a bonus!"
What's this?
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
What you signed is not just a contract.
It's a contract to withdraw a loan from Daikin.
Daikin?
A loan?
What?
That is,
it's a contract to withdraw Daikin from Ryo-chan's bank loan automatically.
I see.
I didn't believe you.
I didn't think you'd know that.
Can you do that?
I can.
Electricity, gas, water,
Even buying things with a credit card,
That's what's going on.
Oh, if you say so,
It's too bad, Ryo-chan.
We can't afford to pay the loan.
The bank loan is probably going to be empty in a flash.
No way!
I'm going to hold a strategy meeting for the 29th Ryotsu Kankichi Bonus Battle.
...I'd like to say that.
Congrats!
This year's bonus battle is confirmed to end with our victory.
Today's the break-off. Enjoy it as much as you can.
No way, I never thought there would be such a way.
Ryo-san has been in debt for two years.
I should have noticed it earlier.
I don't like this kind of way.
When I don't see it, money moves without knowing it.
Well, well, thanks to that, my money will come back.
Hey! Promo!
You're all here, you little punks.
Oh, good!
I didn't force you to sign it.
Ryo-san signed it himself, right?
I told you it was a contract!
I told you it was a contract.
It's Ryo-san's misunderstanding, isn't it?
You! You've calculated that far!
Or did you think I could ignore it if it was a contract?
Huh? No, not at all.
But I don't like this way of doing things.
I've been watching you this whole time.
I've been trying to pay you back with my own hands,
with my own feelings.
But!
I don't need any kind of thanks.
All I need is money to come back.
Huh?
Besides,
Ryo-san was the one who suddenly wanted to pay you back
when you saw the cash in front of him.
Th-that's...
Damn it! Remember that!
I'll get you back!
I did it!
I'm so happy!
I'll get you back!
This is it!
If you do this,
I'll have to ask you to pay the cash in advance,
not to deposit the bank.
How do I convince them?
Hey,
don't throw away the newspaper.
Huh?
Here it is.
Here it is!
200g of pork,
carrots,
onions,
and...
Chief,
I have something to tell you!
Sshh!
Huh?
Nothing.
What?
The second supermarket is a special sale?
We should buy it there, right?
Okay, I got it.
Huh?
You're the chief of the Katsushika office,
but you're a waiter?
How pathetic.
You've been like this for a long time.
Leave it alone.
You've been like this for a long time?
What?
Actually,
not only the house of the chief,
but the authority of the father's family has decreased throughout Japan.
The cause is all
the fact that the salary has fallen into the account.
That's ridiculous.
Is that really true?
Please remember.
The day you brought a thick bag of bonuses to your house and went home.
A thick bag of bonuses?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Here's a bonus.
Wow, a bonus!
Dear,
thank you for your hard work.
Let's go shopping together next Sunday.
Yay!
Thank you, dear.
Let's have sukiyaki tonight.
Here you go, dear.
Oh, sukiyaki!
Now, we're going to the store.
No, don't take these yet!
If you'll just give it to me.
You have to sign it.
Hello?
The gift is?
I can't believe this.
Don't be so arbitrary!
No, it's not!
It's my real money.
This is the thoughts of the head of our family.
My experience кл
But if that happens, it will take a lot of time.
I don't want you to do that to your monthly salary.
At least you should pay the bonus.
But...
President, have you ever been grateful for the bonus?
By the way, last year...
I'm home.
Oh?
Hey, what's wrong with this?
I bought it for the bonus.
You bought it? Without my advice?
Take it to my room.
Sigh...
Without any advice, I bought my own computer, and there was no thank you.
It's my bonus.
President, now is the time.
To restore my father's authority, the bonus should be returned to the cash register.
My Katsushika office is not going to stop that.
What?
I need you to help me restore my father's authority.
This Tonda Gomez is well- anthrop translated for the purpose of restoring the rights of his father, Imaishizu.
This year's bonus is a beleza.
Hey, president!
As expected of a man!
Oh, this is bad!
My hair is burned!
Hello, Kikuchi-san.
I'm free today.
The balance of the production has returned.
That's ridiculous! Look at this!
What?! The bonus at the Kazushika office is in cash?!
The president is talking all over the place.
Ryo, if you get a cashier, I'll contact you.
If you sit there, you'll get in the way.
It doesn't matter where I am.
I just want to get the bonus as soon as possible.
It's them.
They're so cool.
The bonus hasn't been paid yet.
It seems that the cashier has arrived late.
Okay, the payment is ready.
That's why I was against that strategy.
You can't just say that now.
Mr. Tramaya, what strategy do you have in mind this time?
Yeah.
The Sky Eye strategy that uses an artificial satellite navigation system.
And the Peeping Eye strategy that uses a surveillance camera around the city.
The final strategy is the Shaking X, a new weapon that I developed for the president of the Ryo family.
You've always failed in your previous strategies.
I didn't have time to prepare.
There's no way I can do it.
Besides, I'm going to power up the Shaking X.
It's a Shaking X Max.
You can do it.
What?
What's the matter?
Wait, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
This is crazy.
Don't be so annoying.
You can do it.
Yes, yes, you can do it.
We're young.
Stop it!
What are you doing? Get off!
We can't let Ryo-san go free!
If we don't get the money, you won't get the money!
But if you find it, you can get your bonus and escape.
I see.
Don't do that! I'll pay you!
But you always end up with the money.
Damn it!
Emergency!
A cashier was attacked in the Katsushika office.
The bonus of everyone in the Katsushika office has been stolen.
The culprit is a man in a suit!
He's running away with a white shirt!
We'll arrest him with all our might!
The culprit is a man in a suit!
What are you going to do, Pramoya?
If Ryo-san gets away with it, it'll be a big deal!
We'll take the cashier back with our own hands!
What?
The culprit is a man in a suit!
I see.
I'll go hold the cashier.
What!?
The culprit is a man in a suit!
He's running away with our own hands!
We're taking care of this innocent picture!
We have to take care of him, but this can't be.
His power is so weak.
What if he is a policeman?
I don't think it will be a redstone.
What was the culprit doing for a while?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
There was a blue van with a terrible smudge.
I don't care about that.
The culprit's car is a white van.
No, I'm in a good shape.
I'm worried when I see a good job.
Sorry.
I understand. That's the culprit's car.
What's wrong, Mr. Plamo?
He changed the color of the car.
It's true that it's impossible to change it in a short time.
Just temporarily blind the police.
Put it in a place where no one can see it.
Cover the front glass with a newspaper and paint it.
That's how you do it.
If you look closely, you'll notice something unnatural.
The police are looking for a white van.
There is a possibility to overlook it.
I see.
As expected, you're a man.
This year is our victory, Mr. Ryo.
It's the police.
Open the back bed.
Yes, sir.
...
Well, we didn't find a white van.
All right, let's go.
The white van is in a small wolf woman's car.
There is a clue.
What's happened to the white van?
I got a clue.
I'm going to use it.
Hurry?
Yes.
Yes, sir!
The blue van is heading west from Kamiari.
Roger that!
I found it! The blue van!
It's huge!
Alright! Don't let it escape!
We'll catch up with it!
Nakagawa! Don't let it miss us!
Oh!
Money in this place?
Money?
Stop!
Here it comes!
Where's the money?
I found a 500 yen coin.
What's this? It's a coin from the game!
What are you doing?
I'm just going to...
I'm not doing this for nothing!
I need to get a bonus!
Oh no! I lost it!
Stop! The car over there!
Stop!
I'm going to get you!
I'm leaving!
Oh no!
I'm going to get you!
It's finally time to show off the true power of the Shaking X!
Oh no!
You can go now.
You won't be able to run from me!
It's too late!
I'm warning you!
Damn it.
They should be around here!
What do we do?
If we keep going, the culprit will get away!
Is there any way to contact the police?
In this state...
Hmph, everyone is not fooling around.
There is a special way.
What? Special?
Do it like this.
Ah! There is a bullet falling in such a place!
A bullet is falling!
That way, Nakagawa! Hurry up!
But, what about the car of the plumber?
The cash in front of us is better than the car of the plumber!
Senpai, it's dangerous!
Hey, you, go back!
What?
Where is the bullet?
Mr. Ryoma!
What?
Senpai, is that...
Oh!
It's a trunk for the cash transport!
That guy is the culprit!
What?
This is Nakagawa! The culprit was found!
There is my bonus in there!
F-fool!
Can't you see this?
Give me back my bonus!
Get out of my way!
I did it, senpai!
My bonus! My bonus!
Mr. Ryo!
You're going to give me back the cash, aren't you?
W-well...
I'm running away!
I'll take out my bonus for you!
Bastard!
You want to be the nobleman?
He'll never be the nobleman.
I'm from the nobleman club.
I'm accounts for all the bank accounts.
You're still here with the nobleman?
Y-yeah...
The floor is stooped...
You guys have to pay the fine.
And I have to pay the fine, my boys!
I'll give it a try.
Yay!
Kaka!
The first local worker, Mr. Ryotsu Kankichi.
Here.
Here, good work.
Huh?
It's so thin.
613 yen, right?
Hey!
Isn't that a mistake?
No, it's not.
Hey, chief!
I only have this much bonus.
What's going on?
In your case, I've broken a lot of books.
I got it from the bonus.
That's...
You didn't get it this year either.
I'll get it next year for sure.
I tried my best, but I can't believe it.
But I really did.
It's
"Got a lot of books!"
Such a big clause.
I'm filled with words that I can't handle.
Ah!
I can't read books.
So you're reading books?
Are you so surprise?
Then it's important to read the books completely.
I read them to this guide.
I'll give it a look.
♪ Even if you're irritated, let's get over it and get over it ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ When the hot shower goes through ♪
♪ I'm in a pillow and I'm recovering ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ Every Monday ♪
♪ Monday, Monday, Monday ♪
This is bad!
Nakagawa and I have switched bodies!
Wait a second!
Does that mean I'm the Onzouji of the Nakagawa Group?
I can use money, I can eat delicious food!
I can't believe this!
No!
I'm the "Body Jack"!
Nice to meet you!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!