Subtitle by:
Natsuki
From the tap to the toilet, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will also end with a sound
But I lost my happiness again
I realized it, because I'm such an idiot
Because I'm such an idiot
Excuse me, director.
Slow, slow, quick, quick
Quick, quick, quick, Slow, detai
Oh, that, um...
So, you've found me.
Actually,
I've been learning accomplished dance lately.
Excellent dance?
It's better than I thought.
How's that, Ohara?
Maybe you can learn it too?
Good...
I'm the head of the club.
No, no.
At first, everyone gets a little late.
But if you try, you'll get addicted to it.
Please try it.
Ah...
Yes, let's decide our partners and start with the waltz of yesterday.
It's three quarters of a second.
Yes.
It's your first time, right?
Well, Daijiro Ohara.
Yes.
Have you ever danced in the club?
Then I'll teach you the steps.
Please come here.
Yes, thank you.
First, stretch your back and the way you put your hands is like this.
Put your right hand under your shoulders.
Don't be stiff.
Yes.
The waltz is centered on rotation.
The basic rhythm is counted as one, two, three.
I see.
Mr. Ohara, you have improved.
No, it's all thanks to your instruction.
I didn't think there would be such fun in life.
How about it?
Would you like to try it, Mr. Ohara?
Me?
No, it's ridiculous.
The first pair is...
If you don't mind, I'll help you.
Really?
Yes.
In exchange, I would like to practice the waltz of today.
Please promote the waltz to everyone.
Yes.
The waltz of the night?
Is the chief?
That's right.
Well, I guess it's one of the advantages of adults.
If it's a waltz, my wife wants to try it.
Oh, I see.
Then, I'll do it.
It's a good match.
Is that so?
I'm a good dancer.
I can dance and dance...
Nakagawa and Reiko can dance, of course.
Yes.
I was taught from the time I could walk.
I learned it with ballet.
These two are special.
They are different from ordinary Japanese.
If I stretch my back and dance the waltz,
I feel like I'm the second foreign star.
It's strange.
I'll try it, too.
I'm a dancer.
Oh, I see.
Because you are short,
the underarm turn lead won't go well.
I'll teach you, Reiko.
4/4 seconds.
Count is quick.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
From the side step with slow.
Oh!
As expected!
You two are tall, so you look like a painting.
Oh, and I'm wearing a fox trot.
I'm wearing a fox trot.
So...
The fool who dances and the fool who looks at you are the same.
You're an insect!
You're annoying.
What do you mean, a fox trot?
I will never do such a thing.
What?
The prize money is 10 million yen?
I see.
Look at this.
Chief Ohara distributed it to us.
Oh!
I'll do it.
I definitely will!
I'll do it too!
I'll do it, Ryutsu!
Me too!
Are you guys going out?
It's no use stopping them, Ryutsu.
Dance? With that face?
Face has nothing to do with it!
Stop, stop. You idiot. Think again.
You're trying to reduce your rival even a little bit, aren't you?
Giga...
Shut up!
I heard it was 10 million yen, so I'm not supposed to be quiet, right?
I'll do it too! I'm also a Shako dance!
Dance!
Me too...
If Nana-chan can make a pair...
Oh, I see. You can't do it alone.
You need someone to make a pair.
What should I do?
Nakagawa-san is obviously going to make a pair with Reiko-san.
But I can't change the topic.
I see. At this time, anyone is fine.
I have Jody...
I have Nana-chan...
Hmm...
Well, you can't help it.
You're just a bug.
Sakonji-san, I thought you were the only one I saw.
Let's close our eyes to everything else and make a pair for the sake of money.
A pair?
Don't be so happy with that!
No, Naoko.
Chacha-san.
I...
Naoko-san.
Oh?
Chacha-san.
I'm? I...
I guess I'm in trouble...
OK, let's join hands.
What?
Are you a girl manga?
I'll make you a pair!
I'm the one who will make you bloom with a beautiful body without losing to the rival's conspiracy and impudence!
Don't drag the monster in!
It's terrible!
First, let's take a look at the waltz.
Damn it! It's not about getting in or not! It's about being a partner!
Reipo is Nakagawa.
Honda is Otohime.
Volvo is Jody.
And there's more.
Maria is on a business trip at a time like this.
I have to do something or I can't talk!
Next is the word!
Hmm?
Hmm, but when I look at it like this, it's a precise movement like a machine.
It looks like a mannequin is moving.
A mannequin!
Yeah, I think I can do it!
This is where my figure-tech shows off!
Watch this!
It's done!
Uh...
The whole body is...
This is the super-toushin-dai figure-touch dance version where all joints are bent to their own will!
Then, let's start.
Ta-da-da-da-da...
Ah! Ouch!
Ouch!
It hurts!
Damn it!
Even if you can do it, it's the same for me to move it.
Hmm...
Huh?
But it's still difficult to move it.
So, here's a request from my grandfather.
This dance software that dataizes all the professional movements.
Right.
If I install it on my figure, I can dance on my own with my hands connected.
Well, there's nothing you can't do.
But it's a hurry.
If I have two million yen, I can do it, right?
No way!
I need this much.
I need it.
What? You want it for 50,000 yen?
No, no.
Oh, 5000 yen.
That's a good deal.
No way.
It's 5 million.
5 million.
Hmm.
Let's make it a million.
7 million.
8 million.
8.8 million.
Why do you have to increase it?
Why do you have to decrease it?
Hmm.
You're so stubborn.
Then 3 million.
One more.
4 million.
3.5 million.
All right.
The deal is finalized.
In exchange,
make sure you make it to the tournament.
Don't worry.
My staff is okay
even if they don't sleep at home.
They're all so ridiculous.
Do you think they can sleep at home?
Do you think so?
Well, I...
I think so.
Then I'll take care of this.
Well, I'll take care of this.
What?
I can't do this.
You just do it.
Why, what do you mean?
Heيل, I'll show you something.
I have a powerahex.
You're sure to do this.
I'll let you do it.
...
Oh, that's great!
Yeah, it did!
...
Perfect!
You're right, Lotto.
...
But, there's one problem.
You're too tall and weird.
I can't give up here.
I'll stretch my legs for 10 million yen.
What's wrong, Senpai?
I guess you couldn't find a partner after all.
But I don't think Ryo would give up on that.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're late, Ryo.
No, it's just...
You're really tall.
Really? You're smarter than usual.
I see.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Social Dance in Katsushika D1 Grand Prix.
We are now hosting the Social Dance in Katsushika.
Go, Katsushika!
The judges will be evaluated by technique and art.
The pair with the highest total points will be the winners.
First, the preliminary round.
The preliminary round starts now.
So, I'll start with the waltz.
Mr. Ohara, don't be stiff.
Just relax as usual.
Ouch!
Don't throw it by mistake.
I think...
I'm happy just doing this.
Bobby, be careful with your nose.
I know.
Are you okay, Bobby?
It's surprising that Ryo-chan is so calm.
Your partner is great.
Really? Who is that person?
This is the first time I've seen him.
It's the first time I've seen him.
It's good to see him!
Feeling so good at singing.
I'll start as soon as possible.
I'm nervous.
I'll listen to them and get ready.
Yes.
My partnerần
Easy, easy.
Easy.
3, 4...
Not bad.
Now, we will announce the pair that will pass the preliminary round.
Please look at the monitor.
I'm so nervous.
Oh my God.
This is the pair that will pass the preliminary round.
The pair that will pass the preliminary round.
I'm disappointed.
Damn, we have to put the nose out.
Don't cry, Bobby.
But the pair that will pass the preliminary round is...
Of course, they have different abilities than you.
I'm so frustrated.
I can't help it.
They are dynamic and bright.
That's true.
But they became so good in such a short time.
This is true.
Excuse me, what is your name?
Huh?
Is it this one?
This one is rude, Ryo-chan.
The wonderful dance that everyone saw is because of the partner.
Well, I have a name.
I have a name, but...
Ryo-chan, I'm not asking you.
Excuse me.
I'm a man who is not polite and common sense.
My name is Ohara.
And you are...
I'm a dancer.
I'm Izu's dancer.
Izu's dancer?
Well, this is a name that was born to be a good dancer.
Really?
Really.
Well...
Excuse me.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Why is Ryo-chan with you?
Anyway, you look the same as when you always dance.
I'm a natural dancer.
I'm going to the bathroom before the final.
Excuse me.
Anyway, it's the final.
Until the end,
I have to get through it somehow.
Well, I'm sorry for before.
Why are you here?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for practicing the secret steps.
It was dangerous.
It hurts.
Ryo-chan.
I wonder if everyone is fine with this.
Well, it's a little embarrassing, but we're all fans now.
Fan?
Not you, but Mr. Dance.
It was wonderful.
Please sign it.
I beg you.
I'm in trouble.
You said you didn't care.
That's right.
Ryo-chan is a good dancer.
I beg you, Mr. Dance.
So, there are various circumstances.
Eh, what's that?
What?
Wait, Ryozu.
Mr. Dance.
Please wait.
All right, this way.
Mr. Dance.
Damn it.
Give up.
Okay.
This way.
Odoriko!
Odoriko! Odoriko!
It's not what I expected.
You've made it too beautiful.
What's wrong? Odoriko!
Hold on!
My neck is tingling!
It's gone!
I saw it!
Who are you?
I'm the girl manga master, Ruririn.
The girl manga master?
You saw it?
Of course.
I saw everything with my naked eyes.
Perfect!
I failed to complete the plan!
There's only one solution.
What?
In other words, I will replace the doll.
I won't say no!
I'll do my best, Ruririn!
Coach!
Why am I the coach?
You're the coach of the girl manga!
That's true, but...
Anyway, you have no choice.
You must choose me as you partner.
Oh, I see!
He came all the way.
I'll try my best!
Go for it!
10 million!
Now, the final will be released.
The final requires higher techniques and artistic expression than the flying Committee.
Now, which pair will be the best?
I wonder where Odoriko is.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Odoriko looks different than before.
This is bad. I have to do something.
If this continues, I'll take you down with my strength.
I'll take you down with my strength.
What's going on?
32th pair, big minus.
Are you okay?
Ryo-chan, right?
I don't think I have any choice to win.
I'm still at a disadvantage.
Next.
Odoriko is too dynamic!
This is bad.
The 55th pair has passed as well.
I'm sorry!
There are too many winners!
Ryo-chan cannot afford this.
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Yaaaiiiiii!
Huh? That face!
Yaaaiiiiiiiiiii!
Shodormundell!
Damn it! You did it!
My feet are shaking!
I'm shaking!
Ouch! Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Uwaaaaaaa!
What are you doing?
This is getting serious!
This is bad!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
My feet are shaking!
I'm so messed up!
I'm not the winner of this competition!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ryo-chan! Take this responsibility!
I'll pay you for this, Kankichi!
No, no...
The cake is delivered by Hanamuko and Hanayume.
Is this the only part-time job we have?
It's not perfect for us.
Stop it, you monster!
Help me!
Is this a crime?
I'm feeling couldn't help it.
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
T Estados Unidos!
What an existent robot.
The typhoon is coming again!
The storm is coming again!
You made the world blindly open-minded!
What do you think? I'm cool, right?
I still have plenty of ideas to come up with.
It's not evened feet of dream.
Everyone, will you call me Dr. Lyotsu?
heights of everyone's imagination
It would be my pleasure, if I could be your co-presenter.
Somehow, I feel I can make something good now.
I watch you, whatever you do.
Come to our town
Thank you!