〈The
It is a hazy day in the city
I saw it
A stone fell
lt was thrown
It was thrown into my shoes
I wonder if I'll go to the store where I saved up
I laughed as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is only a single slur
The cityscape that does not change even one yawn
It's so gentle
From the tapestry of a cap
To the taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
If you win, you'll be happy again
I'm going to lose
I realized
Because I'm an idiot
Bye, Chief Ohara
Hey!
Hey! Wait! Wait!
Pay the money!
Ryo-san, catch him!
He's running away!
He's running away?
He's in pain
Ryo-san!
Don't let him run away.
I'll catch you no matter what.
Okay!
I won't let it go!
Ryo, don't let him get away!
I'm worried
I can't do it
This is the last chance
Don't worry
You don't have to worry
You can do it
Wait a minute
I'll catch you
Stop him!
Stop!
-Here you go! -Huh?
Huh?
Get on your knees!
Please, I beg you!
-How did it go? -W-we were fine.
Lock, lock!
As you remember, the culprit was arrested!
Huh?
What's wrong, chief?
What's wrong with you?
You idiot!
Who told you to go that far?
You don't know the true nature of the game.
I'm the one who's been trying to get away with it.
Not just physically, but mentally as well.
Who do you think will be the one to be punished?
You're the type to act before you think.
When I cross the road,
I look at the right and left,
then I look at the right and left again,
and then I cross the road after I look up.
Why are you looking up?
Because there might be a meteor shower.
Yes, we're going to the park.
Chief, it's the chief.
It's not a joke.
I'm Ohara.
What?
I'm the chief of the third branch.
Yes, that's...
Yes, I understand.
What's wrong, chief?
The third branch is...
I think the chief was hospitalized for a sudden illness.
Yes, that's why I'm going to be the chief's deputy for a while.
Then, what about this branch?
But the chief will take over.
Great!
What do you mean "great"?
That looks great.
No, I don't think it's okay to be so quiet that the chief is gone.
It says, "He's happy to see you.
What?
I'll try to be quiet without seeing your face.
We're fine because we can spend our days lovingly every day.
I'm getting lucky, too.
If I can get away from this Shimatsu-shou, my management skills will be properly evaluated.
I'm so sad. The chief is not in the operation.
It's not an operation. It's a relocation.
Well, that's it.
Even if I'm not there, everyone will cooperate and go.
Yes.
This is the third exit.
It's a pretty beautiful exit.
But it's difficult here.
What do you mean?
I heard that there are no problems like Ryotsu with young people.
The problem is the young people.
The previous chief used his nerves too much and was hospitalized because he was beaten.
Beat?
Anyway, he's a young man these days.
He only does what he's told to do.
If he's scolded, he'll quit right away.
So my true management skills will be questioned.
OK.
Ah, gentlemen.
I'm here.
I'm Ohara, the chief of this office.
I'm counting on you.
I'm Otsuka.
I'm Sugamo.
I'm Komagome.
What?
What a honest young man.
There's nothing to worry about.
My guidance policy is to make careful decisions and to be proactive...
I have to feed them.
...Eggs.
And to be proactive...
Hello?
Oh, Tabata?
Now?
Is it OK?
It's not a big deal.
Yeah, go ahead.
You can continue.
What?
The problem from the other day...
I'm embarrassed as a police officer...
What?
You've already passed?
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's 11:30.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
Messis.
There's a very popular spot in the magazine.
The line will be ready soon, so you have to line up before 30 minutes.
I have to line up before 30 minutes.
Idiot!
What are you thinking?
I'm working.
Don't you have any sense of self-awareness as a policeman?
I'll quit.
Why do you have to be scolded like this?
I haven't done it.
You guys?
I see.
You have zero management skills.
Huh?
It's our fault that you don't have your own skills.
Hmm?
So, you're not going to apologize?
No, no way.
No way!
He's angry again.
Oh, is that it?
Well, I won't talk like this.
How about you?
You want to go out for a drink tonight?
Don't worry.
I'll treat you.
Tonight?
I have a program I want to watch.
I have to clear the game.
I have to go to the concert tonight.
I can't go.
Besides, we'll go to drink on our own.
Don't worry about us.
Yeah, we'll just get lost if we get involved with our superiors and subordinates.
Everything is up to my own pace.
If I tell them I'll treat them to a meal, they'll just follow me.
What am I thinking?
I was so close to that sick guy.
We'll go to eat.
Chief!
If you're the chief, you have lunch break.
What? It's already 2 o'clock!
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Nothing!
Let's redo all the reports we submitted!
What? What do you mean?
It's not good if we don't have a date or a plan.
I was scolded by the copy dog!
You can't do that?
But I told the chief of the Demoshika.
Damn it! The date of the new game's release!
I'm home.
Chief of the Demoshika!
We have to have a date for this report!
Which one?
This one...
I don't have to sign it or not, right?
Whichever one is fine.
Well, it's better if you sign it.
You don't have to.
But isn't it better if you sign it?
Whichever one you want.
Damn it!
It was perfect to do the check, because I'm a precious chief!
But...
What's wrong with my heart?
It's just please the chief's commanding power!
It's alright!
Damn it!
What are you thinking?
Don't listen to the next person.
It's better now.
Yes, I'm running to the park.
Blue mini-cycle?
I found it at the station.
But the documents are not here.
I gave it to the chief last week.
Right, chief?
Yes, I have it.
Put it here.
I'll deliver it to the police station!
Ryo-tsu is working hard, too.
He works ten times more than usual.
He doesn't have time to be idle.
Damn, one day is over with just the document.
I'm going.
Good work.
Nothing happened today.
You have been given peace.
Yes.
I'll treat you to a feast.
How is it, chief?
Really?
To communicate with your subordinates, you need to drink.
There is a good yakitori restaurant.
It's good and cheap.
I'll treat you to a feast.
No, I can't go.
I'll have dinner at home today.
No, no.
I'll go first.
No, no, no.
I'll pay for it.
Okay, I'll go.
Ryo-tsu?
Yes, I had seen Ryo-tsu in person, right?
What kind of person was he?
Ryo-tsu, huh?
At any rate,
I don't see such a crazy person.
He always wears sandals and wears uniforms on the day of the day.
When he becomes a salesman of the entertainment department,
he also goes to work at the inn to buy clothes.
Cool!
You're so cool!
What? I told you so!
You're so cool?
Mr. Ryo is our idol!
Idol?
He's a civil servant but he's free to live freely without being bound by anyone.
He's wonderful. He's able to go through his own lifestyle.
Don't be stupid!
He lives without looking back at others' troubles and worries.
He's just living freely.
The chief is too old.
He doesn't understand how we feel.
That's right!
What's wrong with living freely in our own lives?
Mr. Ryo is our idol!
Idol? Ryo?
He threw the president off the second floor.
There are 53 destroyed cars.
78 cars?
What happened?
I heard there were 150 cars.
I don't understand.
It has been 2 years and Mk-II :
Senior, you look very pale recently.
Of course. I've been at work for over a year.
I'm your boss now.
Rather than slacking off, I don't have time to sit in a chair.
It's so hard to do that right now you should're worried about him.
He was doing the dishes so he'd do things so fast he could.
I'm worried about you now, so I can't miss you.
Stop it.
I'll walk home from here.
Really?
Good night.
Oh...
Go, go.
This is the law of the 50 ways of communication between a superior and superior.
Chief!
Why do you always come here when you don't read a book?
Chief said...
You always read a novel, but you don't read a business book!
Well, you're not doing well with your subordinates in the third chapter of the eight books, are you?
I'm fine.
Everyone is good young people and I have no trouble.
You're the one who's arguing with the chief.
I'm kidding.
It's very easy to work and I'm in the right mood.
I see.
Then I'll stay here.
I'm the official chief of the third chapter of the eight books.
Even if you become the chief,
I'm fine.
Don't walk in front of me.
I'm going to have a drink with the bird.
Me too.
You're going to lose!
L-Lachai, are you two?
I'm alone!
I'm sorry, but this is the only room we have.
What would you like?
Beer!
Here you are.
You're a good drinker, but you're not good at drinking.
No dumb dude could be so full of energy today.
What would you like to drink?
I'd like two thongs of flavour, two white thongs and a Plus.
You're not paying attention.
And I'd like some shirts, sixs, fives, eights, nine cubs,
Kimchi hot pot!
Ah, I'll have the chirichiri, yudofu, and ishikari hot pot!
Aji no tataki, curry no karaage,
Ika no maruyaki, niku jaga!
Oshinko ni shirasu oroshi,
Morokyu asari no sakamushi,
Akedashi dofu ni edamame!
I'll have tatami iwashi!
Tonsoku ni takobutsu!
Hey, beer no sake da!
Oodokkuri de!
Sake masu de!
Uu, my head hurts.
I did something stupid last night.
But I still can't remember what happened on the way to Chidori.
That's why, in the rare thing jokes series,
the part of the soul is different.
Oh, that's right.
What the hell are you thinking?
Tofudiran and...
Dilan...
Oh! Tofudiran and... Dilan...
Tofudiran and... Dilan...
Emergency call! Emergency call!
A robbery occurred at the second Hotsudo Bank.
The culprit is running towards Kameari Sanchome by bike.
Repeat.
Otsukaku, Sugamoku, Komagome.
That's right.
Get him at the station.
Huh?
But the working hours are almost up.
I have a date appointment.
Don't say that!
Come with me!
I got it!
Oh!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Damn it!
Now, run along!
You'd better be careful!
You're here!
I'm...
The real Ryo-tsu!
So lucky!
What are you?
Ryo-tsu is our ideal type!
Huh? My ideal type?
Your subordinates have more eyes than you do!
This is not the time to be like this!
Let's go! Don't be so grumpy, Ryo-tsu!
I'm not your subordinate!
Don't order me around!
Come here!
Okay, okay!
Let go of me!
Ryo-tsu is...
He's so unyielding to Chief Ohara!
Maybe Chief Ohara is a great person!
What's this?
Yeah.
It must be the culprit's motorcycle.
From the motorcycle's perspective,
the culprit is...
This one.
Think about it from the slipart.
Over there!
Don't imitate me!
Ryo!
You're the one who's imitating me!
Chief, it's too small for you.
Please get out of the way.
You better get out of the way!
Help!
What?
Tanaka!
Help! Tanaka!
What?
Let go of her!
Get a car ready!
Otherwise, I don't know what to do!
Let's call for backup!
What?
Wait!
Don't provoke the culprit!
No way!
But we're the only ones...
Safety is the most important thing!
Anyway...
What's going on?
Ryo-tsu is...
Where is he going at this time?
Over there!
Yeah.
What are you doing?
He's trying to jump from the top!
Quiet!
You're being too violent...
It has to...
What..
What's going on?
What, man?!
Tanya's sleeping!
Bl choo!
Right, bring it on!
What's wrong?
Go away!
Bl choo...
Bl choo, he's not sleeping!
Where did he go?
Bl choo...
Bl cho, he's not sleeping!
Bl choo!
Bl cho...
Bl chooo!
Huh?
No!
Look!
What?
Now what?
I didn't hide anything.
I didn't think you'd do that.
I still have my underwear.
What's wrong?
This is...
You're hiding the truth in your underwear, aren't you?
Damn it!
I-I got it!
Calm down!
Shut up!
I got it!
Now!
Let's go!
Don't let go, Ryosuke!
Hurry up!
Wait!
Damn it!
I won't let you get away!
Gah!
Don't put on a breathtaking act again, chief.
You're but a solid body for my good.
I haven't moved around after so long...
Chief, you're old enough!
What?
What are you talking about?
As long as there are people like you,
I won't let you get in.
Chief!
We were so impressed.
Chief is amazing!
We will follow you from now on.
Please tell us what you want to say.
I see.
But everyone, teamwork is important.
We must not forget that we know each other's strengths and weaknesses.
Yes!
I'm sorry, I have to go back to the park.
Idiot!
What is this report?
What were you doing when I was gone?
I was writing and writing, but I didn't write anything.
Idiot!
-You've been doing this for a long time. -I thought you were back.
You're going to do this soon, right?
But I have to say this.
You're not like the Kameari Park Exhibition.
Well,
do you think it's okay to say that?
It's not okay.
The chief is too stubborn.
Stubbornness is born.
Let's rewrite the report.
Please don't listen to me.
I hear you.
I don't understand no matter how many times I say it.
Honda, don't be so nervous all the time.
Being dumped is a part-time job.
Men are kinder the more they are in love.
I'm sorry.
I was too depressed.
Hey, hang in there.
Hey, Hongza!
Next time,
Run, chapter point man!
Thank you for watching!
♪ I'm not sure if I'm the one that I love ♪
♪ Rumor has it ♪
♪ I have more things to do then a person too ♪
♪ I'm not sure if I'm the one ♪
♪ Who will be loved and welcomed? ♪
I want to ride on a bike in the desert
I want to be free more than a bird
The lady's dream changes at the speed of a full moon
My heart, I'm sorry, wait
The future of the panorama is bright
You understand, right? I'm sorry, wait
Translated by Releska