Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new era lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city in yellow ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing all the trendy things ♪
♪ I'll be more handsome, so let it rain ♪
♪ Everybody can do it, let's run ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Everybody can do it, just a little ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt to spit it out ♪
♪ Holding the bustling curiosity ♪
♪ I'll make it strong and high ♪
♪ To thears in the sky ♪
♪ Which is my life ♪
Ah, my home!
♪ Who will settle this heart which moves the world? ♪
…
That's too late!
Oh, Mr. surplus isn't home yet?
It's normal for you to come 10 minutes before the next train.
Why are you so nervous?
I can't take it anymore. I'm going to eat.
You have 5 minutes to go to work.
Don't say such things.
Sorry for being late.
Who was that?
It was me. It was the monk.
No way!
I'm not surprised.
He is the monk.
Don't be silly.
Monks are like this.
They are like a human.
How can you say that?
If he were a monk, he would have a picture of his family.
Then...
It's true. He has a picture of his family.
Yes.
We take pictures once a week.
Riko, give it to me.
A picture of his family will be fine with me.
That's why I learned that he was the monk.
Was something wrong, Mr. Monk?
I had a hard time at work.
That's true. You said that you bought a house.
How long did the work take?
Around 7 hours at Charlie's.
7 hours!?
The manager did a 5-hourですね
That's 2 hours longer than the manager.
I only have a home we have to live in.
I can't afford it.
I don't want to help the family.
I usually get up before dawn.
It's bad to wake everyone up, so I eat a simple meal with the leftovers on the way.
I ride my bike for an hour to the station.
When the night comes, I finally arrive at the station.
The train is always full.
I have to change trains five times, but I'm late if I miss one.
I have to work hard.
I'm late.
It's a turtle.
I have to go home repeatedly.
It's sad.
I'll break my body.
But my home is a dream of a working man.
I'll sacrifice a little.
It's cold.
I'm sorry.
If you try to eat something nutritious, you won't be able to move.
That's right. I was going to eat.
I'm going to eat something with stamina.
I'm going to eat yakiniku.
I don't think you're trying to make me treat you to a meal, Ryo.
I'm sorry.
I don't have the money to eat.
I have to pay 350 yen for a meal a day.
350 yen?
Then you can only buy bread and milk.
That's a lot of money.
350 yen is enough.
I'll make you eat a lot of delicious food with a budget of 350 yen.
Turtle.
Welcome.
What should I give you today?
You're clearly lacking vitamins.
You need to take plenty of fruits.
Apple.
350 yen will cost you everything.
It's a fresh apple that just arrived from the farm today.
It's delicious and it makes me hungry.
I'm hungry.
It's a fresh apple that just arrived from the farm today.
But there's too much dust in my belly.
It's been at the store for at least three days.
Give me 200 yen.
I can't afford it.
200 yen is enough.
It's a lot worse down there.
It's 100 yen.
It's no use. 100 yen is enough.
I can see that you're eating insects.
It's 50 yen.
I want to give you a contribution.
Yeah, time is running out.
You can't ask me for it.
Why is this apple so pulpid?
Ryo, widen your voice.
Are you planning to sell such a pulp apple to Mr. Shifu Kazushika?
What a poor shop.
It's overflowing.
I understand.
It's only 10 yen.
You can just bring it to me.
It's what you said in the beginning.
I can't afford it.
I'm going to buy you a drink.
No, no, no.
This is a 500 yen blood-sucking service.
It's not even a good deal.
Damn, he's a stubborn guy.
Oh, right.
By the way, you were in front of the market on Sunday.
I'm going.
I'm sure your wife forbade you to gamble.
What are you talking about?
You're going to make me angry.
Miss!
It's true!
Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa!
Oh, my God!
You!
What are you doing?
Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa!
Stop crying.
Look, look.
Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa.
Ryo, please forgive me.
My wife just came back from her parents' home.
Oh, that's good.
And how much is this?
I can't help it.
I'll give you 300 yen.
Hmm.
Miss!
It's true!
50 yen!
No, 30 yen is fine.
Hehe.
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, take it.
I'll take it.
No, no, no, no.
Wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa, wa.
Ryo, you're really amazing.
I'm starving.
I'm so full.
I'd never imagined I'd be able to eat this big for 350 yen.
Yeah, me and Ryo ate the same amount.
So, the price is half of it.
It's all thanks to you, Ryo.
You're right. You're a genius when it comes to saving money.
Call me a shopkeeper.
There's nothing that won't be cheap if I work for you.
You should consult me when you buy a house, Terai.
I'm sure you bought that house after consulting the director, Ohara.
Yes. The director is the one who knows about real estate in the Katsushika book.
I heard he's called the "real estate demon."
The real estate demon?
That's right. He's been working for seven hours.
It's wrong to consult the director.
The director can't buy a whole bunch of daikon.
You can't buy a house for someone like him.
Now, let's get to work.
Oh, no. That document...
What's wrong? What's wrong with you two?
Director! Welcome!
You sound like you're going to say something big.
No, I'm just saying what I think as a professional shopkeeper.
A professional shopkeeper?
The real estate market is different from a normal shop.
It's not as easy as you think.
Why not? It's the same as making money.
I see. Then, let me ask you something.
Do you fully understand the real estate law?
The real estate law?
Do you know the term "property?
If it's a contract of a different price, you need to know the law.
W- what's that?
The Real Estate Law.
The Real Estate Trade Law.
What about the law regarding the property of a building, ownership, and so on?
The law concerning the contract for borrowing, renting, and renting.
You're being ridiculous!
I don't need that sort of ridiculous law!
What's that ridiculous thing?
What kind of thing do you know about a family that hasn't ever bought a house?
If you don't know, what do you know?
I know!
The chief lives in the outskirts of Chiba.
I chose my house because of the environment.
Then the house of the priest is also the environment?
There was no other suitable property.
It's a bad way to look for it.
Then do you say you can look for it?
I'll find a house that's more luxurious and convenient to commute than the chief.
Interesting.
Then, after a week,
let's take you to the house you looked for.
I'm looking forward to it.
What if we can't find it?
Then what?
We'll take you around Tokyo naked.
What?
We'll meet a week later.
Deal?
Yeah!
Ryo, are you okay?
You promised.
I'd be happy if I could find a house more luxurious.
I'm a professional at shopping.
Don't worry.
Oh, thank you very much.
That's all right.
Come on!
Now take a look at this store.
I often do commercials on TV.
It's sweet!
This kind of big real estate is the same as a department store!
There are luxury products and branded products,
but there are surprisingly few for the common people.
And above all, the ingredients are in a bad condition.
I see.
The target is the corner of the shopping street,
and it seems that it has been doing it for a long time and the store seems to collapse.
It seems that it is not collapsed!
It's good!
What?
There's something we can find out about that place.
Let's go, Terai.
What do you mean, "we still have one contract this month"?
But we have a good property.
We can sell it there, but we need to be good at business.
Business is a game.
We need to know how to get the right people at the right time.
Chief, you look like a customer.
Huh?
All right, leave it to them.
I'll make sure they sign the contract.
Smile, smile.
Welcome.
Welcome to Seijitsu real estate, where we answer your needs honestly.
I'm...
I've been a Seijitsu employee for 40 years.
I'm Hanyu Pochiro, the store's sales manager.
What kind of property are you looking for?
How much do you want?
I want a $25 million house in Tokyo, about an hour and a half away from Tokyo.
You're buying from this guy, huh?
He's easy to fall for.
Then...
Wait!
Then I can't make the manager yell at me.
The $15 million is an hour away from Tokyo.
That's annoying.
Sir, you're lucky.
Actually, it's just been completed, and there's a property that hasn't even been advertised yet.
It's only an hour away from Tokyo, and the price is $3 million.
What?
I've been trying to be honest, but I can't do that for other stores.
This is definitely better than Chief Ohara's house.
It's a great thing to look for.
I'll sign this contract right away.
Y-Yes.
I'll sign it.
Wait a minute!
What's wrong, Ryo?
From my experience, there is no store that suddenly offers the best products to its first customer.
There must be more properties than that.
Giku!
What are you talking about?
Even if it's the first customer, they will offer the best property.
That's the reason why this store is so honest.
That's right.
There are so many properties that are so well-known.
I found a better picture than the manager, so it's okay.
But I don't like to buy with a good price.
I may have to negotiate.
This is bad.
Oops!
It's a mess!
Yes, this is Seijitsu Real Estate.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
What?
Is that the property?
Please wait a moment.
I'm in trouble!
Someone called me to buy that property right away.
What?
What should I do?
If you don't give me a good price, I'll sign a contract with you right away.
Okay, I'll sign it right away.
Ryo, give it back to me.
Contract completed.
I'm really sorry.
It's just sold now.
Excuse me.
Yes.
What is it?
The ink on the pen seems to have run out.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Tsukamoto.
It's a pen.
Hurry up and get a pen.
Pen, pen, pen.
Yes.
That's not a good way to rush.
Show me again.
Yes.
It's a pen.
Pen, pen.
Let's sign it right away.
Let's do it.
3.0 points?
I'm sorry.
It's 30 points, Ryo.
There's no way there's such a small house.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
Hey, what's this?
There are times when the ink stains the documents.
Hey, you're thinking too much, Ryo.
Then I'll ask you just in case.
How many pots is this house?
Yes.
It's in the documents.
I'm asking you how many pots.
As you can see.
Well, you can't say how many pots?
Ryo, why are you so innocent?
I'm not that kind of person.
Don't you realize, Terai?
I don't say a word in my own mouth.
Well, you're right.
Ryo.
You're suspicious.
If you can't say how many pots there are, show me the real thing.
If you're going on a trip, you'll be taken by someone else.
Don't say nonsense and take me there right away.
Yes.
How is it?
This is it! This wonderful land, this shining view!
There is no other place in the capital that can be found with more of these things.
So, how do humans live?
Do they have to live on a micro-aircraft?
Are they really 3.0 tons?
That was dangerous. I almost got tricked.
That's true.
There is no way to trick people.
I'm so jealous that you have such a toy house!
I don't call it a human house.
This is a pet house.
Pet?
In the pet industry these days,
there are more and more people who want a luxury pet house
than in the traditional dog house.
You're quite suspicious.
When I first saw you,
I thought you were a pet enthusiast.
I'm really, really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I would like to offer you a high-cost pre-paid property
at a legitimate price of 50% .
Please, let me have a pet.
We need you to show me the real deal.
Don't do that.
Next time, I will make sure you sign up for my pet.
Look.
That is your house.
It is a good house.
It's not a house.
How much is it?
It's usually about 20 million yen, but...
The price is 8.5 million yen.
Really?
To be honest, if you offer it at such a low price, the company will be in trouble.
However...
The company's motto is "Seligitsu"
My motto is "Seligitsu"
"Seligitsu" is written as "Jitsu"
To overcome the "Seligitsu", a little trouble is more than enough.
"Seligitsu" is here!
Let's make a contract before other customers know.
Yes.
It's working.
What's going on?
Show me closer.
I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. Stop it. Stop it.
Why can't you do it?
You're hiding something again.
I can't do it!
Well...
What?
You can't live in a house like this!
It's ridiculous.
I can really live in a house like this.
Now we have a Japanese-style room, a kitchen, and a bathroom.
It's like a eel's sleeping place.
Do you sleep vertically?
It's too big.
How big is the house?
We have to match the size of the house.
We're in a big, calm bathroom.
But we have to take it inside the swimming pool to go to the next room!
It's enough!
We're in the next room.
Don't worry.
We have many of them.
There must be something that customers like.
What a quiet place.
But next...
What do you think of this wide entrance?
Next!
This is the dining kitchen that has been sought after for the day of the day.
This is the bathroom.
How is this bright Japanese-style room?
This house is 15 million yen at a fair price.
The price of the city hall is a price of price.
This won't be a problem for the chief's house, Ryo-san.
There's an earthquake.
Hey! Is there anyone who can close the apartment during an earthquake?
Open it right away!
What? You're going to open it?
Get out of the way! I'll open it!
I can't! I'll open it!
You're in the way!
Wait a minute!
Well, you're hiding something again!
It's my imagination.
I'll give you a good one!
Ryo-san!
This house is floating in the sea!
It's cheap because it doesn't cost a lot of money.
It's pretty stylish, isn't it?
If there's a typhoon, it'll be a mess!
The next property is okay.
It's cheap because it doesn't cost a lot of money.
There's no way I can live in a place like this!
I'm going to feel bad.
Please make it yourself.
It's cheap without the human resources.
Well...
Ryo-san, give up already.
After all, a house better than the chief's house is not something you can imagine.
If I give up, I'll lose!
I can't afford to be a big help to the chief anymore!
Hey!
If this happens, I'll close my eyes to the majority!
Find a better house than this!
Are you really going to close your eyes to the majority?
Yeah!
Then leave everything to me!
I'll close my eyes to the majority!
This is our secret property.
There is no other house in the Tokyo Kinko.
That's good, Terai.
It's a better house than the chief's house.
Yeah.
I'm a little worried about the bad sunlight.
It's not a small thing!
The sun doesn't hit at all.
Why is there a house in the basement?
Because it doesn't cost a lot of money.
Other than the sun, all houses in this house are better.
That's not the problem!
Besides, this is convenient for commuting.
It takes only one second to get to the station.
It's connected to the home, so it doesn't cost a lot of money.
In addition, there is no gas, water, electricity, or telephone.
It's a straight line.
Then it's illegal!
Even if it's illegal, it's better than the chief's house.
You!
You're a policeman!
Chief!
Even if you say that,
why don't you accept my defeat?
I'll beat you up again!
What about your contract?
I'm not going anywhere!
What's this smell?
Chief, it's okay.
I like this place.
I bought this thing.
What?
Is it real?
Yes.
Well, both Lloyd and the chief should stop fighting
and let's have a cup of tea.
I'm gonna put my tea in.
What do you want?
Who are you?
Come!
Hey, Ryo!
Huh?
What?
He's not here.
You really can't find a house!
I bet you had a better house than the chief.
I hope you're satisfied.
Please sign the contract.
But it's already broken.
No, no.
But you said you liked it, didn't you?
But...
Here's the signature.
Please!
Wait!
The outside of the house is already broken!
Don't say that!
Sign it!
What is this land cell?
It has a navigation system, a computer, and a video camera.
Do you have a normal notebook or a boat box like a elementary school student?
But I want this land cell too.
Next time, Hyper Elementary School Student vs. Ryo-tsu.
Thanks for watching!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Even if it rains, tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye, let's wave our hands
Say goodbye to the unpleasant things
Oh yeah, let's live the way we like
There's something good
The sun is calling outside the door