Book of L vierte
When you watch TV, turn on your light to make the room bright, so that you can see and look far away.
Come to me, poor fellow!
Come to me!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen
I know!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds
I wonder what will happen
I know!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
If you know, just come to me!
Shrimp, crab, squid, the arrival of a huge biophysicist!
What is this?
What's wrong, Senpai?
There's a lot of things to do!
Look at this!
Shrimp Tempura
is the shrimp tempura
of a front-age ahead of the station?
See?
Shrimp Tempura
What? What do you mean?
What's wrong, Mr. Terai?
I just got a call about an accident.
What kind of accident?
A car slipped on banana leaves.
A car slipped on banana leaves?
It's not like the old manga.
I can't believe it.
It's time to get to the scene.
It's definitely a real banana leaf.
It's a little too big.
Why is this in the middle of the road?
Oh, did it fall here?
It's talking to you.
Banana's funny.
I remember hearing that voice.
Long time no see, Gorilla-kun.
Professor Ezaki.
So it's you.
Ezaki Bio Lab?
When did you build such a suspicious building?
Did you make the giant banana here?
Yeah.
I was going to throw it away with trash, but it didn't fit in the trash bag.
I was going to take it to the garbage disposal site, but it fell off the car on the way.
He's a noisy guy.
Oh, this is amazing.
It's all dozens of times the size.
It's going crazy.
It looks like a multi-colored giant banana.
All right, let's try how hard we can do it.
I was able to do it with my whole body, so it's very beautiful.
Does this mean I can actually turn the earth upside down without any problems?
Isn't that what the Beastman said?
To be blessed with the victory award, too.
Did you really make a student this year?
You are going to be on top of the euphoria.
I don't think so.
Maybe.
You're the one who's worried about "maybe"!
Nakagawa, you won't eat?
Yes, I'll take my leave.
First, rice.
This is...
Giant Koshihikari 28.
That's about five bowls of rice in one bowl.
How about side dishes?
I'm home.
Natto.
Natto?
Please have some rice.
It's not on the menu at all.
It's just on the menu.
Kau soup.
Kaeware daikon.
Eat it and go home.
How does it taste?
Not bad, but it's definitely not good.
I see.
Not bad.
Not bad, but it's definitely not good.
It's not good.
What are you writing about?
Who wrote this?
It's not good.
It's...
He was really doing a human body experiment with his own body.
What on earth is this?
No, if it's a special body of Gorilla-kun, I wouldn't be shocked.
You're kidding, right?
Nakagawa, let's go home.
Wait.
There aren't many people like Gorilla-kun who have a special body.
Please go out with me a little more.
Of course, I can't say it's free.
I'll pay cash for my part-time job.
Part-time job? Cash?
Actually, I was worried about the food crisis in the future.
It's for the future of mankind.
If I'm fine with it, I'll gladly cooperate.
Oh, you'll do it for me?
Haa...
The seeds are big and hard to eat.
The skin is hot and hard to peel.
I don't have enough bitterness.
Am I a caterpillar?
As expected, you're full, Senpai.
I'm sick of vegetables and fruits.
Don't you have meat?
Of course, I have meat.
Haa...
Here it is.
Hmm?
What is that?
Gorilla-kun!
Huh?
It's here!
It's a flat-faced gorilla!
What?
What's wrong with you?
What is he?
It's a giant whale, Hyonkichi-kun.
Pyonkichi?
It's not "pyon".
It's "hyon".
Hyonkichi!
Does he eat, too?
No, he's a pet.
A pet?
Yes.
My research is not just for food crisis.
What's going on on Earth in 2002?
Watermelons keep decreasing, greenery is exposed to the atmosphere.
Co2 increases destroy ozone layer.
Atmospheric line rains.
Temperature rises.
Because of these factors, the number of frogs is decreasing.
So I'm a strong frog who can't lose to anyone.
It's just so cool!
I've come up with the idea of making the King of Frogs!
So that's what this is.
Stop! Stop!
It seems like Hyonkichi likes it.
What?
He usually catches flies under it, but he doesn't mind.
He likes it!
What's in here?
What is this?
It's a shirasu.
What?
-What? -This?
If you look closely, it's true.
But I don't think it's a shirasu if it's this big.
It's a clamshell.
It seems like humans come out of it.
It's a sea urchin.
It's a huge thorn.
It's hard to catch.
What's that?
It's a lobster!
If you make a tandon with that, you'll get a lot to eat.
Okay, let's start with that lobster.
I'm going to make it a tandon!
All right, got it.
All right!
Here we go!
It's a squid!
This is a crab, right?
It comes out of a crab.
It's a lobster.
Oh, wow.
It's a crab.
What's this?
Look, it's a butter shell!
What?
Hey, you two!
The three weapons will go out!
If they go out of town, things will get serious!
I won't let you get away! My shrimp-tent!
The three weapons will go out! My shrimp-tent!
As I thought, my father's special technique is the best!
It's old-fashioned.
Now that we're in the CG era,
we need to make a powerful screen that pops out of the screen.
It's really popping out!
It's so powerful!
Yes, this is the exit in front of the park.
Huh?
What's that all about?
What's wrong?
It's about giant shrimps, crabs and squids rampaging in the city.
What?
Isn't that a prank call?
This is bad!
What's wrong, Kei?
A giant bioparticle from Professor Ezaki's place has escaped into town!
A giant bioparticle?
Hurry up, Hyon-kichi!
Don't let my ship escape!
That was a prank call!
It wasn't, was it?
What a giant shrimp-tent!
You don't see these kind of shrimp-tents very often.
What do you think?
I'm sorry.
This is a big one!
Two of them in no time.
What's going on?
A giant creature seems to have escaped near Shimabata.
It seems like it's not escaping near Shimabata.
Such a big one?
Where did it hide?
Hmm?
The giant creatures are going towards Asakusa at a very high speed.
This?
I thought it would be like this, so I turned on the transmitter for the creatures.
I see.
Hurry up and say such things!
Senpai!
We're in Asakusa!
The giant creatures are heading towards Asakusa!
Asakusa!
Next is Asakusa, Asakusa...
Hyon-Kichi, hurry up!
It's a Tendon! Tendon!
Incredible!
As expected of Japan's Godzilla country!
It's a Tendon!
Everyone, look!
One of Japan's most famous tourist attractions
is about to be destroyed by a mysterious giant creature!
The giant creature destroyed Kaminarimon
and is currently on its way to the war zone on Nakamise Street!
What's that?
Damn it!
You're just doing whatever you want!
Let's go!
Let's go, Hyon-Kichi!
I'm going to Tendon!
It was a giant frog that challenged three giant creatures,
but it's still a Tendon!
It's not moving, and it's not moving at all!
It's heavy...
Now, I'm going to fly to Kappa Bridge...
What's that?
The Ultra Tendon Big Operation?
That's right.
Listen, here's the plan.
What's that?
This waterfall will be a passageway!
A giant hot pot was set up at the Koma-Gatabashi intersection by the police!
What's going to happen next?
The amount of oil is OK!
All right!
OK, start!
He's heating up the oil he poured into a huge hot pot!
Will he do a tempura?
It looks ready.
Let's go, Hyon-Kichi!
The giant creature is in the middle of an international corridor...
It's in the middle of an international corridor!
I have to find a way out.
Hey, it's time for you to eat!
A huge creature has been sent out from the International Street to Asakusa Street by a giant frog!
Come on, come on!
It's time for you to eat!
If you're going to eat, you better get the batter!
The three frogs are being led towards the Komagatabashi Bridge,
and the other is going to the Kikura Bridge!
We did it!
The giant creatures are like tempura balls, and they're all in the color of foxes!
The crisis of Tokyo has disappeared!
I don't think that's the last one.
As long as we forget our co-existence with nature,
and keep destroying the Earth,
there will be a third and final incident.
That's not the last one.
You have a lot of them, don't you?
Now, all we have to do is cook the rice and turn it into tempura balls.
I'll feed you some, too, Hyonkichi.
What's wrong, Hyonkichi?
Are you tired?
Aren't you sleepy?
Frogs usually sleep in at this time.
I see.
When you wake up from your sleep,
I'll feed you with all the food you want.
Go to sleep.
Amazing!
Then, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
I've never had such delicious tempura balls before!
It's full of meat!
It's a long-standing research treasure.
By the way, what about Ryo?
He wanted to eat it the most.
Hey!
Let go of me!
Why can't I be a commoner with you?
If you are a commoner,
And let go of me!
You want to eat me?
Why don't you just let me go?
Hey, you are a commoner!
Let go of me!
No, I'm not a commoner.
I want to sleep with you.
Let go of me!
Why not?
I don't want to sleep with you.
Let go of me!
I'm young, develop mental health.
Don't you know your mission to kill yourself?
Well then, let's go upstairs.
It's time for a good rest!
Why didn't we sleep well last night?
Yeah, you have a bad sleeping habit.
I'm listening.
Good.
What is this?
Please have a seat.
But it's perfectly unified in red.
If you like, please.
It's strawberry and cherry tomato ketchup and tomato juice.
I used to work at the post office until last month.
I've been a fireman since this month.
Your eyes look bloodshot.
I have a lot of night shifts from work.
But it's a worthwhile job surrounded by red.
The number 602 is insulting that beautiful red.
Well, everyone has their favorite color.
What are you talking about?
What is your blood color?
Red, right?
Red is the source of human life.
Shall I show you?
I got it.
Red is wonderful.
I'll persuade you.
Then I'll ask you to do it.
I got it.
He's a great man with a lot of policies.
So I'm in trouble.
Mr. Midorikawa.
Mr. Omari wants to talk to you.
Really?
Please.
It's like a jungle.
What are you doing?
I'm a nature protector.
You know that green is the best for human eyes.
Green is important to humans, not just eyes.
But...
Red is bad for your eyes.
It's a poisonous color that turns red when it's mixed with the species.
Green is a must-have color to change people's nature.
I understand.
Let's talk slowly while eating salad next time.
Okay. See you.
Next is Mr. Kimoto of 607.
It's open.
Here you go.
What's this?
I have eyes on the gap that overlaps.
Are you okay?
Okay, I'm fine now.
Listen, Mr. Omari.
It's a nuisance for the residents of this neighborhood.
You're an idiot to want to paint your house in a bad color.
But it's all yellow here, too.
Happy colors are on the fortune-telling.
Sorry.
You're really weird.
Next is the doctor.
This time it's fine.
Mr. Shiroyama, are you here?
I've been waiting for you.
I'm the most calm when it comes to work.
Well, how about milk?
If you make a mistake, you'll be taken out of the room.
Modern people are all affected by color.
I'm the best at getting rid of them.
The confrontation here is amazing.
That's why there are so many fights.
Mr. Kimi, do you happen to be the boss?
Maybe.
Kimi, would you like to go out with me for a walk?
Just a little walk.
What is that old guy in gold?
Mr. Kimi in room 610.
He never fights.
He's really myhem behaving without any fight.
Or he might be taken out in a while.
Here you are.
The last one is Mr. Kurohara, anamosomatologist.
Just in case I thought you're a doctor, you're an amamosomist.
Sorry.
It's pitch black.
Hey, Box, where are you?
Here.
Don't be surprised. Turn on the light.
I'm on it.
The room is all black and it's hard to tell.
Go outside for a bit.
See?
You even have your shoes on your face and your face is all gray.
Black is a sacred color.
See? All of your clothes are black.
It's black, right?
You can't tell if you put coffee in a black cup, right?
What about milk and sugar?
I don't have milk, but I have sugar.
Here, black sugar.
I thought so.
Huh? What's that sound?
It's a pet.
A black cat.
Where's the exit?
Hey, Box, don't close your eyes.
You can't tell where he is, can you?
This place is a mess.
I told you so.
I told you to do something.
What?
It started again.
You don't have any sense of discipline, do you?
Shut up! You too!
What?
I'm going crazy.
I don't care.
We're all the same.
It's because of the poor heart that you're poor.
I'll pay you, so let's make up.
What?
I'm going crazy.
I'm going crazy when I'm angry.
I'll go crazy when I'm angry.
Damn it!
I'm gonna make you all the same!
That's why you can't add more green!
Stop!
I'm not going to do it again!
The color's gone.
My gold eyes!
It became black and white.
Look.
Because you're so particular about colors,
the gods got angry
and made it into a black and white anime.
What?
No way!
We're going to...
What should we do?
What?
Don't worry.
When we were kids,
the TV was all white.
But everyone was happy to watch it.
But what about the recent TV?
Color, stereo, digital, high-vision.
Even if technology advances,
it won't be good.
Even if we don't add colors,
as long as the content is interesting,
it's okay.
That's right.
It's okay even if there's no color.
We were wrong.
That's right.
We did it.
What?
Let's show our thanks to the gods.
Even when black and white,
you never change.
Sir,
it's sorry to have our bad temper.
Did you understand, you folks?
Here, have a look!
That beautiful rainbow
that goes with a Happy End!
Hmm,
but you can't catch a single thing.
That's not a black and white anime.
Color isn't good enough.
Translation & Captions by: SWCreative Japan.
I'm a little liar and cheat
But sometimes I'm helping someone
Baby do you know me?
I'm heading to tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't be sick, I'll do what I do
Cute breathing
It's hard to understand
But I want to show you
It's better than looking down on yourself
Oh no!
I lost the wedding ring of the chief who was asked to repair it!
I must have lost the wedding ring of the chief who was asked to repair it!
Why?!
Did you sell 200 rings on bazaar?
I guess I can't help but get it right
See you next time on Find the Insect!
There is a turtle
A turtle is just like a turtle
Come on, everyone!
To our town
Thanks you so much!