"The Big Diver"
Ryotsu...
Hey, Ryotsu!
Ohana-kun, what's this tea?
I put it back in!
Ryotsu!
Hurry up, Ohana-kun!
Ouch!
Who is this bastard?
It's me, idiot!
R-Retsu...
You look pretty good.
No, I mean, how about you, chief?
Idiot! Get back to work now!
I'm so bored.
I should take a nap.
When you're bored, you're peaceful.
Look, the town is full of smiles.
No big deal.
It's just a normal town.
See? Even the chief is running well.
Huh?
What?
Chief!
Thief! Thief!
This is the last time!
Ahahaha!
What a nice weather!
Yeah.
Did something appear?
Why are there ostriches in the town?
They won't keep their signal, and they'll hit each other, won't they?
I was destroyed by a waterfall. What should I do?
Anyway, get me out of here now!
I'm sorry. I just gave the order to all the officers to leave the building, so they will be captured soon. Please wait for a while.
So, I order you to capture them as soon as you find the captain. All of you, leave the building.
Roger!
Here they are! Chase them!
Wait!
Damn! What a speed!
The captain runs at maximum speed of 70 km/h.
Tell me that first!
But why is he in such a place?
The captain is an African creature, isn't it?
That's right.
There is no message that the captain has escaped from the zoo or the zoo.
I never heard that a wild captain was in Japan.
What's wrong, Mr. Ryoichi?
Hey, Honda!
I'm in a good place.
Chase them!
What do you mean?
Just go!
I don't know what you mean, but let's go!
All right!
What?
Oh, that's...
I found them!
All right!
It's dangerous!
I found them!
All right!
Yes, I found them!
What?
You did it!
What the hell are you doing?
If you're mad, you better catch me!
You don't have time to tell me!
This is a waste of effort!
You're being too cocky with the captain's order!
Well, sir, do you understand what the captain is saying?
If you ask me, I feel like I'm saying something like that.
Hey, wait up!
Sir!
You stole again, didn't you?
I was playing with a man who was as strong as you!
Hey!
Stop!
Damn that bastard!
Where did he go?
That bastard? Is he a male?
Yeah, he said he was a male.
What?
You don't understand?
Yeah, well, that's...
Hey, what's going on here?
It's a secret!
Hey, wait!
I caught the captain!
You're a thief!
I'm a police officer!
Damn it! He ran away!
Let's go back and think about our plan.
Get out of here!
He's gone too far.
Hey...
I'm asking you again.
It's just him and his body.
Shouldn't have done this.
He's going to take care of it!
Put him in the hospital and come back.
What are you doing?
That'd be necesary.
Hey looks familiar.
He also has an anal organ somewhere.
Yes.
It also contains two parts:
one for the body of a cow...
and one for the head of a pig!
I've never seen a cow before!
I thought he was talking about the head of a pig.
What the hell is this?
You can't tell by looking?
You were appointed as the head of the
"Dachou Strategy Department" in the Katsushika office.
So why me?
Well, when I heard you could speak the word "dachou",
I thought this "dachou" was something
you wouldn't think of.
I'm looking forward to it.
No way.
You're trying to push me
into this, aren't you?
Zuboshika!
Anyway, from now on,
you'll be responsible for
taking over the "Dachou" in the future.
Yes.
Damn it.
All of them are trying to push me into this.
Why me?
I can't stand being called a fool.
Well,
I have a plan.
Do you have any plans?
No.
I don't even know how to catch a "dachou".
Well,
when can I go back to my job?
I see.
What's wrong?
I have an idea.
Senpai, what is this?
In this costume,
I'll catch it with my own hands.
Can I change the order?
It's huge!
Calm down.
We're sexy "Dachou" now.
"Dachou"?
Good boy.
Darling,
come here.
What?
We must make a proposal for a date.
Hey!
Makes you happy?
Yes, there is.
You're the real "Dachou" I.
That's right.
What's with the clut?
I meet you for the first time.
Good boy,
as good a man as I am,
I always like the girls.
You're my ideal type.
I only have one man,
someone else.
So,
only me.
And you?
Yes, you.
What are you doing running away?
You're being proposed by a long time.
You're proposing to give me my eggs.
You're going to bury me!
Did you catch Ryotsu soon?
I hope so.
Ryotsu!
That's cool.
Chief!
I'm scared...
You're a happy family.
Why do you want kids to be lucky enough to play soccer?
You're forcing your children to play soccer.
Don't come.
Ugh...
Huh?
Ahhhhhhh!
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah!
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Senpai, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm saved!
I see.
I see. So that's what happened.
What are you talking about?
Apparently, this guy lived near Mizuboto Park.
The place where the egg returned was Mizuboto Park, so it means he was there all along.
Why would a ostrich egg live in such a place?
Not really.
Maybe...
Maybe someone dropped it while it was being brought to the zoo.
Or maybe someone threw it away.
I feel sorry for him.
In such a small town, with just one egg...
Ugh, you're making me cry.
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah!
What?!
Not just one egg?!
Nyah!
Huh?
Nyah-nyah!
Aqu romania!
Nyah!
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah!
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah!
Nyah!
Nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah-nyah!
I've got the ostrich!
You're not solving anything!
You need to take measures to stop other ostriches from bothering the town!
It's a mess!
What?
Don't say that!
What are you talking about?
Like, "Thank you for your life" or "I'll take care of you from now on."
Well, it seems everyone likes Ryo-chan.
I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I'll leave it to you, Director Tai-saku.
No way!
Okay.
Everyone, are you awake?
Well, let's have a good time today.
Don't eat yet!
You need to say hello properly!
Okay.
Well, let's eat!
Well, I'll announce today's work.
Dachounosuke and Dachouemon, Dachomiwa Takahaibi, Dachoujiro, Dachoubei, Dachoko, and Dachogoro are going to the shopping street.
You come with me.
The other people will clean the park.
You can stay here with special money.
But you have to earn your own living expenses.
We have one motto.
"Don't eat Dachou who doesn't work!"
Got it?
Yes!
Then, let's get to work!
Be careful in the car!
Good morning!
Well, I'm going to the Dachou Special Police Division.
Yes!
I'm counting on you.
Okay, go!
Please deliver this as soon as possible.
I'm counting on you.
Why is it so crowded?
I can't make it in time.
I think we should go to Sharon.
It seems that there is no time.
But we have to hurry!
Since we have to help you.
We don't have enough money.
What do I do?
You want to work for our company, don't you?
We will do our best!
Well, we'll be there as soon as possible.
That's good.
It is such a good idea.
I want to do the same as you.
Perhaps we can go home?
Yes, of course.
Thank you!
Huh?
Excuse me! Is there a mother of this child among the audience?
Mother!
Mama!
Yuki-chan!
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
What? I just did what is natural as a captain!
Right?
Thief!
Let's go!
I did it!
The
Don't underestimate the speed of the captain!
Stop the bike quietly!
It's not a joke! I can't hold it!
How's that? I can't get in if you do this!
I won't let you!
Captain's unit, start!
Look at you!
Damn! What's going on with you?
Shiro!
What's this?
I'll do it to you!
Get out of my way!
You rascal!
We'll arrest you for your every single move!
Huh, they were doing a great job.
Their teamwork was perfect. Thatド女ちゃん
you are now well-known in Kameari.
Who's this Baros, huh?
Of course, of course.
Please compliment him more!
They were amazing.
They're amazing, the dachos.
What?
They're working so hard in such a small town.
I respect them.
Hey, don't praise the dachos.
I'm the one who taught them.
But they didn't write anything about you.
What?
Well...
"They live a strong life without borrowing anyone's help.
They will receive a letter of gratitude from the Katsushika Shrine."
What? I didn't hear anything!
I don't understand!
This time your work was excellent.
Please keep up your good work for the people of this town.
I'm counting on you, the people of the Dachou Corps!
Wait!
Chief! Chief!
Why are you all praising the Dachos?
It's my fault, it's my fault!
What are you talking about?
You're the Dachou Corps who took part in the fight.
I'm the Chief of the Dachou Patrol.
If they're just like that,
You're like a boss!
You idiot!
If you're a boss, you should be happy to be praised by your subordinates!
You're so annoying and you're so annoying that you're not praised!
Look at the captains!
This award is for everyone!
Everyone did their best for this award!
Don't you think it's embarrassing?
That's not what I mean!
There is a plan to build a new gym soon.
Please continue to support us.
Damn it!
I'll see what happens!
Well, well.
You always work hard.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Huh?
It's a little light, isn't it?
Hey, what's wrong with this?
You didn't eat it, did you?
No!
There's a bug in the drawer!
What's going on?
Did you think me as a human would help?
I thought you were a human being, but you're doing this at night!
So the ostriches are just wild animals after all?
Don't ever come back!
The ostrich army failed.
They were just wild animals after all.
Eating delivery pizza and throwing trash in the trash can is really bad.
It was popular in the past, but now it's gone.
The boom is so fleeting.
Don't worry about it.
I'll get the best out of it.
No, not in my face...
...I'll have to have a탐
Time to eat our lunch.
Okay!
Oh, it that the only thing that we're missing...
...we'll have to get the food.
This is what we would not want!
To think you're your boss.
I know it's Biram!
End of Part 4
I was wondering if they could get out?
Those guys are so naughty!
What the --?
That was strange.
What happened?
Wh-What?
Ahhhh! What!!?!
The chief is impotent, and the culprit is this guy!!
Wh-Why is this thing...
This is bad. This is really bad.
Before the chiefs find out, I'll have to escape somewhere.
You're too late.
Wait!
You're not going to apologize to the chiefs?
I don't think so.
There's a lot going on here.
That's right.
I did it because I wanted to cover up for the chiefs' mistakes.
Is what he said.
See? The chiefs are saying the same thing.
The chiefs are saying the same thing.
Don't make a stupid translation, idiot.
Shofu, don't hesitate and destroy it thoroughly.
I'm going to save the chiefs!
Stop it!
Okay, Mr. Dachonosuke, Mr. Dachoko, I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, yes, yes.
Ms. Dacholina, here's some water.
I'll bring it right away.
Mr. Dachosaburo, your back hurts.
I'll massage it later.
Everyone, take care!
Please do your best today!
Please!
Why do I have to be treated like a ostrich?!
Mr. Dachosaburo!
♪ After the rain, like someone is calling me ♪
♪ I walked while looking back ♪
♪ I held my mother's hand ♪
♪ I felt at that time ♪
♪ a strange feeling ♪
♪ That's why ♪
♪ I walked on the Akihito-Gai dial ♪
♪ on the black road ♪
♪ I walked and saw it ♪
♪ Everyone was a child at least once ♪
♪ but everyone has forgotten ♪
♪ A politician with a proud face ♪
♪ and an old lady with a blue eye ♪
♪ I remember that ♪
♪ I can't even see that ♪
♪ I can see that corner ♪
♪ But I can see that corner ♪
♪ and I will get to see you all ♪
♪ There's aeddity there ♪
♪ That's for sure ♪
♪ Everyone, let's take a ride ♪
♪ to our town ♪
Let's go!
♪ There's aeddity there ♪
♪ Ah, Hit Kamenari! ♪
♪ Everyone come to... ♪
♪ Our town! ♪
♪ To our town! ♪
Thank you!
I really wanted to win the war, so I started practicing Shogi.
But I did not practice Shogi enough!
Alright! I will fight with all my might!
"Shogi! The New Sky, Tatsumaki-Okoshi, the Dragon's Branch!"
This is Shogi, isn't it?
Next time, "Explosive Battle Shogi!"
Thanks for watching!