English Subtitles by: SWCreativeJapan.
When you watch TV,
make sure to look out the window and look away!
Looking at the sunset floating on the river,
watching the sunset floating on the river,
if you kick a pebble, you'll fly to the foot of the river.
I wonder if the head of the gym who was doing jogging
laughed with a smile saying, "It's just a cramp."
The cityscape that never changes
is strangely gentle.
From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi,
to the Taishakuten,
the sunset falls.
From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi,
to the Taishakuten,
I see why the snow is falling.
A time like this is the end.
I realized I've lost my happiness
after wasting too long in Karamaru.
*panting*
Good morning, Ryo-chan.
Hey, Reiko.
Good morning.
Here's your tea.
Do you have any tea or something?
You ate all of it the other day, Ryo-chan.
Buy me a new one.
Even if you buy it now, it'll just be your meal.
*panting*
I'm getting even more hungry.
I have three more days until my payday.
If I keep this up, I'll die of hunger.
*panting*
Reiko, I'm begging you!
Just give me 1000 yen!
No.
Chief Ohara told me not to lend you a penny.
That damn Chief Ohara!
*thunder*
There he is.
Welcome, Mr. Honda.
*thunder*
What's wrong with that face?
It's nothing.
*thunder*
Actually, we're in trouble.
What is it?
*thunder*
A fight between father and son?
You want me to do that?
My father and my brother have been fighting all this time.
My sister asked me to do it.
I'm begging you, Chief Ohara.
Please do something.
I can't do anything about other people's affairs before the payday.
That's not true.
I can only rely on you.
I haven't eaten properly in almost a week.
I don't have the strength to do a party.
My sister is good at cooking.
I'll make you prepare a lot of your favorite dishes.
Really?
So, what's the reason for the fight?
Apparently, they are arguing over whether to follow my father's restaurant or not.
Your family was a motorcycle shop, wasn't it?
Yes.
So I was riding the motorcycle because I wanted to.
It's a motorcycle with a lot of money.
Get out of here!
Don't die!
I'm here.
Are you off today?
Yes.
I'm not a father who usually takes the time off.
Did you come to take the time off because your senior said he would come?
Thank you, senior.
I'm home!
Welcome back, brother.
Oh, it's you, Eve!
Hey, what's going on?
Don't call me "Senpai" all of a sudden.
My sister is really shy.
You're too much.
Okay, okay, come out.
It's Ryotsu who talked on the phone.
She's scary, but she's not a bad person.
Come on, come on, it's okay.
It's like a dog or a cat.
Then I'll introduce you.
My father and my younger brother Kadoki.
But everyone calls me Monkey.
This is Ryotsu, my senior.
Hayato is always there to help.
I'm Hayato's father, Kaizo.
I'm Kadoki.
Nice to meet you.
Why are you closing the shop today?
I was cleaning the shop.
Right, Monkey?
Yeah.
Huh? I thought you two were fighting.
No way.
It's a mistake.
What? You two are close.
You can eat without having a hard time.
Friendship is beautiful.
You can't fight.
Ah, I did it!
I did it!
She's not scary.
Let's eat.
Wow.
I ate a lot.
I'm sorry. It's been a week since I last ate something decent.
Oh, is that so?
Hey, Eve! Bring some plum juice! Let's make some tea!
Oh, tea? That's a good idea!
Let's eat!
Oh, so you're interested in bikes?
Yeah! I like anything that has the name of a mecha.
I like bikes especially because I'm always riding them with Honda.
Then, shall we take a look at our bikes?
What the hell is this?
It's a Riku-O bike, isn't it?
Why is it like this?
Honda, is this a used car specialty store?
No, it's just a new car.
Then, what is this Riku-O?
It's a bike from a company that went bankrupt decades ago!
Don't say that.
I mean, there are new Meguro bikes, but...
What?
That's an old company, isn't it?
The latest ones are Mach 3 and Double One.
They're all bikes from over 20 years ago!
Hahaha. It's hard to sell them.
How much do you sell them for?
It's all on sale.
On sale? On sale when they were on sale?
Of course. They're new.
Oh...
If a bike enthusiast saw them, he'd throw up.
They're sold for four or five times or even more than the average price.
Um, dad, can I sell this bike to you?
What? By a senior?
No, I'm completely obsessed with the charm of bikes.
I want to go touring with you next time.
Honda...
Oh, no, no.
Why are you showing off the bike
by selling it to somebody else?
I just want to ride a motorcycle
Don't say stupid things, Honda-kun
It's a request from Hayato-senpai
It's fine, which one would you like?
I'll buy many at once, it's unnatural
If I choose one, it's the Rikuou
It's a famous car from half a century ago
It's now traded at a discount of 200 million yen or more
If it's in good condition, it'll be 3 million yen
It's brand new
Can I have this Rikuou?
Rikuou?
I'll take Meguro Jr.
Sure
I have some orders, please wait
What a nice father
It's strange that it's not sold at all
Senpai, are you really going to buy it?
Of course, I just have to continue
It's hard to continue
Eh?
What's that?
A motorcycle that's 50 years old
Minami Senju's motorcycle
It's mine
Is it your father?
Yes
If you wear a Tsunagi, your personality changes
As expected of Honda's father
Ryo-san, you said you wanted a Rikuou
Yes, just in case
Just in case?
Are you trying to do something for my Rikuou with such a half-hearted feeling?
No, I'm serious
I've been digging into this motorcycle for 10 years
I've been thinking about getting it no matter what
I've been thinking about it for a long time
Oh, I see
You want it so much
Okay
Then I'll take the test of Rikuou class
Test
What is this?
Why is there a test course in the back of the house?
Are you testing all the customers?
Not all of them
The Bosozoku and Miihana bike fans have no right to take the test
I'll chase them back on the spot
Then I can't sell what I can sell
Rikuou course will take a 10-stage test
First, the first test
It's a love test
I went touring and found an old motorcycle on the bottom of the valley
What will you do?
What do you mean what to do?
I don't know
You idiot
If you really like motorcycles, pull it up for now
If you can repair it, repair it and use it
If you can't, you should ask the boss for help
That's right
Of course I intend to
Good
Then carry this motorcycle and climb that cliff
I'll ask you to grab it
What?
Why is it so heavy?
I wonder
What would you do if you were a 97-speed motorcycle of Rikuou?
The total weight is 500kg
500kg is not a weight that humans can lift
That's why you cover the motorcycle with love
That's why it's a love test
Yes, I understand
It's for Rikuou
I did it
I'm glad
OK, I finished the first test
Next is the second test
He's taking a lot of credit
I went touring
I found an old motorcycle in the river
What will you do if you do it?
I think it will not be used
I'm not giving it up
Of course you will
This is also to get Rikuou
What?
I got deeper suddenly
It's not certain what kind of danger there is in the river of nature.
Damn it!
Someone may even talk about piranhas.
You're not stupid.
Okay, the third test.
When I went to the touring, I found an old bike on a tall tree.
What are you going to do?
Of course I'm going to get it.
This is for the sake of the king.
The fifth test.
When I went to the touring, your bike was broken by an unauthorized person in the mountains.
What are you going to do?
Huh?
You're going to build it, aren't you?
Okay, let's go to the next test.
The sixth test.
The seventh test.
The eighth test.
The ninth test is a draw.
What? What?
Answer the origin of the name of the previous bike manufacturer, Cabton.
It was "Come and buy to Osaka-Nagagawa".
I did it.
What?
62 points.
I just passed it.
I passed the knowledge test.
Next is the final test.
All right.
The final test is that!
You mean I pass that test?
This is not a circus!
When I was touring, I got into the factory of an old furahoop.
That factory became a fire.
What are you going to do?
I got it.
It's good to pass it.
What?
You're gonna give up after coming all the way here?
Time!
Huh?
Hey, Monkey!
Ah, what's up, Dad?
If you have time to go out, why don't you study about motorcycles?
Even if you say that...
You're riding a bicycle, how can you become a great motorcyclist?
But I'm still in junior high school...
Ah, hey! Didn't you already settle the quarrel between parents and children?
Huh? I was being quiet because we were in front of the customers earlier,
but unless you tell me that you're going to close the shop, it won't be resolved!
If you say that... If you say that...
I'm gonna get in a bicycle!
What are you going to do when you get on a bicycle?
No way!
14 years of riding a bicycle!
Honda's son-in-law, Honda Monkey!
This shop is on my level, so I'm gonna ride a bicycle!
I'll change it into a bicycle shop!
Oh...
Your brother's personality changes when he rides a bicycle.
As expected of the Honda family...
Are you still saying such a dreamy thing?
Honda Doll will continue to be a motorcycle shop!
From now on, it's the era of ecology that is kind to the earth.
There will be no more bikes that scatter waste gas!
Let me know the power of the bicycle!
Don't underestimate me, Monkey!
Here crash!
I won't take it anymore!
Hornet...
What's wrong with you?
You'll get hurt again!
Hornet!
Hey, hey, Hey!
As I expected, there's a lot of other side job,
but I can't keep up with him.
It's not a world where you can't do anything.
It's not like this.
Here we go.
This is the best.
Huh?
Hey, Monki.
Stop it already!
Don't stop, Hayato!
It has nothing to do with you!
You bastard!
You're gonna get in trouble in front of the customers!
I'm sorry!
Your family is too messy.
They had a big fight at the store yesterday,
and they've been cleaning up since this morning.
So that's why you closed the store?
Is Dad okay?
I'm sorry, Eve.
Huh?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I haven't said anything yet!
Senpai,
what happened to Eve?
No, I thought it would be hard for this kid
to be surrounded by such a family.
I thought it would be hard for this kid to be surrounded by such a family.
If you have any complaints,
you should just go.
Men get into trouble easily.
I don't have any complaints.
Oh my!
It's Rikuoh's 7th car!
I'm not gonna get in trouble with a good used car like this again!
This is a new car.
Don't be so mean.
There's no way there's a new car from Rikuoh.
New cars are used cars.
Don't be so mean.
I want this one.
I can't move until you sell it.
No, I have the car.
I've already taken the test.
What?
You have a test?
I can't even pass the first test
for a guy like you guys.
You can't understand it unless you try.
I don't think it's worth it.
I told you it's useless.
I understand!
You're not gonna get in trouble like you guys.
I'll remember it!
Who will remember it?
Don't you ever come here again!
Give me the salt!
Okay.
What about my test?
How far did you go?
It's a test.
I even took a test.
But where's the test paper?
Where's the test paper?
Here it is.
Wow!
I can't help it.
I'll have to take it again from the beginning.
What?
You're gonna do that again from the beginning?
I went to the two-wheel road.
I found an old bike on the bottom of the valley.
What are you gonna do?
Maybe I'm gonna die.
No!
Dad!
My sister!
No way!
Eve!
Dad, this is...
I took care of my daughter.
If you want to give it back, bring me the land.
The second one is the map.
That bastard!
What should I do?
I should have told the police.
We're the police.
I see.
Dad, that's not a landmine, but a double one.
How can you give my bike to those guys?
I'll make you regret fighting so much!
I'll come back tomorrow.
What?
The back wheel...
What are you talking about?
Come here, my little girl!
You!
What's the matter with a little girl like us?
What are you going to do about it?
Monkey!
Shut up!
Get him!
Monkey!
It's already alive!
I won't let you get away!
Damn it!
The Jal is lacking in power!
Leave it to me!
Big brother, I'm counting on you!
I'm going too!
Don't overdo it, Dad!
It's over!
I'm the second of the Minami Senju's!
If you think you can escape, you're wrong!
D- damn it!
The elephant escaped!
Eve!
What do we do?
It's up there!
We did it!
We got on the elephant's back!
Eve!
What's this place?
Where's Big Brother?
It's all right.
It's on top of the elephant.
The elephant?
This is bad.
What's wrong?
What's so bad?
I just remembered.
That quiet Eve has once changed her personality.
Before Eve went to kindergarten,
she went to the circus and was on the elephant.
Then when Eve got on the elephant...
What?
This is the worst situation.
Arigatou!
Get off.
We're going home.
Get off?
You two were fighting back there.
That has nothing to do with this.
You're going to fight me?
Help!
No!
You're the worst!
My light...
residents of the forest!
Don't break my room.
Anyone!
Here, here!
All right!
We'll end up having a new family forever.
"I'm surprised"
♪
To be continued...
Hey! You rotten primitive!
Even if I'm a young and cute girl,
you don't have to say you like me in front of your dad!
I hate you so much!
Next time, "The Love of Thoughts".
There's no way that happens, right?