" kayak " Smoke
some sun that floats in the river If
you throw away your love stone, you can fly to the world
From the water tank of the Tongari hat
To the taishakuten, the sun is falling
Tomorrow will end like this
"Katsushika, Shibamata, I'm so happy!"
I realized it after losing it
Because I'm so stupid
Re-emerging Shiratori Reiji
It's finally noon. I'm hungry.
Takaga, I'll order a set meal from Tsurukame.
I'm sorry. I'm a lunch box, so it's okay.
Awesome!
So, Reiko?
I'm a lunch box, too.
Ryo, why don't you eat something different?
Something different?
I only have two more soba noodles left.
If you don't eat more nutritious food,
you'll get sick every day.
Leave it to me.
I'm hungry.
Akaro, come on!
It doesn't hurt, does it?
"W hotspring"
This car is so dirty.
I'll go to the Warriors.
How can I drive like this?
No way.
You've got to be kidding me?
That's because he's a tercer.
You're so stupid.
Well, I knew it.
You're a loser.
That's why I'm so scared.
New Special Episode
It's been so long, poor people.
Leave it alone.
Let go!
It's Shiratori Reiji.
Did you forget?
I almost forgot about it.
It's not possible that he was super poor.
Right.
Why is he riding a Ferrari?
Shiratori R nails his son
I'm sure you're not impressed by me, are you?
Did you cry because of me?
Shut up!
You're like a little child.
Anyway, I, Shiratori Reiji, will be back to help the super rich!
Pick it up, you poor guy!
I'll take all the coins!
What's this? It's a toy!
The super rich only carry cards.
Damn it!
I'm glad I was able to drive without making this happen.
You suddenly became a rich and became an idiot?
Stop, you poor super rich!
I got a bullet!
Oh, I got caught again!
Damn it! I'll pick it up with the condition reflection when I look at the screen!
Listen, don't be surprised!
Look!
It's an automatic!
And a right-hand drive!
I see, this is a replica based on a Japanese car, right?
No, this body and paint are real no matter what you look at it.
Then, did you modify it on purpose?
You shouldn't have done that on purpose.
The manufacturer specially modified it for me.
No matter what the road is, I'm not afraid of anything.
That's why Japanese people can be seen with their white eyes from abroad.
That's right.
Look at this!
What a luxury car!
It's a wide-angle pole!
What is this?
You don't know?
You see, high-end cars often have high-end cars.
This pole is a point, and it's a mark to keep the car at a distance.
Normally, it's attached to a sedan car.
Sports cars are always useless.
Shut up!
You're the only one in the world who has this on an F40.
It's fine, right?
I'm embarrassed, so take it off!
It's not a good look at all!
Idiot!
Sports cars are really cool!
That's the most important thing!
Now we can run to the edge of the earth.
Reiko, let's go on a date.
Are you done with your work?
Not yet.
Then why don't we have dinner together?
You're a stubborn man.
I saw you the other day.
You're ridiculous!
I'm the owner of the Akimoto Trade Company!
I made a reservation for a new restaurant in Odaiba.
The chef there will let me eat the best French food.
That's fine.
I'm glad you're so happy.
I'm happy, too.
I told you I didn't want to!
If you want to eat, bring me with you.
I'm starving.
You have no time for this.
Why don't you have some ramen to go with it?
I can't order ramen like that!
Oh, no!
Damn it.
I hate waiting for my turn.
Come on, go out with her, Reiko.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat French food.
If you're with me, that's fine.
I'll do it!
But how do you get in?
It's a two-seater car.
How can three people get in?
Then let's go.
Why are you crouching?
It's bad to sit in a place like that.
It's an automatic, but it's a Ferrari.
It's a Ferrari.
Reiko, I'll go straight to Odaiba.
Ferrari is quick.
It's the latest carnavi sold by Shiratori Ironworks.
There's no way to get in the ironworks business.
If you do a lot of things, you'll get crushed.
Shut up!
Where should we set the destination?
What do you think?
Surprised?
It's not unusual.
It's on Nakagawa's car.
You talk in various voices.
It's the same as Kei's.
You're just thinking of ideas.
Your company.
Shut up!
Our carnavi is different from the carnavi of the village.
The version that has been approved is set on.
Master, where should we set the destination?
Go to Odaiba.
It's Odaiba.
I understand, Master.
It's the latest carnavi with AI and voice recognition.
It's a revolutionary carnavi.
I see.
It's not much different from Kei's.
Really?
Why is the traffic jam here?
Shut up!
Do something.
Yes, Master.
Avoid traffic jams.
Turn left at the next intersection.
He's driving!
It's dangerous, damn it.
Stop here!
It's the carnavi's instruction.
It must be a shortcut.
This road must be.
I think so.
He said so.
The proud carnavi couldn't search the roadі.
Go back and go to another road.
No!
The road is blocked.
I'm not good at back-hitting, so I'll follow the navigation.
What? Stop it!
We're in trouble!
How's that? Did you get through?
Don't be so mean!
Turn right at the next corner, sir.
It's still rubbing! Rubbing!
Move to the left!
It's rubbing this way!
That's why I hate the lower bus!
Don't blame the lower bus for your poor driving!
Sir, you can go straight ahead.
Hey, why don't you take the highway?
There's an entrance.
Really?
I'm sure there's an entrance to a closer road.
Our carnavigas can't go the wrong way.
Liar!
You told me to avoid the highway because you were afraid of it.
Rascal!
So you're going to go down the hill?
It'll take a lot of time to get there.
Really?
That's strange.
Did we break the carnavigas?
We did a self-diagnosis test, but there's nothing wrong with it.
Rascal...
Hey, it's a highway!
Get in the highway!
Hey, do you hear that?
What's that? It's not responding!
That's right.
It's set to recognize only the owner's voice.
Then you give the order!
That's right!
What?
Hm?
I'm going to change the route setting to go to Odaiba by the main street.
Is it the main highway?
That's right.
Is that okay?
What's wrong?
The user usage level is in beginner mode.
It's set not to use the highway, but is it okay to change it?
Don't ask me that every day!
Huh?
Everyone, do you have a license?
Give it a try!
I have private license.
The road that goes to the main street is about 200m from here.
100m more.
Hey, are you really okay?
He's wearing too much color.
What if he's never used the highway before?
Hahaha, I'm fine.
I have a driving lesson by the school of automobiles.
Ringo!
You can't do that!
This is no good!
You're too slow!
We did it! We made it to the highway safely!
Poor car in the back.
Really?
500 meters to Shibaura Junction.
Enter Odaiba Line at the end of the line.
Please change lanes.
200 meters to Shibaura Junction.
Don't say that so suddenly!
I didn't say it suddenly.
I've been telling you many times.
Please change lanes now!
But there's a truck behind us.
100 meters to go.
Please change lanes now.
Shut up! I know!
Hurry up, Master.
Damn it!
I'm sorry!
What the hell?
We passed the exit.
Are you going to kill me?
You can go anywhere.
You should take the highway.
Oh, yeah.
I want to go to the highway.
I'm sorry!
Get out of the way! I'll drive!
Oh, no! No!
Wait, Ryo!
You're in danger!
It's much more dangerous to let him drive!
What?
You bastard!
Ryo, you're in danger!
Where are we?
The primary school will have a minibus.
Why are there many people of the countryside?
It's because you broke the car navigation system.
You shouldn't blame others for it.
But you guys should be fine.
It will take a while.
Is that a restaurant?
No, it's a restaurant.
I'm fine with a ramen shop.
Don't you have a lot of sheets?
I don't have a car navigation system.
That's a problem.
The screen is shaking.
I'm afraid the sun is coming down.
Can you run more quietly?
It's better to have a video camera.
Go to the left.
What?
Why are you going to the right?
Can you do that so suddenly?
I'm not good at it.
Then you drive.
Which way is the next?
I don't know.
You're pathetic.
Shut up.
I'm not as delicate as you are.
That's perfect.
Then I'll go.
This is fun.
It's not a reenactment game.
Ryo, are you okay?
I'm fine.
This isn't what I want.
I'm not going to be
I was a Ferrari.
Defeat that car.
Be more careful!
Ryo, slow down a little!
The car's gonna break!
Ouch!
I'll follow your orders!
The battery's out!
Huh?
You don't have a spare battery or a CIGAR connector?
I don't have any!
You should have a spare battery!
You're a bad guy!
You know?
I don't know anything without a car.
Where should I go?
I'm going to the gas station!
Huh?
The engine's not broken.
It's just the gas.
I should have eaten French food at the station long ago.
I was just returning to the station.
You're the reason why this happened.
Something bad happened.
What?
It's your fault!
You're such a poor guy!
I'm a poor driver!
You two, stop!
Calm down.
It's no use fighting over a place like this.
Yeah.
I'm so angry that I'm getting hungry.
You're in trouble.
R-Reiko, don't worry.
I'll call the police.
Oh, it's me.
Huh?
Who are you?
Don't you know me?
I'm Shiratori Reiji!
Shiratori Tekko's Shiratori!
The gas has run out and I've stopped by.
Can you come over?
Huh?
Where?
Where is this place?
You don't know?
If you know, you have no trouble.
I don't know where it is.
Anyway, please help me.
Hey, you!
Shiratori Tekko's Shiratori Reiji!
This stupid guy!
You're so stupid.
Damn it!
Anyway, I have to get gas.
I don't think there's any gas here.
I can see it.
I don't think this kind of shop fits super rich people like me,
so I'll just go in.
Hello.
Oh, there's a bunch of stuff here.
Excuse me.
Is someone here?
Okay, hold on a second.
Look at that watermelon!
Oh, and some snacks!
That's a poor man's food.
Yum!
You're not going to eat it?
I can't eat such a cheap thing.
You're a good man.
Welcome.
Excuse me.
If you have any gas,
I'd like to share some with you.
Well, well.
Where are you from?
I'm from Tokyo.
That's a long way to go.
Good job.
Grandma, this and this.
Yes, yes.
All of them cost 145 yen.
Thank you.
So, what do you want?
Gasoline.
Do you have it?
Yes, yes.
Gasoline.
That's 25 yen.
I'll take this.
What's this?
It's a card.
You don't even know what a credit card is?
I've been paying cash since I was a child.
Here you go.
Damn it.
You threw it away.
How about this?
It's a Super Gold Million Card.
You can buy a house with it.
You're so boring.
Give me the cash now.
I'm a super rich man.
So I don't carry cash with me.
What?
You said you ate the stuff at the store
because you didn't have money?
I told you I'd pay with a card.
Grandpa,
call the police station.
They'll eat you.
Hold on.
Super rich man can't win
even if he has 25 yen.
I'll pay for this, Grandma.
Really?
That's fine.
But it's not good to date a rich man like him.
You're right.
Grandma,
do you have a smaller TV than this?
I only have this one.
Reiko,
buy me this, too.
What are you going to do with a TV?
I'll connect it to the navigation.
Give me the money back to Shiratoru later.
I haven't sold a TV in a long time.
And I hope you have gas.
Gas?
Gasoline.
Grandpa,
do you have gas?
Gasoline.
I don't have gas.
I only have gasoline.
Then we'll only use diesel.
Are you sure you're going to drive like this?
If you don't drive like this,
I'll just walk.
Aren't you a little too big?
I can only see half of you.
Don't complain.
Start the engine.
Ferrari!
Navigation system on.
Good morning.
Where are you going today?
Turn off the sound.
Idiot!
Why are you going into the middle of the mountain again?
I'm fine here.
I can't help it.
Then go here.
No, I said I should go as it is.
No, I don't know how far you can go in this state.
It's better to run a little farther than in the mountains.
That's true.
No, I just thought so.
Good mood.
It's a forest road over there.
I know.
It's not right, it's left.
What are you doing?
Stop it, Ryo.
You made a mistake.
I'm sure he hasn't left yet.
You should have just called me.
I heard that you trusted his driving.
Reiko, let me give you a car.
What?
Driver, come here.
This is my favorite shop.
Hello.
Welcome, young master Shiratori.
I was going to have you buy the car I bought last week.
Are you going to buy it?
I'm a super rich man.
Rich people change their minds quickly.
I'm sorry.
Be careful how you listen to me.
Look for a car that suits her.
It's her.
What do you think of this?
How much is this?
Including the cost of execution, it's about 290 million yen.
Two million?
I don't like red.
Is that so?
It's pretty good color.
Hey, don't touch it without permission.
You don't know the manners?
I'm a regular here, so I'm in the showroom.
It used to be a roadside market.
Do you know that?
It's full of luxury cars, so I'm surprised that I can touch it so easily.
And you guys just have a typewriter.
It's a kid in the field.
Master.
Good thing I happened to make you sit in my car.
Uh-huh.
That's a little alec.
Hey.
Do
I know this guy?
No.
All right.
Let me call the roadside market stage.
You knew each other at McLaren F1?
No, no.
This McLaren F1 is a new car.
Please take a look.
I was thinking I wanted one for the parts.
This is a good one.
Hey! You can see it thanks to me!
Don't talk to the owner directly!
Huh?
The owner doesn't have to talk to me and him, does he?
Hey, Reiji!
Dad!
I didn't know you were here.
It's a coincidence.
I was showing the super poor guy a luxury car.
Hey, you guys!
Gie, gie, gie, gie, gie!
You idiot!
I'm the toy of Nakagawa Concern!
I'm not your father!
I'm sorry to have insulted you.
I'm not your father.
I'm the company of Nakagawa Concern!
Dad!
You idiot!
Are you showing the super poor guy a luxury car?
Let go of my hand.
I'm...
Super rich man!
Oh, my!
I knew this was the best.
I've never seen French food before.
Well, Siratori was...
You're too kind!
No, I was selfish.
What have you to say?
Hello, everyone!
You are...
Yet again moved,
and you've come back to the super poor guy.
Huh?
Ah...ah...ah....
Shake!
You sure are a pretty easy person to be.
No way, I never knew I'd become married.
Nariuuki, you surprised me too.
Ryo-sama is my χ Tiger.
Heheh.
I'm excited.
Next time on Ryo's and Minda's Entire Love.
Take care!
"Ladies Who Can't Fall In Love"
♪ I hear rumors that I'm a girl who can't fall in love ♩
♪ But I have so many things I want to do ♩
♪ I want to walk through the mountains ♩
♪ I want to ride on a bike through the vast desert ♩
♪ I want to be freer than a bird ♩
♪ A lady's dream that changes at the speed of lightening ♩
♪ Love ♩
♪ Heart ♩
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♩
♪ The future of the panorama ♩
♪ The dazzling light that dives ♩
♪ You know it, right? ♩
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♩