A
When watching TV
Remember to keep your room light, and look away
The house after a rainy day
That seems to be someone's home
After the rain, I walked while looking back
My mom was holding my hand
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black tile of the arcade
I saw it
Everyone was a kid once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above his eyes
Look around
That corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Come to our town
Thank you!
It's starting tomorrow, right?
The Sydney Olympics
What's wrong, Ryo?
I feel like something important happened at the Olympic year
I think you said the same thing when you were in Atlanta
Didn't you talk about cicadas?
Cicadas?
I remembered
Fat cicadas
Minmin cicadas
Tsk-tsk hat
Sunflowers
Ah! Sunflowers!
I'll sleep for 4 years
I'll wake up for only one day
I'll solve all the difficult cases in the long run!
Super-powerful police officer!
You're Higurashi Neruo, right?
Yes, sir!
Tomorrow is the fourth year since Higurashi slept
So, Ryo
Can you wake up Higurashi tomorrow?
Me again?
It's hard to wake him up
By the way, it was hard to wake him up four years ago
I'm excited to go into that room again
I'm getting more and more excited
Wait a minute
Where is Higurashi now?
Where?
It's definitely in Nico Nico Ryo
Ah!
I remembered!
When Ryo was being repaired
He threw Higurashi with the trash
So, he woke him up on the island of dreams
It's a big deal
I see
So, what happened after that, chief?
Idiot
Nico Nico Ryo's Higurashi room is gone
So, I left it to the head of the town
You're the one who left it
That's right
To the head of the town's spirit room
That's why, tomorrow
I'm going to the head of the town
Wake up Higurashi
Okay, Ryo?
Yes, yes
I understand
Why do I have to wake Higurashi up?
But Higurashi is good
I can get paid even if I sleep all the time
Wait
By the way, four years ago
Before Higurashi fell asleep
Ryo was stressed
You could take a look at the documents
Please
For my brothers
They're longer than me
Higurashi won't
do the same things
Because I'm sleeping
Don't worry
All right
I'll sleep
No problem
This wasn't good
It's true
You were worried
Ryou
Don't be me
Because of you
I thought I'd just have to pay him back the 30 million yen, so I secretly borrowed the 30 million yen.
Then I found out that the 30 million yen was gone at the end of the road.
I thought I did something bad, so I was worried for a night.
But I forgot the next day.
Oh, no! If they find out that I used it...
Hey, you! Don't you dare say anything about my money!
Ugh! I-If I don't do something about it, I'm going to die!
The End
Ryo, if you succeed, you'll really be able to pay me for our overseas trip, won't you?
Hey, if you don't mind, I can let you go on a space trip with Jody in 2001.
A space trip? Not bad.
Yes, then I'll do it.
What was that just now? That was a pretty loud noise.
The End
I don't get it.
I understand that they're supposed to be around here...
Arghhh!
I was wrong. I was next to it.
Is it really alive?
Don't worry and get him out of here.
What is this room?
My senpai told me to recreate the room of Higurashi-san.
And the finishing move is this.
Did he really live in this room?
It's already perfect.
It's perfect.
All that's left is to build a
fire escape room in Ryo's garden.
A fire escape room?
A fire escape room in Niko Niko Ryo's garden?
Okay, all set.
I'll wake Higurashi-san up.
You guys do as I say.
Okay.
Hey, wake up, Higurashi.
I'm still sleepy.
Hey, wake up!
The Sydney Olympics have begun!
It's the year you started working!
The Sydney Olympics?
I think the last time I woke up was the Sydney Olympics.
Darn it.
I woke up a year and a half ago,
and I said that and you fooled me.
It's all my fault.
I'm still young.
I'm 2000 years old.
The Olympics are starting today.
Something's wrong.
Something's wrong?
I'm gonna take a shower and change into my uniform and go to work.
The sun's so bright.
Look.
You're pretty well-prepared.
I'm waking you up every four years.
You'll get used to it.
Let's go.
Isn't it this way?
Why is there a fire escape room in front of Ryo?
While you were asleep, I moved in.
From a fire escape room in front of the park,
it became a fire escape room in front of the Nico Nico.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
When did you start working at the fire escape room?
While you were asleep,
there was a fire escape room.
And this is the newcomer, Volvo Saigo.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Higurashi.
I heard from the head of the Ryo-tsu branch.
The head of the Ryo-tsu branch?
The head of the fire escape room?
What about the head of Ohara?
He moved to the Ryo-tsu branch.
And I became the head of the fire escape room.
I heard he's still dreaming.
Hey, don't sleep.
You have to do a lot of things with your superpowers.
Superpowers?
I can see it.
The soccer representative of Japan will participate in the World Cup.
I came out two years ago.
The song of the Dango may be a big hit.
I'm sure it will be a big hit.
Such a boom has already ended.
The Kochikami may become a movie star.
It's not just a movie, but it's also a stage.
The national tax may be used correctly.
I don't think so.
I can't get any good sleep.
It can't be helped.
I'll go to training for you.
Training?
Higurashi, go!
Yes.
I'll go soon.
A programme for you!
Good for you, Higurashi.
If you have Higurashi's superb powers,
you can easily get back the 300 dollars you spent on it
and come fishing.
What?
Ryo-tsu is in danger?
I got a call this morning,
super hot temperature is appropriate for him.
He's asleep.
These fools have been taking a day off
I'm sure it's a day off!
I brought the unresolved investigation file to solve the problem with Higurashi-san.
What should we do?
Higurashi can work only for one day today.
Let's leave Ryotsu alone and go to wake him up.
I ate it.
It's a great superpower to eat the specialties of an eel.
Thank you for the meal.
Senpai, we have patrols.
Good work.
Don't forget about the sword.
Leave it to me.
Let's get down to business.
Where's the unresolved investigation file?
I don't have the file.
I want you to get a fire.
What are you going to do?
The culprit of the goldfish.
He loves gambling.
I'm sure he'll come to the match tomorrow.
I see.
We have information that the culprit always watches the match near the goal.
I want you to get a fire on the moment the horse reaches the goal from the first to the twelfth race.
The culprit may be in the picture.
I can do it.
I saw it.
Take this.
Have you ever thought about me?
I've thought about you all.
I'll tell you why I'm here today.
Let's play some game.
Good job
The final number is 5.5 times 7 and 8
1 times 130 times 2 times 12
It's like this
I can't display it
God
99.26 billion times
If you buy a rock and roll it at 100 yen
It's 99.26 billion yen
I think it's good
I think I asked Ryotsu for something when I was sleeping
It's a Japanese series
Bad video broke
I couldn't shoot it for 4 years
It's a pity
Bad
I left it to Ryotsu
It was a problem of 2000 years last year
The computers in the world are malfunctioning
The world is in chaos
What?
It wasn't that big
Did you fire the missile?
I'm glad there's nothing
That's right
I'm thirsty
Yes
I'll buy you a juice
Then use this
You have a lot of money
I took the money and slept the next day
I don't use it
Lend me a little.
You have 200,000 yen.
If you transfer this money to the market,
it will become a astronomical amount.
Higurashi, this money is old and useless.
What?
There are a lot of fake money,
so I changed it to new money six months ago.
I'll change it to new money.
See?
That's right, new money.
And it's 2000 yen.
But I should have given you 200,000 yen.
I see, you didn't know.
At the same time as the new money was issued,
it became a denomi in Japan.
Denomi?
Yes, that is, the unit is reduced by two.
The old 100 yen is now 1 yen.
The 1 million yen is now 10,000 yen.
I didn't know.
Has the world changed so much?
Anyway, I'll buy you juice.
Wait for me.
There's no Higurashi.
He's already awakened.
That's not true.
Every year, Higurashi will never wake up until Senpai wakes him up.
Until Ryotsu wakes him up?
It's Ryotsu.
It must be his doing.
Did something big happen?
When you enter the capital,
you can't think of it as Senpai's doing.
There must be a specialist.
Anyway, I don't know Ryo.
Let's go eat.
It's hot.
I've been exposed.
What's wrong, Higurashi?
What's up with this idol?
Is it something from Okinawa again?
It's Morning Komusume.
It's a big hit produced by the Kuntsu of Sharanpi.
It was five at first,
but it became eight,
and then one left,
and then another one came in,
three more,
five more,
and it's probably about 50 now.
I see.
I especially like this one.
It's Mari Goto, who will make her solo debut this time.
Oh, it's Mari.
She's so cute.
Let's continue the investigation.
Higurashi is weak to women.
What's going on this time?
Mari is appearing live.
Ryotsu, let's go see the TV.
No, no.
You're only awake for one day today.
There's still a lot to do.
Hello?
This is bad, Senpai.
I've been exposed.
The chief of the Oogara club is heading there now.
I understand.
I'm going to get out of here.
You do what you don't know.
But...
All right?
Yes.
Higurashi.
Let's go see Mari.
Really?
Yes.
Then I'll call you back.
He's not here.
It's Mr. Honda's room!
What?
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
I think he used it to trick Higurashi.
It's like a spy plan.
What's wrong?
He's out!
Ryotsu!
He's a coward.
Don't act like a coward!
What's that?
Look, chief.
I see.
Ryotsu has seduced Higurashi into predicting tomorrow's match.
It's like Senpai's doing it.
Yes?
I thought it was easy.
But it looks like he doesn't know where Ryo-chan is.
Now all we have to do is catch Mr. Honda.
Ryotsu.
I'll catch you even if you split the grass!
The last challenger, Shimizu!
There's no time! 10 seconds left!
He's doing it! He's doing it!
Jump at once!
He did it! It's a success!
Congratulations!
The winning prize is 1 million yen!
Thank you very much!
Shimizu-san, there are still other wonderful presents.
What?
Today's special guest is Goto Mari-chan, the morning girl!
Oh, it's real Mari-chan!
Congratulations!
If it succeeds, Mari-chan will do such a good thing.
Let's go to the next challenge!
The next challenge is...
That one!
It's 50 meters high!
The top of that platform!
If you jump from there, you'll get 1 million yen!
If you have the courage to do it, please get on the stage!
Okay!
Ryo-chan, you're not going?
I'll do 1 million yen plus Mari-chan's kiss.
I don't care about the kiss, but 1 million yen is fine.
It's 100 million yen before tomorrow's Okuman-choja.
Okay, let's go!
Chief! Kya-chan! Where's Honda-san?
I've come to see him. But I don't know where he's going.
I have to know the location.
Damn it! Where did Ryo-chan go?
The players have left!
It's about the senior. They're doing something terrible.
Or do you want Mari-chan's kiss?
Chief, this is bad! Ryo-chan and Higurashi-san are on TV!
What?
What are you doing?
They're really doing something terrible.
Okay, let's go to the TV station!
Let's go to the TV station!
Let's go!
I'm going to be in danger!
Me, too!
I'm going to be in danger, too!
No way!
You're so mean.
Higurashi, it seems you're going to have a match with me.
I'll take Mari-chan's kiss.
Wow! Higurashi-san flew!
Amazing!
He just barely made a hole in the water, but he landed!
Higurashi-san's got super powers.
Well, I can jump in, too.
Okay!
Chief!
Ryo-chan, come down here!
Chief Ohara, didn't you go to Saihase-cho?
Higurashi, you're being tricked by Ryo-chan.
I'm still the chief of the
What?
That's a lie!
That's lie!
The Honda and Volvo are lying about everything!
You'll be finished soon!
Higurashi, calm down!
The superiors are lying!
I don't believe them!
How about the 30 million yen you saved?
I'll be the chief tomorrow to pay you back.
I knew you were cheating!
I won't lose!
It's dangerous.
Amazing!
Turn the camera!
I won't let you escape!
It's a big deal!
Mr. Higurashi was a super-powerful man!
The Sydney Olympics is starting today.
Kimura will be the winner.
What's the point of the weather today?
The ballast observatory has fallen!
Something is in front of us now!
It's a dragon!
I'll bury the first blow with the biggest power!
Stop it, Higurashi!
If you do more...
Stop it!
I can't hear you!
Higurashi is weak to women.
Especially to Goto Mari.
Mari, let's pray together.
What?
Higurashi!
Mari, let's pray together.
Higurashi, please calm your anger.
Higurashi, calm your anger.
Please!
Oh.
One hour later...
I...I'm back to normal...
Mar-Mari...
Yes...
Give me your signature, please.
Here you go.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
Oh, Higurashi!
Higurashi, don't sleep! You haven't done any work yet!
Higurashi, wake up! Higurashi!
Wake up!
What?!
You want me to deduct Higurashi's salary from my salary for the next 4 years?
Of course. Higurashi fell asleep after that and didn't solve any case.
And the TV station has a request.
No way!
Well, that's how it is. You should quit and get a good job.
Ouch! What's going on? I'm so tired!
Well, everyone, see you in 2004.
♪ Awaken! ♪ ♪ Clock! ♪ ♪ Kick it! ♪ ♪ Little finger! ♪ ♪ Ouch, ouch, ouch!
♪ First, brush your eyebrows ♪ ♪ and go to the station! ♪ ♪ Dance, dance, dance! ♪
♪ On the main train ♪ ♪ I'll sleep with my dad's back on my back ♪
♪ This week too, good job! ♪ ♪ Even if it's too much, I'll do more ♪
♪ But, I'm doing it with one hand ♪
♪ It's so warm and so cool ♪
♪ Even the annoyance of the remaining days ♪
♪ I'll get rid of it with annoyance ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ When the hot shower goes through ♪
♪ I get well with a safe pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ This is the me that you like ♪
♪ Every day is No Problem ♪
♪ A heart is flying, Monday ♪
♪ I'm a no problem ♪
Where the hell are we?
Did we go on a time slip half a century ago?
What? RVing history?
I've never heard something like that.
I don't care why you are doing that!
Next time, "Poor Doinaga-ken"
Thank you for watching!
♪ There is a wall over there ♪
♪ There must be a wall ♪
♪ Everyone come to our town ♪
Thank you!