The
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and
try to look away!
Come to me,
you poor guy!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
That's the advice I'll give you.
Come on,
you blue sky,
you white cloud.
You'll see what you can do
in no time.
WAA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA-HA!
I have no work,
I have nothing,
Come to me!
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red spider is burning
It'll be all right
You know it, right?
If you know it, then come to me!
Men are wild!
What's wrong with this mountain of curry?
Are you starting a curry shop?
No, I'm just selling the curry I bought cheaply from left to right
I'm just trying to earn a middle margin
Middle margin?
But at such a time, the small shop I was supposed to sell had refused
What? This curry is only two weeks away from expiration
That's why it was cheap
Of course it was refused
Damn it, all that's left is debt
You still have the curry
Shut up! I know that even if you don't tell me that
So what are you going to do?
Nakagawa, please buy it for me
What? I'm in trouble if you say that all of a sudden
You're rich, aren't you?
Isn't it a little bit?
It's not a little bit. How many do you have?
A hundred-color cardboard box
That means ten thousand colors?
How about four families and a box?
I have children, so I can only eat sweet curry
What about Reiko?
I decided to eat curry when I went to Thailand and India
You're so stingy
That's enough. If you're like this, eat it yourself
I feel sorry for him, but if he's dating Ryo, the national budget wouldn't be enough
It can't be helped
I can't eat because there's no rice
I can't eat
Well then
If this happens, I'll eat curry and eat curry
After all, curry alone has its limits
I want rice
Mr. Ryoji
How is Honda?
I came to a good place
Do you need curry?
Curry? No, no
That's not all for today
Actually, I want to buy a car
I wonder if Senpai would come with me
I thought you'd come with me
A car? A motorcycle?
That's because
I always have two motorcycles when I go out with Nana
Sometimes we drive together
I wonder if that's okay
Senpai, are you good at buying?
If you buy it cheaply, I'll thank you
Thank you?
Intermediate margin?
I want to fill the curry hole a little bit now
Yes, leave it to me
Really, Senpai?
If that's the case, I'll be in a hurry
Let's go
Senpai, where are you going?
It's a patrol
No, it's not
What are you going to do with the curry mountain in the back?
I won't forget it, so it's okay
I'll do something later
See you
I'll definitely forget about curry
What kind of car do you want?
It would be great if I could ride a Porsche
Porsche?
I see
What's the budget?
I have 100,000 yen
100,000 yen is not enough for the capital
It's not the capital, it's all
I'm looking forward to it
35 years of loan?
It's not a housing loan
It's a little long
The price is a little like a house
Do something about it
Even if you say so
It's worth a lot to a luxury car
Senpai, Porsche is just a joke
After all, 100,000 yen is impossible
Don't be weak as soon as you get off the bike
Then it's that
Is there anything cheap?
What's like a family Porsche?
Something like that
I understand
I will prepare a perfect Porsche for the customer
Oh, how about it?
I'll try it, Honda
Yes, but is it true?
Here it is
Oh, it's small
A same-sex Porsche exhaust
20,000 yen
Hey, how do you ride this?
We want the real one, the real one
However, at our store, as a principle
I don't do long-term loans
How do you buy it without paying the loan?
Such a high car
This is
This is Miyashita-sama
Welcome
Hey, I haven't lived here yet
This is
This is a new model that just entered last week
Hmm, it's pretty good
How much?
Including the amount and the initial expense
It will be about 35 million yen
35 million
It's expensive
Hmm, 35
Then give me one
Hey
Thank you every time
I will continue now
Please come here
You have to pay a lot when you come to this store
Still, the new car is impossible
There is a friend in the used car store
Shall we go there?
Yes
Hello, Ryo-san
CEO, we have a budget of 100,000 Pocky
I want to buy a cheap Porsche
Do you have it?
It's Mr. Ryo's
No matter how many used cars, 100,000 Porsche
Porsche?
I have
It's 80,000
What?
It's brand new.
Wow, this is 80,000 yen.
How is it?
You can pay me 20,000 yen as an intermediate margin.
Yes, but...
Is this really running?
How is it?
It runs properly.
It's like a dream to have 80,000 yen.
Yakko seems to have liked it a lot.
That's good.
It's amazing and cool.
I will invite Nana-chan and go to Chiba.
However, it's a kit car, so I can't get the number.
I thought there was something.
If you can't get the number, you can't run the road.
I will run in my own garden.
I will decorate it and look at it.
There are various ways to win.
No, I want to run outside.
It's selfish.
Then I will look at other cars.
To the next.
Well, I will go out and get down.
That's 30,000 yen.
It looks bad, but I can run outside.
You have a strong shoulder.
Can you walk properly?
Of course, I can still run.
It's quite rusty.
The rust has a good taste.
There are people who make rust with the help of oil.
Natural rust is the best.
The tire feels like Marubozu.
What are you talking about, Ryo-san?
There is no groove in the racing car.
There's no groove in the car.
It's sandpaper polished.
Well, you can pay 70,000 yen for my mid-margin.
It's too hard after Porsche.
I can't understand why the mid-margin is higher than the car.
You greedy guy.
Which one is it?
How about this?
It's beautiful and has horsepower.
50,000 yen is fine.
30,000 yen in head money and the split payment is also OK.
I'll take this Honda.
No, I don't want to go to a luxury car.
I want to drive a more stylish and cool car.
What are you talking about Honda?
This is a stylish and cool open car depending on the design.
This is a mid-margin.
I won't pay for such a thing.
What?
It's a different promise.
It's getting further and further away from my expectations.
It's easy to say that you should drive a stylish and cool car with a budget of 100,000 yen.
Because you're a professional.
You shouldn't expect too much from me.
I see.
You have a cheap and clean left-hand drive.
Isn't it Rolls-Royce?
And it's 20,000 yen.
There's no other car like this.
But I'm sure it's a reasonable price.
Wait, president.
What are you hiding?
I'll tell you the truth.
Actually, that car is a car accident.
What?
There is a rumor that the owner always has a flat tire, so I took it with a cheap price.
But because the price is too cheap, I was careful and couldn't buy it, and I couldn't dispose of it, so it's been there since.
Ah, a flat tire.
What? That's it.
That's a flat tire, senpai.
That's a name.
Rather, I think it's a carnavi, an airbag, and a flat tire as standard equipment.
Ah, that's true.
I don't think so.
Even if you put a carnavi and an airbag, it's a flat tire.
This may be a fate.
I can't think of it.
Well, maybe the flat tire won't happen anymore.
I don't know what happened, but there's no problem if you drive properly.
It's too scary to see the rearview mirror.
It's getting dark.
Senpai.
Don't look behind you.
But...
Go slowly and go straight.
Even if I say that, senpai...
If the budget is 100,000 yen, we have only this much.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I'm interested in cars, after all.
I lost my curry, so I thought I'd fill a little hole in the middle margin from Honda.
What's that?
That's enough.
Let's go home, senpai.
What?
Isn't it a carnavi car?
That's a carnavi car, and it's going to be scrapped.
Are you going to crush it?
Yeah.
It won't be sold.
It's a waste, isn't it?
I've used it for more than 10 years, and the mileage is low.
Hey, look.
It's got a lot of red blood.
Where did you get it?
It's a fire brigade from the Yamaoku village.
I don't think the carnavi car is very active in that area.
It's a waste.
I can't use it for anything.
That's right!
Honda!
Buy this car for your 100,000 yen!
What?
What's the point of buying a fire brigade?
It's a curry!
What is that noise?
What was that car?
It was a car that had a ladder.
All right, that's all.
Hello, everyone in the exam room.
You've worked hard studying every day and night.
How are you feeling?
The poor student's companion, Ryo Curry!
Ryo Curry!
Ryo Curry is here!
Alright, let's go!
Yes!
Alright, come here!
Wait a minute...
W-What?
Hello.
There are many kinds of curry, but there's also a special curry, which is called "Goukaku Curry".
How about that?
Um... What's a "Goukaku Curry"?
It's a curry with raw eggs and lots of nutrients.
And you're the one who's gonna win!
Then, I'll have one of those "Goukaku Curry".
Yes! I'll have a "Goukaku Curry" "Oomori-1"!
Namaste!
"Goukaku Omori-1"! Namaste!
Yes! Ryo Curry "Goukaku Curry" "Oomori-500" is here!
I'll have one "Goukaku Curry" too!
I'm counting on you!
Yes, yes! Namaste!
Honda-kun!
"Goukaku Curry" "Oomori-2" "Chuumori-3"
"Oomori-2" "Chuumori-3"
And then, "Oomori-1" "Goukaku Curry" "Oomori-3"
And then, "Oomori-1" "Goukaku Curry" "Chuumori-1"
"Goukaku curry" "Oomori-1" "Chuumori-1"
"Goukaku Curry" "Chuumori-3" "Oomori-1"
"Chuumori-3" "Oomori-1"
And then...
Oh my god! I don't know what's going on!
Namaste!
Whatever, just carry them in the car, Namaste!
Which one is the big one and which one is the small one?
Well, Honda-kun, the ladder ride-on.
Namaste!
Here, the big one is 500 yen.
And that one is the small one, 450 yen.
Namaste!
The curry with the pass rate will be an extra 100 yen each.
Please make sure you don't miss the food.
Namaste!
200 yen...
We sold out.
It was a good deal on the first day, wasn't it?
Why am I in the curry shop?
It's a great ride-on, Honda.
Please forgive me, senpai.
I wanted a normal car that I could drive,
but I bought a ladder car.
When you saw this, you were as excited as a child.
So you don't buy it, do you?
Here's my 100,000 yen.
It's the end of today.
I'm sorry for dragging you into this.
So buy your favorite car.
Huh?
But, Honda.
A man must not forget the two letters of ambition.
Ambition?
The ambition is to earn more and more from today and tomorrow,
and one day, I'll become rich!
Ambition...
With a ladder car just before Scrap,
I want to be rich from the bottom of my heart.
Senpai, please help me with the curry shop.
What?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
But with that money, I can only buy a kit car Porsche that can't run outside.
After all, I want to buy a Porsche with cash like that rich man,
and I also want to buy a Ferrari and a Benz.
That's my ambition.
I see.
Buy a Porsche.
Buy five or six cars.
That's what a man is.
Yes, sir.
We swear here now.
We'll fight until we sell 10,000 curry shops.
In the name of the dead Chichan...
What?
Senpai's grandfather is still alive in Tsukuda Island.
In the name of the old man!
Yes, sir.
Six days until the curry is sold.
I can't wait.
Hey, the wife of the mammoth.
How are you doing?
Hello.
In the midst of a busy day,
why don't you take a break today and have a lot of nutritious curry?
Two servings, please.
Here, too.
Yes, sir.
I'll take a look.
Oh, my wife here.
You look a little thin.
Oh, my.
It's my first time seeing you.
Oh, really?
You're so good.
Here's a large pack.
Don't get sick.
Lunch break.
Buy yakisoba bread at the store.
You're a junior high school student who wants to buy a lot of things.
Hello.
How about hot curry sometimes?
Oh, my.
What are you doing?
Hello, everyone in the office outside Marunouchi.
If you don't have any customers to survive this impoverished country,
you'll be out of here.
If you don't buy it, you'll buy it.
The enthusiasm and courage.
This is important.
The ladder car is a bizarre idea.
If there is a paper to throw away, there is a paper to pick up.
Is that so?
I'll take it.
Why did you compete in a curry single?
It's a stock market competition.
What?
No, that's not it.
There is little profit.
Of course, there is little loss.
You all have a lot of experience.
At dinner time, the smell of curry flowing from your neighborhood.
That smell that makes you want to eat and drink.
I thought this was the only thing.
I don't want to eat curry anymore.
The curry shop at the end of the road may go to your town.
If you say "Namaste" to me, I will give you a large curry.
Yes, yes. There is still enough money, so please line up in order.
Honda, what's wrong?
I did it.
Cheers to the 10,000th meal within the expiration date.
Honda, don't sleep yet. There are many people waiting outside.
Because there is no curry and rice.
Don't worry. I have already ordered additional food.
Curry and rice for 20,000 meals will arrive soon.
20,000 meals!
Please let me rest a little, Senpai. I haven't slept for five days.
Five days? This is the place of the boy's life.
Honda, where is your ambition?
Ambition?
Porsche, BMW, Ferrari, Mercedes-Benz.
Ambition!
Yes!
The expiration date is three days later. I will sell it and sell it.
Namaste.
Porsche is the best. Porsche is...
What?
It's a fire!
It's terrible, Senpai!
Hey, carry the curry and the lunch break will be over.
That's not the point, Senpai!
Help me!
Hurry up and report to the fire and run away!
Honda, stretch the ladder!
Help me!
Hurry up and get on this side!
That guy is a firecracker!
What?
Honda!
Yes!
Run fast, it is a fire!
Honda, hurry up!
Yes!
Damn it! I'm not letting you escape!
Increase the speed!
Full speed! The body is heavy! I can't go any further!
You don't own 4 wheels and a point!
He went to meet my ambition!
Aren't you disappointed?
What!
Ga, ga, ga!
Tarei's okay!
Stop that!
Wait up!
Uh, a twin, not a double!
Hey, why don't you give it a rise?
It's for a reason!
Wah!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Honda! The criminal went that way!
Put the ladder back!
Alright!
Wait, you!
I'm gonna crash!
Wait!
I'm not running away!
My money!
My 20,000 yen!
Ryo, I have a request for you.
What? A request?
The repair cost of the building is 180,500,000 yen.
The repair cost of the pedestrian bridge, the electric pole, the guard rail and other other repair costs are 100,000,000 yen.
Other than that, there are many other violations of the traffic law.
There are many other violations of the traffic law.
And the cost of the repair cost is 300,000,000 yen.
The loan is not valid.
That's all for today.
Wait, chief!
You arrested the law enforcement.
Why am I the one who's paying for it?
You idiot!
I don't care anymore if you're trying to change the car.
No, chief!
What about my Porsche?
What about my drive with Nana?
That's not the point!
I should have stopped when the curry was sold out.
I shouldn't have done that.
Do you mean that your bad ambitions?
Good grief.
Why did this happen?
Do you have a different method than before?
I don't think I have a choice.
Next time.
Why?
Why did Ryo-san do that?
Ryo's eyebrows look like black hair
Why?
He wears sandals but he runs really fast
Ryo is always arm wrestling
Why?
He's so flimsy but he's loved by everyone
It doesn't matter
The title of this anime is so long
This is Katsushikaku, Kamayari Park's first appearance
Why?
Everyone, let's do it together!
March 3rd is my birthday
But every time I see this day, I get unhappy
This year I was going to have a good time
Why am I making a real Hina doll?
Why am I making Hina dolls?
Next time "O-Hina Sanzan Birthday"
"O-Hina Sanzan Birthday"
Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much.
Thank you.