Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming seasons ♪
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new age lightly ♪
♪ Diving into the city with a hero ♪
♪ I wanna dive into paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing all the trendy stuff ♪
♪ I'll decide everything with my bare face ♪
♪ Let it bleed ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Let's run and run ♪
♪ Dreams can't always stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Love you, love ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if you're a little out of it ♪
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ I'm excited and excited ♪
♪ I want to be strong and high ♪
♪ I want to be a man who makes it through ♪
♪ Give me the strength and hoped for the best ♪
♪ I wanna be the one to be ♪
♪ The one who would tear my heart open ♪
♪ I wanna have every moment of it ♪
♪ All the moments I want ♪
♪ I want to be a man who will go home ♪
I have a postcard for you.
It's for the delivery, right?
Give it to me.
It's not for the delivery.
It's for the deliveryman...
Yone Ryochi.
What?
Ryo, aren't you Yone and Fukuro?
Well, yeah.
Ryo, what are you doing?
It's worse than a postcard for the delivery.
I'm going to the patrol.
"Kankichi, I'm fine."
"I can't reply to any postcards."
"I heard you don't have any letters."
"I've been feeling down for years."
"My father was sick last year."
"So he's very weak now."
"He's been sleeping all day."
"And he's not getting any sleep."
"Kankichi, don't get mad at me."
"Just show me your face at least once."
"Then I'll get better, too."
"I'll be right back, you know."
"I'll be back from the cold and the cold won't be so strong."
Ryo, wait!
What?
Why don't you go back home?
Shut up!
I hate word-of-mouth!
I'm done!
Ryo-chan!
Don't do that.
You'll be in a bad mood if you talk about your family.
By the way, you've never talked about your family before, have you?
There's something I can't talk about.
Chief?
Chief, what's something you can't talk about?
I don't know much about it,
but since I left home after having a big fight with my father at the age of 18,
I haven't gone home once.
So you haven't been home for many years?
Yeah.
I used to go home to my family without thinking about it.
I thought you went back to Shibabata, but it was a waste.
You were always saying that you had a beautiful sister.
By the way, you said you didn't like the talk with Tsukudani.
I talk with her every year.
My family sent a lot of Tsukudani to my mother and father-in-law.
"Kankichi is taking care of you.
I'll be in your care from now on."
I wrote that letter.
Ryo-chan has such a wonderful family.
Oh, right.
Why don't you make Ryo-chan and your father get back together?
That's a great idea, isn't it?
What?
Then your mother won't have to write such a letter.
Don't do that.
If you get too involved in Ryo-chan's affairs,
it won't be good for you.
I'll kill you.
Damn it.
Someone sent me a letter.
What are you doing, dad?
I was feeling good today,
so I thought I'd give you a ride to Sensoji.
Wait a minute.
You don't need a sports newspaper.
This is...
You can't move while you're just lying down.
It's called the head exercise.
Bye.
Dad!
Oh my god.
I was so happy to get the Manba ticket that I was surprised.
Senpai, please come here for a moment.
There's something I want to show you.
Something you want to show?
What is it? Isn't it just a navigation system?
It's different from the navigation system over there.
It's a super navigation system made by the company in my line.
Of course, there's traffic jam information.
All the houses and buildings in Japan,
and even all the dates and food stalls are all in there.
Oh, so you've got such a detailed map.
So let's set the destination and turn on the navigation.
Is there anywhere you want to go?
Hey, I haven't been to Asakusa since I came to Tokyo.
Let's go to Asakusa.
Hey, don't go there. Let's go somewhere else.
Why?
It's just like that.
Anyway,
you should stop going to Asakusa.
I see.
I can't get out of Asakusa.
That's right.
There's no place to play in Asakusa.
It's just old people and old women.
That's right.
There's nothing to see.
Let's go to Shibuya or Roppongi.
You two.
You say Asakusa is lame?
Stop joking around.
What?
Asakusa has been the center of culture since the Edo period.
Compared to Asakusa,
Shibuya and Roppongi are the same.
But Ryo-chan...
Shut up!
There's nothing to see.
You're a jokester.
I'll show you what Asakusa is like.
Huh?
Good morning.
Let's start the route guide.
What's this voice?
Isn't it Maya Katsuragi, the popular anime voice actor?
Ryo-chan,
please go to Asakusa with Maya.
I'll do it.
I don't want to talk to the navigation.
If you input your name,
it will guide you to talk to the person.
By the way,
this is the popular voice actor version.
There are many other software.
Don't do that.
Be more relaxed.
What is this software?
Nakagawa.
It's quite good.
It's the AV actress version.
Change it to another one.
Oh, no.
He's going to control the intersection.
Why can't I turn left?
You idiot,
Kasu!
How dare you,
you bastard!
Ryo-chan,
calm down.
What are you going to do if you are attacked?
The Yakuza version doesn't seem to suit you,
Senpai.
Oh,
Kami-ись
Whoa, that's a lot of tourists!
A big boat!
Yo, what is this?
You don't know Kaminari-mon either, Tagu-mon?
He looks quite scary. What's this?
This is thunder.
And this is wind.
And at the end of the line is the war zone.
It's still early in the morning.
It's pretty busy.
It's not as busy as it used to be.
It's delicious fresh out of the oven.
Look, it's Ryo-chan.
I'm eating this one too.
Here, you can eat this one too.
It's Ryo-chan.
It's Kan-chan.
How are you, Grandma?
It's been a while.
Hey, Kan-chan is back.
Oh, Kanchika. Long time no see.
Hey, Dad.
I was drinking.
Why are you crying, God?
You're the one who's become a good policeman.
I thought I'd destroy the shop in three days.
I was looking forward to it.
What?
You're a little bit naughty.
It's been years since I've seen you.
Ryo-chan is popular.
For the seniors, this is like a garden.
Ryo-chan, who is in love with alcohol, worry about drinks.
I don't understand you and my family.
You're more and more, so...
Oh, this is nice.
Let's go to Disney World in the countryside.
Disney World in the countryside?
Wait for it.
Wow!
The roller coaster here is full of thrill.
I feel like I'm going to be in a private house.
Anyway, Ryo-chan's home is near here, right?
I'd like to see it.
Don't be afraid! We're working!
Let's go back!
I didn't know there was a word "working" in Ryo-chan's dictionary.
Shut up! I haven't been home for years.
I forgot where I was.
Then don't worry. There's a navigation system.
What?
I came all the way here.
It's like coming to Asakusa and having a party at Senzoji.
Is that so? You guys are crazy!
Hey, let go of me!
Oh, that's Ryo-chan's house.
Well, you've seen it, so let's go inside.
What are you talking about?
We've come all the way here, so let's show our faces.
Hey, isn't that Ryo-chan's mom?
What?
Hey, Senpai!
You idiot!
Since I started fighting with my dad when I was 18,
I've decided not to go back to my parents' house!
But he's not sleeping soundly.
You should pay him a visit.
I'm so moved that I came all the way here!
I can't wait to go home!
I'm going home.
Ryo-chan! We've come all the way here!
Senpai, why don't you have lunch?
I'll feed you.
Oh, I see.
If you're going to treat me, then let's talk about something else.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's like a chomoro-guk.
It's not just good.
The price is also cheap.
It's true.
If it's this taste and volume, it's twice as good as Ginza.
How is it, Reiko? Have you seen Asakusa again?
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry to have made you wait.
Oh, I see, I see.
Asakusa is the best after all.
Asakusa is the best?
What a fool!
That's absolutely not it!
If such a dirty thing comes, Katsudoki will be surprised and open his eyes.
After all, this is the real world.
If this is Tokyo, it's Roppongi.
It's Roppongi!
Ryo-chan!
If you keep quiet, you'll get a good feeling!
Hey, old fart!
You said Asakusa was a shithole,
and even though Lord Kannon forgives you,
I won't forgive you!
If you get caught up in my expectations,
where the hell are you?
Huh?
What?
Let's go.
That's why, the wife of that person,
who gave birth to me fifty years ago...
After all, it's your father!
Well, that's what people say in the world.
Kei-chan, you did it!
Come on, Ryo-chan, let's greet him.
Shhh, now's not the time.
Later, later...
Now's not the time, either!
That's right, senpai!
Come on, come on...
It's a bit noisy next to him.
Come on, come on!
Senpai, you're here!
Hello. Nice to meet you.
My name is Keiichi Nakagawa.
I'm always here to help you.
My name is Reiko Akimoto. Nice to meet you.
T-this is...
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Are you alright?
Well, I'm fine.
What are you doing? You're his parent, aren't you?
At least greet him.
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
I-I got it.
H-hello.
I'm your son, Ryotsu.
Do you remember me?
Oh, it's you.
I thought I saw you somewhere earlier.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha...
You're so nosy.
Are you really his parent?
I'm starting to lose my confidence, too.
I'm sorry to disturb you after a long time.
What?
Ryo-chan, I'll go now.
Oh, wait, there's more.
The main race is perfect for the end of the round.
Yes, yes. Take your time.
Thank you very much.
What?
Asakusa No. 1 was expecting a race?
I can't believe you.
Huh?
Ryo-chan, say something.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Ah, ah, ah...
Um, is your wife making tsukudani?
Yes.
Oh, thank you.
Please speak more actively from your father.
Senpai is embarrassed.
Is that so?
Um, the police are talking about various things in the mass media lately.
I think it's quite a big deal.
I'm being taken up, but the house is also embarrassing.
It's hard.
No, no.
I'm already giving up on that method.
It's like a wedding seat.
I don't think it's a very parent-child conversation.
Hmm...
Don't talk nonsense.
If my father was quiet, I wouldn't have come here.
You're the one who's bad with Asakusa.
You said you would never come to Asakusa again and left.
I came here because Reiko wanted to come.
I don't care.
Well, both of you.
It's a nuisance to the customer here, so let's change the place.
I'm sorry.
How are you?
I'm fine.
What a good son.
I can't keep up with him.
Oh, I can't drink this because of the b-ball.
This is...
Ramune drinks by stopping the b-ball with this.
Is that so?
Well, that's why.
This guy is also...
Well, if you think about it now, I don't think I'm mature.
It's bad because my father only makes Tsukudani eat.
When I was in elementary school, I was nicknamed Tsukudani Taro.
So that's how you get big quickly by nourishing yourself.
Tsukudani will become a nutrition master every day.
Just kidding.
Did you tell your face?
What?
This rotten, rotten, rotten, rotten.
You.
What are you talking about?
I won't give up.
You.
Ouch.
It's a fire.
Fire.
Out of my way.
Wait, Dad.
Let's go.
The fire is the father's nose.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hurry up!
Looks like they're parents.
Let's go, Midori!
Let's go!
The firemen aren't here yet?
This is bad.
It looks like the old lady is still in her room.
Huh? Where is she?
On the first end of the second floor.
Over there?
Help!
Oh!
Kankichi!
I'm going to help the little girl.
You take care of her.
Why me?
Wait, Dad!
Little girl.
Why me?
Grandma, are you okay?
Are you okay?
I cramped my legs.
Come on, little girl.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's go.
Let's go, little girl.
Here we go.
Dad, what are you doing?
Hurry up!
I'm sorry.
You're so important.
Little girl, grab my shoulder.
Yes, sir.
Dad, I'm coming to help you.
Wait for me.
Okay.
No, no.
Way to go!
Dad, I can't believe you guys are here.
Yes, sir.
Ryo!
Brother!
What are you...
Brother, what are you doing?
I don't have time for this.
You're dangerous.
Just leave this to us.
Shut up!
Stop it!
You said it's no good!
Let him go.
Dad's up there.
What?
No!
Senpai!
Damn it! What is that guy doing?
Damn it! I should've asked him to help me!
I should've asked him to help me!
Don't say that! You can't call this demon!
That bastard!
Kankichi!
Ryo!
Senpai!
No way...
You're gonna kill me!
Senpai!
I'm so worried!
It's not like I'm gonna die!
Reiko, please be kinder.
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
I'm older than you.
Besides, you're so mean.
That's why you feel guilty.
I'm not that horny.
I didn't tell anybody.
What did you say?
I was a 'women's' up till the 3rd grade.
Stop it!
Who could've saved you!
Who said I could save you!?
I almost escaped...
Damn finish!
He did something to me!
We all know that!
Senpai!
I'm busy talking, but I've got to go back.
The chief's...
I see. He came out in silence.
That's why.
Take care, Dad.
Thank you for the meal.
It was really fun, Uncle.
That was good.
Excuse me.
Kankichi.
You're not going home?
Mom's worried about you.
No, not today.
Besides, the ship is on duty.
I'm going back to work now.
See you, Ryo.
See you.
You're not as good as your mom, Yagko.
You're still a young man.
You don't have to be so pitiful.
You're right.
You're a great officer now.
Don't worry about me.
I'm still a young man.
San, get me another one.
Yes, sir.
That hoodie...
Ryo's dad is a fun guy.
Yeah.
He's just like you.
See you later, Senpai.
Once a year.
See you later.
See you later then.
See you later, donner.
See you later.
Goodbye.
Good luck today.
See you tomorrow, today and tomorrow.
Good luck.
Bye.
See you.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.