Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Overcoming the new era lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city in yellow ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than just wearing trendy things ♪
♪ I'll be 100 times more handsome ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Start running ♪
♪ Dreams can't always stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if you're a little out of it ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt ♪
♪ Embrace the bustling curiosity ♪
♪ And jump high ♪
♪ It doesn't matter what you were looking for ♪
♪ because with your mind, you can do anything ♪
♪ You're a goodutious person, aren't you ♪
♪ don't forget to talk to me ♪
You're really a gentleman.
Of course I am!
Hmm...
There are too few days off for my work.
I want to work five days a week like the rest of the world.
The rest of the world works two days a week.
I'm working hard for the safety of the citizens.
It's a natural requirement.
In Ryo-chan's case, he always works seven days a week.
But to complete this tight schedule,
I need the strength of an iron man.
Yes!
This is Kameari.
Huh?
What is it?
We're taking a break here.
Let's have lunch and then go to the toilet.
Senpai!
We're in trouble!
Huh?
What's going on?
It's like that!
It's dangerous!
Please get off!
Yes, please get off!
It's dangerous!
It's no good!
Please don't get in!
What's going on?
Please get off!
It's dangerous, so please get off!
No, no, no, no, we'll be in trouble if we get in.
Get off!
I'm getting into trouble!
Sorry!
Mr. Nakagawa!
Where's the injured man?
He's not here.
Where is that elephant?
In the勝負's storeroom.
Hurry up and get him out of here!
See? You're used to it.
I'm not used to it!
You mean how is he?
I'd like to get on with him.
Do wait!
Mr. Nakagawa! Do wait!
Mr. Nakagawa! You're being too dangerous!
What's that? It's discrimination!
It's discrimination. Now, hurry up and tell him!
Here you go.
No, thanks.
What? It's a kid.
See? The kid's fine.
The kid's fine.
It's quiet. Is he okay?
Senpai!
Watch out, Nakagawa!
Let me go!
Let me go, Senpai!
Nakagawa!
Bring me milk and milk bottles!
What?
Hurry up!
Y-Yes, sir!
Oh, Mr. Nakagawa!
Mr. Nakagawa!
I'm glad you're okay.
Excuse me.
Do you have milk and milk bottles?
Yes, sir.
There, there.
Don't be afraid.
You're fine.
Just fill your nose with milk.
That'll make you feel better.
Okay, okay, okay.
Nakagawa, you're still not good enough.
I'm done!
Do you drink milk or something?
Milk is the basic of all mammals.
Here, here's your milk.
I'm a cow's father.
I'm sorry.
Here, here, here.
See?
Like this.
Drink it.
He drank it!
There, there.
Good boy.
You're oftentimes surprised, aren't you?
Yeah.
Don't feel bad.
Don't worry.
Don't be afraid.
I know it's a small animal.
It's a wild animal, though.
It's big but it's still a child.
If I don't get excited, it'll be a quiet animal.
But where did this elephant come from?
I don't think someone bought it as a pet.
I don't think it's been swimming around the beach from Africa.
Then it's probably a zoo.
I see.
Well, take care of it until you get it.
Let's go home, Nagagawa.
Please wait for me, Mr. Oomari!
Nagagawa!
No, you can't leave me, Senpai.
It's a wild animal, Zo!
It's the best couple.
Why is Zo here?
He said he was lost, so Ryo-chan picked him up.
Why is he in the escape room?
He should be in the front, so he won't get drunk.
He'll be here by morning.
It's better to leave him here than to leave him alone.
Ryo-chan's been kind to him, so he's completely used to it.
He's loved by everyone but humans.
I'm going to eat you!
Here you go.
Wow, it's a real one! It's huge!
I'll give you 100 yen and you can put it on your head.
Really?
Ryo-chan!
I'm just kidding.
It's free. It's fine.
Try putting it on your head.
Put it on, put it on!
I can't help it.
Here you go.
Wow, it's amazing!
It's so expensive!
It's a real one!
Is there any request for a search?
I've reported it to the head office, but there's still nothing.
Well, if you're going to get caught, I'll give you some milk.
Are you going home, senpai?
What?
Yotsun!
What? What?
What are you doing?
Why are you all looking at me like that?
Tell me!
My work is over!
The TV set is officially democracy until tomorrow!
I can't go home for a whole day anyway!
Go home!
Why don't you take care of this one?
No!
Huh?
What?
It's his schedule for tomorrow's TV broadcast vote.
The schedule's already numbered!
Almost 10 p.m.
A few minutes of breakfast,
9:30 a.m.
Pueblo
Oh, it's already 10:00.
10:45, morning service.
It's already late.
You guys go home.
12:00, lunch.
That's right.
He's a very plan-oriented person.
He's irresponsible.
If you brought him here, you should have taken care of him to the end.
That's right, Ryo-chan.
He's not my elephant.
He didn't bring him here.
He came here on his own.
He's going to be beaten up for this.
Good work.
See you later.
I'm going home.
Let go of me.
You're not leaving me.
I'll take you with me, Ryo-chan.
Don't be silly.
Keep it that way, Ryo.
This is an order from the chief.
What?
Is that a question of that big?
That's an order from the chief.
If you have a complaint, go to the chief of the wall.
Please let me go to the chief.
I won't allow this.
Ehhhh!
I just cleaned the floor.
I shouldn't have to walk on dirty feet.
It's fine. It's fine.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Ryo?
Don't put that in the bath.
It's an order from the aunt.
If you have any problems, tell her.
Ehhhh!
Okay, the other direction.
Okay, now to the back.
I'm pretty clean now.
You just wait here.
This guy will understand what I have to say.
Ehhhh!
I don't understand at all, Ryo.
I'm begging you, stop begging.
What's wrong?
Huh?
You little brat! This is my breakfast!
What are you going to do with our breakfast?
Ryo-san is going to be like this because he brought in an elephant.
You're the owner of the house, you should take responsibility!
I said this isn't my elephant!
Please do something, Ryo-san!
Listen, bring him in!
I'm begging you!
Don't wait! Bring him in right away!
Because I haven't heard anything about the elephant.
Then where did he come from?
Is he a Nora elephant?
Then call the insurance company!
Anyway, we'll contact them once we get some information.
Please do that.
He's just like me.
He's always trying to get into my stuff.
Isn't it
Wait a sec, wait a sec.
What?
What's going on?
You're the one who to blame.
You're the leftovers!
What's wrong?
This is the one I wanted!
8,000 yen.
I forgot my wallet in Ryo's.
Again? Don't say that.
No, I mean it. I'll bring it back next time.
Ryo!
He's already here.
The back door is this way.
Oh! Don't come in, Ryo.
Ryo, there are two more people.
I have an urgent meeting.
If you want, you can bring the money.
Don't be so rude.
I'll pay for it, so please don't sell it.
Please!
No!
I can't stand being caught.
I can't stand it!
This is a police fight!
Why do I have to date an elephant on my holiday?
Don't do it! You don't know anything!
Oh, you're thirsty after running.
Pointing at the tendencies of the door.
Ah, darn it!
10 yen left!
10 yen left...
Oh, here's the 1-0-0-0 grape.
1-0-0-0 grape...
1-0-0-0...
10 yen...
I can't believe it.
It's a little money.
If you're already drunk, you can't tell the owner of the bar by the time you get to the bar.
If you're already drunk, you can return the bottle.
Good, good.
You're a good boy.
Then, here's a little grape.
Oh, no! I spilled my drink!
I can't drink this when my throat is dry!
Give me back my 100 yen!
Give it back, you bastard!
Two more?
I'll get you another one.
My throat is dry.
I can't go back to get my wallet.
And I can't pay for my 10 o'clock bill.
Thanks to you, I can eat breakfast.
And now I can plan my schedule for the day.
I'll give you 100 yen.
What the hell is this?
Did you pick it up again?
It's my wallet.
And it's heavy.
Hey, it's a big one!
Oh, I was looking for that wallet.
Thank you. You saved me.
What proof do you have that this is your wallet?
I think it's a picture I took with my grandchild.
I don't know.
I learned that I can prove anything I want.
Hmm, I'm not that impressed with carrying coins.
You're too kind.
But it seems like a rare pet.
I heard that in Asia, there are many countries that treasure elephants as their gods ever since ancient times...
Gods?
I'm sorry but this is a small animal,
so it's worthy of your food.
Even if it's just a food bill.
What? This much?
I'd say it's about one percent.
Well, good luck.
I-I have 30,000 yen!
I think I've made it!
Then I'll have to go back to work on the afternoon schedule!
You better make it, god!
How much is the ticket for the elephant?
I-I don't have an elephant ticket.
Then I'll take it for free.
It's free!
What?
You're too fat to eat!
If you don't pass, we'll have to say goodbye here!
If you're upset, try jumping!
The elephant's still hungry.
She'll be coming again...
Wait, mister!
The business round trip is coming up soon.
Hurry up, the train is coming!
The person who gets off first.
Excuse me, can I have a second?
Damn it! What the hell!
He's not coming at all!
What's with that old man?
He's just saying what he wants!
This is the last 1000 yen.
If I get this off, I can go back home walking to Kameyari.
If I get 47, it's 20 times as much.
But there's also the 36 line.
The person in the back is waiting.
Please line up after you get it.
The 6th race will start soon.
We'll aim for the 2nd and hope for the next race.
It's the 2nd.
It's the 1st.
No, it's the 2nd!
The next one.
No, it's not!
3738.
100 yen.
The garbage truck and the mountain.
I've never heard of it.
What?
They're both signposts of salvation!
How dare you make me drive a car like this!
You pervert!
You bastard!
What?
Huh?
He won.
What?
You...
You will be the bell!
Here you go, Mr. Bell.
Here, it's a new car.
I'm sorry, you were a wonderful elephant.
Okay, I'll treat you to anything thanks to this Manba sword.
Where did Ryo-chan go with the elephant?
Yes, this is the Kameari Park.
He saw the elephant!
I feel like I can be a good friend with you for a long time.
It's cold!
You're a good boy!
This guy, this guy, this guy!
You look cute when you look at me.
You're a good boy!
Tantan!
Tantan?
Ryo!
Captain!
What's the plan to take the elephant to the city?
I got a call from the dispatch office that a search request was coming from the zoo.
But Ryo-chan is missing.
Anyway, I'm glad the elephant and the senior are safe.
Thank you for your help.
I heard that Tonto's mother passed away yesterday.
What?
The zoo is full of mothers.
I completely forgot about Tonto.
He was lonely and left the cage.
Tonto helped me a lot.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about you!
Hey!
What's wrong with my elephant?
No, no, no!
Ryo!
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Let go of me.
Don't worry, he's alright.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
Captain, he doesn't like it.
I'll take care of him.
You idiot!
Nakagawa!
Come here.
Yes, sir.
Let go of me!
Senior!
Nakagawa, don't ever talk to me.
You are in danger.
What's going on?
But, sir...
Yes, sir.
I need you to help me out, Captain!
All right, I got it!
Stop it, let go!
You won't be able to win now!
Tonto's mine!
Y-You're so kind...
I'm sure I won't forget this when I get back to the zoo, Tonto.
Tonto! Wait for me, Tonto!
Wait! Tonto!
Senpai...
Ryo, you're so kind even when you look like that.
Tonto!
Tonto! Tell me! What's the next Tendo Show?!
I just want him to win in the zoo with me.
Tonto!
If Tendo Show doesn't work, I'll lose!
No, I mean, what's the next Derby?!
Tonto!
Did you fall in love with Megumi-chan, the lunch box lover?
Good job, Honda!
You'll get her for sure on the 102nd show.
I'm a nice middle guy with a lot of experience.
I'll teach you the points of dating.
Next time on "Run, Honda! For Love!"
Don't miss it!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Outside the door, the sun is calling