♪ When watching TV ♩
♪ Make the room brighter and try to get away ♩
♪ Like someone calling ♩
♪ After the rain ♩
♪ Walking, looking back ♩
♪ I felt the дивings here ♩
♪ I felt the divings here ♩
♪ That's why I'd tried to walk in the black dike ♩
♪ Everyone was a child in a "sou royal palace" ♩
I was a kid once, but everyone has forgotten
Politicians who have a great face
And a blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
You can see everyone
There is a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Make money with anime
Oh, I'm excited!
My Robodeca is in the lead!
Senpai's manga is still being serialized?
Who reads this kind of thing?
Well, you can understand my manga's wonderfulness
Ryoji's husband is in trouble!
What?
The TV anime is decided?
Yes, Ryusei-san from the weekly survival magazine said
Oh, I did it!
Finally, this day has come!
Is the anime so great?
Of course!
I'm not a child!
The TV has 10% of viewers
About 10 million people
20% of viewers are 20 million people
The popularity is increasing by a lot
Then, of course, the original comic book will also be sold
Sold, sold, sold
Related products are also released one after another
And this will also be sold more and more
The popularity of the original author is also rising
The TV and the public will be pulled together!
With their pay and appearance fee,
I can get a lot of money!
Hello
Nana-chan
I just heard from Honda-san
Congratulations, Nana-chan
Congratulations
Yes, thank you
Hey, what's so happy?
Eh?
Because it will be animated, right?
Nana-chan's menu
Eh?
Isn't it my Robodeca monitor?
I don't like it, senpai
You didn't even say a word
The reason for the animation is
Nana-chan's pen name "Ai no Miko"
This menu
No way!
Makoto-kun, Ai-chan
This is a repetition
I don't know what's interesting
Senpai, I'm sorry to Nana-chan
That's right
It's terrible
It's not interesting if it's not interesting
I don't know how to make this into an animation
If I make it into an animation, I'll make this Robodeca monitor first
What are you saying?
Menuet is 100 million times more interesting than Ryo-chan's manga
What?
Where is this manga?
First of all, the picture is more beautiful than Ryo-chan's
Eh?
Besides, the story is interesting
No matter what you say, a girl's subtle psychological description is good, isn't it?
I don't need such a thing
But, what is necessary for an animated work is impact and power
And...
It's a man's romance
"Weekly Sapphire" is a magazine read by a girl
You don't need a man's romance
It's strange that Senpai's manga is serialized
It seems that it's going to be noisy if it's cut off
Shut up! What do you know about the amateur?
Most readers are amateurs
My manga is a masterpiece that will remain in the future
It's not like a manga like Menuet
My manga was seen like that by men
That's not true
Even a man's me is very interesting
Nana-chan, this is the story of a manga artist that will never be animated, so don't worry
That's right, Nana-chan
Is that so?
Oh, no, I have to go now
Is it already that time?
What? Are you going somewhere?
I'm interviewing for a film
The first episode of the anime "Menuet" will be filmed today
I'm going to have a special visit
What? Take me with you
As a colleague's writer, I have a duty to see what kind of anime it will be
"Menuet" is a signboard work of "Weekly Sapphire"
You were making a lot of trouble until a while ago
Oh, this is the recording studio
A recording studio, huh?
Huh?
What are these guys?
Good morning
They are the fans of the voice actor
It's very popular to be chasing after them
Um, here is the "Weekly Sapphire" Ryu-senshi
Hi, Miko
Everyone, I'm Miko Ai, the original author of "Menuet"
Good morning
Miko, come here
Excuse me
Hey, Ryu-senshi, I'm here
Ryo-san
Why are you here?
Hey, if "Menuet" is going to be made into an anime,
Of course, my "Robo-Deka" is going to be made into an anime
Of course, it is
Think about it
If not, you should go to sell it
Don't be so rude
Stop it, you should give up
Makoto-kun
What? What's with this voice?
Mika, wait a moment
Makoto-kun!
You are the famous voice actor, Hanazono Sachi-san, right?
Yes, I also imagined it, so I gave you one vote when I auditioned
It's perfect for the voice of love
I'm so happy
No way, you are not an anime otaku
The first half of the pre-recording is over, so let's go inside
Miko, let's take a picture with the voice actor
Yes
This is the "Weekly Sapphire" interview
Everyone, please take care of me
Thank you
I'm the voice of Hanazono, who plays the role of Ai, and Kanzaki, who plays the role of Makoto
Nice to meet you, I'm Miko, who plays the role of Ai
Wow, Kanzaki is a great actor
And also, I'm the voice of Megumi Kihara, who plays the role of Kobori, and Sasa Shigeru, who plays the role of Tange
I'm so happy
Finally, you are coming out, Honda
Miko, the director told me that you should try to say the line "To the girl"
What?
Your voice is very unique
If you can do that with the gravure, I'm sure the fans will be happy
Is that really okay?
Yes, please
I'm so happy
I've always admired you
No way, I can't believe you're joining us
I'm usually the voice of anime, so it's just like that
I'm so happy to be able to shoot a video with a DVD
You're always so happy
Makoto
Ai
They were two people who were swayed by the feeling of love
Wonderful
It's really a wonderful work
Thank you, director
I'll be in your care from now on
Thank you
That editor is so exaggerated
What?
What's wrong, Honda?
It's really good
The atmosphere of the original work is perfectly reproduced
It's the best masterpiece of the girl's anime
Really?
It's amazing
My manga became such a wonderful anime
You can travel to Europe with peace of mind
Yes
Europe?
The second part of Menuet will be set in Europe
It's a travel for that purpose
With the help of Ryusenshi and the assistants,
I'm planning to travel to Europe with the help of the assistants
I see
I haven't seen you in a while
It's been 5 years
Then let's get ready to go
Hmm?
I think they are
Do you know each other?
Yes, he is the father of the stone-stone toy that made my one-in-one figure
Hey
Mr. Ryotsu
What's wrong? You look so gloomy
Why?
That's because...
It's not in the show
What?
My toy isn't in the show
Not even one part of it
Oh, your company is also a sponsor of this show
Yes
So I asked them to make a character goods and put it on the show
They didn't listen to me at all
So what kind of toy did you make?
It's this
It's the transformation tambourine set of love
Hey, you!
Menuet is a pure love
and the main character, Kisaragi Ai, is a normal high school girl
Why do you have to transform?
Actually, I'm thinking of a transformation pose
You...
Yes
Tou!
Paranri Parenra!
Baterenren!
Kuru Kuru Miracle!
Lovely Change!
I wanted to use this for the main character, Kisaragi Ai
It can't be used!
But it's not in the show
Ryoichi, can you convince the staff to make it into an anime?
Don't be so rude
If you can do something, I'll give you a good reward
Reward?
Well, I'm a writer who has a series called "Weekly Sapphire"
I can talk to you
Really?
In return, I'll give you a 50% profit as a royalty
50%?
That's a fine
If you don't want it, it's fine
I'm the only one who can convince Miko Ai and the staff
What should we do?
There's no other choice but to accept it
It's a necessary expense considering the cost of advertising
I understand, Ryoichi
Thank you for your cooperation
Leave everything to me
While Ryusenshi and Nana are in Europe
I think we can make a profit
Huh?
You're the agent for Ai?
Yes, I want to meet the staff of the anime
Thank you for waiting
I'm the director's wife
Actually...
I'm producer Matsuyama
I'm series director Yamagishi
I'm the director of the series
I'm the director of the games
I'm the manager of the family
It's Shibayama
I'm the director of the movies
I'm Kiyokawa
I'm the director of the film
I'm we're...
Hey!
Why are there so many directors?
Who's in charge?
Well, I'm the primary director
Then, other directors don't have names
In the case of anime, theaina is a dreamer
There are 47 people in charge of the main party.
Are you guys a middle school?
Leave the main party 5 or 6 people, and then you can go home.
Actually, today we came to tell you the hope of the original author.
You want me to put on that tambourine?
That's right!
With this tambourine, the main character Kisaragi Ai will transform.
You see, this is the transformation pose.
Transform? To what?
I've been told to do it as the original, but this is the first time I've received such a complaint from the original author.
The teacher hopes for originality as an anime.
However, if you put on something like that, the world view of the original will be destroyed.
That's not true.
It's the only way to show off your skills as an anime professional.
If you don't put it on, the anime will be canceled immediately.
Oh, that's a problem.
The production is already in progress.
From the second episode, Kisaragi Ai will transform with a transformation tambourine set.
This will be decided.
Good?
Oh, oh.
This tambourine... I know it!
I think it's like this...
Paranni, paranna, batteletti!
Zubuzubu, zubuzubu, dazzling change!
This is...
What is this...
Kisaragi Ai has transformed!
Into a beautiful warrior!
Oh, I just finished watching the second episode!
Thank you for your request.
Thank you very much.
Our teacher has decided to write the book which was decided by our teacher.
By Mr. Sheik, the teacher of the class.
Hmm, hmm...
So today.
I brought something like this today.
Hm?
It's a puffy toyoppy!
I thought I could use it in the program.
Oh.
The rules are as usual.
Hmm. Leave everything to me.
Thank you very much!
Um...
I heard that there is a representative of Aino-sensei here.
Me?
Are you Mr. Ryochi?
Nice to meet you, I'm something like this.
I thought that we could use our products in the menu.
In other words, you want to be a sponsor?
All right! I'll take care of it!
Ehh?
You want to get the mascot from the next number?
That's right!
The happy companions of Kisaragi Ai, Puppi and Yappi!
Even if it's the original teacher's wish...
The content has already been uploaded and we are working on the drawing.
It's okay.
Cut 282.
If you add 3 cuts from 32, it will be something.
No way!
Besides, there is no chance of it coming out.
Oh, that's right!
I forgot to say that.
Actually, there will be a new sponsor this time.
This is it!
Oh!
Ochazuke!
Ah!
Ugh!
No!
I can't win like this!
I'm not going!
It's over!
Puppi and Yappi!
I brought the Ochazuke of love!
Eat this and you'll be more powerful!
Yeah.
I got it!
Puppi and Yappi!
It's full of vitamin, mineral and calcium!
Eat Ochazuke and get more power!
Eat the Ochazuke of love and you'll be 3 times stronger!
Wow!
So good!
Senpai!
The mayonnaise in the anime is a bit weird.
The love suddenly changes...
There are no original characters in the original film.
I knew it.
It seems that my fear has finally come true.
Fear?
I use all means to increase the viewing rate of TV.
I don't think it's bad enough to make a character that is not in the original film.
What should I say to Nana-chan on a trip?
I'm the lawyer, Ryo-san.
It's me.
I'll talk about it.
Please be quiet.
He may be in shock and fall.
I'll tell you the story here.
No, no, no, no.
I have to make the product more effective.
I can't stand it anymore.
Subliminal.
But Menuet is a devil.
He's a lover.
I can't be in love with Makoto anymore.
That's right.
I have the same idea.
So, Makoto will be brainwashed by the enemy and will fight Ai.
With this giant robot.
What?
Editor-in-chief, I'm back.
Thank you.
Where is Miko Ai?
She will stay in Europe for a while.
I have a lot of fan letters for Miko.
What is this?
Editor-in-chief!
Have you seen the MENUET of the anime recently?
No. I was busy with something.
I wonder if something happened.
There are a lot of complaints.
What?
A white box has been sent for next week's broadcast.
Let's check it!
However, as long as you see episode 1, it's faithful to the original.
A result of a Sudden Death, Ai is killed.
Aoki Gahara is buried in blood.
What is this?
What's going on?
A.I. Kisaragi, this is the end.
Ryu-senshu, I think this is a different anime video.
But now, I think A.I. Kisaragi and...
Makoto-kun, why? Why?
After all, we were destined not to be connected.
Oh, what was that line?
It's the line from the original comic book, volume 4, page 22.
Then, this is Menuet after all!
Yes!
Sisters, how did you get here?
If there's a Menuet disaster on this Miyamura bicycle,
no matter how bad the road is, it'll be a disaster.
Tootie and Yankie are here too!
A.I. and Tootie too!
A.I. I've brought you the new sake of A.I.
Only this is enough to give you 10x more power!
Thank you, Tootie, Yankie, Tootie!
The flavor of the sake is the best!
Now we're up to speed!
Yes, I'll transform into two!
Got it.
Channel K!
Transform into two!
Menuet Super RS!
Spark!
All five of us!
Super RS Challenge!
The new Spark version!
Our costumes are on sale at the department store children's clothing store!
Buy the figures too!
Menuet machine!
Let's go, everyone!
OK!
Excellent formation!
Jump! Jump!
Menuet Robo!
On sale now!
Price 10,980 yen!
My mecha will be on sale soon!
Makoto...
Even so...
Even so, I love you!
I'll always...
I'll always be waiting for you!
This is no longer Menuet!
Please, please...
I'll be right out!
Damn!
The editing team...
They killed the bullet!
What do you mean, Mr. Ryotsu?
We made it as you said!
Why are you doing this to me?
This time frame...
The next anime is not decided!
Shut up!
Don't worry!
I'll prepare the next work!
Just like Menuet...
It's a super popular manga serialized in the weekly Sapphire!
From next week...
We'll broadcast this!
That manga is...
Of course!
"Robo-Deka Bancho"!
It's a great picture!
I animated my own touch.
"Robo-Deka Bancho"
Robo-Deka Banchi!
What's that voice?
Gahaha!
Surprised!
I'm singing the theme song!
By the way, I'm the voice of the lead.
Eh?
But...
I didn't expect your manga to be animated.
What happened to Menuet?
He was fired from the editorial department.
What?
It's okay, it's okay.
He's not the real Menuet.
Even though he said that, he bought related products.
It's a sad difference.
After all, an anime like Menuet is not unique.
It was destined to be fired.
Well, look at my unique "Robo-Deka Bancho"!
Go!
Robo-Deka!
It is indeed a unique anime.
Isn't it too unique?
That's right, that's right!
The center of the anime world this year is Robo-Deka Bancho!
It certainly became a hot topic.
The viewing rate is too low to measure.
It updated the shortest record in just a week.
Product sales: zero.
Popularity survey: zero.
All minimum records: updated.
Hey, Mr. Ryo.
What's wrong with you guys?
What's going on?
When Robo-Deka Bancho was starting,
you had a contract to give 50% of the profit, right?
Th-that's true.
Robo-Deka Bancho's product was a large amount of red paper.
We're here to collect 50% of the red paper.
You're all stupid!
That's what we were talking about!
If this is the case, you're also stupid!
You're not an idiot.
We're here to collect 50% of the red paper.
We're here to make you pay!
Come on!
Hey, wait!
We're fed up with the anime!
Anime is all about the hard work!
Robodeca-Bancho!
♪ Robodeca-Punch for the bad guys ♩
♪ Fly them to the ends of the galaxy ♩
♪ Fly them ♩
♪ Robodeca-Kick for the bad guys ♩
♪ Disappear with the jade of the Pacific ♩
♪ BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BANCHO! ♩
♪ BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BANCHO! ♩
♪ I came along with the storm ♩
♪ This is Robodeca-Bancho! ♩
♪ BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BANCHO! ♩
♪ BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BANCHO! ♩
♪ I came along with the storm ♩
♪ This is Robodeca-Bancho! ♩
"The Dream of the Big Sky"
When I was a boy, everyone dreamed of the big sky.
The friendship that a model airplane made.
Don't give up!
If you think you will win, you will win for sure!
Next time, "The Wings of Friendship".
Thank you for watching!