Last
Day
of the
"When
you watch
TV,
please
room
brighter
and
look
away."
"Come
to
you
money."
"I
don't
have
money
but
I
worry."
"Look
at
the
blue
sky
and
the
white
clouds."
"I
wonder
what
will
meantime."
"I
know
have
money
I
worry."
"I
don't
but
worry."
"I
don't
but
I
worry."
"Fight
with
me
."
"Fight
me."
"If
I
could
den
better
thinking
tomorrow
do
well ?
Ryo, who always rests on his own, is giving us a vacation.
Senpai, what's going on?
I don't care.
I'm curious.
Today is March 2nd. So tomorrow is March 3rd.
Oh, the Hina Festival.
I see. The peach festival.
But I feel like there was something other than the Hina Festival on March 3rd.
Oh, that reminds me.
That's right.
March 3rd was Ryo's birthday.
Oh, I see.
You were born on the day of the girl, Ryo.
It would have been great if you were a girl.
Don't say things that people care about.
Sorry.
Come to think of it, Senpai.
Something bad didn't happen on your birthday on March 3rd, did it?
Yes, that's right.
On March 3rd, four years ago, I went to the Hina Doll's security on the 500 million yen.
I went to the Hina Doll's security on the 500 million yen.
And I was the third one.
Two years ago, they put a flyover in the big dump during a patrol, didn't they?
Last year, there was a gas explosion accident at the gas station in the last year.
Not only that.
After he was born, he always sees a terrible person on March 3rd every year.
But what does it have to do with taking an emergency leave?
Since I became a police officer, I've been faced with terrible things at work.
If you stay at home, there's a lower probability that you'll meet a bad person.
There's nothing good about staying at home.
That's right, senpai. You have to meet a bad person.
Is that so?
Then...
It can't be helped.
Anyway, no matter what big event happens tomorrow, don't leave the house.
Tell the chief that too.
I will.
What? Ryo-san is off today?
I'm sending him a message that he's on leave.
Oh, I see. But I'm in trouble.
Chief, what's wrong?
Nothing serious, but Ryo-san is busy.
Ryo-san said he'd be at home all day today.
If he's busy, why don't you ask him directly?
Oh, that's right. Let's do that.
Do you have any AV devices or computers that you don't need?
You don't have to move your AV device.
Here is the...
Shut up! You can't sleep with this!
I'm gonna complain!
Do you have any AV devices or computers that you don't need?
Come to think of it, it's similar to what happened on March 3rd 10 years ago.
The speaker in the kirigami hall was too loud, so I had to complain.
But when I went to the hospital, there was a guy who threw cigarettes away, and it was almost completely burned out.
It's dangerous! It's dangerous!
I decided not to go outside for a day today!
I'll sleep quietly.
You don't have to move your AV device.
This is a car from Tokyo.
Recently, there have been damage to the ax.
The person who went out is a professional who is now the 2nd best in Kyushu.
It was discovered by a camera man!
The first master of the Yoka Nisei, Sakurajima-dono-ponkichi will be the champion!
Everyone, don't miss it!
You can't sleep!
All right, let's play a game.
Hey, it's me, Ohara.
Are you still sleeping, Ryotsu?
The fact that the chief came here must be a big deal.
But I don't remember anything that made the chief angry recently.
Ryotsu!
I know what you're talking about.
Hurry up and open it!
He's pretty angry.
What the hell did I do?
Oh, by the way, it's March 3rd, 5 years ago.
He misunderstood the mistake of the monk as my mistake.
He miscalculated the mistake of the monk as my mistake.
He pulled the tire and made me run around the city.
There's no way he will this time.
Is the key on?
I will get in.
I'm not joking.
It was an unrecognizable thing that made me scolded...
Ryotsu!
There's no one here, huh?
Oh, no.
I'm going to stay out here for a while.
I got a little worried out there.
It was March 3rd, 3 years old at high school.
I came out in the announcements.
I was drinking milk in my underwear.
The editor who was in the neighborhood was mistaken, and the police chased him.
I had committed about 20 murders before.
This outfit is not good.
I'll borrow it.
This is Ryo's aunt's clothes.
I can't help it. I'll go to the library in this outfit and borrow clothes from Sakonji.
Sakonji
I found you.
Sakon...
I visited Sakonji on March 3rd, 4 years ago.
Sakonji was in invincible mode.
I'm going to kill you.
Cobra Twist!
Cobra!
Space Triangle!
I've been beaten up.
I'll wait until the practice is over.
Huh?
It's so clean today.
I'll wait until Sakonji's practice is over.
Where is it?
That's right.
Today's practice was hard.
If you keep waking me up, you won't get across with the criminal.
It's hot!
Huh?
That's someone.
I think it's the cleaning lady.
It looks like he's sleeping, so let's leave him alone.
Okay.
He's sweating.
Me too.
This is...
But why are Komachi and the others in the boys' room?
Come to think of it, they came here on March 3rd.
They happened to fall down the stairs...
They got a letter from the police officer.
I saw that.
They're all wet.
If they see us in this outfit, they won't let us go.
We have to run away as soon as possible.
Take a shower first.
Okay.
Hey, lady.
It looks like the drain is full. Can I have a look?
I'm a bit tired...
You were taking a nap. You'll be fine soon.
Stop it.
It's a man!
No!
Where did the man go?
Komachi?
What?
Damn it.
I can't wear this outfit anymore.
Sorry, lady.
What?
Lucky, I have something to change.
This is nice.
I like this one.
Is it someone from the Wanderers?
Oh, speaking of Wanderers...
That was March 3rd, when I was in the first year of high school.
I was walking around the town with Kawajan,
who was a friend of my older brother's senior.
I was involved in a fight between the Wanderers,
and I was arrested together.
I've been arrested.
If I wear this, I'm sure I'll be in trouble.
This is the most reasonable way.
If this is the case, I won't be arrested by mistake.
If you run away this far, you'll be fine.
Why is this a tunnel?
But the Wanderer is a member of the Wanderers.
After all, March 3rd is a good thing.
Hey, what are you doing?
What am I doing?
It's a special training for newcomers.
I'm doing a marathon to the Edo River.
Didn't you explain it to me first?
It's a special training for newcomers?
Oh, this is...
The 99th Mobile Unit of the Demon.
It's a high-quality training and an iron record.
99th Mobile Unit of the Demon.
But there are many members of the Demon that are losing their jobs regardless of their training.
Stop joking around!
Can I go with them?
Hey, newbie!
Hey!
It's you!
What?
What's this?
Don't run away!
I'll kill you!
What's wrong with you!
Damn it!
You're a man who can't escape the training of a newcomer.
I'm not a mobile unit member.
What are you talking about?
Everyone thinks you're 100% a mobile unit member.
Or what?
Are you a mobile unit comedian?
You're not a mobile unit otaku of a cosplayer, are you?
I'm a retired police officer.
But I didn't become a policeman to join the mobile unit.
Most of the people who are assigned here are like that.
But...
From today, you're a member of the 99th Mobile Unit!
Do you think that kind of cry will work?
Don't say anything.
Go back to the line quickly.
No.
No matter what I say, it doesn't seem to work.
If this happens, I'll steal his eyes and run away.
By the way, I'm still a policeman.
I was in elementary school on March 3rd.
I happened to be watching the training of another class.
The instructor misunderstood that I was in the same class.
I was forced to participate in the training.
When I tried to escape, I was forced to run five times as fast as the other people.
I was taken to Hakkodasa, where there was still snow.
I was even sent to the private school.
I was even sent to the public school.
Tomorrow, I'll be able to solve the misunderstanding.
If I work hard today, I'll be able to do it.
It's better than fighting against the enemy and being in a terrible situation.
Left there!
Let's run only in front of the station.
Why do they let us run like this?
We're the "Movement Corps" who protects the safety of Shuto.
The criminals often run into this kind of place!
Do you understand?
I understand.
Don't move.
Fine!
If you lose, you all have to start over!
Damn, I can't help it!
You're taking a break, huh?!
From here, swim and return to the other side!
Everyone, swim with a 20kg backpack and a metal board!
That's so crazy!
What if the culprit is good at swimming?!
What are you going to do?!
If you don't train with this much of a handicap, it won't be a match!
I understand!
Are you ready?
All right! Jump in!
All right!
Jump in!
Hey, we'll finish this kind of training quickly and go back to the dorm!
What are you doing, you idiots?!
You think you understand?!
If you fall down even by yourself, you'll have to start over from the beginning!
Hurry up and swim!
Nobody's following us!
Wait, wait, wait!
Get me!
You're next!
He's pretty good.
Now, let's start the next training.
You have to stretch your body to stop the enemy coming towards you.
Your opponent is that thing!
Stop the car!
Come on!
You don't understand!
The criminals often run away using their cars!
What are you going to do if you can't do that?!
I can't do it normally!
You think you know?!
If you fail, you'll have to start over!
All right!
Start!
You idiot!
You'll have to stretch your body to stop the enemy coming towards you!
Stop the car!
You idiot!
Okay!
Dama! Dama!
Dama!
Next is that!
What!?
Next!
Okay, I'll stop the engine now!
Rieee!
What's going on?
It's a big one!
Even the 99th Mobile Task Force of the Oni is not that big.
Hey, what's your name?
Ryo-tsu Kankishi.
Ryo-tsu, huh? Okay, I'll remember that.
Captain!
Let's go!
It's a big one!
It seems that the man who is a bomb maniac is hiding in the office building.
Okay, I got it.
No more training!
The new crew members will go back to the dormitory and wait!
Good, good.
Finally, they're free.
However!
Ryo-tsu!
You come with us and join the main force!
Huh? Me?
Follow me without saying anything!
Don't come!
If you get any closer, I'll kill you!
Calm down!
What is your request?
I'm telling you not to come!
This bomb can easily blow up one or two of these buildings!
It seems that he's very excited.
Captain, the 99th Mobile Task Force is heading this way.
Yes, that 99th Mobile Task Force of the Oni.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah, that's...
The 99th Mobile Task Force, protecting the safety of the capital, is here!
What's going on?
Why are you guys here?
Thank you for your hard work.
From now on, leave it to my 99th Mobile Task Force.
Even the director is here.
We should keep our distance as much as possible.
Then, I'll give you a plan.
The first unit will try to enter from the front.
However, this is a trap.
The second unit I command will enter from the back entrance.
Secure the culprit.
The rest will wait here.
I'm...
Wait!
Guard the first-class police force.
Wait?
If you keep wandering around like this, the chief and Komachi will find you.
Damn it.
Captain, let me join the invasion force too!
What?
I joined the invasion force not to wait for the rear.
I'm here to protect the capital by myself.
I want to work in the front line!
Ryo-tsu...
You...
You!
Put it on my back!
Yes, sir!
Thank you!
It looks like they're finally going to do it.
Yeah.
The second unit arrived at the back entrance.
The first unit starts the invasion operation.
Enter!
Don't come!
Can't you die, you idiot?
I'm serious!
Damn it!
It's a trap!
You're going to win a big bomb!
You're not going to believe that kind of drama!
I'll kill you!
The culprit is ready!
Yay!
That's our 99th mobile force!
Hey, Tadei!
Get out of here!
That's right.
In this situation.
There was a locker room in a nice place.
I borrowed the other clothes.
I'll say goodbye here.
It's a dimensional bomb!
Did he really set it up?
And there are only three minutes left.
If this happens, I have to cut the cord and stop it!
I'll cut it!
So which one?
Red or blue?
Red!
Wait.
By the way, on March 3rd, I was in the sixth grade of elementary school.
My father asked me which candy I liked, red or blue.
When I ate red, it was extremely spicy candy.
After that, my mouth was so swollen that I couldn't eat anything.
Okay, this time it's blue!
It's getting faster!
What should I do?
I have to get out of here.
That's it!
I wonder if it's safe to come this far.
.
It's time to make a move.
There were other bombs?
But who did it?
Where's Ryotsu?
Well...
Captain!
In the first place, Ryotsu wasn't assigned to my squad.
What?
Ryotsu wasn't assigned to my squad.
Then who is he?
Ryotsu's clothes were in the other room.
Everyone was watching the entrance.
But no one went outside.
He disappeared like smoke.
Ryotsu...
Maybe he was a man God made use of to solve the case.
No one would believe this.
But I'll keep it in my heart.
I'm home.
Thank you for your hard work.
By the way, Reiko.
Did you get in touch with Ryotsu?
No, not yet.
I see.
Since Daisuke made a birthday present for Ryotsu, I thought I'd give it to you.
So cute!
Ryo, he's not at home.
Where did he go?
Isn't he playing some online games?
He must have to go back and forth everywhere.
I'm sure he's not in a hurry.
I think so.
Now it's time to go back.
Suddenly I think about her.
Well then, Ryotsu.
It's this!
Oh, I got it!
Congratulations!
I'll make you happy!
I got it!
Make this a present.
Thank you so much.
Isn't it pretty?
"The End of the World"
Let's go!
Thank you!
Kanda Hijiribashi has hidden Matoi's memories
Matoi was still a high school student, but on rainy days and snowy days, he waited for her on the bridge
Next time, "Hijiribashi Hakusen Nagashi"
By the way, my turn
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!