Translated by 方 Hou.
I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river.
When I kick the stone, it'll fly to my shoes.
I wonder if it's worth it to save money.
I laughed at it as it was.
I don't care how I feel.
Even if I lose my temper, I'm just a little bit of a mess.
The cityscape that doesn't change even a single grumbling is weirdly gentle.
I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river. I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river. I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river.
I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river. I'm looking at the sunset floating in the river.
From the stream of the Tungari-boshi,
I'm going to Taishakuten.
The sunset is falling.
Tomorrow will end like this.
I realized that I was not happy with the Katsushika and Shibamata.
Because I'm an idiot.
Honda's Last Kiss
Happy Birthday to You
Happy Birthday Dear Honda-chan
Happy Birthday To You
You don't have to cry.
It's embarrassing to see you so moved.
Your birthday is the 183th anniversary of our relationship.
Well, it's not impossible.
Mr. Honda, I feel sorry for you.
Who was the woman this time?
The lady from the convenience store.
It's about this morning.
You're late in one minute.
Mr. Honda, hurry up!
I understand.
I'm going to see Mr. Honda.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
Can I get one of these?
Don't worry, Midori.
Love rings are common sense.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I can't believe you're...
Midori, you idiot!
Mr. Honda, I really feel sorry for you.
You're so nice.
Why do I get dumped so much?
It's to get into the Guinness World Records!
No way!
Hey!
I can't.
It's okay.
I don't care what happens.
Senpai, stop joking around.
I'm not joking.
Mr. Honda, this is a birthday gift from Kei and I.
Please cheer up.
Okay?
It's a new model.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're happy, Reiko.
Yeah.
Let's blow out the "dating" thing.
Dating?
Dating...
You idiot!
I almost forgot about it!
I'm sorry, Mr. Honda.
What I wanted to say was that I want you to find a new girlfriend.
Okay.
That's right.
There are so many women out there.
If you wear this and talk to them, you'll be Midori.
Midori?
Midori.
Hey, you idiot!
Your new girlfriend is called Midori.
U-Um...
Mr. Ryo, what is this gift from all of us?
Oh, right.
We don't have as much money as you, so this won't be a big deal.
Is this a geisha card?
Our wish was for you to have a good girlfriend like this.
It sounds good.
I can see you're disappointed.
I know.
Senpai, Maria-san, thank you so much.
I'll put it on my bike and my helmet.
Thank goodness.
Ryo-sama, it was worth praying to God for us.
Yeah.
I also prayed to God that we could become lovers.
Love, love.
Honda, don't be depressed.
I'm the one who wants to be depressed.
Maria is a man.
I don't care if she's a man.
I want a cute girlfriend like Maria.
Look at yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'll introduce you to someone who will suit you.
I'll find a cute girl from Nakagawa Group.
Really?
Yes.
Please.
I'm coming, boss.
Honda!
You're so mean!
Ryo-chan, you're in a good mood.
Shut up.
You're like cloking on a person.
If you change your life when you're not on the bike, even your lover can be happy.
Change my life?
Look at this apartment.
This, that, and that.
Are these men's apartments?
They do look like girls' apartments.
It's like a horror.
The books lined up in bookshelves are all girl's manga.
I don't think they're afraid of the devil's bookshelf.
Right? So first of all...
What are you doing, senpai?
Everyone throws things like this away.
Please stop.
My treasure, Aino Miko sensei's...
Shut up. If you say you're going to throw it away, throw it away.
Stop it!
I'm so glad.
Honda!
You did it, Honda!
No, senpai, it's a misunderstanding.
I won't listen to excuses.
Hey, Ryo!
The cake! The cake!
Ryo!
The birthday party was ruined.
I'm sorry, Ryo.
I said something unnecessary.
Don't apologize, Maria.
It's Ryo's fault.
Shut up!
You two are so mean!
Senpai, I'm sorry about yesterday.
You!
Father!
Honda, I got a list of the most suspicious people in the prefecture.
Do you want to see it?
No, I'm fine.
Honda, maybe your favorite girl...
No, I don't want to.
She's so sharp.
What a mess!
Have you already recovered?
I told you, right?
She gets depressed but recovers faster.
Now, where's the big sister?
I live near the prefectural university.
A super cute new member came into the fourth mobile unit.
Is it a new member, Olive?
Do you know her?
Olive?
She's only 35 kg.
It's as thin as a tree, and everyone calls it "Olive".
Olive, huh?
Yes.
All right, let's go!
Hey, Senpai!
You have to confess your love to Olive-chan.
What? Now?
You should put on a black and white shirt when your wound is shallow.
N-No way!
Ryo-chan is so hardworking.
That's how much he cares about his friends.
I don't want to be crushed!
Come with me, Hoya!
Wait, Senpai!
Olive-chan, my name is Nana Otohime.
You're 21 years old now?
I'm almost 10 years old.
You're so thin. You look like glass.
That's why people call me Olive-chan.
Hey, you!
Are you talking about me?
You're talking so much like an anime voice.
You say that so often. I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I know I'm cute.
But I want to date you.
I've been thinking about the best way to date you.
Oh, Mr. Honda?
Mr. Honda from the school.
You're so handsome, Olive-chan.
But Mr. Honda...
He's the one who yells at you when you're afraid.
Yeah, he is.
You!
Steer the bike!
Do you know what I'm doing?
I'm going to kick your ass!
I'm the one who's doing it.
But your face...
You're usually quiet, but you change when you ride a bike.
Really?
You can't beat me with one punch.
He really is that instructor.
Think of him as Jekyll and Hyde.
I hope you understand.
Yes.
Hey, Olive.
Go out with him.
With the instructor?
Senior, I don't think that's good.
Really?
Olive, are you dating anyone?
Wait a minute...
No, I'm not.
You're perfect.
Go out with Honda.
Senior...
Yes.
Thank you.
Great!
It's a big success!
Senior...
It's not a dream, is it?
Can you give me a hug?
Good!
Good for you, Honda!
I...
I'm so lucky!
Honda Hayato!
Tell me, how many times have I got to tell you this?
I'm not going to let you do what you did to me!
"Honda"
Oh no! It's the Honda of the late era!
What?
That's the Honda of the demon!
Slow down, Hayasu!
Mr. Honda! Chouas!
What are you guys doing?
Huh?
If you're a Housou, you should run faster!
Is that okay?
I'll forgive you.
Now, run, you guys!
This is the time of youth!
Take the wind!
Make love!
Love is good!
Dream Shot!
What's going on?
Isn't it super bad?
Isn't there an earthquake?
What are you doing, Honda?
Oh, Senior.
I was going to throw away the comic...
I see.
So, the power of love has finally changed your life.
As I thought, the love of girls manga is more real than the love of real love.
You're such a fool.
Okay, I'll help you, too.
Ah, that's not good!
Why?
The love of Miko-sensei has been a large fan since the time of Dede,
I want to leave it.
Well, that's enough.
That's the proof that Mr. Honda is doing well with Olive.
You're getting drunk every day.
Nakagawa, let's take a look inside.
Yeah, sure.
Please help me, instructor!
What's wrong? What are you doing here?
The tire got stuck in the groove and it can't move.
Are you a police officer?
I'm sorry.
In this case, use a suspension.
It's dangerous, so take a bike.
Yes, sir.
Sink the front suspension.
Use the handbrake to pull it out.
Yes, sir.
It's out.
If you let go, it'll break.
You're so beautiful, Nakagawa.
Sink the front suspension and pull it out.
You're a good couple, aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Finally, spring has come to Honda.
Turn the steering wheel and turn the steering wheel in the direction.
Yes, sir.
Thank you so much for today, instructor.
Thank you for your hard work.
You've improved a lot, Olive.
I'm sure it's because you're good at teaching me.
I like you when you're on a bike, but I also like you when you're on a bike.
No, it's not that.
Excuse me.
Olive!
Yes, sir.
I wonder if we can go to the movies together next Sunday.
Is it Sunday?
No, I'm fine if you have time, but I don't know.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm sorry to have you invited.
It's okay.
You don't have to worry about it.
See you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not listening to you.
Thank you.
Chico.
I was supposed to see you with Olive.
Be quiet.
I'm sorry.
That's good.
It was pretty good.
Eh?
Senpai, you were asleep the whole time.
That's why it was good.
Ah, I feel refreshed.
This is it.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Ah...
Hey, that's Olive-chan.
No way...
It's common. She's your superior.
There's no superior as cool as her.
Ah, Olive-chan looks so happy.
Well, well, calm down.
It's too early to make a conclusion.
You can think of her as a brother.
She's the only child.
Then, maybe her father.
Don't mess with me.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, senpai.
We went into her house together.
That's common.
You should drink tea.
Common?
A girl...
Senpai, I can't see anything at all.
It's not tea.
Then, let's eat parce de nuit.
No way!
There's no trouble with early lunch.
Okay, okay, Senpai.
Senpai.
Eh?
Ah? What time is it?
It's 4 a.m.
4 a.m.?!
Hahaha!
Thank you.
That was great.
Hehe...
Oh, Ryu-san won't let me sleep.
Hahaha, sorry, sorry.
See you later.
Be careful!
Sen... Senpai...
Is this a common thing?
It's common!
It's no wonder, isn't it?
I did it...
What?
Hey, Honda!
Don't leave me behind!
You're still young!
Shut up!
You're not a woman!
You're not a child!
You don't deserve to be a man!
Shut up!
Get back here!
How dare you..
Shut up!
You!
W-What's wrong?
What's wrong?
You don't look like one of them.
It must be a misunderstanding.
Not like the last time...
That's what I wanted to say!
Fng!
H-Honda!
Pull yourself together!
Senpai...
I can't do this anymore.
I can't get my energy back on the bike.
What are you talking about?
This is just the 184th time you've been dumped!
I'm going to get a serious injury this time.
I can't get better.
Honda-san, you're not completely dumped yet, are you?
That's right. It's still too early to give up.
Ryo-chan, I think it's better to ask him yourself
than to be in a hurry here.
Yeah, that's right.
Alright, let's go!
No, no, no, no, no!
What?
Did you see where he went home this morning?
I'm sorry to interrupt your private life,
but I really want to hear it from him.
Senpai, you're talking too much.
Shut up!
He's...
He's very important to me.
Since when...
Since when did you meet him?
Since I was in junior high school.
What?
Since junior high school?
That's a little too early, isn't it?
It's normal.
Everyone's been doing it since junior high school or high school.
Th-That's too early for a kid like you.
I've been dating three people,
but I can't forget the first one.
Don't make such a cute face.
Have you been with him ever since?
I met him once.
That's right.
Honda...
I don't think I've ever seen a girl like you.
That was brilliant.
Let's have a drink tonight.
Y-Yes...
Thank you for the great memories.
I'm sorry to get you involved.
Goodbye.
What?
That's not...
Please wait!
That's enough!
Stop it! It's not fair to say something so kind!
B-but, I really like you, Honda-san.
Are you trying to get your ass kicked?
Senpai!
What are you talking about?
This is what a woman is!
Ryo, that's enough.
Come on, let's go.
Wait! I'll tell you the truth!
Is there still something you want to say?
I'm sorry.
I'm actually a manga artist!
What?
A manga artist?
Yes. My pen name is Aino Miko.
Aino Miko? I've heard that name somewhere.
A famous girl manga artist!
Oh!
So you're a huge manga fan!
W-well, then...
Olive-chan?
Yes, Honda-san!
Olive-chan!
Are you really Aino-sensei?
I thought you were older!
I've been drawing since I was in junior high school.
W-was that what you were saying earlier?
Yes. I made my professional debut in junior high school.
Then,
I met a first-time manga artist.
I'm a manga artist.
I'm a manga artist who's been in charge of my debut for a long time.
That beautiful man is not your lover, but the editor in charge, isn't he?
Yes. He's always locked in his room during work.
So he takes me to various places to broaden my horizons.
You said you wouldn't let me sleep last night.
That's...
That's because I sent you my name, and the manuscript is about to fall.
I'm sorry.
What's with that?
We seem to have made a big mistake!
I'm so glad, Honda!
But you should have told me from the start!
This is the first time I've ever been to a studio.
If you tell me, you'll be fired.
It's okay! I'll keep it a secret.
Excuse me.
Um, would you like to come to my studio?
W-what?
Go ahead, Honda!
What about the others?
I'm not sure.
We're not that stupid.
Well, we've gone!
I'm so glad, Ryo-sama.
Well, we should go and have a fish-suit.
Let's go! Let's go!
Boss, why can't I get a bonus on Sakonji?
I did give Sakonji anFun
I don't have anything to do with him!
On next episode: "A Doll's Princess"
Please look forward to it!
It's rumored that I'm a woman who can't fall in love
But I have a lot of things I want to do
I want to run across the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be free more than a bird