Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
The Sun
Strike!
What did you say?
Did you say that Levald went to Europe?
He wanted to be the main focus of Paris and London.
He's still a lively old man.
What?
You're a fake brand manager?
You're a terrible businessman.
Japanese people have a strong brand reputation.
But many people don't know anything about it.
Is our rice okay?
The young lady is making the rice, so it's okay.
Lemon is making the rice?
She's making it now.
It's okay.
Niigata Uonuma's Koshihikari.
It's 100%!
Uonuma's Koshihikari is 100%!
That's great! It's real!
Thank you very much!
100%!
We're in the next round.
Yes.
Sasanishiki is 80%.
Akitabijin is 10%.
Echigo-Nishiki is 10%.
What?
Sasanishiki is 80%, Akitabijin is 10%, and Echigo-Nishiki is 10%.
We were mixed up after all!
Will mine be okay?
Let's find out quickly!
He's really being very inquisitive.
I'm making rice.
The rice factory is also in Sotokanda Town.
Don't ask such a thing to a kindergarten student.
Phew. This is the end.
Good work.
Then, next.
I have a summer zhen preparation.
Please enjoy it.
There are many things.
Summer zhen is the main character of our party.
Which one?
Then, this is the breakfast for today.
Eh? There is more?
It's hard.
Ryotsu-san.
Could you deliver a lunch box to Matoi while you go to the library?
Eh? Oh, sorry.
I can't go today because of the schedule.
Ah, no. I'll go.
Hankichi!
The preparation is not finished yet, right?
I'm hungry.
Come on.
Lemon will go to Matoi when he returns from kindergarten.
Really?
Then, I'll leave it to you, Lemon.
Miss, after you finish eating, there will be a meal party for Meiten Ryorikai.
I got it.
Hmm. It's a hard schedule.
Hmm.
Oh, Lemon-chan. You came.
As always, you're cute.
Is Matoi here?
Cute!
Huh?
It's almost lunch time. Let's have lunch together.
Come here, Lemon-chan.
Um.
Sorry, Lemon. I was saved.
Wow, Matoi-chan's lunch box is amazing.
Show me. Show me.
Yeah.
Wow, it looks delicious.
Do you want to eat it?
Huh?
I'm happy, but I'm on a diet.
How about you, Komachi-senpai?
Me too. Sorry.
I have to go on a diet.
Diet is important, right?
Matoi, what is diet?
It's to lose weight and look beautiful.
Hmm. Do you want to lose weight so much?
Recently, men are more likely to lose weight.
I heard that's good for you.
So I only eat this much for lunch.
I eat this much, too.
You're so small.
Matoi, Mikan-chan is here.
Hi.
You must be feeling good.
Good job.
You're so fluffy, Mikan.
You're warm.
You're great.
Hi.
Wow.
You're not warm here.
Oh, dear.
Hey, is that a water bottle?
Hey.
Look!
Look what's here.
Y-You're going to get it right now?
Hmm?
Ms. Cherry, there's another one.
Ah.
Huh?
Ah, no, it's nothing. Good night.
What happened?
He was very depressed.
What? He stopped tasting?
That's sudden. I'm in trouble.
Miss, please.
I don't want to eat anything. I don't want to anymore.
What?
What are you going to do with the taste of today's dish?
Who's going to see it?
Calm down.
It's me, Ita-cho.
Oh, Ita-cho. I see.
How is it, Ita-cho?
It's not like this, is it?
Maybe.
Ita-cho, please be confident.
Is it okay?
Anyway, let's all ask him.
Yes.
How is it?
I don't know.
It's difficult.
You can't give him something weird.
Yes.
It's impossible if it's not Lemon-chan.
Today's dinner is finished.
Can I eat it?
It's not.
It doesn't taste like the flow of Chokanda.
Ita-cho, there's something wrong with Chokanda?
Ah, no, nothing's wrong!
I'm sorry!
I'll do my best!
I'll do it!
What is this?
I'm disappointed.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir. Please wait.
Excuse me. I'm not in a good condition today.
It's not the usual.
The power of lemon's power of listening is amazing.
Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
Matoi!
Where is the lemon? The store is in a panic.
I recognize that the lemon was an important thing.
Matoi, did you find anything?
Even if you say so ...
Oh, that's it.
Do you have any idea?
Maybe I'm worried about getting fat, so I'm on a diet.
Diet?
I heard about Komachi-senpai's diet.
It's not a kindergarten.
But I haven't eaten much in a while, Lemon.
I'm hungry.
Oh, come to think of it ...
Let's eat!
Thank you for the meal.
Is that all?
Then I'll take this too.
He certainly didn't eat.
But he's not the type to go on a diet.
All right, I'll ask him.
What?
What is it?
Not only eating, but also eating breakfast and dinner.
You haven't eaten well, have you?
What are you talking about?
Are you on a diet, Lemon?
I'm not doing that.
Look at your eyes and answer.
I'm full.
Be honest, Lemon.
115 kilograms.
I'll be 165 kilograms by the time I'm 20 years old.
When I grow up, I'll be a sumo wrestler.
No, no!
You're talking about your weight.
You're not counting on getting taller at all.
That's right.
But I don't want to be 165 kilograms!
I'm leaving!
Hey, Lemon!
Lemon!
Everyone...
I'm sorry.
This is for my diet.
Lemon!
I can't eat anymore!
This is bad.
If I keep this up, the Cho Kanda Sushi will collapse,
and I won't be able to work anymore.
You guys, don't panic!
The taste of Cho Kanda Sushi...
is this Ryotsu Kankitsuya!
the taste of Cho Kanda Sushi...
The taste of Cho Kanda Sushi...
is this Ryotsu Kankitsuya!
Listen up,
you know what they call food?
It's dashi!
I just need to slurp it!
This isn't enough!
Bring more!
All right!
What do you think, Ryo-san?
No! We need something!
That's right! Let's add some sauce!
-What? -What?
Sauce in the soup?
In this city, anything with sauce is fine!
This isn't the way the director wants it to be!
I've changed the seasoning a little.
Oh, no!
Kan-kichi!
It's over.
Super Kanda-sushi.
Yes.
It's dangerous in here.
Where are you, Ryo-san?
What's wrong with you?
You're going to get a head ache if you get this in your ear!
That's true.
We couldn't do it because we were so dependent on you.
You can't start reflecting on it now.
To get through this situation,
we have to stop Lemon's diet!
But how?
One more time!
Leave it to me!
Where did this earthquake come from?
Ryo-san, you called me at the right time.
Actually, I'm developing a new diet machine.
Amazing, Lemon!
It's a diet machine!
In the first place, you're gaining too many calories!
Exercise is the best way to lose weight!
First, this!
What's this?
Can't you tell?
It's a running machine.
That's not it!
Why are there lions?
Come on, Lemon.
Try it.
I'm scared!
Kan-kichi, do it for me!
I can't help it.
What?
First, jogging mode.
And then, life-saving mode.
This?
Oh, no, no, no!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're running too hard like this because it's hard to see, so you're forced to lose weight naturally.
You stupid!
How could I let Lemon use this kind of dangerous tool!
Looks like it's going to be a medication, huh?
Let's move on.
What's this time?
Did you not see?
You're kidding me!
Huh?
Eh?
Hm?
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Stop!
-Stop it! -Like this,
-If you burn the fat, you can lose weight in an instant! -Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What are you doing? This is embarrassing!
Now, Lemon-chan, here you go.
I'm not doing anything!
I was stupid to ask Spark to do it!
Then, how about this?
I don't need to explain.
Ignore it and move on to the next plan!
-I'm not doing anything! -I'm not doing anything!
I'm on a diet, after all!
-Diet, diet. -Diet, diet.
Ah, this is...
Senpai, you're the best!
This lobster is the best!
It's even better when you grill the tuna.
You're right! We're grilling super-high-calorie ingredients!
Hey, Lemon, how about we do it together?
-Come on! -Come on!
Come on!
Let's stop dieting and eat together!
Okay!
Lucky, let's stop dieting.
Ouch! What did you say?
The smoke is getting on my eyes, so I came to warn you!
You're so stubborn!
All right, next up is steak with beef shimofuri.
-Aha! -Aha!
How's that, Lemon?
It's my first time eating such a thick steak!
It's so good!
I've never eaten such a thick steak before!
What was it? Did you say it was "amano"?
It's called "amano-iwato".
Lemon!
You're no good!
Kankichi, what are you going to do?
I still have a plan!
Nakagawa!
Yes?
There's an era drama on TV sponsored by the Nakagawa Group, right?
Um, is it "Gin-san in the Underground Mountain"?
Oh...
It's been a long day.
I want to go to Chikayama.
Don't!
Gin-san in the Underground Mountain!
Why are you so skinny?
I just ordered the popular diet, so...
If you have any complaints, this sakura...
Hey, everyone!
Did you find out how uncool the diet is?
Ouch!
Don't make fun of Gin-san!
That's not good, Ryo-san!
What are you going to do?
Then the restaurant will be destroyed before my mother comes back.
Kankichi, do you have any other hands?
No, I don't have any more.
Welcome.
Hello.
Kankichi's grandfather.
Ryo's grandfather?
That means, an old man?
Nice to meet you.
One greeting is not needed.
What are you doing here?
I heard that Kankichi is working part-time.
So I came.
Come in.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Father, mother.
Son, son.
No, it's been a long time.
Please have a seat.
Please sit down.
Kankichi, please have a drink.
What do you drink?
Do you have money?
Just a drink is enough.
For the time being, it's beer.
What do you want me to grab?
I don't know.
I'm fine with Nami's bowl.
What are you doing?
We are relatives.
You're going to give me cheap, aren't you?
Yoroshiku-kun.
Yes, of course.
I read it.
I heard that Gepard is a layman.
What?
Where did he go?
It's like you're drunk.
I wrote it on your face.
I don't know where I heard it,
but this old man is really a hell of a man.
Well, Ryo.
Everyone,
What would you like to eat?
First, Otoro, Uni and abalone.
I'll have that too.
I'll have the same.
Did you come to destroy the restaurant?
This is today's dinner.
It looks delicious.
It's over in a flash.
What?
You guys don't have money, that's enough.
I don't want to eat.
Bring me a chicken.
And Otoro, hurry up.
Yes.
What's this commotion?
The Kankichi's parents and grandfather are here.
They're here.
There was such a good octopus in it.
That's...
Stop it.
Let's eat.
Don't make it a little bit.
Lemon.
It's not a customer who makes food a little bit.
I'm sorry.
It's impossible for such a small child to be careful.
Kankichi, dad.
Clean up properly.
Kankichi, here.
Wait, Lemon.
What, Kankichi?
You're on a diet leaving your breakfast.
It's the same as making food a little bit.
If you say that...
What's wrong with you?
Are you on a diet?
If you do that, you'll become an idiot like him.
You're the idiot.
What?
Lemon.
Matoi, leave this to me.
The boys here don't understand how girls feel.
What's the story?
It was the first time I met Lemon.
I'm the mother of Kankichi.
And I'm the parents' wife, Lemon.
Lemon, could you talk to me for a little while?
When you were a child, your dream was to eat a lot.
You've never eaten?
That's right.
There was a war a long time ago.
Tokyo was also a place of the wild.
It wasn't a time when you were allowed to eat freely.
There was no rice.
I could only eat sweet potatoes or sweet soup.
I even made sweet potatoes in the school yard.
But I was hungry.
So I went to the field with my classmates and ate sweet potatoes.
Did you eat it raw?
Yes. I can't forget that taste.
Lemon-chan is not fat.
She is growing up to become an adult.
Growing up?
Children eat a lot and grow up quickly.
I think everyone is worried.
Everyone?
We are grownups and should eat healthy food regularly.
Your daughter is giving me a feast again?!
I will eat it.
Lemon-chan is coming again.
Sorry.
I eat dinner.
I also lose weight.
Why is food not good?
But dieting is not good.
You have to eat well during growth period.
I think we have passed the growth period.
Dieting is not good.
Welcome.
Eat all the tangerines without leaving any.
Because it is the growth period.
Lemon has changed a lot.
It looks like a noisy old woman.
Ryo, this is it.
1 million yen for the application?
The man told me to give it to Ryo.
What?
I have to go to the gas station today.
Damn it.
I am confused with them.
I will pay for everything.
10 ي.
5 y.
6 y.
10 destroyer.
Tell me.
Please play.
I am not good at this game.
Why?
I'm innocent and poor, isn't that good?
Isn't that right?
I just do what I want to do
Amazing!
Lightning lightning from head to head
крет applause
Kamehameha
Chaito
rice
Thank you
Chuan
It's a place you can sleep
Ka
♪ Mura Koji Mura Koji Baiko Baiko Baiko no Shurinkan ♪
♪ Shurinkan no Kurindai Kurindai no Onpoko ♪
♪ Ki no Onpoko na no Chokyumei no Chosuke ♪
♪ Chief! Are you going to build a house? Then I'll introduce you to a good carpenter! ♪
♪ I'm not good at business, but I'm good at arm! I guarantee it! ♪
♪ I'm not good at business, but I guarantee it! I guarantee it! I guarantee it! I guarantee it! ♪
Next time, "Reform Before After"!
Thanks for watching!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ A turtle, for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!