Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Overcoming the new era lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city in yellow ♪
♪ I wanna dive into paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing all the trendy stuff ♪
♪ I'll be 100 times more handsome ♪
♪ Let it ring! ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Run to the bottom ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the top tomorrow ♪
♪ Let me run! ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if you get a little carried away ♪
♪ It won't hurt ♪
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♪
♪ And make it strong and high ♪
♪ When you come out to the other side ♪
Hey, hey.
Is this really our way?
Yes.
Maybe we can take this path from up this went,
even though we didn't even see a car navigation system yet...
We haven't seen anything from the other side.
How does it look there?
What do you think, Honda?
It's definitely a one-way street.
But, boss, are you really commuting from here?
Yes. The JR, the station, and the bus.
It takes another 20 minutes to walk.
It takes 2 and a half hours to get there.
5 hours to get back?
You're getting a little too far.
By the way, Ryo-chan.
What did you buy for your boss?
This.
It's a secret until we arrive.
What?
We all gave each other money, so you can tell me.
Don't worry.
I chose it specially.
There's no doubt about it.
That's not what I mean.
The people who give presents don't know what they're sending.
That's strange.
That's right.
I'll just say it's the best thing ever.
Boss, you'll be so happy when you see this.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
Wait, when did you enter the apartment?
It should be around the same time now.
What an intensive scene, though.
Hey.
What's happened, boss?
Oh.
Boss.
Senpai!
Um, I'd like to ask you something.
Yes?
Do you know any houses called Ohara?
Ah, that's about 1 km away.
Really? If you don't mind, can you drive me there?
I'll take you there.
But it's just a one-way street. There's no need to worry.
Don't say that. It's just a one-way street.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Get off. He'll take you.
What? What should I do?
You're walking so fast.
Then you don't have to show me around.
Um, I don't want to be on your car.
I'm sorry. Please wait.
Get off.
Senpai.
You can take this car for 5 people.
Shut up, Nakagawa. I don't like narrow cars.
Ryo, you look so pitiful.
Reiko, sit in the front.
Honda!
Don't you think it's wrong to make me wait?
No, no.
Shino, don't get on. Get off.
Here you go.
Why did this happen?
Then,
Let's celebrate your boss's birthday.
That's right.
This is also a piece of the world.
It's a lot of work.
I had to go to the mountains for a holiday.
Oh, my.
I built a house where this raccoon would come out.
Excuse me.
Do you live around here?
Yes.
Well,
Even so,
I can't believe you're celebrating my birthday.
You're really buttered by your subordinates.
That's right.
With hard work and hard work,
I don't do anything.
boring,
I'm really buttered by the story.
What the heck?
That's what you think.
You have to work under people like that.
What a shame.
But you don't want to bother people.
In Senpai's case,
He's been bothering you, doesn't he?
I've been troubled.
They're going to be here soon.
Oh, over there.
I see. So this is the manager's house.
A small veranda,
a garden I made by force,
and a garden.
However...
I guess I was able to send
the reflection of my sweat and tears
to build this tiny house.
Oh, right.
You have to send it to your home.
No, I don't.
I'm here, too.
What?
Because this is my home.
So you mean...
Could it be...
Yes.
I'm Hirobi, the daughter of a man
who's been holding, yelling, and stinking
and not listening to his boss.
Welcome.
Oh, you're...
The manager?
Yes.
So...
You've known about it?
Yes.
I've heard a lot about you
from my father.
I've been very respectful
of you since the day I was born.
You're really like a police officer's mirror.
Yes.
It's okay.
Don't force yourself.
Because my father
is really like that.
Y-Yes, he is.
I'm so happy!
Really?
Hey, Honda's here, too.
I'm home!
Hey, Dad!
Your guests are here!
Hm?
Is there someone here?
Oh!
Oh, hello, hello.
You guys!
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you've been doing your best
to help your cute subordinates.
I'm a thousand times more cute than you.
Oh, welcome, everyone.
I'm sorry.
We were all so busy.
Thank you.
Hm.
Well, you may leave.
See you later.
Well, Chief, you're a great guy.
The building of this entrance
is very well organized,
and you're a very nice person.
Hm?
And the taste of the wall painting
makes the guests feel more relaxed.
You're not getting up!
Huh?
What are you talking about, Dad?
You brought us here.
Come on, Ryotsu, get up.
Hehehe.
I can't believe you're so cute.
I shouldn't have said that
you had a cute daughter.
Hey, Ryotsu,
I'm telling you,
don't get upset over nothing.
I don't think Hiromi would be so kind
as to treat a cowardly man like you.
Well, I'm a cowardly man, after all.
I'm not as good as you.
Wh-What?
Dad, stop it.
This isn't a work place.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Tee-hee.
What's he doing here?
Why did he come all of a sudden?
Oh, is he really ungrateful?
Huh?
Happy birthday, Dad.
H-Happy birthday?
Congratulations, Mayor!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Mayor.
Alright, Dad.
What?
Mucho!
Has anything happened?
S- Bayern.
Ah, everyone, thank you.
Congratulations!
Then you guys,
I'm going to have to do something to celebrate my birthday.
Ah, boss, are you crying?
I-I'm not crying, idiot!
Yes, father, this is from me and my mother.
Oh, leather shoes.
Hmm, I'll use them carefully.
Boss, this is a small gift from us.
What is it? It's quite big.
After all, what did you buy?
What is this?
How is it, boss? It's nostalgic, isn't it?
We're having a nostalgic candy fair in the department store.
Look, there are two balls and a cotton ball,
a silver ball cannon, a pachinko,
a kombu, a sauce, and a squid suzuke.
And this Bakchiku.
In the past, it was called a Nibi, but it was a bigger one.
Boss, is that all the money you've collected?
Of course.
Well, if you have 20,000 yen, you can buy a lot of things.
You didn't know?
Yes, I didn't know that you would choose the present yourself.
Hmm, I knew that I had to leave it to Ryo-chan.
It was a mistake to leave it to Ryo-chan.
Hey, what is this?
What is it? You don't even know what a cotton ball is?
Okay, look.
You can take it like this.
Wow, that's interesting.
A cotton ball is something you put your hips in like this and do this.
Are you going to lose to the boss?
What?
Hmm, this has gotten out of hand.
Huh?
Tsk.
How was that?
Hahaha.
Ah...
Oh...
Ahem...
Well, guys.
Thank you so much for today.
This is a gift, anyway.
I'm so happy that you celebrated my birthday.
I was so absorbed in reading the script.
That's right.
I'd like to offer everyone a cup of tea as a token of gratitude.
Tea?
What's this room?
There's nothing here.
This is the tea room.
It's where we drink tea.
Tea room?
It's a small house, but you made this room just to drink tea?
Ryo, you have to sit here.
Really?
What is this?
Here.
Thank you for taking care of me.
You're welcome.
Ouch.
You can't touch it right away.
Wait until the manager comes.
I'm not going to touch it.
Then please wait a moment.
Ryo, do you know?
When you drink tea, you have to slowly...
I know that much.
I have to turn it around three times.
You're stupid.
If you turn it vertically, the tea will spill out, right?
Uh-huh.
I'm sorry, Shibata.
I went to the tea room, but it's empty.
It's still empty.
I'm sure the manager is in a hurry.
I'm saying this because I'm sorry.
Go to sleep.
You should sleep all night.
No, I'm drinking tea.
What is your fault?
It's just that there is no sound inside the room.
"I love you"
"I love you too"
"Homura san, are you OK?"
"My feet are numb..."
"I'm not sure about you..."
"Here's some sweets."
"I speak of the devil! I got the food you ordered!
"Then now I would like to..."
"Hurt!"
Hey, you!
Huh?
You know nothing about the heart of tea!
You don't have to do anything, just sit there quietly!
Hmm, I understand.
Anyway, I'll give you a taste of my proud tea bowl.
Tea bowl?
This is what I value the most right now.
Oh my!
I found it when I was traveling to Kyoto.
I really wanted it, so I bought it thinking I'd use it for the rest of my life.
It's a black-and-white tea bowl.
It looks pretty good.
It's a work of art.
Oh, I see.
The black luster is wonderful.
I'll give everyone tea with this tea bowl.
Tea bowl, huh?
What kind of stupid thing is that?
Ryo-ryotsu!
Hey, you!
Stop it!
I'm fine.
Let me have a look.
Oh!
Ah!
Chief, that was a close call.
That's what I mean by a good catch.
Idiot!
You don't have to worry about it.
This tea bowl is worth 400,000 yen!
...or buy anything!
What?! ¥ 400,000?!
It's life-threatening, isn't it?!
Hm... Well, in this world there is ...
...something worth undetectable for you!
Huh...
It was quite an effort.
I didn't want to see too much pillow.
The old man and the new man
U-uh...
It was really delicious...
The old man and the new man
Ah, you weren't careful.
Just prepare a proper meal.
Next...
The old man and the new man
Keep the tea ready for the operation.
He's a king.
I prefer the tea to the swing.
Hmph, yes you are the king.
...it might be more suitable.
But I've already prepared the meal, so hold on a little longer.
Dad?
The phone is ringing.
I see.
Well then, Ryotsu, wait.
Don't touch the teacups no matter what.
Got it?
I got it.
Are you sure you're alright?
I'm fine.
Good grief.
What's with the 400,000 teacups?
If they're so big, you could have put them on your bed.
But I was so nervous drinking tea with 400,000 teacups.
Tea tools are so simple, and everyone has their own.
This is it.
This is just right for cleaning your ears.
Senpai, that's not good.
That's right.
What?
I don't care.
Well, I'll set you up to pay the tax.
The real work is to just keep on writing, like a washing machine.
Ah, go around, ah, go around.
Hey, stop it.
Ah, go around, go around.
Ryo-chan, stop it.
Senpai.
Ah, it hurts.
It hurts.
I'm a bit upset.
Huh?
Ryo-chan.
Senpai.
Eh?
W-why?
Ah!
W-w-what?
Finally.
It's broken.
I-it's broken so easily.
How dare you...
I'm sure the manager was believed!
Wait!
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
Hmm?
Ryo-chan, what are you doing?
Huh-huh-huh...
Whoops...
But the manager-senpai is such a wonderful kid.
Huh?
What's the big deal?
Yes, I know.
My hands are so rough, I don't feel like hand-shake.
Really?
Really? Then I'll make tea with it, so give it back soon.
No, no, no.
Please let me interfere for a while longer.
It's not good to let you hold it.
Now, give it back soon.
Just a little longer.
No.
Really, just a little longer.
Hey, Ryotsu, stop it.
What's that?
Hey, wait, Ryotsu.
Don't wait.
Is the tea party over?
I'm preparing for the barbecue.
That's...
Oh, barbecue.
It'll be ready soon.
Yes, thank you.
Where are you, Ryotsu?
I'm right there.
Here, give me the teacup.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Look, Chief.
If you look at it in nature, it's even more beautiful.
This teacup.
I don't care about that.
Give it back soon.
What's the matter?
Oh, well...
You're rude to your guest.
Come on, Ryotsu.
Please eat.
I'm sorry.
I'll forgive you if you give it back now.
Come on, give it back now.
Really?
You'll forgive me if I give it back now?
Yeah.
Men don't have a second opinion.
What should I do?
Please give it back.
It's easy to break the teacup.
What if something happens to Maichi?
You'll get a refund.
You're such a fool.
You're like a child.
You can't eat it.
It's okay, man.
Can you please let her have that teacup for a while?
You're such a fool.
How dare you call your daughter a fool?
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
Mr. Honda,
that's going to burn.
I'll eat it.
Ryo, why aren't you eating it?
It's so delicious.
That's right. You'd better eat it now.
Let me eat it.
I refuse.
Hey, Ryo.
Here, drink it.
I won't refuse.
It's not something to drink beer with.
It's not a big deal.
Don't say that to my big brother.
It's fine. Here.
Here.
Your meat is burnt.
What was that?
What did you say?
I think I saw two bowls.
Are you drunk?
That's not true.
Show me the bowls.
That's...
Ryo, what did you do with those bowls?
I can't stand it when a guy like you
turns an important bowl into a toy.
Hey, give it back.
Wait, Ryo.
No, no.
You're not going to wait, are you?
I'm not going to wait.
Idiot.
You're so annoying.
Ryo, this way.
Hey, Ryo.
That bowl...
You broke it because of the chief.
because it was my treasure.
What do you expect from me tomorrow?
Hey, Dad, don't be so sad.
You can buy a new one, okay?
Oh, it's good.
Ryo!
What? I'll eat it all by myself.
Ryo, you have to apologize.
The chief will feel sorry for you.
Chief, something that has a shape will break someday.
That's the truth of all things.
Anyway, let's eat meat. It's delicious.
I don't need it. You eat it.
Then, I'll hold back.
Ryo, you're so annoying!
Chief, actually...
Oh, idiot, stop it!
That's what I meant.
What?
Chief, I was being too aggressive.
Ryo, you're so...
Unforgivable!
Chief...
Hey, Chief!
I can't eat barbecue!
Stop it!
Hot, hot, hot!
Well, Ryo is selfish.
It's your birthday, Mr. Hiromi.
But it seems like you're enjoying it, Dad.
Ryo's Sumi-be-yaki.
Hot, hot!
This is the best present for me.
Chief, please forgive me!
Nakagawa, Reiko, Honda, Mr. Hiromi!
Mr. Hiromi, help me!
Height 167 cm, weight 71 kg, and both eyes are 2.0.
Chief, are you going to challenge this perfect body?
Of course!
If you really want to compete, come from anywhere.
Next time on the Gokiburi Great Race.
Nice to meet you!
Even if I try to stop the clock,
time will pass by.
Don't look away,
don't look back.
Let's live with a smile on our faces.
Even if it rains today,
even if it rains today,
tomorrow will be sunny.
Bye bye!
Let's wash our hands.
That's the worst thing.
Bye bye!
Oh yeah!
Let's live the way we like.
There's good things.
The signboard is waiting outside the door.
Subtitles by Subdiver
Thank you for watching!