The Central Area of Tokyo
The central area of Tokyo.
The area that started out as Tokyo from the Sumida River has been called Tsukuda Island for a long time.
The Sumida River is divided into three sections called the Harumi-unga.
Originally, it was an island as its name suggests.
After that, it was built and became a direct extension of the northern Tsukishima and the southern Ishikawa Islands.
The current official name is Tsukuda Icho-me.
Tsukuda Island has changed a lot.
I've read in books that this area used to be a boat dock for the Wata-shibune, right?
Yes, this is before Tsukuda-ohashi was built.
Wata-shibune is the one that often appears in historical dramas, right?
It's a little different, but it's similar.
From Tsukuda to Akashi-cho on the other side, both ends of the Tsukuda-ohashi were the wata-shibune dock.
The steam ship pulled the ship and it was a four or five minute boat trip, but it was just used well.
Huh?
Come to think of it, I remembered.
There's a water gate over there, right?
It wasn't there in the past, but they could put a boat out on the Sumida River right away.
The back of Tsukuda Island is a boat dock, and I used to play there a lot.
I made a boat with Tonpei, Chinkichi and the three of us. It's a pretty serious one.
Chinkichi, be careful with that ship on the right.
I'm fine.
Engine start!
The Sumida River is pretty heavy.
When the ship passes, the waves come into the boat dock and the wata-shibune is shaken.
It's good. You can ride it.
It's beautiful.
That was fun.
Huh?
No way.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
That onbora boat.
Huh?
Yattokomaru?
That's a strange name.
Do you remember anything, Senpai?
Uh, uh...
When watching TV,
make the room bright and look away.
Come to me, you poor thing.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky.
The white clouds.
It'll be alright eventually.
Come to me, you jobless guy.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look.
The red clouds are burning.
It'll be alright eventually.
You get it, right?
You get it, you get it?
Don't say anything.
I won't say a thing!
Leave now.
Oh, of course.
Ryo-chan...
I won't say a thing.
It'll be alright eventually.
The monster dragged the grasps of this island's air.
I got you.
It'll be alright, Yattokomaru,
who lost your memories,
It was a powerful movie that connected three screens.
Especially the scene of the storm falling on the raft was amazing.
When I watched it in the front seat, it seemed to be a water splash.
It was amazing!
It was very powerful.
Let's try our boat trip not only around Tsukuda Island, but also on a real adventure.
Adventure trip?
What are you going to do, Kankichi?
We're going to go down the Sumida River.
The Sumida River?
Starting from Senju Bridge, we'll go to Suijin Bridge, Shirahige Bridge, Kototoi Bridge, Azuma Bridge,
Komagata Bridge, Umae Bridge, Kuramae Bridge, Ryogoku Bridge, Kiyosu Bridge,
and then we'll cross the Eitai Bridge and go down to Tsukuda Island.
Wow! It's like a big adventure!
Sounds great! Let's do it!
All three of us were excited.
Of course, we didn't know what would get in the way, so we kept it a secret from our parents.
Thank you, sir!
Hello!
Oh, be careful!
Well, here we go.
There!
Yahoo!
Departure!
Yo!
Full speed ahead!
Go to Hokuhokusei!
Kankichi, what's Hokuhokusei?
Um, it's the other way around.
That's right.
It's fine. Don't worry about the details.
The atmosphere will be ruined.
Right.
Let's go on an adventure!
Let's go!
Hey!
We're almost at Suijin Bridge.
Ah, if we turn this curve, we'll be there.
Right!
That's grain Youngman!
I'll show you some.
Hey!
What's that?
Yeah, yeah!
How about you?
Awesome, right?
Huh?
That's sick!
The butt, pass! Pass!
What!
Think again!
Help me!
Well, let's get going.
Ta-dah!
Wow! You brought that?
What did you bring?
I'm the second submarine.
I'm the South Pole observation ship, Sawyer.
All right. Let's get them into the water.
All right.
Wet.
All right. All right.
Kankichi's Yamato is really powerful.
It looks like a real one.
My South Pole observation ship, Sawyer, is pretty good too.
Wow! It's so cool!
It's them!
Hey, you!
That's a one-shot!
Yeah!
Stop it!
All right. We're in the bridge.
Let's get the ship back.
Hurry up!
Damn it!
The 46-centimeter cannon is broken.
My radar was damaged.
The ship's rudder is...
Come on!
Over there!
I won't let you off!
What's wrong with you?
Why the heck did you do that?
You're in trouble!
And then he found you.
I'm gonna see you in the next video!
Okay, boss!
I hit him.
He's in trouble!
You dangerously soy-
Hey, Kankichi.
Sao.
Hm?
Ah!
Sao, give it back!
Give it back!
What should we do?
There's no one else to replace me.
Are you going to break it by hand?
Huh?
Kankichi!
I ran! I'm going to crash!
There's a lot of heavy water!
Which is heavier?
That's the water over there!
It doesn't matter, just avoid it!
I'm going to crash!
Kankichi!
The water is...
Ah, there was a compass and a map in there.
Give it up.
You can't go back now.
It's like an adventure to lose your luggage on the way.
But...
You have to help each other in times like this.
That's what adventure is.
Everyone, give me my luggage!
Everyone?
I'm the only one left.
Um...
Water bottle, right?
Uh, chocolate plate, right?
And four rice balls.
What?
You're just eating.
Because eating is important, right?
Well, the rest is in the toolbox.
Ah, this one was also washed away.
A nail and a tonkatsu.
Uh, and a small sword.
Ah...
Oh, it's delicious!
There's only a sushi restaurant in the far end, so the route is different.
Stop it!
A family eats regular rice!
By the way, there's only one left.
It's an adventure, so we have to share everything.
I'll share three.
Yeah, I'll do it.
It's me!
Kankichi is not good at mathematics, right?
You're the same, aren't you?
Stop it, you two!
Ah!
Rice balls...
It's not my fault.
Well, don't be disappointed.
It seems that this is a real adventure trip.
Yeah!
It's transparent over there.
Huh...
Where are we?
Well, we just crossed the Koto Toibashi bridge, so we haven't reached half of it yet.
There's still that much left?
Hey, don't drink so much by yourself.
It's fine! It's my water!
Now it's everyone's water!
Don't play around! Give it back!
No!
Stop it, you two!
Stop it!
I'm hungry.
I just ate one rice ball.
Wait!
Tompei, you have to take your chocolate for the best time.
What do you mean, for the best time?
By the way, it's the best time.
That's what happens on an adventure.
Ouch.
I should have brought some fishing tools.
I have a small sword, so I can handle it.
Fish? I like chocolate.
Don't say that. I want to eat it more and more.
What are you doing, Kankichi?
I'm diving to get some fish.
An adventure is something you can do by yourself.
Kankichi, are you serious?
Stop it.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
Kankichi!
He really jumped in.
He hasn't come up yet.
Isn't it a little too long?
That's right.
Kinkichi, Tompei!
Kankichi!
It's huge.
I've never seen such a big eel.
Yeah, it's the owner of the river.
If you grill it on a river, it might get a punishment.
That's right.
I'll return it to the river.
That's the best.
Yeah.
Take care.
If we grow up, we'll meet again.
Let's eat some chocolate.
Oh, you're full, Kankichi.
I don't have that much chocolate.
You're full, Kankichi.
Oh, you're full, Kankichi.
Oh...
Oh stay...
You're hungry.
When?
Oh, that's right.
I'm hungry.
.
Ah, stop it.
I'm hungry.
Until tomorrow, I'll take it to Kankichi.
I'm thirsty.
I want to drink Ramune.
Let's quit.
What's wrong, Tompei?
You can't quit.
I'm sick of it.
I'm hungry.
You've decided once.
It's meaningless if you don't finish the adventure.
What's the point of it?
What?
Say it again.
You're a bastard.
What?
Stop it.
You're always like that when you're in trouble.
I see.
I'll decide when I'm in trouble.
Who wants to quit?
Yes.
Who wants to continue until the end?
Who's the new captain?
I'll do it until the end.
I see.
You're on an adventure, but you're quitting.
Look.
But.
But?
You're too nosy.
I don't know.
I wish I had a better way to run.
Even if you say that, it's not because you have an engine.
You have no choice but to leave it to the flow.
Huh?
I've come up with a good idea.
Hey!
Huh?
What's this pile of garbage?
What are you going to do with this?
I'm going to make a fire.
It's a fire-fighting place, right?
I'm going to pile up the newspaper.
I see.
But I need seaweed.
Here is this crushed rice ball.
I see!
It's done.
Right?
Wow!
We did it!
We made it to Kiosu Bridge!
Now we just need to cross Etaibashi and we'll be there soon!
The sky is getting more and more suspicious.
We'll be in for a heavy rain.
Here it comes!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Koukichi!
Hold on tight so you don't fall!
Koukichi! That's Etaibashi!
That means...
Fukuda Island is to the right!
No! The wind is too strong!
There's no other way!
The wind is too strong!
No! I can't make it!
I'm going to crash!
Whoa!
My mountain!
Hey, come on!
Hey, Etaibashi!
Ayuibashi!
A little longer before the river tips off!
Don't!
Ah no, I'm running out of force!
Daddy, help me!
Ah!
I got stuck!
I don't know where I put my legs!
Come on, Koukichi!
I can't get up!
"Mosto — Numberlithic
It's getting cold.
What's in the world?
Come on.
Absolutely nothing!
Guys, can you just go back in there?
Damn, it's a storm.
I didn't tell you anything about the weather forecast.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Thanks to you, we had a great adventure.
That's right. There's nothing to apologize for.
This boat was 60 kilometers away.
That's right.
It was much faster than the truck at the store.
I'll tell you about this when I get married and have children.
Are you married?
Who do you like?
I know.
You hate me, don't you?
I don't want to tell you.
Then let's say it together.
It's a secret between the three of us.
Okay, let's do it.
♪ The game of finger-cutting lies. ♪
♪ If you don't do it, you'll get a thousand needles. ♪
But it's really hard to get a thousand needles.
I can't drink it.
It doesn't matter.
It's about your favorite child.
Then let's say it.
One, two.
The three-class Momoyo-chan!
What?
Are you all the same?
Because it's cute.
It's gentle.
But Momoyo-chan is a young lady.
Will we be married?
It's stupid.
We're like this now.
But when we grow up, we don't know how great we'll be.
I see.
I may be a space pilot.
I'm a rich man anyway.
I'm the captain of the Earth Defense Forces.
That's not true.
Then, I'll tell Momoyo-chan to marry me.
It's a ship.
It's coming here.
Is it a vessel?
Is it a ship?
Hey!
Is it a vessel?
Is it a ship?
It's flying!
It's a ship!
Is it a ship?
Is it?
Kankichi!
I thought I was going to die...
I'm glad...
Tonpei, Chinkichi, I'm glad you're safe!
Get him!
Get him?
Didn't you say, get him?
Man, he's got a lot of fish in his mouth.
So that's this boat, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
It's been decades since he got caught.
That old man might have died already.
Ah! He's out!
He's out!
What's going on?
I'm alive.
Really?
But you're still the same as you were back then.
So you're the same old man.
How old are you?
I've been doing this for about 40 years.
I'm glad you're doing well.
It's just a coincidence.
No way.
I found something in the ocean after that.
Ah!
It's mine!
It's my Yamato I lost back then!
Wow, Lisa!
That's good, Senpai.
It's my Yamato.
Yeah, that's for sure.
It's this one!
Good, good!
Engine start!
I love the sound of the waves!
I feel so jealous of him sometimes.
You're right.
He's as long-lived as me.
Too long.
No, I...
Good.
It's gone.
Ah, the shadows are still there from yesterday
So even if it rains today, tomorrow will be sunny again
I can believe in that day
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I'm heading for tomorrow with a nice breath
Don't get sick, I'll do what I have to do
With a cute breath
What's hard to understand
Is the war I want to show
It's better than just looking back
Hey, this is bad!
The shakuri won't stop!
If this continues, my life will be in danger!
Someone! Stop it!
Next time!
Shakuri Panic!
I'm counting on you!
Over there is Kameari
Ah, I'm sure it's Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!