Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
When you watch TV,
light up your room and look away.
Hello, goodbye.
If you say goodbye,
you'll be home soon.
Wapara, wapara, wapara.
Don't panic.
Where are you going in this small town?
Hurry and turn around.
Maybe,
you'll find a better person
than me.
Let me hear you.
Let me hear you all night.
I don't hate waiting.
Because I'm a Kameza woman.
I don't want to lose.
I'm a Ginza woman.
I've loved you
for a long time.
I love you,
Kameza woman.
Kameza Woman
Idiot!
What's this?
You said you're going to do some sports during your work.
Well,
this month's living allowance
is only 15,000 yen.
So I thought I'd give it a try.
No, Ryo.
You're just out of pay.
What did you use, senpai?
Yeah, it's not only this month's Eloy Dreamstation 3.
Besides,
I used Bio Inferno,
Bridgett & Neilsenji.
And,
exclusive public version of the Plum,
Great Ointment.
Oh, I used Fugiar.
Then I bought Bibbilman.
And...
Idiot!
You wish to waste your living
just like that?
I don't think you have much time
God,
you're going to have to save your pay.
You can't make money by doing that.
Think more realistically!
That's not what I meant.
There's nothing like that!
Listen, Ryotsu.
You get paid with that kind of attitude.
So you should use it in a good way.
You should change your mind and think about working seriously.
The money you earned by sweating is really valuable.
But even if I sweat and earn,
it doesn't change my money.
Then you should make money with ease.
Idiot!
If you don't change your mind,
I'll give you a new law next month.
What?
The one who comes to the end of the human race seriously wins.
The one who doesn't understand that
is a big idiot who doesn't know the real joy of living.
Then I'll go back to the main office.
Yes, sir!
Thank you for your hard work!
Ryozan.
Are you there?
Yes, I'm in the back room.
What's wrong?
Help me, Mr. Fukai.
I don't care.
Matsukichi.
Who's that?
You're lying, aren't you?
You know Ryozan.
It's cold, Ryozan.
It's Matsukichi, Kato Matsukichi.
Kato Matsukichi?
See?
Ten years ago, in the winter,
at the convenience store in front of the station.
Ten years ago?
The convenience store in front of the station?
Yes.
Yes...
What's this?
You tried to escape!
So that's all you are, Mr. Oomari,
reading an erotic book while you're working.
This is...
I was trying to dig the notes.
Probably, I got lost in the stars because of you!
Digging, huh?
Please don't forget to subscribe!
You're the one who was doing the Manpiki!
Long time no see.
What do you want?
Ryo-san, this is it.
Ryo Tsukankichi-sama, 15,000 yen for a sepiro-dai-kin?
What the heck is this?
He tore his clothes off when he wore them.
He said he didn't have any money.
Then, he asked me to borrow him because he knew Ryo-san,
Thank you!
Don't be silly!
I don't have any money either!
I don't have any money to lend you!
Ryo-san, Ryo-san!
What?
Put on the clothes that you're wearing!
Hurry up and take them off!
I won't return them!
I'll have them pay for everything!
Ryo-san, please!
Don't get involved!
Get out of my way!
I don't have any money to lend you!
My wallet?
Ryo-san, you have 15,000 yen!
Well, I see.
Here's your receipt.
See you later.
Why am I in such a mess?
Help me, Mr. Fukin!
My name is Kato Matsukichi.
What's your job?
My job?
I can't say it in one word.
It's like a day full of dreams and romance.
It's like a day full of freedom.
A day full of free time.
What's your address?
I don't have one.
Well, you can take the wind if it blows,
or you can take the wind if you want,
but the only thing you can do is travel freely.
I don't have one.
What's your second-hand insurance?
What?
I've heard there's no one who can lend me 15,000 yen!
I don't have any money to lend you!
I see.
If you can lend me 100,000 yen,
I'll double it tomorrow.
How?
I'll tell you how.
I'll put in a couple of times
to make sure you get it.
I'll double it,
or even triple it!
You idiot!
If you do it so well,
I'll become a swordsman!
Then I'll take 50,000 yen.
What kind of logic is that?
You two look alike.
You're right.
Then let's not talk about the horse race.
There's a way to make money more easily.
What?
The one who's always expanding his power
in the store when there's a festival.
Choco Banana!
Banana?
Ichigo Daifuku, who has stirred up a new wave in the candy industry!
What about it?
The third hit fruit series I thought of.
Miso Melon!
I'm sure this will be a big hit.
It'll make a lot of money!
Oh, I'm a genius.
I'm going to make my own sense.
You idiot!
Who's going to eat that?
I don't think you should stick to it.
Then,
the three Dango brothers
put their hands on it
and make four balls?
The Sazaibon
put their hands on it
and the Chibimarubon
put their hands on the Nelton Party.
Don't you ever put your hands on it!
You see?
The only one who can make money easily
is the one who has the luck and talent.
If a super rich man like you
thinks you can make money with that idea,
Listen, Matsukichi.
Think more realistically.
Think about changing your mind
and working seriously.
Listen.
The money you make from spilling the sweat
is the real value.
What?
The one who comes to the end
seriously and seriously
The one who doesn't know that
is a big idiot
the true joy of living.
Oh, you've grown a lot.
Zuchan!
You said something
that I've heard before,
Ryo-tsu.
Well,
I thought about it
and I deeply regret
what the chief said.
I deeply regret what the chief said.
Oh.
I don't want him
to make the same mistake
as I did.
I don't want him to make the same mistake
Oh.
Well,
I think he's just showing
his regretful attitude.
Then,
let's delete the constitution.
Well,
it depends on his attitude.
Oh,
Ryo-tsu, Kankichi.
I'll encourage you to work.
this is for you.
Thank you,
Mr. Fukui.
I see.
Ryo-tsu is borrowing money
from you.
What do you mean?
If you're looking for
his job,
I have a feeling
that...
Well,
please lend me money
No, no, no.
I'll bring it to you right away.
Yes.
I was in trouble
because I didn't have enough
people to work with.
I can do it today.
That's fine.
Oh,
Matsukichi,
I've decided.
Hey,
why are young and cute girls like you
in such a dirty and dirty store?
What time are you going to work today?
Don't you go to eat something delicious?
Stop it.
She's the young lady here.
Come here.
You're not introducing the chief.
What do you want to do?
If you want to work,
I'd like to work in a cool building.
I'm good at suits.
You're a little kid like you.
Where are you hiring a foreign one?
Then what about the artist?
I'm good at karaoke.
I'm going to make promotional tape
and sell it.
I wonder if you're doing well.
If you take care of the young people like that,
you'll grow up.
Look at people's actions
and fix my actions.
Hey,
what's the matter?
Really
It's easy to do a good job with money.
I don't care.
If there's something like that,
I'll do it.
I'm serious.
Think seriously.
I'm going to get back my money.
You look pretty good.
Senior.
That's Mr. Matsukichi's.
I'm taking care of him.
What kind of work are you doing for Mr. Matsukichi?
That's...
This is Kameyari Park Exhibition.
What?
You're so stubborn.
You left the job
that someone found.
This time,
you're going to get your money back.
Huh?
It's a letter from Mr. Matsukichi.
Chiyo Kato.
No, Ryo.
He left a letter without permission.
Shut up!
In this case,
he's a fugitive who stepped on the debt
and ran away.
This is a mission
to catch his feet.
A mission.
Well...
To my brother,
I rarely give you letters,
but how are you?
Actually,
my father is going to be hospitalized.
I won't say it out loud,
but my father wants to see you.
My mother said
she doesn't need to wear a wedding dress,
so she wants you to go home.
Please,
come home soon.
Hey!
Don't tell me
you're trying to rob a bank.
Huh?
Chiyo is my sister.
Ten years ago,
I had a fight with my father.
I will never be like my father!
What?
You're a criminal and you're so cheeky!
I'm off, mom!
Chiyo!
Matsukichi!
Brother!
My sister is a young entrepreneur.
She came to see me when I was about to leave.
I had to hit her once to get back.
So you're going to go bankrupt with Miso Melon?
Don't be a burden to your family.
I'll do something about it.
Go back to your country without complaining!
Besides, you don't have to look like a young entrepreneur.
You don't have to look like a young entrepreneur.
Huh?
Young entrepreneurs these days have more debt than wealth.
Compared to that, you're more wealthy.
Ryo-san...
It's been 10 years since I came back.
You're not doing well as a young entrepreneur.
Sakata and Hashiguchi are lucky.
Goro and Akio and Mitsuko are the best.
You didn't have to say that.
Excuse me.
30 of these.
You're going to buy souvenirs for everyone in the village?
I like this bag too.
Don't buy souvenirs for Tokyo or Hakata Mentaiko.
Well, take care.
Thanks for everything, Ryo-san.
If they're happy, give them back the money you borrowed from me.
Matsukichi, the door is closing. Let go of me.
Hey, let go of me!
Ouch!
I'm your boyfriend!
Then why don't we go to Morioka together?
Why do you have to go with me?
I'm saying let's go to the next station.
Ohmiya. Ohmiya.
I have to take care of you.
Then...
I'll give you a ride.
I'm not brave enough to go home alone.
What are you talking about? Go back!
I don't know what to do!
Where do we go when we get back home?
You can look this side.
Go that way!
Ouch!
The fish in my country is very delicious.
Yes, it's my treat.
You're the culprit?
No, it's for democracy.
Thank you for the hard work!
You're a mean man.
Hehe.
But a young professional and a policeman are the same.
Wow, I'm so tired.
Your suit suits you, Ryo-san.
You're my secretary, so you should keep your mouth shut.
I'll get this suit back, too.
How long will it take?
About two and a half hours.
Two and a half hours? What's taking so long?
Let's get back to work. I'm getting a little nervous as I get closer.
How long will it take?
All right, let's rehearse.
Rehearsal?
Ready?
Yes.
All right, get ready.
I-I-I'm back!
No, you'll open the door when you get home.
Yes.
Gara Gara, I'm back!
Huh?
Oh, Dad, you're okay?
You idiot! I'm not okay because I caught a patient!
Huh? Oh, I see.
There's something else, right?
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, Dad, you're not done yet?
You idiot! What are you going to do if a patient gets into a fight with you?
You look pretty energetic.
You're going to say something a little embarrassed.
That's how it is in this situation.
That's right.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, Dad, you look pretty energetic.
I-I-I'm not going to lose yet, though.
What are you talking about?
Why do you say things that will excite the patient?
Even if you say that...
The smell of salt...
Whoa!
I can't wait to eat.
Dad, I've been working in this fish market since I left home.
You're not interested in fishing.
Me?
It's early in the morning, my work is tough, it's no joke.
Besides, I'm going back to Tokyo.
Huh?
Matsukichi!
It's Matsukichi, isn't it?
I heard that you're doing well in Tokyo.
Not really.
It's a boring thing, but this is a souvenir from Tokyo.
So please share it with everyone.
Oh, thank you.
By the way, your father, I haven't seen him since yesterday.
Did something happen?
As I thought...
Hey!
It looks like a loose.
I thought you had a similar voice, but it was Matsukichi!
I thought it was someone else's father, Goro!
Here, take a look.
Oh!
By the way, I don't have anyone at home.
Do you know where he went?
You don't know?
Your father was hospitalized yesterday.
Chiyo and your mother are in the hospital.
Hospital?
They are all here.
Matsukichi!
Mom, Chiyo.
Father.
My brother!
Get a grip, Matsukichi!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
My father should be dead.
Doctor!
Is he all right?
Did he succeed in the surgery?
N-No.
He succeeded.
Thank you very much, Doctor!
Well, then...
Thanks!
Dad!
Dad...
Hang in there, Dad!
It's me! I'm your son, Matsukichi!
I'm back!
Dad!
Idiot!
Don't make such a big sound!
Excuse me!
You look much better after the big surgery.
What's your father's disease?
It's a disease called "disease"!
Disase?
Matsukichi, by the way, who is this?
This is my secretary, Ryo-tsu.
Nice to meet you.
You're so cool!
Who called you such an idiot?
I didn't come here because I wanted to!
Well, well, you two.
This is not a fight between kids.
Dad, don't turn your back on me!
This is easier!
You're so shy!
I really wanted to see you.
Who said I wanted to see you?
Hey, do it as we rehearsed.
But it was G.
It's not G, so do it!
Yes...
Anyway, I'm glad my father is doing well.
Is he doing well?
He's your son, so he's not doing well.
What?
Dad, you came back,
but you can't say that!
That's right. It's been 10 years.
I haven't seen you in 10 years.
You're so mischievous.
How dare you?
I'm not mischievous!
I said I'm mischievous!
What?
Dad!
Calm down, Matsukichi.
I got it.
What are you talking about, dad?
I'm not mischievous, I'm doing my best.
I came here today because I had a busy job.
I was sensitive to the trend since I was here.
I made clothes and succeeded in the apparel industry.
The company has grown rapidly.
The building is on the top of Aoyama.
We're going to have a branch overseas soon.
Wow!
Really, Ryotsu?
Well, yeah.
Here's a souvenir.
This is Eromes' scarf.
Thank you, brother.
Here, mom.
Oh, it's a Hakata Mentaiko.
I gave my father a good one.
You're so stingy.
I'm not stingy at all!
Hittaro, I'm not like my father.
I'll never be like my father.
I'm not a man who will end his life like you.
It's already this late.
I have a meeting today, so I have to go home by evening.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Chiyo, this is Kinjirou's work.
Are you leaving already?
Yeah.
The boss is hard.
Take care.
I'll take care of today's meeting.
The boss should stay here for a while.
Right?
No, I can't do that.
But...
Let go, Ryotsu.
Ryotsu, what are you doing?
My Aromani is expensive.
I'm sorry.
I'm really stupid.
You're telling lies.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, Matsukichi.
I won't do it again.
Father.
If you stay here,
I'll hear your words.
I'm not old enough to be a butcher.
So I'm not going to pretend to be the owner.
Matsukichi.
-Machi! -Machi!
Mr. Ryoichi!
Your stupid son has helped you.
No, I...
I was wrong to raise him.
He's become such a half-baked idiot.
But his life is his.
I think he should live as he likes.
As he likes.
Thank you for waiting.
What are you doing, Matsukichi?
You're going back to Tokyo?
This is a specialty here.
Take it as a souvenir.
So you're staying?
My father is a grandpa.
I thought I'd have to take care of him.
What a noisy father.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ryo!
You're so mean.
You're so annoying!
Let go of me!
You're making me a fool!
Let go!
So this is Matsukichi?
You've become so strong.
He's really a man of the sea.
Mr. Ryo, thank you for your help.
I was going to return the money I borrowed in the first month, but...
I'm going to return it to you with a huge amount of money.
I'm really going to become a fisherman this time.
My father said he wouldn't take it.
I told him I'd continue even if it was for fun.
Now I'm planning a fishing trip.
Please come and play with me.
You can go out at sunrise and do fishing.
You can experience all kinds of fishing so that you won't get tired of it for the whole day.
You can go fishing.
There's a lot of money in the savings.
It's all a whole bunch.
What do you think?
Good.
Don't you think this idea is cool?
How will it look in your eyes?
After a fight, you always give me a short kiss
You were so dear to me
How much can people get
With such irreplaceable things?
You are me
I am you
I was satisfied with just that
Just laughing at you
I felt that all the pain was healed
Oh, fireworks?
I played well when I was a child
I played with my friends in a rocket fire
I stabbed a 2B bullet into a dog's poop
No, not like that
Next time, "A Gift Bloomed in the Night Sky"
Please watch it!