"I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a job."
When you watch TV, make your room bright and try to look away.
Those who have no money, come to me.
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
You'll get there somehow.
"I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a job."
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a job.
You know what I mean?
I know.
If you know, shut up and come to me.
The End
Good morning, Ryo-san!
Huh? What's up?
Ryo-san, did you eat mochi?
Mochi?
Yeah, it's New Year's Eve, but I haven't eaten any mochi.
It's just leftover from the Osechi cuisine.
I'll cook you some mochi.
Osechi cuisine, huh?
I used to have a strong desire to eat it on New Year's Eve.
But I haven't had the time to do so lately.
I haven't had the time to do so lately.
Okay, Ryo-san. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, I've got a good feeling about this.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ryo-san, why don't you eat something?
Okay, okay.
Hmm, hmm.
Japanese people love mochi.
Ryo-san, you're so full of food!
Is that so?
Oh, it's rare.
It's a fairy tale.
Yamato Damashii Hozonkai
Oh, it's real, huh?
Ah, it's my Japanese brother!
Lucky!
Japanese brother?
You're trying to protect the heart of Japan?
Let's use the correct Japanese this year as well.
Yes!
Then, the white-bearded old man has come.
Let's start.
White-bearded old man?
A sacred legend from the north, the white-bearded old man has come.
The white-bearded old man has come.
But I found aifique a girl who just came to give me a gift.
Shibame is the same as the white-bearded old man.
She don't know much about ingratitude.
His name is Sakuragawa.
The white-bearded old man is not a anymore.
Oh, right here!
Is it a candle?
Really?
Yes
I know.
What kinda candy was this?
Sounds good.
Uh, Figure-san, hurry up.
Take care.
Wait, wait a minute.
Please be more careful!
Too much, don't you think?
Um, oh my God.
Oh, did you eat something?
Yes, yes, yes.
What does "Merry Christmas" mean?
It's too straightforward to understand.
Shinohige-ji-san put the new items in the children's bed,
which is sleeping soundly,
and went back to the north.
The children were very happy the next morning.
The eldest son, Taro, got the electronic camera he wanted.
The eldest daughter, Hanako, got the small-sized board for the morning girl.
The second son, Jiro, got the Western Kemari.
The third son, Kuro, got the Western Kemari.
The digital camera, the Moms CD, and the soccer ball?
That's what happens when you say it in Japanese.
It's a scale.
Why do you force yourself to translate it into Japanese?
To protect the heart of Japan, right?
I'm sure you're trying to convey the wonderfulness of Japanese to the children.
Hmm...
That's good, good.
Now, to everyone who watched the paper play to the end,
let's give Ume-ama-ni-senbei.
Yeah!
Thank you, big brother.
Huh?
I also put up with it and watched until the end.
Why are we talking about Christmas now?
I didn't have time to talk about the New Year's Eve,
because it was something I made by hand.
But since it's New Year's Eve, I'll give you another New Year's ball today.
Yeah!
Here, take one of your favorite things.
Oh.
What is this?
It's a gift.
I was going to play with this one.
I'll try it on.
It's not a bad idea to play with toys of the past like this one.
Hey, this octopus looks weird.
Is it going to fly?
It's flying.
It's going to rise really high.
Look, it's stretching its tail like this...
Ah!
It's tangled up again.
What?
Give it to me.
Christmas is the year of the octopus.
I guess it's the year of the octopus.
Have you ever had an octopus?
Yes!
No!
Huh?
There aren't many places to fry octopus now.
I was wrong about this.
I didn't know that this was happening to a turtle.
Alright, leave it to me!
Ray, are you ready?
I'm ready anytime, Onyo-san!
Here I go!
Alright, let go of my hand!
Wow!
Look closely.
This is how you fry an octopus!
Wow!
Isn't it fun to fry an octopus?
Yeah!
It's a good thing to do sometimes.
We're Japanese, so we should fry an octopus for New Year's.
You're young but you're great.
I'm impressed.
I'm sorry.
Our Japanese is in a state of crisis due to the spread of foreign language.
I want to protect the beautiful Japanese language and restore the culture and customs of Japan that has been forgotten.
Would you like to have a cup of warm tea?
Huh?
Are you sure?
There's only me and Terai here.
I don't mind.
Happy New Year!
Here's your present!
Um, this is...
I met her in the park over there.
My name is Fuzi Yamato.
Ah, hello.
Ha ha, it's delicious.
As I thought, Japanese people love Japanese tea.
Yeah, yeah!
This is a souvenir chocolate. Does it suit your taste?
In fact, this is a favorite, a traditional drink of Nangoku-san, a hot spring.
Oh.
Amazing.
-Amazing. -Isn't it?
Yamato-kun is good at speaking without using foreign languages.
I'm a big fan of Yamato.
If you say that, please say "he's really good at it".
Can you do anything in Japanese?
Yes, well...
Then, what do you call a plastic model?
It's a synthetic plastic assembly model.
What about the TV?
It's a box-shaped prototype.
Give it back!
What about this electric guitar?
It's a 6-core electric jamisen.
Give it back!
What about canned coffee?
It's canned soy bean soup made in South America.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
What about the lighter?
It's a mobile phone manual lighter.
What about this head?
Take this.
What about this?
Hey!
You can say anything in Japanese.
That's right.
It's so amazing.
Well, forget it.
What about this?
It's 300 yen!
What?
It's nothing.
For us, we think we've used too much English.
But this might be a good chance to try watching you in Japanese.
If you say so, we should come to you.
It's great!
Impressive. It's like a rare Japanese man's food.
It's not that bad.
It's cold.
Hey, Reiko. Do you still have the chocolate from the souvenir shop?
What are you talking about? I ate it all three days ago.
Oh, that was the last one.
I was going to give you food until the payday, but I should have given you a little more.
I'm so tired.
Oh, Senpai, the person who came here the other day...
See, the person who's particular about Japanese has come to visit you.
Yamato? What do you mean?
Is the 6th floor around here? You're really down to earth.
It's all because of Yamato.
Ah, yes. It's this house.
Please!
Senpai, the times are changing.
You're so Japanese, aren't you?
Yes!
Welcome.
Eh?
This is Yamato's house.
It's your turn, Nakagawa.
It's okay. I'm American, but I can speak Japanese fluently.
You're Yamato's friend, right?
Oh, thanks.
Could it be your god?
Yes.
It's Catherine.
But I'm surprised.
Yamato's god, who hates foreigners, is American.
So I don't hate foreigners.
I look like an American, but I'm a Japanese with a strong personality.
You speak Japanese very well. When did you come to Japan?
I came to Japan for my first overseas trip when I was in college.
I moved here a year ago when I married Yamato.
I've loved Japan since I was a child.
I studied a lot in the past.
Your impressions of Japan are quite different, aren't they?
Yes.
Like this...
When did you come to Japan?
And then...
Hey, are you a Japanese?
But when I met Yamato at that time, he was the Japanese I thought.
He was serious and honest.
He was like a real Japanese man.
I fell in love at first sight.
I see.
It's a pleasant day at the beginning of the new year.
New Year is New Year's Day.
Japanese New Year's Day is Takoage, Hanetsuki, Komamawashi.
It's a wind.
Nowadays, only the inside shops of Asakusa or Tokyo Tower sell things like this in Japan.
That's right.
So we want to give the children a little bit of the wonderfulness of Japan.
Yamato taught children how to play in the past while working.
I teach children how to play solo.
She wrote the words of the octopus.
It's better than me.
I can't read your words.
I'm looking forward to the day when I'll have takoage with Yamato.
If it's takoage, it's the day of the paper play.
That day was very windy.
The humidity was low and the crows were not crying.
Yamato said it wasn't takoage.
What?
Let's have takoage together next year.
Yes.
Yamato is very good at takoage.
Right, Yamato?
Yes.
By the way, did you call us to brag about the beautiful god?
Close it.
Yes.
What?
Please.
Is this the ninja mansion?
This is.
What?
What's this?
What is this?
OMG.
Oh my God!
Yamato?
Not found!
I've been looking for it, but I can't find it!
I just got Michael Jordan's signed shoes!
Calm down!
What's going on with you?
Oh, that's right!
I've been a typical Japanese guy who loves America since I was a kid.
Basketball, football, candy, Hollywood, rock and roll!
America only!
Viva America!
I'm a big fan of America!
Why is he doing something like that to protect the heart of Japan?
Yeah, it's just a habit.
Catherine likes Japan as it is.
I think the same way.
I'm not going to let this happen!
Chikara.
Welcome.
Three years ago in the summer, I was working part-time at a pub to save money for my trip to America.
Then I was sent there.
I happened to see Catherine passing by.
Wow.
I fell in love at first sight!
I believe Catherine is the mirror of the Japanese man.
Why?
That's why I'm traveling to America.
Now I'm the owner of a pub.
I'm the owner of a pub.
Chuhai, Umesawa, Nikujaga, you know!
I'm not a fan of Catherine, who likes Japanese beauty.
So when I was having a strange fantasy about Japanese men, I was not involved in her.
I hid myself in her.
I started to take in the boyishness of her.
She'll divorce me if she finds out about this.
No way.
Can you continue in your life?
This is my America.
If I come out of this, I will become fiery for Catherine.
I'll do my best.
Uh!
Ah!
The hole...
It's here!
I'm sure there's an empty space in here!
So, the shoes of the most precious person, Michael Jordan...
Shit! Unbelievable!
Come back, Michael!
Mr. Ryo, please!
Please take my treasure back!
I get it, I get it!
Calm down!
What were you talking about, Yamato?
Well, it's a man and woman thing.
Huh? The empty space is being captured!
Mr. Ryo!
I've been wandering around here for a while
and I've been bored.
I've been trying to get down from my neck.
Here, take this.
Thank you very much!
I'm so glad.
Yamato, are you back?
I forgot something.
I'll be back soon.
Are you all right, Yamato?
How long are you going to keep doing this?
You'll find out someday.
Even the gods who believe in you won't see you.
I'll talk to you someday.
I see.
Bye.
What's wrong?
Um, can you teach me how to make takoage?
I've never made it before.
It's cheap.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
Yamato?
What's this?
Is this your room?
No, this is...
Yamato, did you like basketball?
Well...
Um...
Did you like Michael Jordan,
Karin and Eastwood?
Catherine, that's...
Did you lie to me that you like Chiyonofuji and Takakura Ken?
Did you lie to me that you don't need anything else
but natto and pickles?
That's right!
I'm not a Japanese-style man.
I prefer hamburgers to rice.
I don't like sweet painful taste.
I've always been wondering why you were hiding something from me.
Why didn't you tell me?
If I tell you the truth,
I don't think I'd be able to say anything to you.
What about you, Yamato?
Did you marry me because I'm an American?
Did I have the same collection as you?
No.
I'm not that kind of woman!
I'm just sad that Yamato lied to me!
Idiot!
Catherine!
Catherine...Catherine is out!
She's out!
Did you find out?
Yes...
I searched all around the school, but she's not here!
Please help me!
I can't live without Catherine!
Yeah, I know. Hang in there!
You didn't go back to America, did you?
C-Catherine!
It's all my fault. I was stupid.
I couldn't play takoyaki with Catherine after all.
That's right! That's what happened!
Huh?
Yamato...
No! Please stop!
Don't say that! Let's go play together, sis!
It's fine!
Just one drink is enough!
Excuse me!
What's wrong, bro?
One more?
How about we drink at home?
The food is the best!
And we have alcohol too!
Alcohol?
Yes!
The legendary drink, "Otokozakari Kippon" is available!
Please have a drink!
Otokozakari?
Sounds good!
Hehe...
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Hm?
Long time no see.
Catherine!
You're late!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I couldn't get off work.
Are you angry?
No.
This way!
Here! I forgot this place!
Alright, let's go!
Yeah!
Alright!
Here we go!
Here comes a nice breeze!
Let's go all together!
Okay, Junpei and Kanpei!
You go, too!
Alright!
Yeah!
Don't race!
Pull the string!
Good!
Next!
Can I go now?
Yes!!
Ready?
Wow, you're amazing.
That's right.
It's not the time to be happy.
Yamato, it's your turn next!
Be brave!
Yes!
Good luck, Yamato-kun!
Okay!
Hurray!
Okay? I'll let you go!
Okay!
Pull the string!
Don't be hasty!
Pull the string as it is!
Put the octopus on the wind!
I did it!
I got it!
Okay!
It's looking good!
One, two, line up!
Yamato, you go to the other end!
You go between Junpei-kun and Pappe-kun!
Don't let the string get tangled!
Yamato, God is watching!
I'm watching!
Wow...
Catherine...
Catherine!
This is how I feel!
What?
I...
I... love...
I... love... you...
I love... you...
I love you!
I'm glad you came out of nowhere.
Thanks, Captain.
I'll help you to the table, so be prepared.
Thank you, sir, for asking me to work for you.
I'll help you to the table, since we'll have an open gate tomorrow.
Thank you, Captain, for your help today!
Thank you, Captain!
Thanks, Captain, for your help today!
Thank you for your help today!
" AMAZING CHAKAN, Monster"
Thank you!
Thank you, Captain!
Why, why, why, why, why?
Ryo, why?
Why?
Ryo's eyebrows look like black black eyes
He wears sandals but he runs really fast
Why?
Ryo always does arm curls
He's so flirty but everyone adores him
Why?
It doesn't matter
But the title of this anime is so long
Katsushikaku Kameari Park, here
Why?
Everyone together
You're here again, Professor Tondemo
What? A mask?
You can make any face with this?
It's like the double-faced Kaijin
Okay
Okay, we'll play with it
Next time, Ryo's double-faced Kaijin
Thanks for watching
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!