Team up with Sando
When you're watching TV
Make the room lighter and try to look away
It's like somebody's calling
After the rain
After the rain, I walked back and forth
I held my mother's hand
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black side of the Ake-dogai
I was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
The politician with a proud face
And the blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and see that corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall there
Ah, I'm sure
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Another politician's bad habit?
Seriously, he only cares about his own good
He doesn't think about the people at all
I think that if you don't improve the bad system in Japan,
I don't think the bad habit will disappear
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about adult society
Oh, I see
Then it has nothing to do with me
As usual, you are indifferent to politics
In the world, it is easier to live without knowing anything
If you make a plastic model every day and read a manga, you will be happy
I envy such an idiot
What are you talking about?
Then it's like I'm living without thinking about anything
I'm thinking about politics
Oh, then tell me the name of the politician
What?
What's wrong? Don't you know?
First, Ryunosuke Akutagawa
Hikoroku Hayashiya
Mikimatsu Yanagi
Parco Hayashiya
There is no one correct!
Well, you should die without knowing for the rest of your life
You don't have to say such a disgusting thing
It's more difficult for you to understand politics than teaching the chimpanzees English
You don't have to say that
It's true
But it's not good to say that you don't know and throw it away right away
How about telling Ryo-chan that he understands it easily and carefully?
I see
Well, then, as you understand, I will tell you about food very carefully and kindly
Let's say there is an animal village here
We are the residents of the animal village
We are going to build a building in our village
We will choose a company to build there
Raise your hand if you want to make it
Yeah
But in fact, the construction company has already decided
A lot of money flows to the mayor, the officials, and the politicians
And because the building will be built in tax
We will spend several times the real amount of budget
Then we will divide the money we have earned and earn it in the back
When the construction is over, the back money will not be included
So I will ask the mayor for the next construction forcibly
Of course, I will give you the money
Thank you very much, sir
The mayor will also earn a lot of money
So I will give you permission to build a lot of buildings
Yes, OK
Hahaha
To put it simply, it's like this
Do you understand?
Our tax money is like that
Millions of dollars are used for public construction every year
What?
Millions of dollars?
That's right
It's really used like that
Really?
It's hard
I'll tell everyone
Everyone knows
Only Ryo-chan doesn't know
Why don't the citizens get angry?
You can't complain about that
Even if money moves in an invisible place, the real feeling is thin
I'm giving up half
It's the same as saying yes to not complaining
It's such a bunch of people who just spilt the work that they worked with
It looks like a strange life
There's a election, right?
Election?
I see the election
That's right
In the election, vote for the person you think this person is
He will work for you
If that person acts, won't the crops go away?
It may not be that easy.
Look at this!
Who is the person you can trust?
Can you tell that easily?
I-I don't know...
Alright! I've decided!
I'm going to the election!
What?
Leave it to others.
If I become a politician, everything will be solved.
It's not like you're going to vote for a student council member.
That's right.
There are a lot of election funds in the election.
That's why, Reiko Nakagawa!
Can you give me a little bit of your money?
I thought that was the case!
I refuse!
Why do you have to go through such stupid things?
What do you mean, stupid?
I'm done with you.
Hey, Nakagawa-kun.
I refuse, too!
Why?
The motto of the Nakagawa Group is not to give money to any student council or candidate.
No way.
Is there no way?
I can't give it to anyone.
Are you sure you can't give it to anyone?
I'm sure.
I'm sure you can't!
Is it wrong for you to ask for so much money?
No matter how much you ask for it, I can't!
Men, do something about yourself!
Yo-chan, do you really think you'll be an elected candidate?
He's going so far...
But I'm worried about the future of Japan if you actually find it right.
I got it!
Thank you for waiting!
Oh, you're quick!
I'm the best!
If you want to run for election,
leave it to me.
The one who will be the first to win
is Congressman Daigoro?
Yes. From the small presidential election
to the US presidential election,
in every election,
I will definitely let the candidate
who will be the third to run for election
win.
Professor, leave it to me!
I will definitely give you
the red carpet!
Professor,
you sound good.
You really will let me win?
Of course!
Alright, I'll leave it to you.
Thank you!
Now, I would like to
start the election campaign.
Then,
let's go to the car.
By the way,
how much is the election funding?
We don't have that.
You don't have that?
No.
No?
No, it's fine.
Let's start from the election funding.
How?
The fastest way is to have a party.
You're encouraging the
Chief of Staff, the Chief of Staff.
You're encouraging the Chief of Staff, the Chief of Staff.
Rolling Stones, Momus,
Sugerio and Fujiwara Norika.
Is this true?
I wonder.
It seems that the ticket is very popular.
Anyway,
let's go and see.
Anyway, let's go and see.
So,
It's too late.
I'm so anxious.
I've been on the line for a long time.
We're in a big success.
We've got so many people.
Thank you for taking time to show us your work.
But today is really a mess.
Thank you for the wonderful food.
I hope you will enjoy the best.
We've been hanging around.
Ridge of the Golden Calf.
You're kind, aren't you?
You're a bad wuss, and you don't have to go back to school.
NO!
Let's play!!
What's with you?
You were drunk, so that's why you're here and you're gonna steal her from me, m'boy?
What the hell, you're such a scumbag!
That's a good point!!
"Do it, now!"
"Laaay!"
Take my life...
I'll put it in a zip-up thread...
"No!"
Take my life...
I'll put it in a zip-up thread...
♪ Love is a trap ♪
♪ I'm in danger ♪
Thank you for your help.
Please come to my house.
I want to thank you.
What are you talking about?
I'm glad you're not injured.
I'm sorry.
Are you a traveler?
Miss, I'm a traveler.
I'm not a traveler.
Please let me live in the car.
What is this?
Thank you for your attention.
Now, I will introduce the performers.
First, Mr. Taro Sugiryo, who appeared in the movie "Friendship".
Mr. Taro Sugiryo, who appeared in the movie "Friendship".
Taro Sugiryo, who appeared in the movie "Friendship".
I don't believe in Mr. Taro Sugiryo.
Next, Mr. Norika Fujiwara.
Mr. Norika Fujiwara, who appeared in the movie "Friendship".
This is different from Mr. Norika Fujiwara.
This is certainly Norika Fujiwara.
Please take a good look at the pamphlet.
klfv
The letter is written as "Qual" instead of "Kaoru".
Gah!
I-I'm going to use my dirty hands!
It's like the pamphlet, so it can't be helped.
In this case, Rolling Stones and Morning Musume will also...
Thank you for waiting.
Now then, the second part, the start of the calligraphy show.
The singer is everyone's familiar...
Rolling Stones!
And the backdancer is...
Morning Musume!
The backdancer is...
I knew it.
He's too arrogant and angry.
Well then, let's hear it.
My Way!
Now!
I don't want to get involved, so let's go home.
That's right.
Well, as expected.
Yes, it was terrible.
But, teacher, now we have a perfect election budget.
I see.
I'm going to go to the election with such a look.
I will definitely, definitely win!
Teacher! Good morning!
How are you, teacher?
I am sorry to interrupt, but this office...
Yes, it's not so bad.
Speaking of Thor...
What is this poster?
I don't remember taking such pictures.
And why is it Raghavan?
It is an image strategy to get the vote.
The people of this city are deceived by these refreshing images.
So we used the computer to compile it.
I made a hiragana so that it was easy to remember the name.
Who bought this dharma?
Yes, it's me.
Ryouto sensei is a big power candidate.
I'm ashamed of you.
I'm sorry.
It's big.
Sensei, I'm going to ask for a discount.
Discount?
It's the "Niwa Akatsuki" I won.
That's right.
However, it doesn't matter how you make a election pledge.
There are few people who win and protect their pledges.
Therefore, it's good to have a speech that has an impact on the hearts of the people listening to it.
I'm an ally of the salaryman OL.
Japanese people work too hard.
The red moon I won is the one of the state.
They are forced to work 24 hours a day and have 3 hours of time for work.
They also receive two months of holidays.
I will make sure that this will be realized.
CG is 10000 yen to the younger people.
Video software is 150 yen.
Movie tickets 80 yen.
Academic there are two courses and a limited time.
Old school although现在 4學校。
I'll protect all this.
Dads, when I want to be a member of the government,
I will get my family's food after receiving the Government's food policy and I will avoid trouble and muddy food making at home.
Thank you, teacher!
You have a good schedule after this.
Please rest for about 20 minutes.
But I'm not sleeping with my hands in the air.
I'm showing this outside the car, so don't worry.
It's not worth it.
I'm back!
Camera, hurry up!
Teacher, as agreed.
Leave it to me. I have confidence in my acting skills.
I have confidence in my acting skills.
Hello, everyone.
Ryo-san, how are your hands?
I can't read them clearly.
I'm just working hard.
You're so thin. You're working hard.
Teacher, it's time for dinner.
Thank you for your hard work.
Only rice balls?
You're so fit.
If I die while exercising as a politician,
I'll be in trouble.
Wonderful.
Teacher!
A telegram from your family!
What's wrong?
My father...
My father has passed away.
He fought against the Byouma to support my victory.
It's too bad.
I'll definitely win for my crying father
and offer him a silver bowl of rice balls.
Now you have 30,000 votes.
But, is it okay?
I killed your father without permission.
Don't worry about that.
Your father invited you to a hot spring far away from the people.
Don't come out until the election is over.
Teacher, thank you very much.
No, it's nothing.
I'm finally back.
I'm hungry.
How's the vote count?
Well, the Kisamachi Party is in the lead,
but the votes aren't enough.
If we get 100,000 votes, we'll be safe.
Leave it to me.
I have a good idea.
Mr. President,
Ryo-chan's political broadcast is starting!
I didn't expect him to be on TV
other than the incident.
Next, we'll broadcast
Mr. Ryo-chan's political broadcast.
Born in Asakusa, graduated from Senzoku High School,
15 times on the streets,
became a policeman,
and killed countless people.
He was executed 18 times.
He's making me embarrassed.
This is Mr. Kankichi Hatsuyoshi's political broadcast.
It's meaningless.
Welcome to today's meaningless show.
Here's a letter.
From Mr. Kankichi Ryo-chan.
Does this have any meaning?
Or not?
The chief told me
to be a little more normal.
Ready?
It doesn't mean anything.
What is this?
It seems to be mistaken for a variety show.
I expected it.
The votes are coming in.
I'll get a vote too.
Please write "Tanuki, Tanuki Saburo"
in the tomorrow's vote.
Please make the sleeping Kiroshiro a man.
On one hand,
Mr. Kankichi Ryo-chan
is thinking like this.
First, Tanuki.
You can't lie to your wife and go to a beautiful place and a hot spring.
No, no.
Ah, is that really a curse?
No, that's not a magic either.
I'm sorry.
Sleepy.
You have a pool-like bath at home, but you can't go to the bathhouse and get your old man's back washed.
No, no.
Why are you sleeping?
Oh, no!
Hanamaru candidate.
What is it?
I'm saying that men and women are the same, but I'm not doing anything.
I have to do everything from water-based laundry to children's class.
No, no.
You said it well.
It's not something to avoid.
No, no.
Then, to everyone, come on, Kameari.
Top no.
No, no.
Donna Deba?
Dynatti?
No, no.
Hanamaru?
Yes, sir, please.
No, no.
Stop it! Stop it!
Where are you going?
You pervert! Stop it!
What's that?
That's your armpit too!
Kiss me!
Bye!
I fell!
You're so mean!
The voting starts at 7pm.
Mr. Uda, what do you think?
Hurry up!
Don't worry, teacher.
Look!
The computer predicts 99% of the votes.
I see.
It was a tough battle.
The media is waiting for you.
It's time for the climax.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Everyone, please step forward!
Is this angle OK for the dharma?
OK. Perfect.
Mr. Moriguchi, what do you think?
I think it's a wise choice for the people.
What?
Mr. Tokio, you've just finished the voting.
Mr. Kiyoshiro, you've got 650,115 votes.
Mr. Yoshiko, you've got 580,3585 votes.
What?
Mr. Saburo Kanuki got 5502113 votes
Mr. Kan-Kichi Ryotsu got 1 vote
Mr.Kan-Kichi Ryotsu got 1 vote
Mr. Kiyoshiro?
Is this right?
Sorry tomorrow.
Mr. Kiyoshiro, you've got 6 wishes.
H-hey, stop it!
Your viewers are out of brings.
This means that there are only a few of us.
So, the candidate who was very popular seems to have disappeared like fireworks.
How about this, Mr. Moriguchi?
I don't want you to underestimate politics, but it's scary.
What the hell is this?
I got enough votes on the data.
Why is it seven votes?
The teacher must perform such a full-scale performance.
Even if he receives such a vote, it will not be able to reach the vote.
The people are serious, so they will not vote for such a person.
Everyone, this is the end.
That's right!
No way!
So,
Ryozu Kakushi,
I came back while being embarrassed.
Well, the election is a water problem.
I thought I might have to work hard at the police station again tomorrow.
What are you talking about?
You are no longer a policeman.
What?
If you run for the state, the civil servants will lose their jobs.
It's Article 90 of the Civil Servant Law.
In other words, you became unemployed at the same time as the Rakusen.
What?
Did you not know, senpai?
Poor thing, it will be hard from now on.
Chief, can't you do something about it?
Hey, let go!
There will be no use of my power at this rate.
I'm not a general!
Don't be suffocated! It's annoying!
Please, chief!
Do something about it!
I hate the election!
What?
What is this?
My fingers hurt
I'll just brush my eyebrows
and then I'll go to the station
DASH DASH DASH
I'll sleep on my dad's back
on the main train
This week, I'll be doing my best
I'll be doing my best
I'm putting the bucket in one hand
but I'm feeling a bit hot
I'm feeling a bit cold
I'm feeling a bit irritated
but I'm feeling a bit irritated
I'll get over it
Every day is no problem
If the hot train passes through the blue
I'll get better with a sleeping pillow
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
Monday
Monday Monday No Problem
What?
The cash carrier that was carrying the bonus was attacked!
Damn it!
Taking away my precious bonus!
I'll take back anything and everything!
Huh?
You're a plumber, you idiot!
Why are you all accusing the culprit?
Next time on Bonus Soudatsusen Five
Please take care of me!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!