First Meal withstory
"Ah, again this year the summer has come."
"The weather is getting hot, the water is boiling, the hot weather is swollen."
A big chest, a chest, a chest, a chest
A big chest, a chest, a chest
"Wake Up! The Civilian Police!"
The
The number of medals?
No, it's not that.
When it comes to the Olympics, there's always something.
The Olympic temperature?
It was good in the Tokyo Olympics, wasn't it, Minami Haru?
No, it was more impactful.
Ah, the one where a woman smacks her face with powder.
That's compact.
Hmm, it's coming out to the throat, but I can't remember.
Huh?
That's right, it's a cicada.
It's related to cicadas.
Cicada?
The one crying right now is an oil cicada, right?
It's not an oil cicada.
Then, is it a tickling star?
Huh? It's getting closer.
Was there another one?
Ah, the one that cries "Kana Kana"?
Huh? Is it an idiotic cicada that can't cry with kanji?
It's not that, it's a sunfish.
Huh?
Sunfish?
Yes.
I see.
I forgot about it.
It's impossible.
It's the same as the Olympics, and it's only once every four years.
It's been four years since then.
What are you talking about?
Other than us, the sunfish is working in this office.
Huh?
I don't know such a person.
Me neither.
I don't know you guys have been working here lately.
I guess so.
I guess he was the last one to go to work.
He was working for the Barcelona Olympics four years ago.
So, you've been working here for four years now?
I'm just a lazy man.
I started working here about three days a month.
But it's become so much easier for me.
I'm only working here once every four years now.
Once every four years?
Yeah.
That's why it's called the Olympic Man.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe there was a man worse than Ryo-chan.
I can't believe I'm being fired.
The sun life has a special ability.
Special ability?
You'll understand if you bring it to me.
E-Ehh...
I-I'll hold back.
You're the only one who knows about the sun life.
Go ahead and tell me!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah, yes.
What!?
The sun life has a special ability.
Senpai, you're just going to wake me up,
but why do you need heavy equipment like that?
You'll understand when you come.
You live in the same dormitory as Senpai?
I feel like this is the room.
Senpai, it's a storage room.
It's not a storage room.
People are living here.
Ah, here it is.
It's rusted.
Nakagawa, open the door.
Yes.
Move, Nakagawa!
Hey, sun life! Are you there!?
I'm not going anywhere.
You're not going anywhere.
You've been dead for four years.
But you can't see anything if it's this dark.
Nakagawa, open the door.
Y-Yes.
O-O-Ouch!
A-A-A-A...
My face is sticking to my face!
C'mon, show yourself!
Now what are you waiting for?
How are you going to act before a police officer is here?
A batik coat?
It's so bright!
I'm gonna have to use the bath...
Oh, I was thinking...
that's why you better do your thing.
Nakagawa, lend him that.
Here you are.
I'm glad you're here.
Every time I wake him up, he's like Dracula.
Is that Ryotsu?
Yes. I'm here to pick you up.
What? It's still the summer of Heisei 4...
No, I slept a little, so it's not autumn yet?
It's been a long time, and this year is Heisei 8.
You're stupid.
Then what happened to the Japanese Shinto, which was booming after the war?
That's not a big deal anymore.
What?
So what about the
Then, isn't the Prime Minister Mr. Miyazawa?
Mr. Miyazawa?
Well, that was four years ago.
While you were asleep, you changed to Hosokawa, Hada, Murayama, and now you're Hashimoto.
Did you really change that much?
The governor is also Yukio Aoshima.
I'm Yukio Hiroshima
You can't win me
The Osaka governor is going to say that Yokoyama is a nock
Wow, I understand
Really? What happened to Wakahana and Takahana?
Wakano and Takano were renamed
Oni-chan became Ozeki and the younger brother became Yokozuna
The world has changed so much
It's like Urashima Taro
That's right
Ryo-tsu, who is that young man?
Nakagawa, who became the head of the escape room this year
Anyway, don't sleep and wake up
Don't say that
I know you'll be mad
First, I'll get a hang of it
I can't do it, I can't do it
Please wake me up
It's broken
This is
I can't get it
I bought it when I went to sleep
Buns and bread are no good
It's red
What about the milk?
No good
It's heavy
What?
It might be cheese
This is okay
You
It's okay
I don't need Mom
Then watch the TV until the end
I'll be making a break
See you
It's good to watch while sleeping.
Next, let's go to the bathroom.
I'm sorry, but I'll take you to the bathroom next time.
Where is the bathroom in this room?
Is the washing machine the bathroom?
You put on your sheets and pillowcase.
I'll wash them with you.
And turn the water bottle upside down.
This is the best.
It feels good.
It's a great place to be.
Change into this.
I'm sorry, but please open it.
It's a time-consuming thing.
Shut up.
Are you okay?
Yes.
But I'm not feeling well.
I might not be able to sleep.
You're too sleepy.
Am I?
This way.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
When did you make the stairs here?
They are old.
Did you forget about them?
Come to think of it, I fell on them four years ago.
Yes, I fell on them eight, 12 years ago.
It's after all.
Hey, don't tell me you came here and walked for 15 minutes.
It's boring.
Let's go by my car.
Did you have a car?
A new car!
It's a new car!
I bought it 20 years ago.
I've only ridden it twice, so it's a new car.
You can take a taxi twice in 20 years.
It's a pain in the ass to pick it up.
I've never been out of town.
I'm going to go.
Step on the clutch and put the shift lever in the row.
That's right.
The clutch...
The clutch is like a new car.
Turn it down in 3 seconds and you'll be in town.
It's amazing.
But I woke up.
I brought you here.
Thank you.
It's been a while since I walked, so I'm tired.
I'll go to bed.
You're still a big boy.
You're still the same as you were four years ago.
You're really taking care of me.
It's him!
Hey, wake up, Higurashi!
Yes, yes, I'm awake.
Say hello to the chief!
Chief, it's been a long time.
Are you still the chief?
Thank you for your help.
I'm a monk who was dismissed three years ago.
Hello, I'm Higurashi.
Y-yoroshiku.
I'm a fan of Mr. Miyazawa Risa.
The other day, I bought a popular photo book called "Yontafu"
and I want to see it with you.
Oh, yes.
I don't like people who talk about such a photo book.
Next is...
I'm home!
Hey, Reiko, I'll introduce you to someone.
Oh, this is the rumored...
Hello, I'm Higurashi.
I'm a monk.
I'm Soun Higurashi.
Yoroshiku.
I'm Reiko Akimoto.
Higurashi has finally woken up.
You're weak like a woman.
I can feel it!
What is this?
The incident is calling me!
W-what happened?
Higurashi finally got a real record.
Hidari!
Bring me the unsolved case file!
Okay!
Yes, sir!
The first one is an unknown man.
I see him.
He works in a construction site in Yamagata City in the Northeast.
Terai, write to the headquarters immediately!
Yes, sir!
This is Higurashi, the first officer of Kameari Park.
He woke up!
The second one is a jewel thief.
The culprit is hiding in a house in Sumida River.
The Yamanawa team is taking a detour to the apartment on the other side.
The Kekkon Sagi team is taking a detour to Kaminari-mode in Asakusa.
That's amazing.
They have a lot of investment.
Higurashi solves unsolved cases like this every time he wakes up.
Next!
I'm tired and sleepy.
Idiot!
You haven't worked for four years!
Reiko, rub my shoulder.
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
Higurashi has a great ability.
OK.
It's a camera.
Here.
OK.
See?
What are you doing?
A light shade.
Now Higurashi can record an incident that happens within 24 hours.
You can do that?
Yes!
What's that?
It's the underwear thief!
There's been a lot of damage to the ship lately.
But we don't know who the culprit is in this photo.
It's pretty cool that he's hiding in the shadows.
Well then, let's see it in this photo!
Four in a row! That's amazing!
I'm getting more and more good at this.
Huh? What's that? It's a dog!
It's a dog that barks a lot while patrolling.
Alright, let's go!
Okay!
This house...
What's this?
This is the house that delivers the most underwear theft.
It's called "Toudai Motokurashi".
This house is full of Amura's nasty women.
Amura? What's that?
Amura is a fashion icon of top idol Amuro Nanai.
Wh-What?
Isn't the top idol Ms. Miyazawa Risa?
Risa has lost weight and is currently on a diet.
N-No way...
Don't get depressed, Higurashi.
I'm not.
Let's go!
Why is Taku-chan the culprit?
You can't arrest a culprit, so you're just making excuses.
What?
Wh-What is this?
Higurashi has a motor power.
He has a motor power.
This is the secret to their power.
That underwear is stolen!
No way...
Higurashi, you did it!
I can still feel it!
Nakagawa, the camera!
Okay!
So it's a bank robbery this time.
I remember this bank. It's right in front of the station.
Look, the clock is on.
It's 3:05.
We only have 10 minutes left.
Okay, Reiko. We'll head straight to the bank.
You take care of this.
Roger.
Hurry, Nakagawa!
Yes, sir!
The next day
Everybody, raise your hands!
Give me the money!
Welcome!
It's a gorilla!
What's a gorilla?
You bastard!
Hey!
You're in my way!
I'll kill you!
What?
Now!
Damn it!
Put your hands on the table!
Hey, Higurashi! Put your hands on the table!
You're sleeping, you bastard!
You all did well.
But Higurashi has a really great ability.
I don't know why he can't get a job.
What's wrong with Higurashi?
Huh? He's been here before.
I'm tired. I can't take it anymore.
If you don't like the race, just keep the main race.
I don't care how many cars you get, just let me drive.
What are you doing?
Sir!
Higurashi is trying to solve another case.
Is there one or two cars?
Did you hear?
Huh?
Boom!
Wow. I feel it. I feel it.
Which car is it?
Which one? Which one?
I can't believe it!
I knew you were going to use a race car.
What?
Oh!
I-I'm being pulled into the truck!
Yeah, that's definitely Ryotsu.
That's a bad photo.
Hey, Higurashi! Why would you take a photo like that?
I don't know. I just took it.
It's not a quick death. It might save you from a traffic jam.
I'm not a follower! I'm not going to be pulled into the truck!
Ryotsu, don't worry. There's a mistake.
I'm perfect and confident, but I'm not worth a billion dollars.
Are you encouraging me? Are you bragging? I don't believe you!
You're blushing while saying that.
I'm not joking!
Senior, I'm outside as long as I can see the photo.
I'm safe if I don't go out for 24 hours.
Shut up! You're scared of the police?
I don't believe you!
Hey, Senior!
Don't do that, Ryo!
Shut up! I don't care!
I told you to stay out!
I'm not going out!
Hey, Senior!
Ryo!
Are you okay, Senior?
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
So this photo is the moment you hit the truck you're in.
Hey, Higurashi!
You should sleep for a million years!
Don't wake up!
I'll do that.
But before that, Chief...
Oh, the usual ceremony.
Reigo, 10 Tendon, 10 Una-don, 20 Yakiniku, and 10 Sushi, please.
What?
Why don't you...
Ah, I forgot to tell you guys.
topics.
We have two projects taking place.
The first is to go on the road,
and the second is to go to town.
I see.
There have been issues in many places.
They want to see you,
but we aren't very welcome.
I see.
Oh, I see.
Then,
We're going to the Olympics.
I can't believe you're this fat.
You're like a different person.
Then, I'll see you in four years.
Shut up! Go home and sleep.
Well, then...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Next time we meet, it'll be the 2000th year of his life.
The next Olympics are waiting for us.
Good night.
Don't be silly.
Go to sleep with us.
You can say that.
Do you know Kachidoki Bridge?
When a big ship comes,
the bridge is split in two.
The bridge goes up a little.
Unfortunately, it's not open now.
But this Kachidoki Bridge
has a nostalgic memory of my childhood.
Next time, open Kachidoki Bridge.
Thank you.
Let's smile anytime
Even if something ridiculous happens
Please smile cutely
You can go out with a face that doesn't matter
Please smile
You're not bad
With the same mood as before
Yeah
Always smile
The woman who has a deep heart
is not beautiful
You should smile right away
If you're not a child
You're not a child
You always had to smile
Even if you are a child
You still have to smile
Don't cry
"The