John's
When you watch the television, make the room bright and look far away.
Mari
Come to me if you're not rich.
I'm not rich, but...
I'm worried about you
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen
To the blue sky
Come to my place
If you don't have a job
I'm not here
But don't worry
Look, it's burning
Red clouds
I wonder what will happen
To the blue sky
You know, right?
You know, you know
If you know, be quiet and follow me
Leiko's Summer Memories
A special express Azemichi train run in the fields as far as possible
The scenery reflected on the train carriage seems to bring the heart that modern people have forgotten back
The journey is really good, isn't it?
Right, Leiko?
Yes
What are you doing, the Night's
Soldier?
It's not easy to get drunk with a can of beer.
It's true.
And it's a special express train.
I've been on the train for a long time, so I've been bored.
It's not just a trip.
I'm going to find a memory of Reiko-san.
A trip to find memories is romantic.
It's a nostalgic view.
It's a place where you can see the old memories of Reiko-san.
It's nostalgic.
Senpai was born in Tokyo, right?
I've been in Asakusa all the time.
When you say hometown, you remember this view.
That's right.
I think this is the hometown of Japan.
Just looking at it, you can see the warmth of the sun and the smell of the grass.
Ryo-chan, you're like a poet.
Which one?
I'm not like a poet.
I'm a poet.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm a poet.
I've seen this view when I was in elementary school.
Don't be stupid.
This is the landscape of Japan.
Reiko-san was born in France and grew up in Europe, right?
I don't think she was in Japan when I was in elementary school.
But it's true.
This is the landscape.
That's right.
I remembered.
When I was in elementary school, I came to Japan only once.
I saw it at that time.
Really?
Yes.
That is...
I came to Japan as a new generation ambassador to deliver paintings to elementary schools in Japan.
I was impressed by the landscape of Japan that I saw for the first time.
Is that here?
I wonder.
There are similar landscapes all over Japan.
It's definitely here.
There's no doubt.
But there's something more important.
What was it?
Hey, Ryo-chan.
Can you take me to this place?
Why me?
Summer vacation.
I told you that I haven't taken it yet.
I'm good at finding things like this, too.
So why do I have to do that?
During this time, a piece of the drink that the chief was cherishing came out of Ryo-chan's trash can.
What?
Who was it that said that he would make a fire in the back and burned the book?
Oh, I got it.
I'll go with you.
Yes.
Thank you, Ryo-chan.
I'm obsessed with the weakness of people.
But even if you say you're looking for it...
I'll ask the publisher.
It's a terrible countryside.
You can't go back to the day.
You have to ask for a strong assistant in the countryside.
So I called the queen of the countryside, Miss Mammushi.
It's not Miss Mammushi.
It's Miss Kakashi.
It's the same thing.
No.
What's more, it looks like you're taking me on a trip.
Oh, it's my own.
What a big, stupid train.
What's your age?
You're in quarantine right now.
Is this a mountain road?
Are you sure this is the right way?
What?
I can't hear you.
I can't hear anything because the cicadas are so loud.
Well.
Leave the navigation to Komachi.
I went to the countryside on purpose.
I caught the man who sells at a high price for this opportunity.
I'll make you pay for this. I'm stronger than I remember!
Hm?
What's up? Why are you so quiet all of a sudden?
I knew it. I thought you wouldn't move if I was here.
Ryo-chan, you were talking too much.
We're in a big place.
Right? We're on the way to the countryside.
This is why we need to be careful.
As expected of the queen of the countryside.
She's grown up in the countryside, so she knows the way to the beast.
Shut up.
I've never heard so many cicadas.
Hey, Komachi. Why are the cicadas in the countryside so energetic?
I don't know.
Because the cicadas in the countryside fly from one forest to another for a long time and they move a lot.
I told you I don't know. You're so persistent.
Do you have a dialect for your crying voice?
Hey, Komachi.
Shut up!
Moscovite!
Hmm...
Wow, this is a long road.
That's enough.
An endless horizon.
I feel dizzy just thinking I keep walking this way.
I feel like my head is going to hurt if I keep walking down this road.
It's okay. The air is good and the car isn't running.
Sorry. There's no bus or taxi.
We're all from the countryside.
We're used to seeing the horizon and it's nothing.
But in Tokyo, you don't see the horizon first.
We, the locals, are overwhelmed.
We don't want to be in the hands of primitive people who are wild.
Even if we have the strength, we're just stupid.
Stupid power has nothing to do with it.
It has a power to move, but it doesn't have the ability to move.
And we're bored with the same scenery.
That's not true.
We're surrounded by such a rich nature.
The dust and the red of the city are being washed away.
There's a problem with nature, too.
Ryo, that's how you think about it.
It causes environmental pollution and natural destruction.
Reiko, you're not saying anything.
This thing itself is an environmental pollution.
This thing?
You're a misnomer.
I don't want to hear that.
I don't care.
I'm going home.
You can do whatever you want.
But the train station is 30 kilometers away.
You don't have the money, do you?
Only 100 yen.
If you can go home, go home.
Damn it.
It's a hell if I go home.
I can't see anything.
And it's so hot.
You're a fool.
I didn't go home.
I don't want to go home.
Seriously.
You're so crazy, when I say the name same.
This is an issue.
OK, I'll see you at 9 pm.
Bye-bye.
Oh no!
Let's leave him alone and go.
Yeah, we can do anything with Nojuku.
Wait, I'm kidding. I'm sorry about Nojuku, too.
You must be tired.
But the stars are so beautiful.
The sleep of insects is so romantic.
You're so moody.
He was only in one room, so I had to do it with him.
Let's be quiet for a while.
I'll be quiet for a while.
You'll be.
What? Where's Ryo?
He's sleeping well.
He was really tired.
Well, let's go to bed.
Yes!
I'm the big boss.
I'm the boss.
Money!
It's mine!
Let's take a break at this shrine for a while.
It's better to take a walk in the morning.
It's over 35 degrees again in the afternoon.
Is that true?
It was pretty cold last night.
After that day, it gets extremely hot.
I dragged him out on that cold night and caught a cold.
What?
The least about ourselves
The lost old man
It's here.
Look, curious bird.
Come on, it's here.
The head debt
What's about an unnamed bird?
Where does it live?
What about the bird?
It's the place where the painting was drawn.
There's no doubt about it.
Yay!
While I was delivering the painting to elementary school,
the car went flat.
While I was fixing it, I was waiting here.
French?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
But I remember that a French woman was with me.
Isn't that Reiko's mother?
No, she's different from her mother.
She was someone else.
This is a new mystery.
Maybe if I go to elementary school where I delivered the painting,
I'll remember more details.
That's right.
We came all the way here, so let's go.
Yes.
Are you still going?
You know where we are, so it's okay.
There are more than that.
Don't complain.
We came to find Reiko's memories.
I remembered one more thing.
The person who drew that painting,
Mamia Shinzou.
What?
Is he famous?
We know him, too.
He's super famous.
Is he expensive?
He's a famous painter in Europe,
who's the result of the Ecole de Paris movement.
His new works, of course, and his old ones
are also traded at a considerable price.
A considerable price?
About 10 times.
10,000,000 yen?
Is this a elementary school?
You'll feel better when you hear about money.
It's not like I'll be mine.
There are three, but which one?
I don't remember the name,
but which one is this?
The direction is completely different,
and the distance is long.
It's a 1/3 chance.
What?
At a time like this,
the idea of growing up in the countryside of Miss Mammush is useful.
Come on, Komachi,
Choose one.
Um...
That one!
I'll take the one!
It's a 1/3 chance.
No, it's not like this.
I haven't walked for three hours,
and it's useless.
There was a big clock in the middle of the school.
A clock?
I hope someone is there for summer vacation.
Shall I ask?
What is it?
Ah, that's Ipponsugi Elementary School.
Really, it's the opposite direction!
I can't guess the feeling of Komachi.
What?
I need to go there.
What's the matter?
It's fine.
Huh?
The school will be closed this spring.
The demolition work should start this afternoon.
Hurry up!
I'm so excited.
I'm suspicious.
The school will be closed.
It's a demolition project, so we don't need any pictures.
Yay!
I got 100 million yen!
I got it!
The school will be closed.
It's going to be destroyed soon.
Damn it.
We have to stop it.
Go, Ryo-chan!
I came all the way here to get 100 million yen!
Hey! Wait for me!
Stop!
Ah...
We've been looking for you.
Shoku...
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
We have to give up soon.
Ryo-chan!
Don't you think you could give up?
What?
If you don't give up, your memories will disappear.
Not just your memories, but French people too!
Ryo-chan!
Don't get mad.
How do you understand what I mean?
The one who finds the picture and makes his own is everyone else's.
Let me know!
Eat my stone!
I can't find anything.
It's okay, Ryo-chan. I'll give up.
Reiko.
Excuse me, but are you looking for something?
What?
I've been working as a mercenary here until this spring.
Hmm...
Ah, you're back to normal.
I remember that painting very well.
Oh, so you were the young lady from that time.
Yes, but I couldn't reunite with the painting of my memories.
No, if you're visiting that painting, you don't have to worry.
Huh?
Is that painting somewhere?
Yeah.
Ah!
Where is it?
Where on earth is it?
It's in the museum.
The previous principal donated it to the museum.
The museum?
100 million yen?
Ah, don't worry about it.
So, what is the museum?
Ah, it's about 3 hours away from here.
Are you walking again?
If you don't mind, I'll send you by car.
Really?
Why can't I just run?
It can't be helped.
It's a four-person ride.
Yes, it's a full-time job.
Idiot!
I'm sorry.
15 years ago, there was a museum in the prefecture, and they collected art pieces related to Gotouchi and exhibited them.
I'm glad.
With this, Reiko's memories will come back.
Uh-huh.
I'm sorry.
Shin, be quiet in the museum.
Even if you say that, I can't breathe.
This is that painting.
I'll tell you the name.
PK-4
Huh?
It looks exactly like the pendant Reiko-san is wearing!
What?
The colors and shapes are exactly the same!
This is a piece of her grandma's work.
She cherished it so much.
That means, perhaps...
The model of this painting is Reiko's grandma?
Then, the girl is...
Reiko-san's mother?
Grandma...
So that's how it is.
This is Mamiya Shinzo.
Mamiya Gaha-kun!
One hundred million yen!
Idiot!
I drew this landscape decades ago.
I wanted to visit it again because I saw it on a travel magazine.
It's strange that I can meet you there.
I thought it would be a surprise when I passed by you, but now that I see it, it looks just like Madame Arbeil at that time.
Soon after the war, I decided to become a painter and went to Paris.
I thought that if I went to Paris, all my wishes would come true.
But the reality was more severe than I expected.
Sadly, I couldn't sell a single painting and I ran out of money.
I was kicked out of the apartment I lived in, and despair was wrapping around my chest.
...
Her name is Arbeil.
She was a great artist like Fujita Gohaku, who was active in the war.
She spoke one-word Japanese.
Her family raised me with kindness.
I felt at ease and thanked everyone, not even a word.
I couldn't thank anyone.
I wrote a painting with all my feelings of gratitude.
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . ...
After that, I returned to Japan and was lucky enough to be recognized by the world for my work on Japanese scenery.
The one on that magazine is also like that.
So that painting led you and Reiko to this point.
Yes. After I finally started selling the painting, I left a letter to Arvel, but I came back without a clue.
Since then, I have never heard of her rumors.
I don't know much about your grandmother either.
According to her, when I was in elementary school, I was told that I would donate this painting to Japan.
I didn't know that this painting existed in Japan.
Probably because I was Japanese, that's what she said.
Yes.
If Arvel hadn't saved me at that time, I wouldn't be here today.
Thank you.
If you have any troubles with money, Arvel gave it to you to sell.
Yes.
But that's what I never left behind, no matter how hard it was.
It is yours.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thanks you.
I'm glad we came together.
Yeah.
That painter was probably alone.
That means, maybe he's been thinking about Reiko's grandmother all along.
Well, it's kind of romantic, isn't it?
It means that everyone has a heart-pounding memory.
What?
What do you mean?
I didn't get any money, but this trip was worth it.
He's smiling.
How creepy.
Oh, the bus is here.
Everyone, get on.
Yeah.
This guy is so painful.
The bus is here!
Wait!
Ryo, the bus is here!
The bus is here!
I'm relieved.
Wait!
The bus is here!
Where did he go?
Where am I?
Hey!
How am I supposed to get home?
I don't want to go to the subway anymore!
Let's drive!
"A"
"H"
"I
"W"
"U " "R"
I walked with a look back
I asked my mom
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So
I walked on the outside of the arcade
Only the black part
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above my eyes
Look up
That corner
Everyone, everyone can see
There is a wall
Ah, there must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Ghost?
Why are you attacking me?
Did you defeat the temple priest?
What? Find a lover?
What is the 12th floor?
Where is the 12th floor?
See you next time!
Thank you!
I'm sure there is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!