Appearance of Kylo Ren
Hey, hey, when you watch TV
try to make your room bright and keep away from it
ONE HOUR LATER
When it rains, as if someone is calling
♪ After the rain, the place where it started to rain ♪
♪ I walked while looking back ♪
♪ My mom pulled my hand ♪
♪ At that time, I felt a strange feeling ♪
♪ So I walked on the red-colored tile ♪
♪ I walked on the black tile ♪
♪ Everyone was a child once ♪
♪ But everyone has forgotten ♪
♪ Politicians with a great face ♪
♪ And a blue aunt above their eyes ♪
♪ Turn that corner ♪
♪ Everyone ♪
♪ Everyone can meet you ♪
♪ There is a wall ♪
♪ There must be a wall ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
Hypercop!
Kanden Police Hypercop!
A criminal organization of evil
Hitakura!
A special police force created to fight against evil!
That's Hypercop!
To protect the peace of the earth,
the five members of the Hypercop continue to fight today!
I'm going to release the toys of this program at my company!
Look at the poster!
The company's name is in it!
It's true!
That's good!
With this, your company will become a major!
When is the ceremony?
From next month!
Every Monday from 4 a.m. to 4:05 a.m.
Every day, from 4 a.m. to 5 a.m?
It's time for everyone to sleep!
Even so, my grandpa is still awake.
It's a child's play, rougan!
This is the toy기로 for the play.
The Sports曲 "HyperArm"!
That is the masterpiece!
"Hurricane Punch"
What is a serious 8-year-old doing here?
With the computer,
it responds to the motion of the sound.
It can sound like a lot of things.
There are toys that look like before!
When you use the special move, you have to turn your arm like this.
Isn't that a trick?
What? Don't do that with me.
My special move is even more amazing.
First, turn around 35 times.
And then turn around 20 times.
Again, turn around 15 times.
And then turn around 7 and a half times.
Again, turn around 5 times.
It's like a safe.
It looks like it's going to be pretty tough.
Special Hurricane Punch!
What do you think? Isn't it a powerful sound?
Well...
You can use not only your arm but also your legs and your belt.
When you combine them all, you get a hypersuit.
And you can play a lot more.
Okay, I'll try it.
Automatic lock is on.
What is it?
When you wear a hypersuit, it locks automatically.
So that it doesn't come off easily.
I see. It's well made.
It's pretty cool.
The only problem is that it's a little heavy.
Because it has a powerful motor.
This is the instruction manual.
It's as thick as a phone book.
Okay, let's try this Hyper Claw first.
Hold your right hand at 75 degrees.
Turn around 365 times in front of you in 1.0.5 seconds.
You're going to do 365 times?
250th try, and now you're going to do 10 times with your right leg.
Yeah.
In addition, put your bar out on top of your head.
Stand on your toes and rotate your entire body 10 times.
Put two pencils on your nose.
Move forward with a gyaru.
Pull, pull, pull, pull.
I don't think it's a very heroic move.
Finally, push from the inside.
And hit.
Hit.
See, it worked.
What's this?
That's why you're too poor.
You don't have any sound effects.
I think so.
I thought it was interesting.
In the first place, there are too many times to say 365 times.
Children will get tired.
No, no, no, no, no.
This product will never sell.
In fact, there is another function in Hyper Suice.
Voice sensor function on the back.
What?
Voice sensor?
See, heroes have various決めポーズ.
Hyper Attack.
Hyper Fighting.
Hyper Carnival.
That makes it easy.
How?
When you shout out loud, this voice sensor catches that voice.
Hyper Fighting Pose.
I see.
You move with the spring of the whole body.
When you stand for 10 seconds, the pose will be automatically released.
Use this from the beginning.
Oh, that's right.
All right, let's try it.
Oh, are there five people doing it?
There are five Hyper Cop.
In fact, we have a test product for all.
All right, you guys can wear it.
Let's do this pose.
What?
Why are we?
We have to wear it.
That's right.
We are working, senior.
That's what you mean.
Listen, from now on, this company will be tied up with the TV station without knowing it.
When you try to go out of your way to sell toys.
I don't think you'll get a punishment if you monitor that product.
Isn't that a police officer loved by the citizens?
Hey, you can say something to him.
Can't you cooperate with us?
This product is a matter of our company's good fortune.
Please.
All right.
If that's the case.
I will cooperate.
What?
I'm fine.
It's a good feeling.
Ryo.
Ryo, there's one more left.
Don't worry. I'll do my best.
Hey, Ryo!
What do you want?
I've been waiting for you, Honda!
Wow!
Tokusatsu heroes usually ride bikes, right?
I've been longing for it since I was a kid.
Okay! Let's start with the basic pose!
Hyper Red!
Hyper Blue!
Hyper Pink!
Hyper Yellow!
Hyper Blue!
All five of us, the Hyperpops, are here!
It's all set, everyone!
It's like a TV show!
Okay! Next is the gathering pose!
Let's go!
Are we doing it here?
We should stop it for a bit.
I don't want to do it!
You're annoying!
You can't escape from the sensor function!
Hyper Pyramid!
No!
You're annoying!
Are you okay, Ryo?
I told you to stop it!
Hyper Pyramid is impossible in such a small place.
I hope it's here.
Here we go! Hyper Pyramid!
Ah, no!
This is my cup of tea.
Hyper confetti!
Oh, no!
You're not giving me a drinks!
You want to play a game or something?
Come on!
Hyperly!
How do I do?
Do it!
Oh, I'm glad you enjoyed it!
This is not funny. I'll monitor it for a while, so you can leave it alone.
Really? That will help.
Then, please take care of it.
Leave it to me.
Well, what kind of pose should I take next?
Are you still going to do it, senior?
You've already done enough, haven't you?
I have to go back to work soon.
I'm going back to the exhaust pipe.
Hyper through!
Hey, Ryo, what are you going to do?
It's not like that. Hyper through is a pose of hyper pink, so I made it a little.
Oh, my God.
Hyper shift!
Ryo!
This is also a pose of pink, so I made it a little.
Give me that explanation.
Hyper bandai!
Hey, Ryo Tsukakichi!
Hey, hehehe!
Uo!
Kutukutuku!
Oh, no!
Ryo, stop it!
Hahaha!
Hey!
Hyper Komane!
Oh, no!
Hyper In!
Oh, it's embarrassing.
Hyper Chonwa! Chonwa!
Quick! Quick!
What?
Hyper Chikuribambo!
Eww!
No!
Oh, my God!
Hyper Emi!
Eww!
Hyper Sama!
Sama!
Eww!
No!
This is so much!
Hyper Gentai!
Stop it!
No!
Hyper Doona!
Hyper Chichiguribambo!
Chichiguribambo!
Gyu!
Hyper Komanechi!
Komanechi!
Ehi!
Hyper Chonwa!
Chonwa!
Oh, Bambi!
Enough!
Not funny!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hahahaha!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Um...
But I really have to go back to work.
We can't just leave the station open forever.
This is automatic lock, right?
What should we do to get it off?
What's that?
You're a bad person to be with.
Huh?
What's that?
The automatic lock release method.
Release, release, release.
Found it!
Turn your right hand 300 times and do the moon 100 times with your left hand.
Huh?
And do the rabbit jump 150 times.
Next, do the vertical push-up 80 times.
And finally, do the Hindu squat 200 times.
Huh?
No way!
Is that the only way?
I think so.
This seems to be the only way.
No way!
This is fun.
Anyway, we have no choice but to do it.
I'm so tired.
My arms are sore.
You can do it, Honma!
No!
You can't.
That's too sudden.
You may have to start over.
Almost there.
Hang in there!
Hyper Fighting Pop!
Ups!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
Did I do something?
DON'T DO IT!
Almost there.
Hang in there, guys!
RYO-CHAN!
Ah, ah.
Hyper Fighting Punch!
Ryo!
Why did you get in my way?
Nothing.
This is a big deal, so stop being mean!
Hmph.
That's because you're weak.
I'd be easier.
Hmph.
Then show me the proof.
Alright. Watch me.
Hey, watch me. Watch me.
It's almost over.
Hmph.
Hyper Fighting Punch!
Hey, Reiko!
It's the money you gave me.
Damn it!
But it's not even that bad!
125, 126, 121, 128, 129,
75, 76, 77, 78,
197, 198, 199, 200!
How's that?
Oh!
You're the best, Senpai!
You're so strong you'll go crazy!
I guess I'll just have to break it and take it off.
You're the only one who can do that.
By the way, where's Ryo-chan?
What are you doing, Senpai?
Powering up the Hyper Suit!
Strengthening the motors and springs in each part,
the battery uses five powerful lithium batteries.
It also increases the voice-reaction pose.
Is that okay?
You're modifying the product on your own?
It's an improvement.
It's better than before.
The auto-lock is on.
So that's how you get a golf club.
Hyper T-shirt!
You can swing in an ideal form.
I see.
And even in tennis,
Hyper Smash!
Hyper Homelike!
Hyper Ping-pong!
For pro-wrestling fans,
we've included the Mexican pro-wrestling Lucha.
Hyper Lucha!
Hyper Paw!
Hyper Kawaii!
Senpai, it hurts...
Let me go!
This will change every single person
to become a pro-wrestling athlete.
It will also sell to adults with lack of exercise.
As expected of you, Senpai.
What about some herb tea?
Great idea!
Herb tea?
It's about herb tea.
Consider it tea then.
You guys use side characters too much.
Hm?
Here! The herb tea!
Uwaaaah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What's wrong, senpai?
Suits is doing the Hyper Lucha pose without permission!
Uwaaah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Why is he suddenly doing that pose?
Reiko-san, what did you say when you were making the tea?
I think it was "Here! The herb tea."
Uwaaaah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
That's right!
Senpai's suit mistakenly recognized Reiko-san's "Here! The herb tea" as "Hyper Lucha!"
Uwaaah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
What the hell!
I'm sorry.
Oh, my voice sensor is too loud!
I'm Tsurukame Ken.
Oh, right, I was asking for a date.
Here, parkour mask.
Uwaaah!
What are you doing, senpai?
This is Hyper Gomen!
Let me explain.
Hyper Gomen is a terrible technique that makes you hit yourself until you feel like it when you make a mistake or make a mistake.
I see. So this time, you misheard Hyper Gomen as Hyper Gomen.
It's certainly similar.
Hyper Gomen and Hyper Gomen.
Hyper Gomen.
What a terrible technique!
Hey! Don't say Hyper Gomen again and again!
Uwaaah!
Senpai, you'd better take it off. It's dangerous!
Come to that!
Why is it not working?
The reaction has become dull.
I'll fix it.
Come on, do it again!
One more time!
200!
It won't come off.
It's not broken, is it?
200!
What the hell?
It can't be helped. Let's disassemble it.
You should say that now!
I'll do it.
Hurry up.
What's going on?
It's broken because I modified it.
I don't have the strength.
I'll take it off.
What's going on?
It's broken.
This time, it's Double Hyper God Hand.
It's too narrow.
My head is crushed.
I can't do it.
Hyper Fighting Pose!
I was saved.
I see.
That's how it works.
As expected of Reiko.
This time, the Hyper God Hand Switch...
Hyper Fighting Pose!
I was saved.
If it gets dangerous, I have to take this pose.
Don't you want to fight?
No.
Captain!
Ryotsu.
What are you doing?
I don't want to fight, so I'm not posing like this.
What happened?
Captain.
The bank robber is running away with the cash.
Go after him immediately!
Roger that!
Ryotsu, you too.
Take off the toy quickly.
If it's easy, I won't have to work hard.
I'll take it off.
He's coming here.
Don't block the road.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
Captain, I'm going to show you the power of this toy you made fun of!
Hyper Sprint!
I see!
Is this how you use it?
It's a real Hyper Cop!
He's run away!
What?
You can't run away!
Hyper Choke!
You too!
Hyper Kick!
You won't get away!
Hyper Sprint!
It's a big horror!
Oh no!
The Hyper T-Shot switch is working!
Hyper Fighting Force!
Hyper Sprint!
This is bad!
Oh no!
The Hyper Home Run switch is working!
Hyper Fighting Force!
Hyper Sprint!
The Home Run Show!
That officer is shouting something.
Hyper Tackle Kick!
You're taking your time.
I'm going to shoot you!
Hyper Fighting Force!
What?
I knew it!
You're starting to take that pose when you scream.
You!
Hyper Fighting Force!
You always do that!
Bello! Bello!
Oh no!
Hyper Sprint!
The pose is fixed!
What?
Mr. Nick, wait!
Hyper Sprint!
No!
This is Hyper Sprint!
The most important specification.
Hyper Sprint is the most powerful enemy,
hit by jet radiation,
and self-destruct,
a super-imoto move.
I can't believe this really can self-destruct!
.
It seems like it's a big hit.
What do you mean a big hit?
They even put a self-destruct device on the toy, geez.
Anyway, it's good that the president of the toy company became a major.
There's too much trouble with safety.
Hey, Ryo-san, are you okay?
Hey! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Thanks to you, I got hurt.
No, it's bad, it's bad.
But thanks to you, Hypercop has a high ratings.
And I even decided on a part two.
So, as the second episode of the Hyper Suit series,
I made a thing called Hyper Suit DX.
Hyper Suit DX?
Try it again, Ryo-san.
Don't be silly. I'm definitely not going to do it.
Ryo-san!
Hyper Suit is no longer a toy.
It's a Gori Gori!
Aww! I'm hungry!
Why did I have to keep eating until I get my medical checkup done?
Huh?
After this, we'll all go to eat yakiniku together!
Let's get this over with!
I'm totally fit and healthy!
It's going to end in a flash!
Next time, Ryo-san goes to eat with humans!
Don't miss it!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, surely Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!