Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset that floats on the river bank ♩
♪ I took off my love stone and flew to the end ♩
♪ I wonder if I'll be able to go on a jogging trip ♩
♪ I laughed that I was just a child ♩
♪ Even if I'm doing well somewhere ♩
♪ I have a reason to be happy ♩
♪ The cityscape that never changes is kinder than evil ♩
♪ The wind is blowing because of the glass ♩
♪ Are there any yakitori hovari? ♩
♪ I'm wearing a hat ♩
♪ From the water's stream to the taishakuten ♩
♪ The sunset is falling ♩
♪ I'll wake up tomorrow and end it ♩
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♩
♪ I realized that I'm an idiot ♩
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ But it seems like I was wrong ♩
♪ Please listen to me closely ♩
♪ I'm a robot ♩
♪ It's irrational ♩
♪ It's impossible to get there ♩
♪ I don't know where I should go ♩
♪ I have to hurry ♩
♪ I heart-wrench myself ♩
♪ So I can always fall ♩
♪ I'll take your life with all my might ♩
♪ Take your life with all your might ♩
"Ryuu-chan's house"
Hmm...
That's good.
Cleaning done!
Let's go!
No!
I'm going to polish the windows from the morning, so I'm going to do this!
Ryou-chan, it's dirty!
Ryou-san!
Hey! I'm not a dog!
It's really cold!
The chief Oohara warned me that there would be a lot of important guests coming today.
How about me?
I'm the chief of the police, so I don't care about important guests.
I'm sure the chief Oohara was worried that you would be a bother if you told Ryou-san.
The police chief will be here today, senpai.
Police?
They will give you a list of the national police stations.
The police chief will give you a list of national police stations.
Bye-bye!
It's called "Michelan" and it's like a ticket for the police station.
Ryou-chan, you've heard of it, right?
Hmm...
I've been in a police station for five years and I got a test for a missing person.
Hey!
I knew you'd come!
It's like a visit to school.
Anyway,
If you're in the top three class, you'll get a gold medal and a good reputation as a model police station.
A gold medal?
Bye-bye!
Anyway, the gold medal is a great honor for the chief Oohara.
We want to help you.
The police station is a safe and secure place for citizens.
It's a safe and secure place for citizens.
I think it's a strong shield.
And I want the inspectors to see the efforts of the people who share the same thoughts as you do every day.
I want the police station members all over the country to know about it.
I strongly, strongly...
The chief said that.
So Ryou-chan has to be especially good at business.
Don't make me a fool!
I'm not a bad person.
I'll do it if I have to.
So, is the chief still there?
He said he'd come out early today, but he's late.
Oh, welcome.
You're late, chief!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Huh?
No, Ryou-chan.
The preparations are in full swing, chief Oohara.
I see, Hiromi.
You're a young lady, aren't you, chief?
Ah, thank you for your hard work, Rei-ko-kun.
Everyone helped me.
I see, I see.
It's a priest.
Oh, it's a priest.
Chief?
Nakagawa.
It's Nakagawa.
Nakagawa, thank you for your hard work.
I'm nervous now.
What are you going to do?
Please be strong, chief.
It's dark.
Chief!
Are you all right, chief?
Please be strong.
Ryou-chan and I are violent.
Then I'll be light.
What?
I just fell for it a little.
I forgot that I had something important to tell everyone.
Something's on your face, Ryotsu.
You didn't wash your face?
You're such a pain.
Hey, are your eyebrows connected?
No, they're not, chief.
Chief, you look weird.
Yeah, pretty weird.
What happened?
Chief!
You're so hot, chief!
It's alright. I'll just keep working.
Chief, you should lie down.
Yeah.
I'm really fine.
Chief!
This is bad!
What's good for your fever?
Give me Nakagawa's coat and iron.
Okay.
Reiko, there's an actual futon...
Yeah, I'm going to get daikon!
Hey, why is he going to get some daikon?
Well then..
The hot pot...
That's where you put it, right?
No.
That's the futon.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I have some medicine so, I should be in bed for a while.
I'm fine.
Why don't you rest here for a while,
and then send her home after you calm down?
Right.
I'm such a big boy.
I don't know what you're talking about, so you don't have to talk, boss.
When the death comes, I'll greet you.
Don't forget to wake me up.
Boss!
You're so clumsy!
Listen!
Now that you've gone to Daigo,
we'll have to get through this.
Yes, sir!
Excuse me!
Here they come!
Hello!
Hey!
What's up?
It's the day of the factory!
What's this plastic thing?
It's a figure from the Robodeca Banjo I ordered from the factory.
The Robodeca Banjo?
It's the character from the manga you were working on, right?
You can have it delivered to Nico Nico Ryo!
Yes, but the factory is a week late,
and if we don't paint it and send it to the customer,
it'll be a problem.
You're going to have a difficult time making it work.
You'll have to wait forever.
Let me go!
No wonder they get it so easy for now.
Oh!
No, no!
I hope the factory doesn't get shut down,
and we'll be able to get this done...
And so I hope the factory gets loud!
If we can't get things done,
I hope this won't turn into a nuisance!
You know what?
I'm getting dizzy, but I'll go check on the chief.
Nakagawa.
Huh?
Look at this.
What's wrong with the website?
Here's the problem.
Why is my picture here?
Thanks to you, Roboteca Punch's figure has been ordered ten times more than it was supposed to.
This is a violation of the copyright!
I can't let this happen!
So, if the figure's delivery is delayed, you'll be in trouble too.
Isn't that terrible, senpai?
Don't worry, Nakagawa. We'll take care of this.
I understand.
I'll help you.
Then I'll have to hide this somewhere.
You're so honest.
Don't let it come out. We don't have any left.
I know.
See? It's sticking out.
You're so clumsy.
Reiko.
Yes?
What's sticking out?
The chief?
If the chief finds out, we'll be in trouble!
Shh!
Ryo and the others are so loud.
Reiko.
Yes?
What's sticking out?
The chief said that the fever is coming from the cold.
I took a shower, and my legs are numb from the unadjustable seat.
Please bear with it.
I'm worse at cleaning up than you.
You're bragging about your long legs.
No, I'm not!
What's wrong, Reiko?
No, chief.
Whose legs are long, Reiko?
See? You can hear everything over there.
What can you hear, Reiko?
That's...
The senior is the one who's bad!
Which senior is bad, Reiko?
I'll do it to you, too.
What are you doing?
Reiko!
What are you doing? I don't know.
I can't hear you!
Reiko!
Yes, chief.
I think the inspector will be here soon.
No, chief.
You have to sleep.
I'll wake you up when he comes.
I'm sorry, Reiko.
Yes, chief.
You won't be able to sleep all day today.
It's not a problem.
It's a problem.
There is a problem.
There are only empty stations.
Who's next?
Kameari.
What's wrong?
You're here?
That's the security guard?
No, it's me!
What? What? What?
What's wrong?
Ryo?
Senpai?
Don't look at them. Help me!
Father?
Ryo?
You're the one who did this?
I didn't do it!
If you collect things like that,
the security guard will be very surprised.
I can't be a doctor anymore!
Father?
I was wrong!
Hey! I'm not the one who did this!
What?
Then...
You're wrong!
I was wrong!
That was close.
I hope the director's fever goes down.
I'm sure it will.
I'm sorry.
I really am sorry.
I was wrong.
I have a problem.
I don't know why.
I'm sorry.
If you need anything, you can call me.
Yes.
He's really sharp.
He's also a tough guy.
But he's a bit of a pain.
But the problem starts here!
Help me! I'm going to be eaten to death!
What is that voice you hear in the back?
Can anyone explain it?
I'm not sure.
Emergency training begins!
Hey, wait! You're throwing away your weapons!
You guys, scream!
Please stop!
The villagers are sad!
Who the hell are they?
Like this, we, the first-class officers,
are prepared for emergency training with a sense of tension.
Training, huh?
Emergency training, first.
Don't bite me!
So, who's in the back?
Hey, hey, hey!
You're going to die!
Help me!
Who's there?
Super Team, fight!
That's tape!
Tape?
Hey, you there!
You're not allowed to park here!
Move the vehicle now!
I'll make the biggest move expensive!
See? It stopped.
It's tape.
Tape, huh?
It's either a good or a bad.
Thanks to you, the worst situation has been cleared.
Yeah.
Then, I'd like to ask the representative.
What?
Representative?
Please call the chief, Daijiro Ohara, the chief of the patrol.
What should I do?
Um, the chief is a little...
I see. The chief is a blood-related person.
Tape.
Wait a minute!
The chief of the patrol is here!
Reiko!
I said...
Then, call him. Right now.
He's here, but...
He's here, but he can't show his face.
Is that so?
You're a arrogant, arrogant, and perverse chief.
Tape.
No!
Reiko!
Oh!
Don't write that!
I'm not even a police officer.
I'm the chief of the patrol, Daijiro Ohara!
I'm not qualified to be the chief of the patrol!
I'm going to be punished!
What?
What are you doing?
I'm going to be punished?
What do you think you're talking about?
I've just been here to check on the police.
Give it back!
I won't.
Reiko, calm down!
The enemy is bad, Reiko.
Who are you two on the side?
The police are really arrogant and even more.
My name is Reiko Akimoto.
Write it down here!
I'll call the chief right now, so please wait there.
Ryo!
Ryo, it's hard!
This is harder!
The police officer wants to see the chief.
What should we do, Ryo?
What do you mean, what do you mean?
This is...
I said I'd call him.
Why did you say that?
If you don't want to be punished, give it back!
Not now!
What do you want me to do?
I'll ask for your help.
You're late.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm the chief!
Chief?
Thank you for waiting.
I'm the chief, Daijiro Ohara.
Ryo, you can't shake hands.
I see.
What can I do for you?
Then...
Then, I'll ask you some questions.
What questions?
Ryo, you're the chief.
Just an easy task!
As expected, Senpai, if you say "yes", you'll be dependable.
Y-Yes.
Then, please种 what kind of work you doing, What are the target objects
Within 5 seconds...
Within 1 seconds, 2 seconds, 3 seconds...
That's an easy one.
We're talking about convenience.
Within 3 seconds.
Within 1 second.
So, by improving the staff's health,
and by aiming for a fun and comfortable place to work,
everyone's morale will increase,
and it will lead to the safety of the citizens' lives and a peaceful life.
In other words, if you think about the future,
it will be desirable to introduce a single computer from now on.
There are double beds in the break room.
At night, it's troublesome to lay and raise the futon one by one.
If you keep laying it, your parents will scold you.
Ryo-chan...
He's getting better and better...
Ah!
Digital sun plasma TV!
It's super thin and big.
The break room is small.
Plasma?
And, of course, the bath.
The one that produces bubbles.
If possible, it can be used as a sauna.
And it's a mountain bike for private use.
This is bad!
They'll find out!
-Fish! -Fish!
It's coming again!
Ah!
I'm not done yet!
Let's go!
Ah, no, no, no!
I'm not done yet!
I can't go on!
Eh?
Is that it?
What is the end?
Well, what would you like to hear?
Ah...
I'm going to buy something to drink with you.
Why did you do that?
This is a statue of Buddha and Buddha.
It's a statue of Buddha and Buddha.
I used to do it well with color.
Hey!
It's not up to the color.
I explained that there is a color.
Is that so?
I didn't see the sample.
So I dyed it in my favorite color.
The color of the flesh is the back of the face.
Well, here is black.
I'm telling you that's the face, grandma.
You are helping me with all your effort.
You are the one who is in trouble.
Ryotsu sensei.
Please.
Listen carefully.
From here to here is the hair.
I can't see the boundary with my eyes.
So don't make it all black.
Hey!
Don't leave me alone.
The examination is not over yet.
The heat is going down.
I'm getting a fever.
The inspector wants to see the director again.
What should I do, Ryo?
What should I do?
If this happens, I'll go.
Do you still need anything from me?
Yes.
What are you doing?
What are you?
Where is Ryotsu Kankichi?
Where are you, the commander?
Ryotsu!
Help me, senior!
You are...
What are you talking about?
I'm the director!
You are so mean.
I'm here, Ryotsu!
Ryotsu!
Sorry I have to go back to work.
I'm sorry...
Figure! Figure! Figure!
I'll shoot a figure!
Monkey?
Figure?
Give me the money.
Figure!
Oh no!
What color was this, Ryotsu?
I'm a big flower!
Ryotsu!
Don't say that!
I think you need to be strong to protect your safety and safety at home.
And I want you to watch the hard work of the police officers who are doing the same.
I strongly want the police officers to know.
On rainy days, windy days, and snowy days,
there are still many things to do before the Kamenari Park.
I'll explain it to you.
This is...
Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad! Bad!
Rain Bad!
Oh my!
Five people work for the police officers before the Kamenari Park.
They are going to the Pyozan office.
What should I do here?
On rainy days, windy days, and snowy days,
there are still many things to do before the Kamenari Park.
I'm glad there are many things to do before the Kamenari Park.
I can say this!
Thank you!
The evening after the rain
like someone's calling
Looked back while walking
in the morning, pulling my mom's hand
At that time, I felt
a mysterious feeling
So, I walked around Ake-dogai's yard
Everyone was once a child
but now they've forgotten
To politicians with cheeky faces
and
the old lady in the blue shirt
♪ Turn around and look at that corner ♪
♪ You'll see it for yourself ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!
Reiko brought a rich prince!
If you like him, you'll get a great reward!
What? You want to see Tokyo?
Then leave it to me!
I'll make you unforgettable memories!
Next time, "Reiko's Cute Prince"!
See you!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!