Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a stone ♪
♪ And flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ With my bike in the corner ♪
♪ And they laughed at me ♪
♪ That I was still a child ♪
♪ Even if I'm doing well somewhere ♪
♪ I have no choice but to fight ♪
♪ It's all my fault ♪
♪ The cityscape is so unchanging ♪
♪ It's so gentle ♪
♪ The glass is falling ♪
♪ The sky is darkening ♪
♪ I'm all burned out ♪
♪ I wonder ♪
♪ What kind of world ♪
♪ Should be like, starting from ♪
♪ This hazy island ♪
♪ And quipping all the suns? ♪
♪ The sunset is falling ♪
♪ I'm gonna wake up tomorrow ♪
♪ And end it, yeah ♪
♪ But I'll say, someday... ♪
♪ Even if I'm happy, ♪
♪ I lost it and I realized ♪
♪ Just that I'm such a stupid person ♪
♪ The world just ♪
Let's spread the word! The circle of change!
Kei-chan, that hair is wonderful!
Do you know?
Mouche Francois, right?
Mouche? Francois?
Yes, he is a friend's hair-making artist living in Paris.
His staff went to the shop in Roppongi this time, so they came to the opening ceremony.
I was also invited and had the latest cut of spring.
How is it?
It's light, natural and spring-like. As expected of a scissors champion.
Honda-kun, do you know?
Well, it looks the same as usual.
It's the same as usual. It's hair. It doesn't matter if it's there.
It can't be helped if a man wears only cool clothes.
Nakagawa! Nakagawa-san is cool! Please sign it!
Shut up!
Sign? Nakagawa is not an idol.
Damn it, it was almost finished, but it's remade again.
I'm sure Reiko-san went to London and had the cut, right?
Yes, to Mrs. Elizabeth.
No, are you going abroad on purpose for a three-part?
Rich people are different after all.
When I was just a policeman, I used to travel abroad in a Concorde for haircuts.
Concorde...
During my training period, I had a hair stylist come to see me at the charter school.
Charter school?
Ding-dong!
Oh, wow it's a charter school, the others aíl wasted money and spent useless money on my hair,
It's a hair sixth.
Even though you said that, your hairstyle was a big point that determined your impression of the person, right?
Speaking of which, Senpai is always awie, aren't you tickled the same?
My Angle of´Bird´sел rat is simply easy to order, I'm done with it.
If there's a cheap shop even for one yen it won't be expensive for you.
He drives his bike anywhere he wants.
My policy is that I don't care about his hair.
That's right. If you're a senior, you might want to cut your hair at that shop.
What?
There's a shop that specializes in cutting hair in Fukagawa.
Specializing in cutting hair?
Yes, but the owner there is a little different.
He's a little difficult to get along with.
What?
He doesn't like customers who don't like it.
What's that?
But he doesn't take money from customers he likes.
Really?
He's like a craftsman in the city.
I think he'll be popular again.
He's popular in cutting hair.
I heard that he'll have a cutting hair boom soon.
Okay.
Get the car, Honda.
That's the shop, the owner of Ryotsu.
Yes.
It's a normal shop except for the square signboard.
I'm scared of my father.
You bastard!
He's getting beaten up.
Don't show me that head again!
I'll beat you up, old man Kakugari!
You bastard!
I see.
What should I do for the eyesore?
I haven't been in the shop since I'm not a fan of Kakugari.
I don't like being scared.
What's that?
Never mind.
It's not like I need a smile just to be cut.
The eyesore here is my specialty.
What's that?
Senpai, be careful.
Yeah.
If I don't come back alive, I'll ask Kameyari for help.
Senpai...
What a blind face.
Where did you come from?
Money!
The match starts now.
I feel it.
I'm Hikaenasu.
I was born in Ryotsu, Kankichi.
I'm a smart guy.
I live in Kameyari now.
Oh.
I'm Shibata.
Is this where you learn about Kaku-gari?
I was born to be a guy.
I've never tried any other hairstyle other than Kaku-gari.
I'm clumsy.
Wait here.
Yes!
You're amazing, Asagawa-senpai!
You easily beat the first member.
The models look scary, too.
I'm not sure if I can beat them.
But Kaku-gari suits you.
The signboard, cream, and hairspray.
Even the decoration.
You're so good at everything.
You're a Kaku-gari master.
Done!
No turning back this time.
Too bad.
Turning back?
Next.
Yeah!
One Kaku-gari.
Before we start,
there are a lot of rituals.
A barricade on the hairpin.
Alright!
What's this?
What's next?
You're as good as you think.
You have a straight hair,
thick eyebrows,
and a thick neck.
You were born to be a Kaku-gari.
Thank you.
This is the first time I've ever been praised for my face.
I guess I've never been praised for my face before.
I feel like the manager likes you.
Most young men these days
are barely as good as you.
But when it comes to Kaku-gari,
you're not good.
You're not good enough.
OK.
This is it.
I eat all kinds of soft food.
My chin won't grow.
Dad!
Hey!
Don't move!
I'm coming.
This is more than 4,000 hairpins.
He's quiet.
How was it?
You got your manly face up, right?
Yeah.
I went whoop in the back.
That was a fun day today.
No big deal.
Lucky.
It is necessary to do that.
Sorry.
Bro,
buy it first.
Oh?
Some change?
My dream is that
all men around the world
may be Kaku-gari!
All over the world?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Senior Asugawa, you got a point for the first time.
What? A point?
Seriously?
That's amazing!
What are they?
I'm envious of you because you got a free pass for the first time.
What? A free pass for the first time?
This guy had such a great score.
What's with him?
I'm scared of Ryo-san's head.
I've been popular with girls for a long time,
but I was the most popular one for kids.
Is it because of this place?
We have to wait until they grow.
But the customers like Shibata's store.
They even give out things like this.
Is it a business?
It's rumored that the internal affairs are pretty strict.
He's really a stupid old man.
But if Shibata's management doesn't get better...
Then...
Then the free pass is a given.
No, it's not.
What? That's a problem.
What's a problem, Ryo-chan?
N-nothing.
Huh? Reiko-san, that hair looks great.
Oh, you know?
Yeah.
I don't get it at all.
It's natural and casual, like she's taking over the era.
As expected of Miss Elizabeth, the Scissors Queen.
There's a World Scissors Contest this weekend in Tokyo.
So, I came here suddenly.
I got a call earlier and got my hair cut for lunch break.
Miss Elizabeth is participating in the World Scissors Contest?
That's right.
I was asked to be the hair model for the day.
Me too.
I got a call from Monsieur Francois earlier.
If Monsieur Francois is participating in the contest,
it's a one-stop shop with Miss Elizabeth, right?
That's right.
What's that World Scissors Contest?
It's a world-wide hair cut contest
that is selected by hair stylists from all over the world.
So, it's going to be held in Tokyo.
Will you get a prize?
I heard the prize is 10 million yen.
10 million yen?
Honda, you said that the Scissors is going to be popular soon, right?
Yeah, it's a rumor in the Fukagawa area.
If you're going to talk about the spread of Scissors and the good of the market,
I think it's for the money.
My dream is to make all the men in the world a hair cut.
I'm not going to refuse that stubborn guy.
Maybe, senpai…
I'm going to pull Barber Shibata into Scissors Contest.
Barber Shibata
You can't be like that, Ishiatama.
Huh?
What happened the other day?
You bastard, what did you want to say?
I talked about the contest with Ishiatama the other day.
And then...
You can't just keep on talking about it!
Look at the world more!
Shut up!
Don't ever show me that bright head again!
Get lost, Kaku-gari-jiji!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Senpai, that's a bad guy.
Shibata, you two are parents, aren't you?
I'm not afraid of leaving Fukagawa after all.
You don't say!
Then let's have a contest!
Here's an example.
Yes.
The Riyoshi Association wrote a letter of recommendation for you with two replies.
I went around the neighborhood and heard that if Barber Shibata was to participate, he'd be cheering for you.
Everyone is looking forward to you!
Let's take the world with Kaku-gari!
Dad.
I understand. But only this time.
No way!
The prize is one in a million.
The contest will be in one Kaku-gari.
But that place is flashy, so Kaku-gari alone won't stand out.
That's the aim.
Honda.
Yes?
Yes.
Honda, contestant three.
Simples is best.
Look at the colorful and flashy scenery and play satisfied with all the black hair that stands out!
You're not talking about hairstyles. Your face is the main evolutionary factor.
Furthermore, the judges are mostly foreigners.
The votingés are from Tokyo.
So that's a good thing -- you already know the taste of Kaku-gari.
That's a bit boring, isn't it?
What?
It seems like if there was no blood, Kaku-gari wouldn't exist.
It's like you're not going to win
That's not what I meant
What do you mean, Honda?
In other words, you're the best at fighting
But you're weak
What's weak?
You think I'm second place?
Say something
You need a model that looks good at fighting to participate in the contest
I can't do that
Don't worry, I'll be the model
But the contest is over, right?
If you don't have a hair to cut, I won't be able to participate
Don't worry
Ta-dah
What's that?
You need to get the medicine
This spring, Nakagawa Chemical will be releasing the ultimate medicine
I got this from the back of my hand
Put this on your head
Rub it well
Wait a little
Oh?
It's about time
What?
You're like a primitive
I think I put on too much
Anyway, I'll be the best at fighting in Japan
I'll be the best at fighting in Japan
And I'll be the best at fighting in the world
I'll win for sure
Good
I have another plan
But I won't reveal it now
The next day
Let's go, Shibata!
Do you mean Takada's father?
Yes
Let's go!
Hurray, hurray Shibata!
Sorry to keep you waiting
We have a special guest
He's theислijke for the Sizzards
We will give him 100.000 yen
and a pair of scissors
That's enough!
Give it to me!
This pattern is broadcasted worldwide on satellite broadcast.
World Scissors Contest 2004!
Oh, it's started!
Now, the players will enter.
Oh, it's Reiko! Reiko, you can do it!
You're a hairdresser, aren't you?
That's fine.
Oh, there's Nakagawa!
Huh?
Nakagawa, you can do it!
What are you talking about?
I found a primitive man!
What? What's that hair?
He's like a real primitive man!
Shigata, you seem to be on a stage you're not used to.
I think everyone else is used to the contest.
Ah!
I fell!
Dad, are you okay?
I just got out of Fukagawa for the first time, so I'm a little nervous.
If I start to borrow, I'll be the same everywhere.
Alright!
The contest will have a technical department competing for accurate and elegant scissors,
and an art department to show off their originality.
Originality?
The two departments will decide the winner.
The total score of three top three people will be awarded with the Scissors Master Award.
The judges will be the world-renowned mass media, fashion designers,
and the public opinion experts.
Then, the technical department of the first stage, start!
You have twenty minutes.
Let's scissors!
Dad, you can do it!
Senpai, you can do it!
I'm sorry!
It's okay, so calm down!
You can do what you always do!
Leave the rest to me!
Okay.
You don't have to worry.
I'll take 10 million yen!
Whoa!
Huh?
That's… that's some hair!
What?!
Why is it growing?
How did this happen?
It's gonna be fine!
It's growing!
What is going on?
Could this be…
Alright, that's good.
You're doing good!
Shibata seems to have gotten better.
He seems to be feeling good.
Yeah!
*Badass music*
Alright, I'm done!
Finished!
Wonderful!
Beautiful!
I got the first stage!
*Giggle*
Next time, I'll be the best and get 10 million!
Senpai!
Eh? No, this is bad.
What did you say?
I think you mixed Kei-chan's company's medicine into everyone's spray!
This!
W-What are you talking about?
*Giggle*
Eh? Ah! W-What are you doing?
I knew it!
During the competition, the most important proof is that Senpai's hair was the only thing he wanted to drink!
Do I have proof that I did it?
When, what time, how many minutes, how many seconds?
Don't say things like that!
Ryo-chan is the only one who thinks like that!
That's right!
That kind of hair won't be a match!
Give up on winning!
There's no cheating in the second stage!
Next is the art department.
Then, the second stage!
Let's start the evaluation of the art department!
The time required is 30 minutes!
Listen! The enemy will decide in a flashy way, but don't be fooled by such things!
Just attack with a square!
Good!
Ah!
Please show your originality as much as possible!
Let's start!
Eh?
What does originality mean?
Well, it means that you are unique or that you have no other hairstyle, but...
Unique?
What's wrong, Shibata?
Look, Dad!
No, well...
They're already moving on...
Don't worry about others!
Ah...
Huh?!
It's a square!
We're just square!
Ah...
What's wrong?
Square cutting is tradition!
Is it okay without original hand?
It's okay!
But isn't the square cutting too plain after all?
No, it's fine.
When it's a flashy on parade, the plain ones stand out.
We just had a meeting yesterday.
Don't be confused.
Dad.
Nowaday, the kakugari is not popular.
Look at the world more.
Okay.
It's cold.
Shut up.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Nowaday, the kakugari is not popular.
Look at the world more.
What are you going to do?
30 seconds left.
Time up.
I did it.
Okay.
No way.
What?
Shibata.
Dad.
What's wrong?
What?
What's this guy?
It's Kenichi.
I thought the kakugari wasn't bad.
He quit running and started working at home.
It's a celebration of his adulthood.
I'm glad I got a hold of him.
I wasn't able to find him, though.
What's with him?
He's clumsy, so he doesn't like it.
He's troubled by his health.
I see.
Ryo.
I've been looking after you.
Thank you.
No, I'm not going to treat you like that.
I'm going to buy the head of the customer.
I've got more money.
It's going to be hard to manage.
No, it's okay.
I'm going to take care of it.
I'll see.
Oh, Ryo-san, can you please take this off?
You're not allowed to use the free pass.
What?!
I'm sorry about that.
I'll take the money, so if you don't apologize, I'll call the police!
Oh, there he is!
Hey, you were on TV the other day, right?
You're a thief, aren't you?
Can you just do it?
Hey!
You guys are suddenly talking back?
You're a guest, so don't get carried away.
Wh-what are you doing?
I'm telling the seniors to be careful how they talk.
Otherwise...
I'll do it like this!
Please forgive me for that.
I'm going to play with people's heads!
♪ After the rain, someone called me ♩
♪ I walked with a look back ♩
♪ I've felt an exclusive feeling from the memories from the past ♩
♪ So I walked on the dark side of the arched street ♪
♪ So I walked on the dark side of the arched street ♩
♪ I walked on the dark side ♩
♪ Anyone was a child once, but everyone forgets it ♩
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a camera over there, there must be a camera
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
I made a bicycle for Lemon
What? You stole it?
I won't forgive you! I'll let you know what will happen if you make me angry!
I don't have a bicycle!
Next time on Cycle Big Operation!
There is a camera over there, there must be a camera
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!