"The Greatest Fiction"
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and
look away.
"The Greatest Fiction"
Come to me,
you poor boy!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
What are you going?
Look at the blue sky,
the white clouds.
After a while,
I hope it's going to work out.
"The Greatest Fiction"
The old lady
Come to me!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look, the red cloud is burning
It'll be alright somehow
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then keep quiet and follow me!
I'll be waiting for you!
Kisan Sanzan! Once again!
Hmm...
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
I'm worried about tomorrow.
Ah!
I see. Tomorrow is March 3rd, Ryo-san's birthday.
I can't see Ryo-san's face on his birthday every year.
I can't go to work. I can't stay at home.
How about going to the game field?
The game field?
No, I'm going to lose!
Then, what about the pachinko?
Pachinko?
If I lose, the ceiling will break and the pachinko balls will fall.
I'll go to the manga cafe and read the manga.
The manga cafe?
I feel like I'll get in trouble for the fire.
Don't you think you're too worried?
No, I'm not!
I've been in trouble so far!
But I don't think that your bad luck is just because it's your birthday.
Ryo-san always seems to be in trouble.
That's the momentary end.
I'm in trouble.
Really?
I'm worried about my self-preservation.
Self-preservation?
Yes.
When I think that today is a bad day, I remember only bad things.
When I think that today is a good day, I get a good impression.
Good and bad days are determined by the mood of the day.
Ryo-chan thinks that bad things will happen on her birthday, so she feels like she's in trouble.
But in fact...
That's right.
Let's have a birthday party for Ryo-chan tomorrow.
What?
Really?
Yes.
After Ryo-chan finishes her work, I'll make you some food.
I'll prepare a present for you.
Then I'll have one too.
That's a good idea.
Let's call Honda-san, Volvo-san, and Sakonji-san and have a fun party.
Yes!
But maybe the party will be canceled because of some incident.
It's not good to think like that.
That's right.
Tomorrow is a good day.
If you think so, it will be a good day.
Got it?
Yes.
Finally, my birthday is coming this year.
Mail?
I think today will be a lucky day for Ryo-chan.
I believe so.
I believe so, too!
Yes, I do.
It's a nice day.
I'm sorry!
You're a good boy!
I think today will be a lucky day for Ryo-chan.
I believe so.
That's right.
I'm lucky today.
Thanks to you, I saved something.
Thank you.
It's just water from squeezing out my muscles...
Well then, let's eat and go out.
I think the rice balls I bought last night...
My rice balls!
Hey, give them back!
No, no, no!
Wait!
Give me back my rice balls!
No!
Damn it, what's going on?
My breakfast!
I think today will be a lucky day for Ryo-chan.
I believe so.
Yeah, I'm lucky today.
That's right, today Reiko will prepare a lot of delicious food.
It's better to eat a little less rice.
No, if I ate that rice ball, I wouldn't be able to eat delicious food.
Lucky, lucky.
Ah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Huh?
I've been wearing sandals for a long time!
Maybe the wind I've been wearing...
Maybe it's because of the sandals.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure.
Tonight is a party, so changing my mood a little...
Glad I had a sandal broken!
Huh?
The brake doesn't work!
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Ah, no, no, no!
I'm dead!
Ah!
Come on!
I was saved in a soft place where I fell.
Water, water, water!
I'm glad there's a river nearby.
Senpai, you're late.
I guess I'm not.
I'm here.
Ryo-chan!
What's wrong, senpai?
I went to Tokyo Bay.
What did you go to?
I had a lot of things to do.
Ryo-chan is the star of tonight's party, so don't go anywhere without permission.
I know.
I brought you the three greatest delicacies of the world, truffles, foie gras, and caviar.
It's the best you can think of.
Please eat half of them.
Really?
Yes.
And the sake is also the best in the world.
Lucky!
I can't wait to try them.
Senpai, how about going to the battle?
That's right. Tonight's the party, so you should feel refreshed.
That's right. I'll do that.
Have a good day!
Ah!
What's going on?
There are crows everywhere!
A lot of crows.
What?
What's that?
Ryo-chan!
Let me go!
You can't get away!
3 of us together!
3-line Joy!
Okay!
Next, the trampoline set!
Hey! Let go!
Let go!
Stop it!
Hmm...
Senpai, what about the bath?
If I leave now, I feel like I won't be able to return.
Is that so?
Um, Ryo-san...
It's time for patrol, but...
You guys go ahead.
I'm going to take a day off.
Oh.
It's okay, Ryo-chan.
If you open the birthday party safely,
all the bad luck you've had will be blown away.
I wish so.
Okay, I'm going.
Wait!
I have to go to the library, too.
Ryo-chan, take care of the house.
Yeah.
I'm not going anywhere today.
See you!
I'm so bored.
I'll make a plastic model.
This one.
This will be easy on the desk.
Here we go.
Hello?
Senpai, I found a very interesting shop
while patrolling.
It's an interesting shop.
It's an old toy store,
and there seems to be something you like.
What? Really?
Okay, I'm going right now.
What?
I feel like I won't be able to return here
if I go out now.
Senpai, what's wrong?
There's nothing good there anyway.
It's just a waste of time.
What?
I'm not going.
But, senpai...
I don't want to get a call like this again.
I'm going to turn off the power so you don't have to come.
Just in case,
I'll hang it on my desk
so I don't have to go out all the time.
Huh?
If I hang it on my desk,
I can't make a plastic model.
Here.
This is good.
I'm starting to feel tired.
I've been up all morning.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm here to get my desk.
Um, hello?
Stop it.
He's really bad at waking up.
If you wake him up,
it'll be a big deal.
Is that so?
But, which desk should I bring?
This one, I guess.
There's nothing on it.
Put it on the truck.
Okay.
Ready, set...
Go!
I'm sorry.
I feel refreshed after going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Shall we go?
♪ Limitless
-Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
W-What the...? What's going on?!
Why?!
I'm back.
Oh, the desk is gone.
I heard that the old desk was going to be taken by the business.
But it wasn't here.
Where's Ryo?
Ryo!
Where did he go?
He said he wouldn't leave here.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Damn it!
Why is the desk I was supposed to be on here?
Why is it here?
Oh, the key!
The key!
Damn it!
I'm on the expressway!
Where are we going?
Huh?
Ryo, you're not here?
No.
When we got back...
You were saying something about the competition.
But I was really looking forward to today's party.
And he said he didn't want to leave the station.
But it seems he turned off his cell phone.
Anyway, let's get ready for the party.
Yes.
Let's go.
We'll look for Senpai.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
Then I'll contact him around here.
It can't be.
Snow?
It's snowing.
Damn it!
The weather forecast is off.
It's snowing.
It's cold when we go fast in this cold weather.
Kawatsunagi is still better.
I'll invest if it's free.
What's wrong?
There's a human hanging on the back of that truck.
It can't be.
There's a picture on the truck.
I see.
It is.
But it's a real picture.
The feeling of rain is getting stronger.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous! It's dangerous!
Oh, right! I had this!
I'll ask Nakagawa to come and help me with my phone.
Yes!
Senpai! What happened? You suddenly disappeared!
I don't know what happened!
I was sleeping in the toilet and then I suddenly came out!
So, where are you now?
Umm...
I'm in Aomori!
I'm heading to Hokkaido...
Damn, it's a street!
What a mess!
Did you contact Ryo-sama?
Yes, but he disappeared immediately.
Did you find out where he is?
No, I just found out later.
Oh?
Maybe he's not around here.
I'll try to find out more about it.
Finally I'm in Hokkaido!
What's this road?
It's not paved!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Oh, crap! The trail was wrong.
Guess I have to go into that road.
What?
Don't worry.
You probably can make it through a deep river like that.
Hey!
Hey, where are you going?
Stop! Don't fall!
Hey, stop!
Oh, crap!
Bung!
It's okay.
Oh...
-Let's go. -Yeah.
-The machine stopped. -I think something got stuck in it.
Sake
I forget.
It downed here.
I almost stammered.
Sake
I thought to die.
Somehow the task is done.
I can go back to Kameyaru.
Why do I have to climb the river at this time?
"Aaaaaaah!"
"Hey, stop it! I'm going home to the squirrels!"
"The world's three greatest gods and the world's most famous beasts are waiting for me!"
"W-what?"
"Why is the bear still sleeping?"
"Aaaaaaah!"
"Aaaaaaaah!"
"G-gurana!"
"Hey, stop it!"
"It's not good for me to eat!"
"I'm going to eat you, bear!"
"You're in my way!"
"Look at me! I'm not going to let you get away with this!"
"I'm going back to the squirrels and I'm going to drink the world's most famous beasts!"
"What?"
"W-what?"
"Hey, let go!"
"What are you going to do to me? You're going to eat me anyway!"
"I'm going back to the squirrels and I'm going to drink the world's most famous beasts!"
"G-gurana! G-gurana!"
"It's decided!"
"Uwaaahhh!!!"
"Aaaaaaaah!!!"
"The third Pet Bottle Rocket Competition is finally at its climax!"
"Today's target rocket is finally here, the fireworks of your life!"
Here it comes!
How far will it go?
Countdown begins!
Stop it!
There's no one here.
What's this?
It's so cold!
Damn it!
I came to the North Pole again just like last year.
March 3rd is the worst.
No, today is not the end of the day.
If I go to the party, I will have a hard time laughing.
What?
There are many white bears!
All right!
I'm motivated.
I don't want to be calm.
I can do anything.
I'll go back to my dream.
The three greatest celebrities in the world,
the world's famous people,
and the presents from everyone are waiting for me.
All kinds of surveillance videos from around the world
will be sent to this plane in real time.
You will definitely find your seniors.
President, I found someone like that.
Really?
Yes, please take a look.
Let's zoom in.
Yes.
Senpai!
Ryotsu!
Yeah!
Damn it!
There are still so many of them!
No good.
I can't even get a sense of distance.
After all, March 3rd is...
What?
Senpai!
Nakagawa!
Yes!
Let's go, Ryotsu!
Are you all right, Senpai?
I'm fine.
Okay, it's over.
Hi, Mr. Ryo!
Welcome back!
Are you ready to party?
Yes, we're ready.
March 3rd is not over yet.
It's not working. Let's make it the best day ever!
Oh, this is...
-Yay! -Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
Senpai, this is a present from me.
Oh, a 50-inch plasma TV!
I'll use the game software.
This is the limited edition "Sensha Yaro" that was released 3 years ago.
You got it well!
I bought this at the toy store.
-Me too. -I'll take this.
It's a proof of my love.
Thank you, everyone.
This is the best day ever!
Ryo, turn off the candlelight.
Oh, it's Reiko's homemade cake.
All right.
Hello?
Oh, Captain.
I found Ryo.
Yes, I got it.
What? It's Captain Bakuryu.
Captain Bakuryu?
Yes, he was helping me with your research.
I see.
He said he's going to pass through this sky and hand out the present.
Hand out?
Oh, it's the sound of a helicopter!
Huh?
It looks like a model of a tank.
That's good, Senpai. I love tanks.
I love tanks.
But the track is too big.
I know.
No, that's the real one.
A present for you!
Senpai, watch out!
The plasma TV, the game, and my party!
Right now, the 3rd of March is over.
This year was the worst day of my life.
Damn it!
That's why I hate March 3rd so much!
March 3rd
March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd
March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 3rd March 2
I'm saving someone, every once in a while
Baby, do you know me?
I'm heading for tomorrow
I'm breathing with a nice spirit
Don't get sick, I'll do what I have to do
I'm breathing with a cute spirit
What's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than starting over
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
When I was a kid, we were influenced by adventure movies
So we decided to go to Sumida River by hand
From Senjuohashi to Tsukuda Island
It's an adventure trip
But it doesn't go as cool as the movie
Next time, "Adventure Kankichi"
Thank you for watching!
There's a turtle over there
There's a turtle for sure
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!