YoR меня共和国
When I was watching TV
I Republic the room, say look at the next door
English Translation w/ peace
I just perfectly!
Look at a beautiful etching
When I kicked the stone, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if it's going to be a joke
I laughed and said it was a good thing
Even if I try to cheer up, I can't help but laugh
The cityscape that doesn't change even a single yawn is strangely kind
From the fountain of the Tongari Boshi to the Kaishaku Tengen
The sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I'm sorry
If I let win again
I've lost happiness
Because I noticed
"It's because a silly me."
Ryou, you're becoming smaller!
Hey, Konaida
Speaking of the eatie,
TENPACHI!!!
Tenpachi desktop!
That's so annoying! What if my boyfriend does that?
Tenbatsu!
Tenbatsu Dekimen!
Hanayama Security Department!
Tenbatsu!
Tenbatsu Dekimen!
Wonderful!
Gentlemen, we have the answer to the mystery.
Don't let your eyes go!
Yes sir!
Tenbatsu!
What a suspicious man.
I don't know who it is, but I'll take it.
Don't let him go!
Yes sir! Tenbatsu!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Tenbatsu Dekimen!
What's wrong, Ryo?
My stomach hurts! I can't take it anymore!
No, Ryo! Did you eat this?
This is sushi from a week ago.
Don't take anything!
I'm done.
If you're done, I'm off for a day in the office.
I'm going out now.
Let me make sure you move to a more nutritious place.
I'll drop by your house.
Okay, I'll do it right away.
Using the Tenbatsu!!
What a man!
Tenbatsu!!
I think I'm getting a bit hungry.
I'm hungry!
And another clearly hungry tasted one!
Arrrrgh!
Gyaaaah!
I'm saved...
You're still too young to be a hero!
Tenmaaaaaaah!
Huh?
Aaaaaah!
My hair's gone!
Chief General!
Well, I'll go to the bathroom later.
I got better after I took out the eggplant.
You're a tough guy.
I'll show you what I've got!
Tenmaaaaaaah!
Gyaaaaaah!
Gyaaah!
Gyaaaah!
My Pramo-chan!
Gyaaah!
I bought this for 100 yen at the grocery store.
What the...
Huh?
Gyaaah!
Senior, are you all right?
What's up, Honda?
I heard you were starving, so I brought you some hot water.
I don't want to!
Mito, I'll show you!
Tenmaaaaah!
Gyaaah!
Hey! Honda!
Excuse me!
This is the Pramo-chan I bought.
Huh?
What?
Ah! It's broken!
I'm sorry, Senior!
Give me back my money!
I bought this for 50,000 yen.
50,000 yen?
Yes, 50,000 yen.
It's 10 yen.
Please give me a discount.
It's a big profit with a 100 yen promo.
You liar, fraud, and pervert!
Tenba! Tenba! Tenba! Tenba!
Chief Hanayama, he's not going to give you the punishment no matter how much you give him.
You unworthy scum!
I'll throw you out!
I'll call the Chief of the Underworld Security Division!
I'll throw you out and make you pay a thousand times more!
It's so refreshing.
What's wrong, old man? Are you lost?
You don't know where to go home?
I'm Hanayama, from heaven.
You're not here, you're going to go now.
What are you doing?
I'm busy right now.
I'll come back next time.
Come back when I'm bored and dying.
I'm the Chief of the Underworld Security Division from heaven to turn you into a human being.
Yes, yes.
I'm going to turn you into a human being from now on.
I'm the Chief of the Underworld Security Division from heaven.
I see.
You little!
This is even more interesting.
I won't forgive you!
Go to the land of justice, you wretched boy!
How's this?
I'm a child!
Remember your pure heart when you were a child
and reflect on your actions and be reborn!
Lucky.
What?
Buses, trains, movies, all these are the children's allowance.
Besides, there are many children.
I can play with you all day long.
It's like a dream.
Thank you, old man.
What are you doing?
I'm a poop.
Poop.
Are you still going to do it?
You're old, so you should not overdo it.
I will never forgive you this time.
I will make you suffer even more.
TENPATU SPECIAL
What do you think?
Do not bother me.
I'm a poop.
Hanayama is going to be destroyed.
I'm back.
Senior.
Senior?
Ryo!
He's not here.
Ryo, you're going somewhere again.
You're so annoying.
Did you say something?
No.
We didn't say anything.
That's strange.
I'm here.
Ryo.
He's hiding.
Senior.
There's a bug on your shoulder.
I thought it was Ryo's voice.
I'm here.
Here he is.
Good morning.
What's wrong with the three of you?
You are getting on my feet.
No, Reiko.
Under Ryo's feet.
Ryo.
What... what are you doing?
I don't know. A weird old man came and said something about magic or something.
Magic?
Rather than that, please lower it quickly, chief.
I... I got it.
This... this is happening in reality...
It's like a magic girl anime.
But it's small and cute.
What are you talking about?
If it came, I wouldn't even look at this.
It's not!
Don't hesitate, Mr. Muzo, put your things on the desk.
Eh?
Hey, I'm not going to take it from you anymore!
Mr. Ryo!
But how am I supposed to eat this?
If it's food, I'll feed you.
Hey, don't treat me like a pet!
Oh, I'm sorry, I just...
Here, open your mouth.
It's hot! It's hot!
I'm sorry, it was hot.
What kind of word is that for a pet?
I'm sorry, I just...
Reiko.
Reiko, you're working, do your job.
Yes!
Then what about the food?
What about my food?
Don't be so spoiled!
Take care of yourself!
Everybody's busy!
I'm sorry.
It's hot...
This...
It's like a volcano eruption.
I should wait until it cools down.
Ryo!
It's hot!
Chief, here's your tea.
Oh, wait!
It's so hot!
Hooray!
Don't!
Get off, Kein-chan!
W-what?
Get off already!
If you'll excuse us.
Okay...
Did something happen?
Ryotsu, you free to take a Exit?
Can I ask you a favor?
Your job?
I'll take out the change and you can use it and work with me.
Oh, you're playing a show!
Keep it in mind.
-Go away! -What?!
Looking for a trap is a policeman's job.
I understand. You can just go.
How big is it?
Damn it! It's a heavy 500 yen coin.
Good work.
This is my treasure. I'll take 10% off.
10% off?
Oh, it's heavy.
Hey, even if you get smaller, you'll still be strong.
You'll be strong even if you get smaller.
He might be able to make a good money.
I'd like to have one of these 36 figures colored.
Three figures colored?
One is 1000 yen.
It's 3000 yen per figure.
It's the only thing in the world that can make that little doll look good.
Ryo is the best at using the little things to start a business.
I can't take the fish bones that are stuck in my throat.
I want my Mi-chan to drink it.
My hands are not in the way.
A big profit! A big profit!
It's not bad to make this money in just a few hours.
As always, you are a rich man, Senpai.
Besides, your body is enough to live on a hundredth of what you have so far.
You don't have to pay rent.
I envy you.
Senpai, I bought it.
Mika-chan House.
I've been waiting.
Hurry up and show me my new home.
Yes.
It's nostalgic.
I used to play with this when I was a child.
I'm a little worried about my girlish hobby.
It's pretty luxurious, isn't it?
This is big enough.
Senpai, I've prepared the bath.
How's the water temperature?
It's just right.
It's like the father of the eye of the Gegege no Kitaro.
How about the food?
That's perfect, too.
I've collected all of your favorites from the high-class desserts.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll deduct the amount of work from the last Promo's money.
Yes, thank you.
Well, everyone, I'm leaving.
Thank you for your hard work.
Well, then, let's eat.
He's living a much more luxurious life than I do.
Uchiyo.
Ryotsu, what's this?
Well, I'm on a part-time job.
On a part-time job?
You idiot!
You're not going to be spoiled because you've become small.
You have to get a good job as a policeman.
Yes, sir.
Don't spoil me, everyone.
I'm going to treat you as a person.
Are you all right?
Yes, sir.
Well.
Is it around here?
That's right.
Nagagawa!
It's a phone call.
You get out, Ryotsu.
What?
Don't force me.
I can't get out.
It's okay.
Get out now.
I understand.
I can get out, right?
Get out.
Ready.
Hello?
This is Hachijo Koenmae.
What?
I can't hear well because the park is small.
This is Hachijo Koenmae.
Yes, I can hear you.
What?
What is the case?
What's wrong with you?
It's the Tokuda-sensei-tachi.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
What?
You hate the presence of "Hachijo Koenmae"?
What should I do with you?
The pouvait profile picture is from the tube card.
What?
What should I do?
What is the profile?
It says, what is the profile?
What the profile.
Right.
How many people are there?
The weapons that have the number of people are...
They are very bad. We can't get close.
If we don't do anything, the hostages will be in danger.
I can't do anything.
By the way, where is Ryo-chan?
Hey, Kitaro!
What?
Hey, Ryo-chan!
Yes, what's up, Chief?
It's hard to do something.
Nakagawa-kun, lower your head a little.
Y-yes, sir. Is this good?
Hey, Ryo-chan, you can't be joking.
Now we have to figure out how to get to know each other without being noticed by the culprit.
Oh, I see. So this is the way.
You are ignoring human rights! You are terrible, Chief!
Only you can do this task.
I don't want to go!
We are filling the holes that we are skipping every day.
Listen, check the situation inside.
And report to us.
Senpai, be careful.
Do your best, Ryo-chan.
Now, you guys are useless!
Let's go, Ryo-tsu!
Ouch!
You bastard!
The Territory Chisel Chisel
Chisel Chisel
Chisel Chisel Chisel
"30 years old, and he's a real villain."
"The weapon is AUG and Smith & Wesson's two guns."
"The host is a young man."
"He looks fine, so he'll be fine for another 10 hours."
"He even has a room map."
"The weapon is not available, so he was sent to the prison after an hour."
"But how do I give this memo to him?"
"I'm going to give this memo to him."
"What's that?"
"Looks like a dagger."
"What are you looking at?"
"Someone used that to shoot something."
"No! It's not me!"
"It's not me, either!"
"Hey!"
"Yes?"
"Is there a problem?"
"Someone should be in the room. Search!"
"There's no one but host."
"There's no way! Just search!"
"What?"
"I don't think there's anyone here."
"Use this to cut the rope by yourself."
"This is... this is... this is..."
"What does it say?"
"What is it?"
"The letter is too small to read!"
"What?"
"Someone, bring the microscope!"
"Is someone hiding?"
"Hey!"
"If you were, you wouldn't know."
"Damn, it's so hard!"
"I finally got it out."
"You're so cute."
"Hey, you!"
"Yes?"
"Isn't he hungry?"
"No, he hasn't eaten anything since morning."
"That's not good!"
"I can't wait to give him a meal!"
"I'm so sorry, I'm going to have to feed him now."
"Hey, I think I can eat something, too."
"I'm saved."
"I found some cabbage, bro!"
"You idiot, I'm a rabbit!"
"I'll give you something to eat to fill your stomach again!"
"Yes, anything."
"I'll eat it, but it won't work!"
The food is coming, so wait!
Oh, what a bad boy. You went outside.
Here, the cabbage is for you.
Is it good?
One of these will fill your stomach.
Then, I'll leave the rest to you.
Let's leave it here.
It's cold!
Hey, open it!
What is this?
Is this a sign of Egypt?
Even though the letters are from Japan,
only a few people can read them.
It's the same as the code.
Lend it to me.
♪ We'll make all weapons useless ♪
What?
Ryo would only leave in 10 minutes.
Hmm.
I'm worried about Ryo's trust in your orders.
But I'm not going to let this go.
I have to see what's going to happen.
Okay?
I'll be right back.
♪ Wake up ♪
*chomp*
You're still hungry?
Wait a minute...
*chomp*
Ah!
I'm saved!
*chomp*
Hey, stop it!
It's getting weird outside.
*chomp*
Oh no!
It's been an hour!
I have to take off that gun's firing pin!
*chomp*
Go!
Come on!
*chomp*
Oh, come on...
Your guns are useless!
*chomp*
It's true!
Now, give up!
*chomp*
Bro!
Don't overdo it!
I-I knew I trusted Ryotsu.
Hey, go!
Go!
You bastard!
*chomp*
Should we retreat for now?
I'm counting on you, Nakagawa!
Chief!
Are you scared of guns and you want to be a police officer?
*chomp*
You beat me!
My sister...
I was so scared...
Okay, fine.
Good, good.
*chaos*
Chief!
Okay, okay.
*chaos*
That was good.
Everything is fine.
Well done, Chief!
By the way, where is Ryo-chan?
He may just get broken down in this situation.
I made it!
What do you think, Ryosu Kan-Kichi?
You must have thought that your existence was small!
You...
Yes, that's right, completely.
Then, after reflecting on your deeds up until now,
will you continue to live with a humble mind?
Yes, I have completely reconciled myself.
I have been reflecting on what I have done up until now,
deeper and deeper than my heart.
I see, I see.
Then, let's return to your original form.
Tenbatsu-Baba-chan!
-Ryo-chan! -Ryo-chan!
I'm glad! You've returned to your original form!
Give me back my strength!
If you don't, I'll be...
You're a waste of time!
Sakamoto! Remember your smallness!
Help me!
But I can definitely....
No!
Now it will be the last time!
That's right!
I hope this isn't your last time!
You're one ofител isoulm...
I'm not...
I'm not like you.
I'm Hiyoshi Yamazaki.
♪ Bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum-bum
BOM
What's up, chubby?
Are you bewitcheded over Marylin, Marya's little sister?
She's got a boyfriend named Jody.
There's a guy named Rudy!
What? And he double booked his date on his birthday?
Next time, Double Date in Hell!
He's popular, isn't he, Bulbul?