Precious
Heat the room when watching TV and look out the window
Come to me who doesn't have money
Even though I don't have money, I get worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
They'll get better eventually
Come to me, you jobless one
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red clouds are burning
They'll get better eventually
You know it, right?
If you know it, then keep quiet and follow me!
I'll help you stop it!
Dr. Joseph's
I've eaten only the little I've got
I've held onto the bloody Depois
I'll help you out
There's no trash in the bucket.
I wonder if someone's coming.
If possible, a monk.
Next, Nakagawa, Reiko,
food,
money,
money!
Miss!
What?
The chief?
Chief!
Help in front of the building?
That's right. Deliver some food.
If something happens, help me.
Wait.
The front of the building is
Kohaku mochi and ohineri.
It's money, not coins.
Also,
Furumai sake and food.
Yay!
Money and food, bonus!
What?
No,
the chief of Ryotsu,
will go to celebrate the front of the building.
Yes.
Replace the celebration.
I'll pay later.
What?
You don't have money?
Oh, dear.
What kind of life do you have?
I'm going.
Listen.
Two sake for the celebration.
A man's name tag.
Got it?
Yes.
You only give me two coins.
You're stingy.
I'm hungry again.
I'm getting dizzy.
Two coins for sake.
I can't use this.
No.
I'm hungry.
What is this?
I say,
but I split it.
I'm not afraid of my survival instinct.
I...
Oh, tea.
Added croquette and curry rice.
And potato salad and stir-fried vegetables.
Yes.
I ate.
Ouch!
Ah! The money I borrowed from the chief!
I can't help it now.
Well, I'll manage.
It's a free meal and free sake.
Here's your sake.
Excuse me, please leave it there.
Oh, what a beautiful house!
Thanks to you, my house has finally become popular.
Look at this pillar. It's the best firewood.
It's my 10-year-old dream house.
No, that's really good.
I also have a reason to celebrate.
Ryo!
Oh, yes.
This is from my chief.
My chief is very kind.
He only gives me a little money.
That's all.
I can't buy it.
No, I'm sorry for being so polite.
Well, as you can see, there are many people today.
I'm sorry for being so rude.
Oh, it's okay.
Are you still building?
That's the end.
It's just finished.
It's a pity.
No, it's not.
I came here because I was looking forward to it.
Let's do it again.
Are you serious?
I'll go home as soon as the building is finished.
You're right.
I'll go home.
Are you going to do the building again?
Please.
Just a little bit because it's just a shape.
Everyone is already hungry.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ryo.
I'll start.
I've been waiting.
Oh, Ryo.
Were you here?
I'm here to look at the building.
Do you cook?
Of course.
Do you drink?
I'm surprised.
Now I'm going to celebrate Yamamoto's new home and start building.
I've been waiting for you.
Hurry up and turn over.
Yes, sir.
Just a little bit.
I did it.
I'm fine.
Yes, sir.
I'll do it over there.
Sorry.
Yes, sir.
I'd rather be fine.
I would rather be healthy.
That's right!
I did it!
I'm a 100 years old man!
Ouch!
Who built a pillar in this place?
Please make the center of Ryo's place.
The house will be destroyed.
That's right.
That's right!
I wonder why it's raining all over my place.
It's raining all over my place.
Hello, everyone.
I'm done with the seats.
All right.
A lot of food.
Huh?
They're all gone.
I see.
It's time for celebration.
I'm so happy that I'm exercising.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a seat.
Yes!
It's sushi.
Ryo.
You said you'd go home after the celebration.
I don't remember anything.
Well, that's all right.
Today is a happy day.
Don't make a mess.
I don't care.
I'll have one of each.
You're a good eater.
Come on, Nomine.
Do it more.
All right.
Here.
Wait.
Cheers.
Thanks, Tom.
Thank you very much.
Cheers!
Oh, no.
He's the best full drown.
It's fine.
It can't be wrong.
Good for you.
If you say so.
It's just like cooking.
Yes yes, you're right.
I'm doing this.
Oh no, hide Sakadaru!
Eh? No matter how many people there are, two is enough.
Hey, sorry, I came to get some alcohol.
-Ik! -Here you go.
Ah, it's troublesome to get this one.
Look, he's different from other people.
-That person is... -Wait, this...
-Ah? -Ah...
-It's a Disney drink. -You too, my friend.
You're with your friend?
-Where are you going? -My friend, I'm going back to work tomorrow, so it's about time.
What? You're drinking something that's worth drinking, so don't interrupt me!
I'm sorry.
I'm totally drunk.
When comrades get drunk, they don't know what to do.
No way!
You're a sick person, Ryo-san.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to make you think about what to do, but it's troublesome.
Let's celebrate the 7th world cup!
Cheers!
Here it comes.
It's very dynamic.
Eh? What?
What?
*stab*
AAAAHHHHHHH!!!
Tch!
Toshio, you're pretty good at this.
*stab*
You still can do this one!
Gah, that's a little too much!
*stab*
Why are there many pillars here?
It's a nuisance!
There are too many pillars in this house.
Yeah.
Just one on every four corners of the house is plenty.
You're right.
*stab*
Okay.
Here I come!
What are you doing?!
Hey, what are you doing in this place?!
P-Please stop!
Hey, you can leave the house to the carpenter!
Can I leave it to him?!
This place is in the way, too!
Shall we go?
This way, too!
Yes!
This guy, too!
P-Please stop!
Please stop, sir!
What are you going to do if you destroy the house?!
What?
Stop!
You guys, get out of here!
Oh, sir...
Okay, okay, don't be so violent.
What?
It's just a chaos!
You stringy bums!
Stop, sir!
Please stop, Zoro!
You coming!
My home, my sweat and tears, my home is the end of the world!
Idiots!
Ouch, don't shout so loud, chief. It's a double.
Of course. I'm going crazy.
You know, Yamamoto-san's home, you take responsibility and rebuild it.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Terai, buy me a cup of sake.
It's a great sake. It's the best to refresh.
That's not good!
Listen, Ryotsu. You're a nuisance to people.
What?
You've caused trouble. You have to at least pay for it.
I know. So I'm going home.
That's right. But it's not enough.
What?
You have to reflect.
Yes, I reflect.
It's sake. No alcohol. No drinking.
What? No way!
No way or nothing.
I'm going to take responsibility for your director's
"Fuuki-todoki" and I'm going to ban you from drinking.
No way! What's going to stay if I take sake? No way!
If it's no good, it's no good.
I'm going to ban all kinds of sake for a week.
Listen, Nakagawa, Reiko, Terai.
If you find Ryotsu drinking for a week, you can take a fine for it.
A glass of beer, a glass of sake, a glass of chocolate, a glass of anything costs 10,000 yen.
What? 10,000 yen?
Sir, I don't have money.
It's okay. You can cut off the fine and get paid.
No way.
A glass of beer, a glass of sake, a glass of sake, a glass of sake, a glass of sake.
Well, chief.
I'm getting a lot of drinking signs today.
Call me.
No way.
I don't have money either.
The chief took all the drinks.
Okay.
If I close my eyes and walk, I can't see the sign.
Ouch!
No.
I can't walk around here if I close my eyes.
Huh?
Oh, it's sake!
Hehehe.
I'll have a cup if you collect what you have left.
Ryo-tsu!
Hmm?
I told you not to drink sake!
Ah!
C-Consolidation!
It's you.
I'm sure you're thinking of drinking sake even with this complicated means.
I thought I'd try to get drunk with this method.
You did, didn't you?
From now on, I'll send you to Ryo every day.
Yes, yes. It's hard to do.
"Skatt Soukai Kandei Amakuchi"
"The Master Shimobashiro"
"The Man's Sixth Sense"
Damn, why do you always do the alcohol commercial?
Is Ryotsu here?
What's with that happy face, Sakonji?
I got a new fighting game. Come to my room.
It's in, it's in.
It's pretty hot.
It's fine, it's fine. Sit down.
I'm going to change the stove this season.
I'm a little cold.
I'll get you a hot carpet.
I'll get you a kotatsu.
It's a game, a game. Choose a character.
I did it! I won!
Shut up. If you weren't sweating, I would have won.
But it's hot. It's like a sauna.
Your throat is dry, right?
Here.
Here, Ryotsu.
If it's this hot, beer is the best.
No way!
Sakonji, you!
You're trying to trap me and get me into trouble!
I don't know.
You're not the only one here.
Here's a beer for you, too.
A beer?
You're welcome.
Cheers!
Game...
Beer...
Damn it! I'm gonna lose!
I lost again!
Senior!
I was passing by the can of beer with a pachinko...
You can't do that to me!
Senior...
Both of you...
I won't believe you for a week!
Ryo!
Come here!
What? Cherry blossoms?
These are cherry blossoms.
It's the best time to see them.
Well, I thought you were fooled,
so come here.
There are special sushi,
and there are special meat and sukiyaki.
Well, I'm bored, so let's have a look.
This is also a serious thing.
Isn't it?
It's delicious.
There are more.
Edokko?
He is from Asakusa.
He is a good eater.
Edokko is from Asakusa.
Edokko is sushi, isn't it?
Sushi is a food with sake, isn't it?
Of course.
Come on, hold the bowl.
This is also a good shape.
Isn't it?
This is a Shimo-bashira.
The color is nice.
The scent is good, too.
Ryo-san, Edokko.
Edokko is very good at eating.
Mr. Edokko, you're going to eat too.
I'm not going to drink it.
I won't eat that!!
I'm not going to eat that!!
Ryo-san!!
He ran away.
He thought we were going to pay him a fine.
And?
He became a man, didn't he?
But, it's just a week today.
Not yet.
I'm going to ask the chief to punish me.
Punish you?
Yeah, now it's finally over.
You've put up with it.
What do you think, Ryotsu?
If we get this done, we'll be completely banned.
That's not a joke!
Hey, Terai, let's go back and drink.
But...
Too bad, but we have work tonight.
What?
It's the security of the Shinsen reception of the Takepon Kingdom's Chinese ambassador.
The security of the Shinsen reception of the Takepon Kingdom's Chinese ambassador.
Is there anyone suspicious?
No, nothing unusual.
There's no suspicious person, but there's something suspicious about the drink.
Hey, Ryotsu!
What?
Why are you dressed like that?
Reiko and I are personally invited to this party.
Really?
Then it's unfair for you guys to be able to eat this luxurious room for free.
So, go home.
What?
Reiko, you can go.
Then, should I wear my dress?
Huh?
Then, we'll go around the place.
We'll keep watch, so don't worry.
Huh?
There's only Tadazake and Wansato in front of me.
Oops, I almost got excited.
This time.
What's wrong?
Something under the table?
Did you hear a moat?
That thing?
*History activity of Taishi*
Well, there is nothing changed...
What a strange man...
*Return of Takao*
Welcome to the party, ladies and gentlemen.
I, Takao them, have prepared a bouquet from Takepon King.
If you are surprised, please win this bouquet of flowers.
It's an old bouquet. Reiko-san, how was it?
It's okay if the person who received the bouquet says they can get married next time.
Anyway, the person who grabbed this bouquet has to drink with the Shunichi ambassador.
Oh, senpai!
What? What? What?
He's pushing me out.
One, two, three!
Don't push me!
Please come here.
It's senpai.
I have a bad feeling.
Well, hello.
Would you like whiskey or sake?
I would like anything.
What? Sake?
Can you drink sake?
It's a drink comparison with me.
Yay!
No, I'm a little...
Don't refuse, senpai!
That's right, Ryo-chan.
Why are you doing that again?
In the Takepon Kingdom, it is the most rude to refuse to drink even though I received this bouquet.
No, I can't do that.
I'm just a little too excited about the international issue.
Ryo-chan, I don't care.
Please accept my apology.
Really?
What?
Ryo-chan, you can drink it.
I can drink it.
But I think I've done too much.
What?
And, the
The roof's turning?
What? I heard the roof is turning.
That's not what I mean!
The floor's shaking.
Ryo-chan, you've opened up this pillar and it's tilted.
No, you haven't отдел core.
I'm going to mend this.
Interesting, very interesting!
I'll help you.
I'm so tired of this.
Alright, everyone, I'm going to fix you!
Next is this way!
Alright, I'll do it!
Alright, this is the last one. Let's go!
Next is this way!
Thank you!
Damn! That Ryusenshi guy!
Even though he's an editor, he still rides a helicopter and is popular with girls.
He eats up all the delicious food and I envy him too much!
In this case, I'll become an editor who's better than an editor!
I'll become a super editor!
Next time, Super Editor!
Thanks for watching!
Thank you!