"Long Time No See"
When you watch TV, make the room bright and try to step aside.
If you're poor, come to me,
I'm not here, but don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Look at the blue sky,
white clouds.
You'll find a way out eventually.
When you're jobless,
Come to me!
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
It'll be all right
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
The Anger of the Fortress
What? A present for Chief Ohara?
This time, I'll receive the 35th award of the metal.
So, what do you think is the best gift?
Of course, the cash.
No gift that is worth the cash!
But, something that will stay in your memory...
I've been remembering all the money I've received since I was five years old.
That's about the same as mass production.
After all, something that remains in shape is better.
Is that so?
Hey, what about a bronze statue?
A bronze statue?
No, no, no!
A middle-aged man's naked face is just disgusting!
It's not naked, Senpai!
It's a statue of the emperor!
Oh, I see.
It's not funny just imagining a pose of the emperor naked.
Where are you going to put such a thing?
Hey, let's make a bronze statue secretly now,
and give it as a present on the day of the awards ceremony.
That sounds great!
Wait!
You can't make it without your own help, right?
Oh, is that so?
I think you put a straw in your nose,
and then you harden it with a iron,
and then you raise your shoulders.
You have no choice but to do it secretly while you're asleep.
That's how you make a life mask, right?
It says that you can make it if you have a few photos.
Oh, really?
Well then, let's go order right away.
Right.
Wait, wait!
What?
If I were you,
I would be able to make a face of the mayor without looking at the photos.
I can make it cheap.
No!
It's not like you're making a plastic model.
I've always done it like that,
and I've left it to my seniors.
Have you ever done it properly?
It's best to leave it to a professional!
Got it?
Damn it.
You're copying me on stereo.
I think this photo is good.
It looks good.
That's because you're the mayor.
This one looks more like you.
See?
This is a picture of the mayor's anger that you took before.
This is not good.
I think the mayor's face is the most angry.
That's because you're always angry.
You're usually very angry, Mayor.
I don't think this is good.
Then, I'll choose this photo.
It's decided.
Terai, you'd better choose this photo.
How persistent.
Okay.
I'll accept your request.
Eh?
Have you received the photo of that person?
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's fine.
Then, please enter it with this.
Yes.
Enter?
In this workshop,
based on the photo,
we create a prototype with 3D computer graphics.
Eh?
It's quite high-tech.
It's already done?
It's amazing.
It's realistic.
Is it okay?
Like this.
Well,
I think you should tighten your mouth a little more.
Yes.
That's more like a policeman.
Like this.
Yes, yes.
It's like that.
The mayor's personality is well expressed.
There is kindness in the strictness.
Then, please enter it with this.
I understand.
It seems interesting.
Please try more things.
Yes.
Oh, Ryo-chan.
Senpai likes new things.
Then, it will be completed in about two weeks.
Understood.
Senpai, I'm going home.
Please go home first.
I'll be back after observing a little more.
Ryo-chan, don't get in the way.
I understand.
I have to go.
But everyone has the same expression when they are competing.
You are too serious.
It's not interesting at all.
It's usually a souvenir, so there is no choice.
Do you want to make something more unusual sometimes?
Well, there is no such thing.
Do you want to make this expression?
It's interesting.
I have never made such a competition of expression.
I know.
Even professionals think so.
I can do it, too.
I was saying that this picture is better.
Is that so?
Yes, let's make a sculpture with this picture.
But what is the order?
This one expresses the nature of the head of the club well.
This one is definitely better.
But...
I said it was interesting.
I said I wanted to make something like this.
That's...
You're an artist, aren't you?
Are you satisfied with making such boring things?
But this is work.
I'm going to make it as ordered.
Where did the pride of being an artist go?
Did the passion for that burning creative disappear?
I'll do it!
I've been making sculptures for 35 years.
I'll make a masterpiece that includes my life and marriage.
I have to come like that.
I'm going to make a sculpture.
I'll do this here.
You're a professional.
That's right.
I'll change my clothes.
How about this?
You're good at it.
And the hat.
Great!
Are you done?
It's only been three days.
You rode on the glue.
You made it in a blink of an eye.
It's a great work.
Look.
This is President Ohara, isn't it?
What are you talking about, Ryo?
Nothing.
You are misunderstanding President Ohara.
I changed him into the right president.
As expected, at that time, I shouldn't have left a senior and left him alone.
This is not President Ohara.
I have a longer relationship.
This is the correct.
I told you before, it's because Ryo-chan is getting angry.
That's why it's the real leader's appearance.
Even if it's close to the real leader's appearance, I can't give you this as a present.
Did you forget? This is the 35th anniversary present of Chief Ohara.
I see.
I want you to look at yourself again in this opportunity.
There's no one who would be happy to get this!
I have no choice but to get it redone.
I can't show it to the chief.
Hey, what are you going to do with this?
Ryo-chan will take responsibility and dispose of it.
Certainly, I'm not happy if I get it myself.
I'll sell it somewhere.
I see. How about 10,000 yen?
What? Is that all?
Please color it a little more.
20,000 yen.
It can't be helped. I'll do it.
What's this hand?
So you'll take it with 20,000 yen, right?
What are you talking about? I'm the one who gets the money.
What do you mean?
This store is buying expensive goods.
There's no way this will sell.
20,000 yen is the amount of withdrawal.
If you don't like it, you can take it.
You'll take it home, right?
I got it. I won't ask you again.
I know it's a bit much, but there's no other place I can take it.
What's that?
It's a gift for Ryo.
What should I do with such a thing?
It's perfect for the interior of the cafeteria.
Please don't do that.
How about a bath? It'll make the hot water come out.
No, it's disgusting.
Then, let's decorate the entrance of the dorm
with a symbol statue.
No, no, no.
No one will come near.
I didn't think you'd hate me so much.
Here we go.
I can't help it.
I'll leave it in my room.
It's true that it's not good for you.
I'm hungry.
What?
What is this?
This is chief's statue.
I surprised it.
I put the statue there.
The Foreign Secretary has come to Ryo's place.
I was too nervous.
Really?
Are you after me?
Yes.
Huh?
I can't calm down because of the chief's surveillance.
I'll turn around.
That's good.
I'm worried about him suddenly turning around.
I'll cover my eyes.
How about this?
Well then...
Don't look at me like that!
Now I'm relieved.
Where should I put it?
This part of the room is a blind spot.
I might get a bruise.
I don't want to get hurt.
Ryo-sama, you've made too much meat.
Let's eat together.
Oh, what are you doing?
Don't scare me.
Actually, the statue...
Statue?
That's what it was.
Then tonight I'll stay in your room.
I'll give it to you.
Why do you say that?
Because I don't want to be alone with the statue.
Oh, I see.
I want to be with you.
Tonight I'll protect you.
Wait a minute.
That's not good.
Why?
It's not good.
Because you're a man.
Ah!
Well, it's better than being alone with the statue.
Ryo-sama!
This is the third time.
This time I slept next to you.
Shall we change the place?
Please.
Good night.
Yeah.
Now I can finally sleep.
Let's go back to the hotel!
The second night's so special!
The next day
There has been a terrible storm.
Delirious.
Ryo-sama, have a good day!
I'm completely out of sleep.
It's all thanks to this guy.
This is the last resort.
Don't get me wrong.
Don't scare me.
Ryo-sama!
How long are you going to sleep?
What are you so surprised about?
What? Is it real?
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
You can't sleep while you're working.
No matter how many times a major incident happens, it's inevitable.
I understand.
This is terrible! It's a murder!
What did you say?
There are dead bodies in that garbage dump!
Really?
Ryo-san, head to the scene immediately. I'll contact the station.
Understood!
Hurry up!
There!
There's a huge corpse in the trash bag!
Look!
What's this place?
Isn't it amazing?
It's not amazing at all! That's a statue!
It's a statue!
What?
Damn it, that cat's doing it!
Ryo-san, where's the corpse?
No, there's no corpse anywhere.
What?
It looks like a corpse.
No, no, it's a mistake.
It looks like he thought a mannequin was a corpse.
See?
Then show me that mannequin.
I have to write a report.
A report?
If it's a report, I'll write it myself.
But...
Leave it to me.
Come to think of it, isn't this a garbage dump?
I'll dispose of this properly.
What the hell did he do?
There!
Now I'm relieved.
I won't see him again.
Oh, welcome back.
Oh, grandma, I'm home.
Ryo-san, how are you?
Oh, well.
That statue is gone, so I can sleep...
Huh?
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
A, a statue is walking on its own!
A statue?
Oh, I brought it.
What?
It was closed today, and it was chasing a gang of robbers, and it went into the scrap yard.
I lost sight of it, but I found this.
This statue is exactly like Chief Ohara, isn't it?
I thought this would be a great gift for you, so I brought it home.
I see.
Why do you do such a useless thing?
I'll take it.
Don't ever come back!
I hope you're okay this time.
What's that?
What?
Why is it here?
Yeah.
I left it here.
Sakonji, I think you went to the judo camp.
I just came back.
Actually, I was running along the beach this morning,
and this was shot up by the beach.
It was just like Chief Ohara's, so I thought I'd get hit and left it.
It's not funny at all!
What's going to happen to that statue?
Probably the air will come out in the middle of the Pacific Ocean and fall into the sea.
As expected, it won't come back.
Now I can finally rest assured.
Ryotsu, are you there?
What's up, Volvo?
I'm sorry.
I was about to go to bed.
Don't say that.
I brought you some overseas souvenirs.
Oh, I see.
You said you were going to America on your vacation.
What are the souvenirs?
Alcohol or food?
This is a funny story.
It just came down from the sky just before I returned.
From the sky?
Don't be surprised.
What?
Did you make a statue of Ohara?
It is a sculpture of the Chief Ohara.
Are you still working on it?
The 35th anniversary of the metal ceremony is tomorrow, though.
It will be completed in the night and will be delivered directly to the venue tomorrow.
I heard that the first one that I made was a retake, so it took me a long time to get it.
What about the first statue?
Do not talk about that!
Don't get mad at me!
Could it be that you still have it?
Please don't let Chief Ohara notice it.
That's right. No matter how generous Chief Ohara is,
if he sees that statue, he'll get angry.
I know!
I want to do something about it as soon as possible.
Just bury it.
Bury it?
That's right.
In a place where no one can see it.
How about the Jukai?
The Jukai of Fuji.
You can't find it there for a rare cause.
This is it.
Let's bury it.
It would have been better if you buried it from the beginning.
There's a fear you'll find it if it's shallow, so bury it as deep as possible.
At this rate...
It's about time it was buried.
I was about to die.
I was buried in front of the statue,
so I don't know if it was suicide or murder.
Alright, if this is all I have,
I'm definitely safe.
Bye!
Hehe, this is the end.
Don't hesitate and get up!
This is the end!
One, two, three, four, five...
Chief Ohara's statue
has been successfully built.
Good. We were right on time.
Ryo will be greeting us, right?
Yeah, leave it to me.
You've been working hard.
Yeah, I don't have to worry about anything anymore.
Wh-what is that?
A-a hot spring!
A hot spring is coming out!
From now on,
Chief Ohara Daijirou
will hold a 35-year
award ceremony!
Hurry up!
The ceremony is about to begin!
Yes, sir!
Chief Ohara Daijirou
has celebrated his authority
as the Head of the entire police force
of the Katsuchika Prefecture
for years on end.
Time's running out.
Next up,
there will be a total of
Nagaga!
Not yet?
That is...
Oh, here it comes!
Thank you for waiting!
Thank goodness!
We finally got together.
Then, senpai, I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me!
Thank you for waiting!
The presenter is a long-standing relationship with President Ohara.
Ryozu Kankichi, 13 years old!
Ah, ah...
President Ohara, 35 years old. Congratulations.
Ah, ah, thank you.
When I think about it,
the one who taught me, who was not sure of my right or left,
was President Ohara, who sometimes was kind and sometimes was strict.
Because of my youthfulness, I sometimes got arrogant and arrogant.
But deep in my heart, I was proud of my older brother and my parents.
Ryozu...
I was kind in my insensitivity,
and I had a sense of dignity.
The fact that I was kind and generous to him,
was indeed a mirror to a policeman.
He is my ideal.
So I decided to present the ideal policeman, President Ohara,
as a statue.
Please look.
This is the ideal of President Ohara.
Ah!
Wha, what?
Why is this here?
I should have put it here.
I see.
That's your ideal.
Ryotsu.
I'm going to keep going in the ideal form.
I'm scared of the real thing.
Subtitles by: Tanya Duarte www.tanyaduarte.com
Thank you!
Wow! Memory sight?
Why do I have to travel through a country to find memories of Reiko?
Wow, that's a lot of people!
Hi!
Alright, this is a trip to find the Kua-Kata!
Next time, "Reiko's Summer Memories"!
See you next time!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, I'm sure it's Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!