Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the passing seasons ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the
♪
It doesn't hurt even if I walk out of it
I'll hold the disturbing curiosity
Strongly, high, League
Ryotsushiki Test Victory
Win Hebrews
Oh man, that was nice.
DXR-002 RoboJack.
40,000 yen.
Even if we stop it now, we can't buy it.
Yeah, we can't.
We're also going to die of a cold before thehog's day.
That's right.
Oh, no!
Wait!
Junpei, stand up!
You're in the way again.
Junpei, are you sure you want to study?
You have a test tomorrow, right?
Yeah, but...
Even if I do it now,
I don't suddenly get a good head.
That's true.
Ryo-san.
Gigu.
You're such a good-aged adult,
but you're with a kid.
I wonder what's so good about that.
It's the best solution for a full-action robot
with a 4-channel radio controller.
Those who understand will understand.
Those who don't will not understand.
I see.
If Junpei can get at least 80 points in the test,
I'll buy you a lot of things like that.
Really?
You'll buy me a lot of things?
I'm serious.
It's just an example.
You can't get 80 points.
Brother...
I'll buy you a lot of things.
Look at the Nagashima Titans this year.
They turned the 11.5 game difference in the first half
and won the league championship.
If you want to be a human, you can do anything.
If Junpei gets 80 points,
I'm sure you'll buy him a radio controller.
Well...
I guess so.
All right, I've decided.
What?
Let's go, Junpei!
Yes!
Hey, Ryo!
Ryo, wait!
What?
What are you going to do, Ryo?
Leave it to me.
If you get the radio controller,
I'll buy you one for free.
Yes!
I'll do it.
I'll do it for sure!
What's Ryo's problem?
Huh?
What about a family instructor?
What's his problem?
What is he talking about?
No oneCon popcorn?
He got worried about it.
What?
Hi, Ryo!
You're more than welcome
to stay with me for the rest of the week.
There's plenty of free time.
But...
Ryo,
There's something I need to tell you.
I didn't study hard enough to pass the exam!
You didn't sleep at all?
Why are you saying that?
I'd forget everything I learned.
That's extreme.
But people don't really stay focused.
Yes. They say it's more efficient to take a break at work.
That's a silly thing to say.
My ability to stay focused is different.
Common sense is not working like this!
It's more correct to say they don't know it.
Listen closely!
They'll slowly metroce the pace of the exam.
Then, they'll drop.
Then, they'll slowly metroce the pace of the exam.
I just start sometimes from the peak.
And then, I go back to the exam.
You tell me...
- corrected! - He
really holds back his concentration. I
can't believe it. But
this is what happens. If
you say you're focused, you become anxious and hurtful. If
I were him, I'm constantly focused on my brain and fingers. My
senses are 100%. But
if anything comes to my attention, I suddenly lose my concentration. I
see. It's like a process plane. That
's most like you.
So, I'm going to use my special technique to start the...
Where are they?
Wow, amazing!
Oh, no!
Oh, I knew it!
I hid my plan!
Wait a minute!
Stop it! Don't touch it!
Ryo, are you really going to teach them?
I know how concentrated you are, but it's a different matter than your academic ability.
How do you expect Hineru and Ryo to become house teachers?
I don't know.
How long are you going to play?
Are you really going to study?
Of course!
If it's for the radio, it's going to be in the fire or in the water!
Come on, give us the question paper.
What's the exam range?
Okay, let's start with the language question.
What's this?
What does this mean?
"What's the meaning of the following phrase?"
"50 steps, 100 steps..."
What? It's easy, isn't it?
Of course, it's obvious.
It's 50 steps, 100 steps.
This is the starting line.
Okay, Junpei.
Try walking 100 steps from here.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Is that so?
Seven, eight, nine...
Hey, Ryo.
Watch out when you're on the street.
That's just the math you need.
Oh, my.
...100 steps, 100 steps.
Nice one, Ryo!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
Ryo.
What are you expecting?
What?
46, 47, 48, 49, 50!
-Number 50! -That's it!
Exactly!
In other words, 50 steps and 100 steps means that even if you're 100 steps away from a child's feet,
you can still walk 50 steps if you're an adult.
-Yeah, I got it! -Yeah, I got it!
I see. So that's the kind of interpretation there was.
That's not true.
-You mean, from the second floor? -Huh?
-Hey, Ryo-san! -What do you mean?
Well, you should try it.
Here I go, Ryo-san!
Okay, I'm coming!
Aim well!
I'm really going to use the eye drops on the second floor.
Yay!
What do you think, Ryo-san? Do you get it?
I'm getting dizzy.
I'm going to use the eye drops on the second floor.
If I use the eye drops on the second floor, it'll help me speed up and it'll be very nice.
-Hey, Ryo-san! -Yes?
The explanation is completely different.
-What? -The eye drops on the second floor are useless,
and they're not effective.
50 steps and 100 steps is a saying that was passed down from China.
People who run 50 steps on the battlefield can laugh at people who run 100 steps.
So there's no big difference between them.
Come on, you're a home teacher.
Okay, I'm going to use the eye drops on the second floor.
Hello?
Shut up, Reiko!
If you're so logical, you can't get married!
What did you say?
Um, the neighbor called and asked us to take a car that was being illegally parked.
I'm going to ask her to take us there.
Fine.
Okay, Ryo-chan, I'll be right back.
It's not a problem to tell me anything.
Got it, got it.
I'm going to go to work.
Just relax.
You can relax and come back.
Really?
Now, you're all quiet, so don't be so loud.
If you have any questions, just ask.
Okay, Ryo-san.
Hm? What is it?
What's a crane turtle?
What? A crane turtle?
This.
Ah, um, what is it?
There are cranes and turtles.
If you count the number of heads, it's 20 in total.
If you count the number of feet, it's 62.
How many cranes and turtles are there?
Hm, the cranes have two legs and the turtles have four...
Um...
It's a crane turtle!
Help us!
Ah, no, help us!
Hey, Ryo-san, are the cranes caught?
Don't be so loud!
Hey, how are the turtles?
They're fine.
They're fine!
Alright, it's about time.
Don't get so angry.
It's the other way around.
Look, there's a turtle.
Alright, now we finally have a crane turtle.
Hey, hey, hey!
You wouldn't know if you stopped your feet.
Stop that!
Oh, come on!
I don't like cranes.
It's Rika! Rika! Rika!
Rika is my favorite animal!
Rika, are you alright?
Even though she's got very soft clothes on,
This is Rika...
The issue with a cranes is that
you naturally have to use the Concrete and Fertility Law.
A Concrete and Fertility Law
is a theory that the individual that borrows power
is also the one who takes the most of it.
If you inject a amount of air in a bottle filled with water,
and send it all the way out...
Wow!
The compressed air will blow out water,
and the same amount of force will be released
from the plastic bottle, and it will fly.
This is the same principle as the real space rocket.
Hey, Ryo,
can you make a bigger one?
A bigger one?
Alright!
It's a matter of application.
Alright, it's done.
The drum rocket is ready!
Let's launch it!
Alright, let's go!
Ryo, I'm counting on you!
You coward!
Ryo!
Ryo, are you okay?
I'm fine!
Let's go to the society!
Turn right at the intersection,
and there's a small gate.
I didn't think there was a sign
on the map like this.
A blue mark.
You're acting weird.
The circle is better.
The circle is a district office or a village hospital.
Oh! A ninja mark!
Yes!
This is a sign for the Manji Shuriken.
There are also cross-shurikens,
hexagonal shurikens and octagonal shurikens.
You're familiar with them, Ryo.
Of course!
By the way, cross-shurikens can be made with origami.
Really?
Yes!
Cool!
I used to make this and play ninja games.
Tell me!
Okay, first we make the origami into a tatami mat.
Keiichi Nakagawa, I'm back.
Reiko Akimoto, I'm back.
Thank you for your hard work.
How are your family?
It seems they're doing it quietly.
Are you doing well?
Oh!
Oh, crap!
I'm so sorry!
What?
My oh, my oh, my!
Keeki!
History is simple.
If you memorize everything you can get a point for sure.
Yep.
Umm...
How many years was the Great Age of the Deceased?
What?
The Great Age of the Deceased?
No.
It's the Age of the Deceased.
The Age of the Deceased.
Darn.
It's 645 years.
Huh?
If you remember it,
you'll remember it as the Age of the Deceased, the Age of the Deceased.
What?
I see.
So you can get a point for every person.
That's how you memorize the Heihoukons.
But...
Suihei, Ribe, Boku no Fune.
That's the original.
Huh?
There are other ones like
Nakuyo, Uguisu, Heiankyo,
Iyoku ni Moeru, Kolombusu.
There are also such things.
Yeah! That's it!
Iyoku ni Moeru, Kolombusu,
Suikin, Chikamoku, Dotten, Kaimei,
Kyojin, Taihou, Tamagoyaki,
Oh, Kaneda, Hirooka.
Oh!
Kaneda,
Hirooka,
Nanjatte,
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What the heck is that?
What are you going to teach your children?
That's what I learned when I was a kid.
If you have any complaints, tell me.
Hey, hey.
That's not enough.
Tell me.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
You remember that the Age of the Deceased was the Age of the Deceased in 645.
Yeah.
Next is Ono no Imoko.
Oh!
I know that one.
Ono no Imoko is Imoku,
and the word "bu" is a popular one.
I miss it.
How did you become a Kenzushi after eating a potato?
Kenzushi?
Wasn't Ono no Imoko the only person who ate and yelled at Imoku?
Why is there a name left in history?
Because it was the first time I ate and yelled at Imoku in Japan.
I don't like it anymore!
Oh, I can't stand it anymore.
No, no.
Hmm.
Hmm?
There was a Kenzushi instead of Kenzushi, right?
There was.
It's about 20 years after Kenzushi.
There was a Kenzushi ship, right?
Yes.
It was a ship used to go to China.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Wasn't that ship shaped like this?
The one that many people love, right?
Wow!
I think it was shaped like that.
You remember it well, Ryo-chan.
Yeah.
I'm starting to remember it.
I remember it well.
I remember that a ship was on a shipwreck, and a shipwreck was on a shipwreck.
Wow, that's cool!
But you remember the small parts of the ship well.
I've been imitating the ship many times.
I'll draw Kanrinmaru, too.
Kanrinmaru is a small wooden ship about 50 meters long and made in the Netherlands.
Wow!
I think it was used as a practice ship for the Navy.
It has five cannons each.
It's detailed.
Someone said it was from America.
Who was it?
It wasn't a shipwreck.
It was a shipwreck, right?
Yeah, that person.
He doesn't have any knowledge of history, but he remembers only the picture of the textbook.
I'll draw a person.
How about Ferry?
Ferry?
Hmm.
I think it was a face like this.
Wow!
Yeah!
I think it looks like him.
Why are you drawing it right away?
It was on the textbook, right?
I always drew like this during class.
Hahaha!
Sugita Genpak was also here.
It's like this when I draw it in Ukiyo-e style.
Wow!
He's good, isn't he?
He was the happiest when he drew the most mischief in his life.
Wow!
Hey, Ryo.
Can you draw Minamoto no Yoritomo?
What about Hideyoshi?
Yeah, of course.
Wow!
Hahaha!
I'll draw it.
Hideyoshi is a good guy.
Nobunaga is a good guy.
Francisco Xavier is a good guy.
Wow!
Senior, do you know what kind of person Sugita Genpak is?
Of course, you are.
He is a Rakugo artist.
He drew a famous disassembly new book.
Wow!
Hmm.
I thought he was a Rakugo artist when I saw him in the second grade.
He was a person who drew the Yajikita Dochukyo.
That's Juppenshireik, right?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't believe you're such a good student.
I don't know.
Whatever happens in the exam...
Hm?
Ah!
Don't write it down!
Hahaha!
I see he's good at drawing!
You know what?
Ryo can teach us something boring!
I'm impressed by myself.
That's all for today.
See you again.
Hey!
Hey, what are you going to do with the radio?
I can't do anything about it.
Geez, there's a limit to your mischief.
Ryo, bring it back.
What, me?
You're still learning to say things like that, right?
Geez, where did they go?
They...
Could it be...
What the hell...
Ryo, are you in trouble?
Hey, shut up!
Hey, I found you!
It's...
Ryo!
You guys, stop it!
You're so out of your mind!
I'm sorry...
Hey, Ryo, look!
You're not getting it!
But look! It's just like your favorite cartoon!
Huh?
Ah, that's...
Hey, aren't you gave a good break, huh?
As I thought.
He is always like that!
Stop it!
You guys, let me go!
Ryo! Don't let him get away!
I'm going to arrest you, Mamushiro Tatsu!
How did you know?
You're really a troublemaker.
I was just telling them that I was going to do something like this.
You're in a good mood.
I wouldn't say that this test was perfect.
If it was perfect, I wouldn't say it.
You idiot! It's obvious that it was perfect!
Who do you think taught you that?
Ryo!
Look! Look!
You did it! 80 points!
No, 50 points.
What? 30 points isn't enough. Why?
I helped arrest the criminal, so I got it from a good cop.
I'm glad.
Yeah!
It's true.
In this world, study is not everything.
My practical study is the truth.
Yeah!
For example, my boss came here with a single study, so he became so stubborn.
He doesn't even laugh when he watches TV.
He gets angry.
Hey, Senpai.
It's true.
A coward like him can't be a good cop.
He's just a stubborn old man.
Ryo!
Chief!
Yesterday was a good day.
I'm glad that you helped the citizens and arrested the criminal.
And I'm glad that you erased the draft of the practical study.
You're kidding me, Chief.
They did it on their own.
Don't be so stubborn.
Erase it now!
What are you talking about!?
Be quiet!
Shh~
Shut up!
I don't have a choice.
I have my own reasons.
You're trying to kill me!?
Be quiet!
Just shut up already.
Hey,ATA!
I don't understand.
Are you stupid!?
What are you doing here!?
Come back!
Don't come back here!
Don't worry about us.
Hey, you are my friend.
You don't understand me.
Don't, move your head!
You can't do that.
I'm so happy to clean up!
You forgot to tell us, but we're going to deduct the money from your salary.
What? No way!
Chief Shion!
Bonus, bonus! I'm so happy!
What? You want me to pay back the debt?
No! This is the money I earned by spilling sweat!
I'm not giving it to anyone!
Next time, "Bonus Battle!"
Thanks for watching!
♪ Even if I try to stop the clock ♩
♪ I'll be too busy to stop ♩
♪ Don't stare at me ♩
♪ Let's laugh and live ♩
♪ Even if it rains today ♩
♪ Tomorrow will be sunny ♩
♪ Bye bye ♩
♪ Let's wave our hands ♩
♪ Goodbye to the unpleasant things ♩
♪ Oh yeah ♩
♪ Let's live as we like ♩
♪ There are good things ♩
♪ The sun is calling outside the door ♩
♪ ♪
♪ Let's go beyond the darkness ♩
♪ Goodbye to 2019 ♩
♪ To you who you are now ♩
♪ Let's travel to the then. ♪
♪ Let's travel to the then. ♩
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.