Translated by이나
I was drowsy and peeing in the middle of the river
I threw the dice and went up to the lake
From the tapestry of a pointed hat
The sun sets to the taishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again
I realized
I'm an idiot
Ryo!
Thank you for the feast.
I didn't eat anything for three days without money.
Really?
Geez, I can't leave this place if Ryo-san is here.
Are you going somewhere?
I was thinking of taking a break and going to the hot spring.
But there are people who are hungry in the middle of the night and come to the kitchen.
I'm worried and can't go anywhere.
No, Grandma.
Tomorrow is my day off, so I'll be fine for the rest of the day.
It's okay.
Go to your favorite place, whether it's a hot spring or not.
Really?
Yeah, it's okay.
I don't want to steal the fun from the old people.
Is that so?
Actually, there is a cheap one at the town hall.
If you're okay with it, let's go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, come on.
Then I'll leave this to you.
What?
It's a fee.
A fee?
When something happens,
you have to pay for it.
Okay.
Grandma, leave Ryo to me and go to the hot spring.
What's this?
Today and tomorrow, the local government's Ryo-tsu teacher will be in charge of the replacement of Ryo-bo-san.
So don't be too serious and bother him.
Ryo-tsu.
Ryo-tsu is Ryo-bo-san?
That's kind of funny.
The first one is Prince Misawa.
The second one is Tsutaro Tsurutaro.
Damn it.
I'm completely destroyed.
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it.
But now I have enough money from my grandma.
I have to do something about it.
Hey, Ryo-tsu.
What's wrong with you guys?
The washing machine is not working.
Huh?
Oh, the washing machine.
See? It doesn't work at all, Ryo-tsu.
It's obvious if it's packed like this.
We should just pull the laundry out, right?
Yes, Ryo-bo-san. Please.
Damn it. It says you shouldn't bother me.
I can't stand it.
Take this!
Oh, what are you doing?
What?!
Oh no. I even got the screw out.
Senpai, what are you going to do?
This is just a box.
Oh, wow.
Wow. Oh, wow. What are you going to do?
Please do something, Mr. Ryo.
That's right. I'm a wife.
I see. I see.
I'll go and clean it.
Really?
Yeah. Bring all the laundry.
I will.
Thank you.
Why me?
Isn't this your job?
I'm a wife.
Help each other when you're in trouble.
I'm always like this when I'm in trouble.
What did you say?
I was wondering if there was a cleaning shop.
For a coin laundry, it costs 200 yen per floor.
If the cleaning fee is 2000 yen per person,
if I use the coin laundry,
Honda!
I'll clean it here!
Senpai, isn't this a coin laundry?
I know that.
I'll just have to wash the laundry.
Here, put your clothes in.
And my clothes, too.
Senpai!
You, too, get out of here.
If you wash it together, the laundry will float.
No! No!
You don't know what you're doing.
Senpai, you're terrible.
What's wrong?
Calm down, Honda.
Senpai, someone came.
No one comes in this mess.
What's wrong?
It's Reiko.
What?
I washed the laundry.
I can't believe Reiko is coming.
What are you going to do, Senpai?
Hide.
Hide? Where?
Where?
On the ceiling!
What?
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
Hurry up, Reiko.
No.
I can't go on.
I'll go first.
Ouch!
You're a pervert!
I don't care!
Senpai...
I'm sorry, Reiko.
You didn't hold back, did you?
Eh!?
What a crybaby you are!
Ugh.
You got away, didn't you?
How'd you get out?
You are such a show-off.
And there was this.
The dry-cleaner Reiko asked me to bring
to dry you to the working day.
And now there's the Chief.
Senpai...
I'll do it here.
It's enough to dry for 30 minutes.
I can't do this.
Honda, open the lid.
The lid is open.
I can't open it.
I'll burn to death.
I'll escape with all my strength.
Ryoichi, Honda, what are you doing?
You're an idiot.
But it looks like it's sunburned.
It's strange that you're alive.
Now all I have to do is press.
I'll do it here.
What?
Ryo, it's unusual.
Do you need anything?
The president asked me to do it.
Pressing laundry?
That's what happens in our factory.
It's okay if you can do it.
Hey, I'm done cleaning.
Ryo, what is this?
It's like a brick.
I pressed it with a lot of glue.
My body is stretched and I can't move.
I can't do it because it hurts.
Do you get 2,000 yen for this?
Shut up. Don't say luxurious.
It was originally caused by a rag.
The one who broke the washing machine was Ryo-tsu.
Excuse me, Mr. Ryo.
I slipped in the bathroom.
You can't come back for the time being?
What does that mean?
It means that Ryo-tsu's wife will continue for the time being.
I don't want to do that!
What?
That's why we have to do something about the money we got from the
money we got from the money we got from the money we got from the
money we got from the money we got from the money we got from
the money we got from the money we got from the money we got from
the money we got from the money we got from the money we dashed
what?
..
Oh, you're 21 years old.
Mm-hmm.
Nice to meet you.
I feel like you're not bad, Senpai.
I-I think I'm good, too.
Well, let's move on to the evaluation.
Yes, you passed!
I'm so happy!
You said you were okay!
H-hello. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you're married!
You're married?
My hobbies are anime, figure skating, and game.
Game?
I'm particularly worried about the Doki Memo.
I'd like to ask you something.
What should I do to invite Saotome Saori to the pool?
Well, I have one right now, so would you like to try it?
Oh, you passed!
Nice to meet you.
You passed!
Good luck to you both!
Here we are.
Nice to meet you!
Well...
Welcome!
So all seven rooms came together.
Include your ten-month rent...
Make it 65,000 Yen...
...and that makes you 26,000 Yen.
That's an all-in-all 7,000 Yen.
We're at around 1.8 million Yen!
Well done, Ryo.
No, it's all thanks to everyone's help.
It's getting fun, Ryo.
The room...
No, no, it's too much.
Chief!
What's too much?
The room is empty and the manager is listening.
Why is the chief...
The Room is empty and the manager is listening.
Chief, why did you come back alone again?
My friend went back to his home today.
He came to take care of me tonight.
Is that so, Chief?
Can you wait a moment?
What are you going to do, Ryo?
I have no choice but to open a room somewhere.
Open whose room?
What?
Ah, ah, ah, ah?
I have no choice but to sacrifice this place to Honda.
Yes.
Honda, tonight is the only night.
Oh, no!
Oh, it's pretty beautiful, isn't it?
Well, I have a tough eye.
Well, Chief, take your time.
Do it, do it.
Ouch!
You brat!
Ryo, what's wrong?
I, I, I can't do anything!
Chief!
There's no way you can't do anything!
Open the door!
Ryo!
Ouch!
Huh?
A tricycle?
Why is there a tricycle here?
Ryo.
Well, that's...
Ah, it's Honda's.
Ah.
Why does Honda have a tricycle?
Have you never seen a tricycle before?
A tricycle, isn't it?
It's clearly a tricycle.
I know.
Oh, I see.
Ah.
A tricycle?
No, it's a tricycle.
It's a tricycle.
A tricycle.
Where are the tricycles?
It's a tricycle.
Si-si-si-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha.
If it has a handle, everything is okay.
One, two.
What?
One, two, one, two, one, two.
Let's go, let's go, let's go dancing.
Ryotsu, is there a woman here?
There's no way there is.
What's with that voice?
This is...
You must be hiding something.
Hiding?
What do you mean hiding?
This is the room.
Open it, Ryotsu.
But...
Get out of the way. I'll open it.
No, you can't, chief.
Why not?
As a human being...
What are you saying?
Let's dancing.
One, two, one, two.
Let's go, one, two, one, two, one, two.
Let's go, let's go dancing.
What do you want to do with me?
You're my lover, I got it all.
I'm not just a AIDS patient.
I'm the only killer.
I'm the only one who's not the killer.
I'm the only one who's not the killer!
Are you dead?
You broke my heart.
I'm not a killer.
I'm the only one who's not a killer.
I'll go try and find that white monster.
Everybody dead.
Eخ! Ech!
Well, Chief, tonight we'll be staying in this room alone.
Take it easy.
If we don't lock the Chief up tonight,
he'll find out that we're renting a room for free.
But how?
That's what I'm trying to figure out!
Mr. Oya.
Huh?
Is the bath open?
Yes, it's open.
Come in, please.
Come in.
The floor is on your right.
Okay.
Senior, if the Chief finds out, it'll be over.
So don't even think about what to do!
You...
That's right!
Huh?
The Chief has been very busy lately.
That's it!
What do you mean?
Chief! What's the matter?
I was thinking of taking a bath.
Senior, this is bad.
I know.
Chief, actually...
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
Since the Chief is here tonight,
I'd like you to tell us about your favorite poem.
Huh?
You want to hear my favorite poem?
Please!
It's very popular in the Katsushika library.
Really?
Is my favorite poem that popular?
It's already very popular.
Please, please, let us hear your favorite poem.
Well, I can't help it.
Please, let us hear it.
I understand.
Then, please prepare it in your room.
Huh...
Hey, Ryotsu.
The Chief is very popular.
But it's not just about popularity.
It's also about the fact that he's terrible.
What?
In the previous meeting,
he said that 30 people had fallen.
We can't afford to lose.
If this happens, we'll all be disqualified!
Why do we have to go with him?
He's so hardworking.
It'll take three hours to get home.
That's right!
You can call me at 4 or 5!
Now, we'll start the O-Hara Meijin's
Poem Concert.
O-Hara Meijin, please.
Then,
Bensei!
Shikushiku!
What's this?
The song is being turned off!
Gohan!
What?
This is terrible!
Again!
What's wrong, everyone?
No, the Chief is too hot.
I'm getting hot too.
I'll open the window.
Oh, no!
It's better to close it.
It's more effective.
Then, let's start from the beginning.
What?
From the beginning again?
Of course!
I can't believe I can hear the Chief's voice again!
Is there anything else I can be happy about?
Now, Chief, please start from the beginning again.
Then,
Bensei!
Chief, I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you more, but
it's time for the power outage.
I see.
The temple is far away from home.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be so sorry, priest.
Huh?
I'll light you up again.
I'll call the priest and undo it.
Then, Bensei...
I need to go to the toilet.
Oh, yeah?
I too will...
No, Chief!
This is an area we haven't been around.
I don't want to go to the bathroom.
If you leave this room, everything will be over.
Yes.
There is something wrong.
You don't have to be patient here.
It seems so.
I'm sorry.
My dad will leave Kobe tonight.
I have to go to Tokyo Station.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little ...
I see.
Everyone seems to be busy.
I'll leave it here tonight.
What?
Chief, you're wrong.
Nakagawa wants to listen more carefully.
What?
There is no place for us to run away from you.
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
I'm touched by your picture and I'm crying.
I see.
Then I'll cut it.
No, Chief.
You're the best in Japan.
It will be my revenge.
The mouse is running away.
The mouse ran away to the cockroach.
He goes aside.
Huh, I'm not!
Ah, what is this?
Yukimura!
Yukimura, it's cold!
I'm almost done!
Mika, you guys!
I see. It'll be easier if you just faint.
Hey, Nakagawa!
Huh? Me too.
Sagonji, you too?
I'm getting better!
Kyuusen! Kousen!
I'm sorry!
What? The air force is destroyed?
Senpai, we're going out tonight.
Okay.
It's over!
This is bad!
Senpai!
We can't take it anymore!
What happened?
It's a trap!
I'm so sorry!
This is bad!
It's a trap!
What's wrong with you?
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
I was just trying to make you...
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, please.
Don't worry!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Peters.
It's okay.
It's okay!
English translation by alyssa
There are rumors that I am a girl who can not love
However, there are a lot of things I want to do
I want to run in a bike through a vast desert
I want to be free more than a bird
A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a full moon
I'm sorry, my love, wait for me
I don't like it
It's quite bright
You can understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me