Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you watch TV ♪
♪ Make the room brighter and try to get away from it ♪
♪ Hello, goodbye ♪
♪ If you live just for the night, you'll be home soon ♪
♪ Don't panic, in this small town ♪
♪ Where are you going? Just go around ♪
♪ Maybe there's someone better than me ♪
♪ Someone better than me ♪
♪ If you're there, let me hear it, let me hear it all night long ♪
♪ I don't hate waiting ♪
♪ Because I'm a woman sitting on a throne ♪
♪ I don't want to lose, I'm a woman sitting on a throne ♪
♪ I've loved you for a thousand years ♪
♪ I'm a woman sitting on a throne ♪
A Gift from the Night Sky
The room temperature is 37 degrees.
Don't check it. It'll get hotter.
I'm home.
I bought ice cream.
Yay!
And then, I bought fireworks.
You too, Reiko?
What? You too, Kei?
Yes.
And then, I bought them directly from a friend's factory.
There's so much, it's 5,000 yen.
It's cheap, but what are you going to do with it?
It's obvious, Teraikun.
There's a fireworks show in the back park.
She's got a lot of fireworks.
I know the stuff she's making.
I know too, but they change colors.
There it is.
It's so nice to have had one.
Ich inevitably
I'm going to chase after her!
She's chasing me!
I'm going to chase her!
I get catched!
Oh, it's Ryo's doing again.
What is this?
What's this, Nagagawa?
Don't you know the Rat Fire?
I was abroad when I was a kid.
You can't predict how it'll work, can you?
We used to play a lot when we were kids.
And if you call it a fire, it's this.
Cha-cha-cha!
It's the King of Fire, Fireworks!
What?
What a size!
It's no good, Ryo!
That's right, in a place like this...
What are you talking about?
The firework is what makes the sky so bright.
I made this for you.
It's the 200th time I've made it.
What?
Get out of the way!
It won't come up.
That's strange.
It's the plan of the great king.
Ohara-kun, it seems there's no one.
That's not right.
That's strange.
It'll be fine this time.
Ryo!
Huh?
Chief!
The president too!
Huh?
What are you doing in this place?
Well, that's...
You're hiding something.
No, it's nothing.
Liar!
No, it's true.
You're free to do whatever you want!
I don't care!
D-don't six!
W-Water, water!
Ugh... I'm saved...
What?
Ryotsu, are you ready?
S-sir!
I'll never forgive you for this!
You're fired!
I understand your anger, sir!
But isn't firing too heavy a burden?
If he's so bad-tempered...
If he's so bad-tempered, then it's all over!
Anyway, Ohara, it's your responsibility!
Huh?
You've been so spoiled all this time, so you can't do it!
Hey, do you want to go shopping for the holidays?
No, I can't!
Please, I'll take care of it somehow!
What?!
You're fired?!
That's right.
This month's salary will be cut by 50%!
50% is half, isn't it?!
That's not fair!
It's not even cheap!
If you cut 50% off, I can't live!
I don't care!
It's my own business!
Can I be your father's cute husband?
You're not cute!
You're just a nuisance!
If I die, I'll go to the chief's place every day!
You can live by eating weeds!
Chief's demon!
Yeah, I don't care if you're a demon or not!
I'm tired of taking care of you!
...or something like that.
I think you'll have to pay for your own service.
You're right.
I won't care if you're a good man or not!
What?!
Ryo-chan, you're saying too much!
Yes, I am, Senpai!
Heh!
Anyway, I don't understand you, the men or women!
I'm not a man or a woman, but...
You, keep quiet!
I'll change my words!
I... I don't think so.
I don't think you're a chief, or a ohira!
Enough! I don't think you're a subordinate!
Yes, yes! I'm at the exit in front of the park!
Yes, yes!
Um, Chief!
This is from my wife.
Ah, it's me.
I see! You were born!
So, where's Hiromi?
Tell me you're here.
Chief, that was...
You have a granddaughter, huh?
Ah, she's a girl this time.
Wow! Congratulations!
So, you're a family now?
I was asked to think of a name for my daughter.
I thought about it a lot, but...
How about Sakura?
That's a good name!
Really?
I-I guess so.
That's strange!
The eldest son is Daisuke, right?
If the eldest is Daisuke, the youngest is Hanako, right?
Then, it's a manzai duo.
Otherwise, the eldest is Torajirou, right?
Isn't it Torasan?
You should change your last name to Hayashiya, Pei, and Paako.
Ryo-chan!
Well, well.
I don't have time to fight such an idiot.
Anyway, when Hiromi is discharged, I'll prepare a feast.
Come and see your grandchildren.
Huh? A feast?
It has nothing to do with you.
You're not my subordinate.
I know!
After all, they're all newborn babies.
They all look like monkeys.
It's not interesting at all.
Oh, right.
I'd like to see you next Sunday.
There's a fireworks festival in the neighborhood.
It looks good from the garden of my house.
That's nice.
I'm glad to see you.
I have to think of something for the celebration.
Don't worry about it.
I'll tell you I was asked to do it.
But half the salary is hard.
I have to do something about it.
But I don't have time to do it.
A part-time job?
Ryo-chan?
Right.
In this season, there are fireworks events all over the place.
So, it's time to start.
I want to work there, too.
Right?
I'm in trouble with my salary being reduced.
Right? Right?
Well, things that are too busy are too busy.
Anyway, it's a dangerous job.
Even if you call it a part-time job.
I'm experienced.
Have you ever made a fireworks?
There's no fireworks but I'm a veteran of explosions
You can't blow up
But explosions and fireworks are the same
It's not the same even if you use a gun
The fireworks are an art of the sky made by craftsmen
This is the handmade fireworks
Red, green and blue will change to three colors while the fireworks are burning
It looks like a fireball
It's like a fireball
Many stars in the fireworks will change colors and fly in all directions
But they won't be the same if you just fly
It won't look good if you fly in circles
So you have to line up like this
You have to calculate the colors and make the stars
I see, it's a craftsmanship
Right
That's why people with a rough personality won't like it
I'm a rare face
You can tell by my face
I have a license to handle dangerous objects
And I became a veteran because of the fireworks
Of course
If you help people while you're alive, you'll be fine
Don't kill me easily
I trained my son so I can give him a reward
I told you to stop
I can't help it
I did it, will you hire me?
Ryo, you got a lot better
You're right
I have an idea for a new fireworks
A new fireworks?
I'll give you an idea
It's a huge hit
The last firework
Like this, the last firework had to be lit with candles.
This is troublesome, and the candle light disappears in the wind.
This is what we improved and made it compatible with matches.
When you light a fire, it becomes a flash fire.
In a ski resort, you can turn this into a torch and do a night ski.
You can take this.
I failed a little earlier, but this time I'm fine.
This is a giant snake firework. It's called a "Taija firework."
This one is a big deal!
This time, it's fine. It's a "Message firework."
A "Message firework"?
A machine with a fluorescent diode is placed inside the firework.
You can send a message to the fluorescent diode.
When it explodes, it will open.
When the fireworks are lit, a message will appear in the night sky.
That's amazing! If that's true, it's a big hit!
By the way, this prototype is called "Banzai."
Let's give it a try!
There was a lot of firewood.
This is no good.
"Banzai"
Thanks for the good service!
Miyasako, is this a picture of your grandchild?
Yes.
Isn't it cute? How many have you got?
I've got three this year.
It's almost my birthday.
I'm thinking of giving her a gift.
Is your grandchild really that cute?
You bet it is!
Just looking at the picture gives me the energy.
I don't even have a grandchild or a wife.
Actually, right after she was born, the company I founded had to go bankrupt.
I was already very happy, but when I saw my newborn grandchild's smile, I felt that I had to work hard.
So you came here.
Yes. I've been dating the president here since I was a kid.
After all, my grandchild is the source of my energy.
What do you think of Sakura?
Come to think of it, the president also had a very happy face.
What?
Hey, you two! It's the president's fault that I had to work here!
What's wrong with my grandchild?
To be continued
Hey, have you decided on something for Sakura's present?
That's quite difficult.
I think it's good to have something with the name Sakura.
Hey, Ryo. What are you planning to do?
Hey, Ryo.
Ah, shut up. I'm tired from working part-time.
I don't know anything about the president.
What?
What are you doing?
You're working part-time?
Yes, it seems so.
Hey, you idiot.
Don't you have the will to do something about this?
Listen. Don't tell anyone about this.
If the president hears about this, I'll do whatever you ask me to do.
What?
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Anyway, I'm counting on you.
Yes.
But I'm not used to seeing you like this.
You're not used to seeing me like this.
Oh, I see.
By the way, when my president's first grandchild was born, I took a picture of him from Nobe's closet and watched him.
Oh, you're the president's wife.
The president is not a normal person.
It's enough to call a boss who doesn't protect his subordinates.
I see. I don't think that's the case.
Huh?
I've told you before.
I was a small boy, too.
I was running the company myself.
I didn't know how to do work properly.
Since I'm an employee of your club, I don't know how to do it right.
I'm with you, but I'm also with you.
I understand your feeling of love.
Now that your government has said so, please don't cross yourself out.
Thanks for telling me the truth, but after Jae was killed,
I found out that he had nothing to do with the murder.
This is where Ryo's part-time job is.
It's a fireworks factory where the president was scolded.
Excuse me.
This is the man.
How is he? Is he working hard?
Are you talking about Ryo?
Yes. I'm not suspicious.
Are you the president?
Uh, well...
Ryo is always talking.
You're worried about your subordinates, aren't you?
Well, I'm sorry. Excuse me.
What's wrong?
I thought the wind was nice.
The wind...
The wind, huh?
Reiko!
Oh, Komachi and Naoko.
What are you doing here?
I'm picking a present.
It's the president's grandchild's birthday present.
Is the president Oohara's?
Yes. The second grandchild was born the other day.
Tomorrow, we're going to see each other's faces.
Oh, right.
Speaking of Oohara, the other day...
What? What happened to the president?
I saw him the other day.
What?
Actually...
Please. I'll take care of it.
I'll be punished just like Ryo.
So, please watch over me this time.
Did the president say that?
Yes. And both of them will have their pay cut by 50%.
What?
You think you're going to be a burden on your own?
You don't even think about your subordinates.
I don't even think about my subordinates.
I have to go see Ryo-chan.
Reiko!
Komachi, what are you going to do?
We don't have any time to be together.
Before that, I want a lover.
What? The president?
Yes. Komachi and the others saw it.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Is the president still thinking only about himself?
Yes.
Tomorrow, come to Sakura-chan's birthday party and apologize to the president.
Is that okay?
That's right, Ryo-san.
I was worried about you earlier and came to look into it in secret.
What?
The president?
That's just right.
My grandchild will go in and make up with you.
That's right, Ryo-chan.
Please come. Absolutely.
So, did the senior come?
I don't know exactly.
I told him to come.
Ryo-san is stubborn.
I'm sorry.
Thanks to you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Really, they have come so close.
You look like me.
Really?
Your dad says you look like yourself.
We look alike, don't we?
Like the spot where the eyes are open.
Come to think of it, I wonder if that's true.
This is a wedding dress for you.
Mine is a set of clothes that can be learned from a zero-year-old who is kind to the environment.
Mine is a set of paper blankets.
I'm sorry, you have to be careful.
Thank you, thank you.
I'll be able to prepare for dinner soon, so don't hesitate and relax.
Yes.
Ryo-san, I wonder if he's coming.
I think so.
He just said that.
Done!
Thank you, Miyasaka-san.
It's all thanks to you.
Even though you're the head chef's grandson, I can't keep quiet when I hear that you're doing this for your grandson.
I'm counting on you for that, too.
Thank you for the meal.
You're welcome.
I'm full.
I feel like I've eaten for Ryo-san.
The fireworks show is about to start.
You can see it clearly from this garden.
It's up.
It's beautiful.
It really is.
It's a special seat.
Ryo-chan, what's wrong?
Ryo-tsu?
Forget about him.
Let's enjoy the fireworks.
Okay.
I hate them so much.
I'm sorry.
Please...
"Let only the pretty one know."
Hey, you can talk, Ryo-san.
Ryo-san, the fireworks show is about to start.
No way.
Please hurry.
Let me tell you.
Do they really have to do that?
Isn't that true?
They're trying to drag us down here.
The fireworks!
Ryo-san!
It's so dark.
What's the big deal?
It's okay.
Ouch!
Where's the fire?
Wait!
Wait for me!
Someone please catch that fire!
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I think it's still burning!
Ouch!
Ryo!
What happened?
Senpai!
Ryo!
You little...
You're doing something stupid again!
Right?
No, Chief.
There's a deep reason behind this...
I'm going to get sick of this!
I don't even know what's going on!
I told you there's a reason!
It's about you anyway.
It's a stupid reason!
Dad, look!
That fire!
This is...
Amazing!
What?
This is...
Great!
I-I did it, Ryo!
I did it!
No one can ever imagine
a birthday celebration like this!
That's Ryo!
Ryo!
Thank you!
Dad!
Meow!
It's not much of a gift,
The fortune-telling is a gift that remains in my heart.
Ryotsu.
Chief.
Let's drink, Ryotsu.
Yes.
Hey, are there any more feast left?
Yes, there are still many.
Chief, is that okay?
This month is a lot of work for the chief's house.
It's all your fault.
In the season that's changing so slowly,
I've become better at making laughter.
How will I be reflected in your eyes
when you're looking away and changing?
After a fight, I always give you a short kiss.
You were so dear to me, with tears in your eyes.
How much can a person get
from such irreplaceable things in life?
How much can a person get from such irreplaceable things in life?
You are me,
and I am you.
That alone is enough to make me full.
Just by laughing,
I feel like any pain was healed.
And to the pain I reaped,
I can't hide the pain anymore.
If you act as you have to act,
then you'll come back to be happy,
and I will be the one to come back back to you.
Please leave it to us