Whiff pretty girl
When watching the television, please keep the room bright and try to look away
Come to me, you poor thing.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll be fine.
Come to me, you jobless.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll be fine.
I know.
If you know, come to me quietly.
Your work has caught up with trouble.
What will you do?
Leave it to your colleague.
Solve it yourself.
A
Your boss came by chance.
What will you do?
Make excuses.
P. Run away
Hmm, I'm at a lost place here, but it's B.
B. Your luck today is the worst day.
No matter what you do, it won't work.
What? That again?
This is the fifth time in a row.
I can't understand it now. Do it again.
Stop it already.
Senpai!
Ah, Honda-san.
Welcome.
What are you doing?
This.
It's a fortune-telling book on the magazine.
Look, it's a flow chart.
Ah, you're choosing A or B.
Ryo-san, you've only had the worst day so far, and you're doing it again and again.
Shut up! You didn't get a good result, did you?
Was it a very, very normal day?
Yeah, I'm normal and that's enough.
You don't have a good spirit.
It's not that kind of problem.
Ah, Tera-san, it's patrol time.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going.
See you later.
Have a good trip.
Be careful.
Now, it's on, Reiko.
Eh, you're still doing it?
Of course.
I'll do it as many times as I get a good result.
Ah, wait a minute.
Yes, the exit before the park.
Ah, Chief Ohara.
Eh?
It's a bank robbery.
Huh?
Eh?
Yes, I understand.
Ryo-chan, it seems that the robber went to the Tsuchanaka Bank.
Go to the scene immediately.
Ah, I got it.
Ah, God.
Dametaro Nihononosuke.
Long time no see.
You haven't been fired yet, you bad police officer.
Don't bother.
Where are you going, God?
Ah, an incident occurred.
I'm going to the Tsuchanaka Bank from now on.
Wait.
Wait, my luck today is the worst.
If I go to the scene as it is ...
Prepare the car.
Wait, my host, release me.
Shut up.
Ah, ah, ah.
What a thing.
I'd rather leave this place to Dametaro than go myself.
What did you do?
OK, decided.
I left this incident to you.
Eh? Senpai.
If you do your best and give me a reward, you might be able to set up a robot police station.
Robot police station?
Ah, I'm burning up.
Let's go, Dametaro.
Wait a minute.
Are you OK, senpai?
I don't care.
On such a bad day, it's better not to do any work.
Oh, you don't want to work so much.
Let's go.
I should have told Reiko immediately to you that you would be on the scene.
Oh no.
What should I do?
Should I make a good excuse or run away?
I'll run away.
Ah, Ryotsu.
Ugh...
Ugh, it'll get greasy.
Hey, I dropped my bag!
Wait!
Hononosuke!
Ginkogoutou, you're under arrest!
What?
Keep your swagger!
Watch your step, you idiot!
What? I'm an idiot?
Oh, no! If this happens...
Don't make fun of the robot!
That's...
Could it be...
I knew it.
Today is the worst day of my life.
Wait a minute!
It's too early to finish anything!
That's right.
I was wrong to run away from the chief there.
Do it again!
I'm back.
What's back, Ryo-tsu?
I told you to go to the scene immediately.
Now, here's the problem.
I was in a bad mood when I chose to run away from B.
This time...
It's A!
Actually, I just got a call from the hospital.
The father was in an accident and was hospitalized.
Your father is in a bad mood there.
Hey, Kankichi!
I dropped my wallet.
I met Oharu-san in a troubled place and let him stay in the bus.
So? Why are you here at this time?
I was wrong.
It was not my father, but my mother.
What did I do?
It's a shame to make a bad excuse.
If you don't want to be fired, go to the scene immediately!
But...
Hey, Mike!
Don't!
Ryo-tsu, do something!
Stop!
Kankichi...
Get up!
Oh, that's the robot.
So, was that a bank robbery?
Get out of my way!
Kankichi, I like you and you stuck with me.
Ouch...
It's a gunpowder factory!
Alright!
You're under arrest!
You're under arrest, you bank thief!
D-dumbass! You're in trouble for coming here!
What? You call that an idiot?
Stop making fun of Robots!
Stop it!
Today's the worst day of my life!
Wait a minute!
This is worse than before!
Oh, I see. I'm out when I see the chief.
I'm going to start all over again!
Subtitles by Subdiver
I'm back.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Where are you going, god?
Actually, there's an incident.
I'm going to the Sucharaka Bank.
What's wrong?
If I choose A here, I'll meet the chief and have a terrible ending.
That means...
It's B!
Huh? B?
Sorry, but I don't have time to fight you.
Let's go, Honda!
Oh, yeah...
What the hell?
Let's go, boss of the Ryotsu!
Oh, god...
Now we can avoid the worst situation.
What are you talking about, boss of the Ryotsu?
Nothing! Don't worry about it!
A new pachinko shop.
A. Call the pachinko shop.
B. Go straight to the scene.
Okay, it's A!
Honda, stop!
Huh?
Hey, didn't you go to the Sucharaka Bank?
It's okay. I'm not going to work today.
You don't know even if you're scolded later.
I did it!
Good job!
Haha...
I thought you'd get to do it.
Just get to the point, boss!
I think it's better to stop right now.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Can I quit here?
Oh, I have something to tell you.
I prepared a special limited edition product for today's Prince.
It's a special black crab Wagyu!
Wow, a real cow!
I'll try it.
This is bad.
What? A cow thief?
Hey, that's not it!
Someone, catch me!
What? A cow thief?
God!
Damedaro and Hono Onosuke!
If Hono Onosuke catches you, you'll be in trouble!
Run away! Get away from that stupid robot!
What? Stupid?
Don't make fun of robots!
Ha! Chester!
Alright, I've done enough.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
No!
Alright, I'm ready.
Let's take a break until the rehearsal.
Come on! Jump in!
What?
Today is the worst day ever!
No!
This is bad!
Let's start all over again!
The End
Died
Yeah...
I'm going!
Bye, bye, everyone.
Take care!
Take care.
Hey, you're back?
Huh? What's going on?
Ah, well, it's nothing...
Wait a minute, okay?
What are you doing?
We make ourselves pretty고
If I analyze the pattern, I can choose the one I think is this.
The terrible ending is waiting.
That means...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I can choose the opposite.
Okay, I've decided! I'll choose the opposite thoroughly!
Ryo-chan, it seems that the robbers went to the Stock Exchange Bank.
Go to the scene immediately!
What?
I got it!
Oh, God!
Hono Onosuke and Dametaro.
I'm going to leave this place to Dametaro.
But I'm going to stay here.
Sorry, but I don't have time to fight you.
Let's go, Honda!
It's a new stock exchange.
I usually stay at the stock exchange.
But I'm going to stay here.
Oh!
Hey, Ryo-san!
Hey, Pramoya! What's up?
I just got a call from a friend of the toy shop.
The limited edition figure of the C.I. Joe Asigaru version that Ryo-san was looking for...
It seems that it will be released in a hundred sets at the event venue in Hanyake.
What?
If I go now, I may be able to make it in time.
What should I do?
A. I'll go buy it right away.
B. I'll be patient here.
What should I do?
That's a given, right?
Of course!
Yes.
If I choose the picture here, it will fall into the same pattern as before.
I'm sure it will be the same as before.
No, no!
This is B!
B?
I'm on my way to work!
I don't have time to go to such a place!
Hurry, Honda!
I got it.
I'll go to work!
Damn, the figure of the C.I. Joe...
What's up with that muzzled embroidered thing, McDonald?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, McDonald!
Oh, what's up, Sagonji.
I was down at a nice spot.
The limited edition DOKIMEMO FIGHT SUPER EDITION is going to be released at an Ikebukuro event.
What!?
Of course, you're going too, right?
I'm going to buy it right away.
I'll be patient here.
I want to go to the mountains, but now is not the time to do that.
Ryotsu...
"The Elephant
Oh, Ryotsu, you're in trouble.
The Elephant Winner Perfect Model is going to be sold at the event venue in Asakusa.
What?
It's hot!
Oh, no!
No! I'm not going, absolutely not!
Honza, hurry!
Ryotsu...
Ryo, did you find the video you were looking for?
What?
Ryo, look at this!
Ryo, I got the ticket for the K-1.
Oh, Ryo, let's go to the K-1 together!
Hey, Ryo, I got a new ticket!
Oh, Kan-chan, it's been a while!
Ryotsu!
Ryo!
No! No! No!
You can't be fooled by such a choice!
I'm going straight to the venue!
Oh, no!
I finally got here!
Oh, Ryo and K-1!
Komachi, Naoko, are you the only ones here?
Where are the others?
They're not here yet.
We happened to patrol the area and got the first place.
Is the culprit still inside?
Yes.
But we have to hurry and get him out of here.
Hmm, what's wrong?
A. I'm going to rush in right now.
B. I'm waiting for the support.
Hmm, they're both here.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
I'm usually the one who tries to get my work done, so I'll go for A.
That means, on the contrary,
I'm going to go with B!
Huh?
If you force yourself on us, it'll be dangerous.
We're waiting for the support!
I got it!
Here he comes!
I'm going to run away!
What are you going to do, Senpai?
Uh...
The culprit who ran to the right...
B. The culprit who ran to the left...
Baaaah!
It doesn't matter which way you go!
This is A!
A?
Me and Honda are going to chase the culprit who ran to the right!
You guys are going to chase the one who ran to the left!
Got it!
I got it!
Okay, we've caught up!
Baaaaah!
Whoa!
Baaaah!
Aaaaaaah!
Huh?
This is Kameari Stadium,
where the first baseball tournament by a construction worker
is about to begin!
The top batter is in position!
Booo!
With a power-shovel on top of him,
he's on to the first ball!
He threw it!
A cruiser!
Whoa!
Oh, oh!
It's growing up!
Will it fit in?
Oh, my!
It took Senta's crane!
No, it popped!
Now, the road roller on the left and the bulldozer on the right are heading for the ball!
The bulldozer has picked up the ball!
Oh, my!
Wh-Why am I in such a mess?
The dump truck and the concrete mixer car are in contact!
Oh, my!
The dump truck is in a mess!
And the concrete is flowing out of the mixer car!
What?
Dynamite!
I don't like it!
Oh, my!
The concrete will get stuck at this rate!
Leave it to me!
Now, it's time for the special 97-type tank to come!
Stop!
Oh, my!
Oh, no!
Today is the worst day ever!
NO!
As I thought, I'm going to choose the left side!
It's a B!
Oh, no!
My car is a mess!
What was that?
This is bee!
Senpai!
I'm going to run away!
Hey, it's a B!
B?
Me and Honda are pursuing the criminal who ran away to the left!
You two, follow the one who ran away to the right!
Go on, rip the pig skin!
I got it!
Wait, you bastard!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
What's with you bastard?
Hey, stop! Let go!
You idiot!
Here at Kameari Stadium,
the first baseball tournament by a former construction worker is about to be held.
Play ball!
He's got the first ball with the power shovel on the mound.
He threw it!
Hey, Masaki! Stop!
He's got the pressure.
He shoots!
It's a big one!
He stretches it out and...
Will he get it?
Oh, he got the pressure in the center.
He took it!
No, he missed it!
In the end...
It's the same as before!
Hey!
Today's the worst day ever!
In the end,
we shouldn't wait for the cheering.
We have to do something about the scene.
We have to rush in right away.
Okay, let's go back.
Is the culprit still inside?
Yes.
But we have to do something about it before he runs away.
Okay, A!
We're rushing in, Honda!
Mr. Ryoji, where do we start?
A, front.
B, back door.
C, window on the second floor.
This is A!
It's front!
Okay!
No!
This is not good!
Then, it's the next!
Mr. Ryoji, from where does he go in?
B, back door.
Okay!
Crap!
Why do they jump like this?
Next, C!
C, window on the second floor.
Shida, let's enter from the second floor!
Got it!
Damn it! There must be other options!
Make me do it more!
No matter what I say, today is the worst day ever!
Why is there no proper ending?
What's going on with today's story?
This is the flowchart of today's Gochikage!
There's not a single proper ending!
Damn it! I won't talk about this anymore!
It's over! It's over! It's over!
It's over!
Why? Why?
Good morning! Why?
Lemon-chan is a kindergarten kid, but she loves historical drama. Why?
Why?
Her little mustache is slightly small. Why?
I wonder why her personality changes when she rides a Honda-san's bike.
Why? Why?
Why does she only live once in every four years? Why?
She doesn't lend money to her parents, but she can easily borrow a tank or a fighter. Why?
Why is that?
Reiko is a rich woman, but
She works at a sewage system. Why is that?
Why is that? Why is that? Why is that? Why is that? Why is that?
Next time
Huh? Chief Ohara is FUCKING ATTACKING the main city.
That's right, you have to get out of the city when a noisy man like you appears, don't you?
All right. I will get the two coins that the chief wanted.
I'll give you presents as a celebration.
Next time, the last present, I'll get them all.
Next Episode
A Soko wa Kameari
A Kitto Kameari
To our town
Thank you!