Too bad for me
When you're watching TV, remember to keep your room bright.
Keep your distance, too.
If you're broke, come to my place!
I don't come to your place, but I'm worried about you.
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
I'm sure it'll be alright
You got it, right? You got it, you got it!
If you got it, then shut up and follow me!
The End
The Last Present
Y-Yes!
I'm the head of the police station, yes?
Yes, we at the police station highly evaluate your work.
Even if you say it's work, I just do my usual work as a police officer.
I just do my usual work as a police officer.
Of course, it's important.
Come to the police station and show your skills.
Yes, sir.
I'll do my usual work.
Congratulations, Oharu. You're doing well.
It's all thanks to you.
You're doing your best.
Then...
I think the official announcement will be next month.
Until then, I'll keep this a secret.
Yes, sir.
I'll keep this a secret.
I'm the head of the police station!
I'm hungry.
I'm at my limit.
Please lend me a thousand yen.
Even if you say that, I don't have cash with me.
That's what they say.
You can't keep it to yourself.
Such a long relationship.
If you say so.
Go to Ohara.
Damn it!
Chief!
Are you going to make me a slave?
You are devil!
You are a villain!
You must be a villain in your past life.
You are a villain in your past life.
You must be.
How can you make such a face?
Senior.
Ryo.
You don't care about my face.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, Chief!
Good morning, Chief.
Good morning.
Good morning. What were you talking about?
About how you didn't have money and haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
You must have done some stupid shopping.
You're so stupid.
It's easy to understand.
It's self-reward. You have to put up with it until the payday.
How many days do you think you have left?
If I become the head of the village, how many days will it take to be with him?
But if you don't eat, you'll have to work all your life.
I'll treat you today.
Follow me.
What's wrong? Don't you want to eat?
No, I'm happy to eat.
Chief Ohara treated Ryo-chan.
It's rare to eat like this.
It's bad for your health if you don't chew well.
What did you say?
Well, it's not like it's easy to break.
It's nothing.
Eat it.
Is that so?
Then...
How many years has it been since this place was rebuilt?
I think it's been about 15 years.
I see.
It's been that long.
I thought it was just recently.
As soon as he came to the depot,
I had a meal like this.
How many years has it been since then?
Thank you very much.
This shopping street has changed a lot.
What? Has it changed that much?
It has changed.
Try to remember the first time you and I were on patrol together.
It seems to change surprisingly.
Is that so?
Well, the city is changing more and more.
I can't remember how it used to be.
That's enough.
Hey, chief.
What's wrong, chief?
You have to eat it, don't you?
Ah, my wife made too many bentos again.
I'd like to make you eat them because it's a waste to throw them away.
Instead, do your job well.
Yes, sir!
Thank you very much!
Lucky, you can eat your lunch today.
Your wife is even more upset.
She made too many bentos in three straight days.
That's a lie.
Eh?
I've been making it for you.
It's unnatural if you don't think so.
That's right, Ryo-san.
But it has never happened before.
Maybe he's planning something.
Or rather, isn't Director Ohara's condition strange lately?
It seems like he suddenly calmed down.
If you say so, it's quite unusual.
Senior, haven't you been scolded by the director lately?
Hmm, that's true.
That's right.
Oh, right. This happened yesterday.
Did you know that this place was made of wood?
When I first came, it was already a building.
I see.
This office has been here for a long time now.
You must have been attached to it.
Hmm?
It's as if he's saying goodbye to the office.
What?
Hey, Ryo-san's boss!
I heard that you have a business meeting with Director Ohara.
What?
Huh? Is that not true?
It's been a big rumor in the Katsushika office.
I confirmed it with my friend in the office.
It seems that Director Ohara's business meeting with the director is almost finalized.
An official case will be filed next week.
I see.
Director Ohara is also a bit of a water-sweater.
If that's the case, you should have told me.
Considering your personality, I'm sure you're going to keep quiet until an official case is filed.
The director's business meeting?
It's going to be lonely.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Ryo-chan!
Hey, why don't you give something to the business meeting?
Sounds good.
Yeah, let's do it.
I'll help you.
What about you?
I can't help it.
I'll help you.
I'll take care of you for a while.
So, what are you going to send me?
Japanese islands?
According to the director's wife, the director has recently been interested in Japanese islands.
But there are many kinds of Japanese islands.
Besides, the prices are also ...
The director will come to this department store to see Japanese islands when he has a day off.
Apparently, there is a favorite item.
Let's celebrate the shop with a Japanese island.
A Japanese island.
Is this a side dish?
It's a bit longer.
Senpai!
Is the price so high for this short thing?
Yes!
That's it!
Well ...
Wonderful.
I've seen it several times. It's a wonderful product.
I'm even really jealous.
Oh right.
The fact that you're purchasing it to comfort the head of the tradition...
No, no!
You're the official, so you can't pull anyashig.
You're wasting your time doing this.
The head of the tradition Galleristash this is about being my official.
I can't be patient.
Okay.
...
This is what the chief was looking at.
Eh!? A million yen!?
...
Senpai, are you really going to use this?
Certainly,
it's too expensive even for a ceremony.
Ryotsu, this is a celebration of your promotion.
...
From today, you are also the chief of the police.
You have to dress a little bit more stylish.
Amazing! This is really expensive clothing!
What do you mean, clothing?
If you give me a million yen,
I'll give you a plastic model.
You idiot!
How much do you think this is?
I bought you the best handkerchief
Seriously!
...
No, I'll use this Japanese-style.
Senpai...
If we all pay for it,
it'll be fine.
This is the chief's celebration.
It's a great gift.
I have to give it to him.
...
Here's the delivery!
Thank you for your hard work.
We finally received it.
To think that we could buy a Japanese-style
that would cost a million yen...
Most of the employees
paid for it.
It's the chief's merit.
It's going to be a lot of money.
I'm excited.
...
I'll take it off.
Good morning.
Good mo...
What is this?
Nothing, really.
Ryotsu, what were you thinking?
Nothing.
Chief, about the report yesterday, I was...
Then I'll go first.
No, I'll go first.
I'll go first.
I see.
I was thinking the same thing.
I helped you.
How about you, Terai?
I'm the same.
Well, I'll go back to the camp.
You're not doing anything wrong, but you're making me nervous.
Really.
I was surprised.
I'll go patrol.
I'll go too.
I'll go shopping.
Ryo-chan, take care of the house.
I was thinking the same thing.
Out of nowhere, Chief suddenly came out and we couldn't see a thing.
True, he's full of energy.
He shows his strength and is shining.
I know he wants you.
I used to keep him in my mind.
If I were fresh like he was in the Edo period, I may have been a good swordsman.
Wait.
Now that you know the secret of my group, you can't just give it back to me!
I'm just a bounty hunter, Ryotsu Fuyonosuke.
Don't you think I'm different?
No questions asked! Kill!
The dog immediately turned its fangs on me.
They're a bunch of troublemakers.
Get him!
You're strong...
I'm just clumsy.
I don't have any manly techniques.
Come at me with pleasure.
There's nothing more terrifying than a dog's fangs!
Just choose one!
Huh?
I can't go! My tooth is stuck!
This is a little conspicuous.
What do I do? It's a present for the chief.
I have to think of a way to trick him.
Huh? Where are you going, Senior?
Nakagawa...
That's a present for the chief, right?
Where are you taking it?
If I leave it in the office, the chief may find it.
So I'm keeping it in my room.
I see. That's true.
Right?
But be careful.
If you get hurt, you won't get a present.
I know.
Well, then...
How much will it cost if I...
What?
How much will it cost if I get this sword sharpened?
Well, it depends on the class of the sword, but at least 100,000 yen.
That sword may cost about 300,000 yen.
300,000 yen?
I see.
Huh?
I'm not kidding.
I'm in debt to pay for the present.
How can I get 300,000 yen?
I have no choice but to do it myself.
It's still about 5 mm deep.
It's going to take a long time to sharpen 5 mm overall.
It's a little rough, so let's grind it with the grinder.
I'll make it look better.
The roughness is gone, but the overall condition has become distorted.
I have to sharpen it equally.
It's becoming even, but it's becoming a thinner sword.
I'm getting close to the fencing sword.
This is bad! I have to put it on right away!
It fits perfectly.
It bent! I have to do it again!
No, it's already stuck.
That's enough!
A gift is enough for a plastic sword.
You don't have to do the real thing.
But it's the captain's celebration.
It may be the last gift I send.
But I don't have any money.
Eh? Senior, you're not here?
He said he'd rest for a while.
He's having a cold.
He said he'd come out on the day the captain's celebration was announced.
He said he wanted to give a present by himself.
I see.
But he seemed to be fine when I saw him yesterday.
Senior, are you all right?
I bought something that looks nutritious.
Is he sleeping?
Senior!
What?
What on earth is he doing?
This is...
I saw it!
Senior, you were having a cold.
I guess I'm cold!
What?
You broke our President Ohara's gift!
That's a loud voice.
The members of the office are paying for it.
What are you going to do?
It can't be helped, so I decided to make it myself.
Make it yourself?
What's a Japanese tower?
I also prepared tools.
I borrowed books from the library.
Is that all you can do?
I can.
I made one yesterday.
Next time, I'll make something that fits the original size.
I just make things that are fun to play with.
Now that I know him, I'll ask you to help me!
I knew it.
Let's go!
Yes, come on!
That's right!
I'm sorry!
Come on, get it together!
Come on!
Done!
You did it, senpai!
It's just right size!
It's a piece of cake.
What's wrong, senpai?
This sword is more dull than before.
Is that so?
And if you look closely, the color is a little different.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
No!
This is a failure!
Wait, senpai!
This is the last present for the chief.
Can you give me something good?
Senpai...
I'll make it again!
Yes!
All right!
Come on!
Let's break up!
Hey...
Look!
Here, take this!
Take this!
You two go back to your usual jobs.
We must go back to our homes.
It seems like he's having a bad time.
I told you he would come out tomorrow even if I had to.
Because tomorrow is the Chief's...
Tewai-san...
I wanted to spend the last time with him here.
Tomorrow, we have a big announcement for everyone.
Come to the library.
Yes!
It's finally time.
Chief Ohara is gone.
I'm going to be lonely.
It's done!
This is it! This color! This glow! It's the real thing!
I made more than 20 of them until I got to this one.
I thought it was a good thing I did it myself.
No one would think that I am a fake.
No, it's already so late.
Wake up, Honda!
Wake up!
I'll beat these two!
Are they going to make it?
We have a good news for you.
Ohara will be heading to the main city.
You're late, Ryota.
He's in a bad shape.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it would have been better to go get a present.
Ohara, please say hello.
As the president just told us, we will be moving to the capital.
We thank you for your support.
I'm the one who should be thanking you!
Huh?
Bun-chan!
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-san.
Thank goodness, we made it!
We made it!
Ryo-chan.
I'm a sign of gratitude to all the members of the office.
M-my, I see.
We all put in our money and won it!
This is the Japanese island the president wanted!
B-but you guys.
Ohara, you can use it.
"Sepai"
I can't accept this!
Right?
Oh no.
What will you do if you get caught?
I wonder what's wrong.
You don't like it?
I don't like it or anything.
Ujo!
Excuse me!
Ryotsu.
Th-That's a fake sword I made!
Actually...
Sepai broke the original sword and made it himself!
I don't know!
Is that true, Ryotsu?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Rin?
What are you doing?
You...
Wonderful.
This is the first time I've ever seen such a wonderful Japanese sword.
If you look closely, you'll probably get 10 million.
I thought it was too expensive to accept it.
You made such a great sword?
I made a sword that's more amazing than anything I've ever bought.
That's not all.
I'm sure I wanted to give you something good.
I was just surprised by you until the end.
Captain!
To celebrate the last time, please show me the sword of the swordman you're good at!
All right.
I will.
I'm sorry.
This is my last chance.
- - Oh
ara-kun! My
... face...! What
's this, Ohara-kun?! I
brought an example for you! Seems
like you don't need it. We
'll let you assume that nothing happened on this one. W
-W-Wait!
Hey!
Chief!
As I thought, you're my god of medicine!
Chief, watch out!
If you swing that sword...
Oh, watch out!
It's not my fault!
-As I thought... -Go on, go on.
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why...
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why...
Even though Lemon-chan is a kindergarten kid...
Why does he like historical dramas?
Why, why, why, why, why, why...
His little mustache is slightly small...
Why, why, why, why, why...
When he rides a Honda-san motorcycle...
His personality changes...
Why, why, why, why, why, why...
His daily life is only once every four years...
Why, why, why, why, why...
Nakagawa-san doesn't lend money to the mass-production company...
But he can easily lend money to a tank or a fighter...
Why, why, why, why, why...
Reiko-san is a very rich person...
But he works at a gas station...
Why, why, why, why...
Why was Reiko a student teacher?
What's going on?
It seems Reiko and not Reiko...
Reiko and not Reiko...
They get along quite well...
Next time on "I'm Reiko and..."
"I'm Ryo-chan!"
Don't miss it!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, Kitto Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!