Kochikame Special is brought to you by Bandai Namco Entertainment and the following sponsors.
This is too tight.
Good day!
You can go home now.
What's with that hand?
What's with him?
I thought I'd make a senbei.
Good morning, senpai.
Oh, it's you and Reiko.
What are you doing this early in the morning?
The death certificate?
This is it.
A propeller?
Yeah, a drone.
You're making a drone by hand?
I can't help it.
I was planning to buy it as a summer bonus, but it was taken away by the debtor.
Damn it!
If it wasn't for him...
It's clear.
I've been waiting for you, Ryo.
No.
I'm the son of a French person born in the United States.
What?
Ryo is so naive.
I can't run away from us with such a disguise.
I don't want to be in debt.
Let's have them pay for it!
Okay, I'll pay, so just you wait!
You're the one who's naive!
Just as planned.
It's a million years too early to steal a bonus from Ryotsu Kankichi!
Who's there?
Higurashi?
You only wake up once every four years at the Olympic Games!
Wait, this year's the Olympics, huh?
Once every four years?
I've been sleeping for eight years already!
Oh, come to think of it, you haven't been sleeping for a long time.
Shut up!
Because you didn't wake me up four years ago,
the members at the home team have changed.
The most popular one right now is...
AKB48!
You know I've been sleeping for a long time.
Shut up!
While I was sleeping,
SKT, NMT,
HKT,
NGT,
and Nogizaka 46 were also formed!
Why is only Nogizaka 46?
Do you want to die?
Shut up!
I'll make you pay for leaving me here!
Ouch!
Stop!
Hah!
We got this day!
Time for the show to end!
Mika, test your luck!
I'll give you a gift if you use a drone.
What?
Our group'sbattec studio will be producing and selling drones.
I have a prototype.
I have a new work of art, so I'll bring it to you.
Nagagawa!
After all, what you should have is a celebrity friend!
Senpai, stop it!
Chief!
Please don't misunderstand, chief!
What are you playing at?
Ryo-tsu, let's go to the end of the day.
I'll go patrol!
Hey, Ryo-tsu!
What a hopeless guy.
We're at the end of the day!
Don't go to the end!
I kicked a pebble to jump into the air.
I was convinced by Jokingu, the head of a gym.
I stood up.
The sun is setting
Tomorrow, it will end like this
If I win, I lose happiness again
I realized it
Because I'm an idiot
Brave
Princess Sabrina of the Kingdom of the Warmth has arrived at Haneda International Airport today.
Your beauty has been the hot topic in the recent year's rare metal mining.
"I'm going to take a look at the princess of Atakaino."
"Many people are gathering in the yard."
"The Japanese government is also going to deepen their exchanges with Atakaino."
"We are going to give them national goods."
"Hmph. Rather than spending tax money for that kid, you're going to raise my salary and..."
"Hmm?"
"I'm wearing a disguise, but I'm sure it's Kanbei."
"Are you going to do something again?"
4 days before!
A word?
"Mountain."
"Water."
"Yes."
"I was after that place six months ago."
"What's that behind the glass?"
The antenna is like a mountain.
It's very suspicious.
The password is mountain.
River.
Good.
Who am I?
Kanbei!
Kanpichi.
Why did you find out this place?
I was scared because it looked so suspicious.
What is this high-tech facility?
You must be surprised.
We are addicted to American science director drama now.
We reproduced it exactly like the real thing.
Is it a drama joke?
Joke?
It's not, Kanpichi.
We succeeded in hacking the main computer of the capital.
It's a joke.
Agent Tomo.
Bring out the video of the security camera installed by the police in the capital.
Roger that.
It's too early to be surprised.
It's the secret file of all police officers in the capital.
It's true.
Your evil business is also in the Eiffel Tower.
The high-tech facility.
You broke the TV station many times.
The police chief left the ridiculous data.
The reason is that you are completely unaccessible.
All of us are arrested.
Don't say such a hard thing.
You can easily rewrite data.
Really?
Ryo.
I'll erase it.
Please.
Instead, keep our secret base in a secret place.
If you can erase it, then so be it.
Clear?
I didn't erase anything.
Hey...
The voice.
What is it?
Is that the one?
Yes.
This time, he cut that part.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to go to the hospital.
I'm sure if it's a good idea to go to the hospital.
DWARF
Hey, stop!
We're not ordering!
You stop now
Increase the speed!
Miyazubou!
2 Yeah
You better leave.
Oh, right, I leave it to them to support me.
Kanbei, a kidnapping has occurred on the crossroads in Kanda.
The suspect's car number is...
A wagon carriage was found.
I'll lead you, so you have to follow my orders.
- Wait. - Roger!
The tower is bent just like the one in the Kanda sushi restaurant.
Alright, let's go around!
It's him again!
- Hiromu, get him! - Yes!
- - Hey,
hang in there! Damn it!
Don't come
any closer! You're dead! You dirty bastard!
Now, raise your
hands and get out of my way! Alright! This is
Ichik
awa Chika. What is that?!
Well...
You!
Excellent!
Huh?
Leader?
Damn it.
Ah!
Well done, Kankichi.
I'll call the police.
Got it.
Thanks.
Thanks for helping me.
You're welcome.
What?
Lemon!
Lemon?!
But I can't go out anymore.
Then I delivered the special sushi.
That's good.
Daikin will be fired from Kakichi's part-time job.
He he he!
It's a demon!
But it looks like you very much.
Princess and lemon.
When I first saw Lemon, I thought I was myself in the mirror.
I thought so too.
There are two Uri except for the hairstyle.
Isn't it a way of talking about historical drama?
Do you know historical drama?
Yes.
Please call me Sabrina.
I was doing it on the news.
It seems that I mastered Japanese in dramas and movies.
That's great.
Sabrina.
If you like historical drama, there is a DVD in Lemon's room.
I wonder if we can watch it together.
Yes.
Hmm...
Would you like to take a part-time job?
Sure.
Over here.
I like sushi too.
Cool.
Lemon.
What is the spear that Princess uses?
It is Naginata.
Naginata?
Yes.
We also have Naginata.
Great!
I'd like to see it!
I won't use the real one, but I can use it for training.
How to hold it is like this!
Yes!
To!
Welcome!
We are not guests.
We came to pick you up because we heard that a pretty princess is here.
I'm glad you know this place.
I taught you.
Chief!
I got a call from your grandfather.
He said he protected the princess from the kidnappers.
Well.
Then the princess's immediate relatives said they would like to ask you for the princess's protection during the next day.
It's a very honorable thing.
Don't take it back.
I'm not kidding!
They've been selling automatic guns!
I refuse!
Chief is also a temporary bonus.
I'm telling you to give me a bonus.
A temporary bonus?
Bonus, bonus.
I'm sorry.
Don't take it back.
Leave it to me!
If it's for the princess, even if it's in the middle of the day or in the water.
So, where is the princess?
It's in the lemon room.
I'll bring it.
It's the first time for her.
It's a big deal.
She tried everything.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to go back in time, so I brought the
It's a nice view.
No, it's not.
I think she's done.
It's not.
He doesn't seem to go anywhere he likes.
Even if you say that...
That's right! I have a good idea!
Sabrina and Lemon are very similar.
How about we switch places for a day?
That's a good idea!
You idiot!
If you do that, Lemon may be kidnapped!
I will never forgive you!
Please!
I won't let you do it!
If you let me switch places, I'll give you this.
I don't want to get a pendant.
Look, Kankichi.
It's a sparkling diamond.
A diamond?
Cream, cream!
I want this!
No!
Oops.
I should've told you to find someone else so you won't fall for it.
handicap
I'm glad I got your help.
Okay.
I'll take care of Lemon's bodyguard,
just you and Rako.
I don't know that they're well-versed in the sea life.
He's just like a figure in the sea life.
I understand. Good bye.
Please come again to play!
... I see.
So far, Kochikame Special was brought to you by Bandai Namco Entertainment and the following sponsors.
This is a project sponsored by the Bandai Namco Entertainment.
It's the false world!
What is the reason why the kidnapping failed this time?
Hm?
Yes!
I believe the reason was that the leader was beaten by Sushiwake!
The leader's mistake is the mistake of your subordinates!
Did you understand?
Yes!
It's our mistake that the kidnapping failed!
That's fine!
Don't make a mistake tomorrow!
Uh... Yes.
"Long live the King of Saburina!"
- It's delicious! - Right?
Well, see you later!
Ryo-san, do you want to eat a fried doll?
See you later!
It's popular, isn't it?
Now!
Ryo-san, pay the bill!
Shut up!
The city of the north is the best!
I see! That's good!
Sabrina, what are you going to have for lunch?
Monja!
As expected, you like the city of the north!
Oh, look!
That's the Sky Tree!
Wow! It's so high!
How high is it?
It's 634 meters!
It's the world's highest self-propelled radio tower!
Amazing!
As expected of a first-class hotel!
They carefully filter domestic ingredients and pour French truffles.
Which one tastes better?
Reiko-san! Nakagawa-san!
You can't drink!
Oh, no!
Nakagawa-san, wake up!
You have a sleeping pill in your mouth!
Lemon-chan...
Don't contact Kankichi!
Let go!
Ladies, let go!
Monja is a good one!
Is that so?
Because Monja is end-class gourmet representative ofIIaka!
What?!
I can't believe it!
Where is Nakagawa-san?
Memon-chan...
I won't be kidnapped...
Nakagawa! Hey, Nakagawa!
What? Lemon?
There must be a car that left the Grand Hotel within five minutes!
Check it out immediately!
Understood.
If there's anything wrong with Lemon...
It's okay, Sabrina.
Lemon is a smart and strong girl!
Besides, I will definitely save her!
I can only see the car of the car owner who carries the seats from the back door, not the taxi or the hire!
That's suspicious.
Bingo!
The car was in the same car as yesterday, and it was repainted!
Use the video of the crime scene to catch that car!
Lemon, I'll do my best until I get there!
Understood.
I want to check the safety of the princess.
Listen to my voice!
Hey!
Hello?
Where's the counterfeit money?
Commander, what did the criminals say?
They asked for one billion yen in cash.
One billion yen!
Commander, there's a message from a man named Ryotsu Kankichi.
Ryotsu?
He's my subordinate.
Switch to the monitor.
I've found the car used by the criminals.
I'll send you a video.
How did you know that?
I've been looking for a video of the crime around the hotel just after the crime happened.
Why?
Why can you do that?
I mean, where is it?
I don't care about that!
Anyway, find the car of the criminal and contact me if you find it!
Please contact the phone!
Then!
Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu!
Agent Kanbi!
I found you before the cherry blossoms that are stepping on the temple!
It's Osakusa Bridge!
It's huge!
Please follow me!
Kan-kichi, take this!
Oh! I'll be saved!
Hehehe!
Lemon-chan?
Yes, yes, I understand!
I'm sorry, but today's training will be canceled.
Ah...
I'm sorry...
Let's go!
Ryo-tsu's boss!
Oh!
Kanbi!
Hmm?
Ryo-ryo-ryo-ryo!
All right!
Hey, you're pretty fast!
I've been driving at 200km/h!
All right!
Ouch!
Huh?
I'll go, too!
No! It's too dangerous!
But...
Trust me!
No, no, no! I want to go, too!
Oh, no...
Oh...
Ryo-chan!
I'm sorry!
We were following you, but you kidnapped Lemon-chan!
It can't be helped!
They were the ones who were the top!
Anyway, you came to the right place!
I'm counting on Sabrina!
And you follow Kanbei's instructions inside!
All right!
Sabrina, wait for me!
I'll definitely bring Lemon home!
Really?
Yes!
Promise?
I promise!
All right! I promise!
Let's go!
Ryo-ryo-ryo-ryo!
Move!
Kanbei, can you hear me?
Yes!
The Ryokai are heading for Ryogoku!
I got it!
Ryo-ryo-ryo-ryo!
Huh?
It's my turn!
All right!
Damn it! My body's all wet!
Ryo-ryo-ryo-ryo, over there!
Are you planning to escape to Tokyo Bay?
Don't think you can escape from me!
Damn it!
You're on a drone, aren't you?
I'm ready!
We're going to make sure you don't catch on!
If you come this far, you'll never catch on!
I'm sure Kanchi will come and save you.
I believe you, Kanchi!
What the hell?
Oh?
Don't be a fool, it's not just a game of chess.
Love the sea and protect justice.
Who called you, Poseidon?
I'll put you in a tank, Tansunigon!
Special Detective, one of the Sandglass, Dolphindecker!
Kadoima Sword!
Hahaha! I was asked to bring Ryo and I came to get Lemon-chan back!
Well then, I'm going!
Senpai, please be careful.
I'll break through the wall with my gun!
Come, Dolphin!
Amazing!
I'll break through! I'll break through even more!
Good, good! I'll show you a more amazing move!
Bravo!
Did you see that divine move?
Hm?
Where did he go?
Oh no!
What the hell are you doing?
Kanaguchi!
Hey, what's up?
A large cruiser with unknown nationality is landing ahead of the kidnappers.
They're going to get on it.
If the cruiser runs away to the Pacific, it'll be a disaster!
Before that, we need to do something!
Huh?
Captain Burgliew, you're here!
The Ryukai are planning to take over the large cruiser in front of them and escape!
I see.
So we just need to get the hell out of here before that, right?
Yeah!
Leave it to me!
It's about time.
Yeah, it's going to be easy.
It'll get you on the money when you do it.
hopefully.
It won't be so easy!
No way!
Lock him up?
Fire!
Romeo!
What?
What's that?
D-don't you want to kill him more!?
Why is there even a truce between the Americans!?
This can't be the same debacle as Kanaguchi.
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
Romeo!
What's going on?
It's a U-turn!
Ryotsu, should we sink the motorboat?
You bastard! The lemon's on it!
Ha ha ha!
I knew it!
I'm praying for success!
Good luck!
Ugh...
Oh, Eder!
What's wrong?
It looks like a weirdo is following us!
The front helicopter is his job too!
I'll shoot him down!
Stop!
I don't have any weapons!
That way!
Yes!
Take this!
Now, this way!
This way!
Good job!
What is this?!
Aaaaah!
What's going on?
A strange man is...
Huh?
I'm not just talking about other things.
When an accident occurs on land,
I solve everything with a single pan!
One of the special detective, Sandbarglass...
...Kaipande!
I'm back!
Haaah...
He looks like a traitor!
I don't care!
I'll take care of him!
Roger!
Uwaaaah!
Hmph!
What's this guy doing on the floor?
A regular banana?
Hmph!
What? A gun?!
Ugh!
Hmph!
You let the enemy escape, but you're still acting cool!
You're too naive, Ryotsu.
Instead of a gun, you used a GPS transmitter.
Oh! I've reviewed Kaipande!
Huh?
Oh...
It's so embarrassing!
Ryotsu!
I've informed the kidnappers of the place where the 100 billion minoshiro money will be transferred.
What?! The Haneda Airport?!
I've told them to prepare the charter plane, so I'm going overseas.
I won't let you!
Thanks to Kaipande's transmitter,
we can trace the location of the kidnappers!
Then, lead me!
...
Get on the high speed!
Yes!
...
It can't be helped! Turn right there!
Yes!
...
What's that?!
Why is the plane stopped?!
...
It's not just a cool transformation!
Look at the moon's energy on its back!
Hey! Turn right there!
Yes!
...
Hey! The factory isn't finished yet!
Are you serious!?
Aaaaaah!
Eh, eh...?
Ouch!
Aaaaaah!
The End
The following Kochikame Special is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Grandma! You're here again!
Leader! The cute girl is dirty!
Don't show her!
Get her out of here!
Let's go, Matai!
I'm coming!
Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaaah!
Damn you, Teru!
Remo-chan!
Damn you!
You can't run away anymore!
Throw your weapons and raise your hands!
Die!
Game over, huh?
Hmph!
How about that?
You even have bombs ready!
Get even closer!
Prince, you're the best!
As expected of the leader!
Stop fooling around!
Let go of that girl!
I'm the real Sabrina!
What?!
What are you talking about?!
I'm the real one!
But...
I can't let you get in the way of the danger anymore!
Ugh!
It doesn't matter if you're a princess or a fake!
When this bomb explodes,
the 500-meter radius will be covered with flames!
Now!
Leave one of the Padogas behind,
and all of you leave this place!
How's that?!
Stay where you are!
Urrgh!
Sheila!
What a shame!
Now!
Wah!
Nn?!
Grandma!
Wait up!
Are you alright, Lemon?!
Woah!
Lemon!
I'm so glad we met!
Sabrina!
Yes!
Lemon!
Sabrina!
Gakuchi!
I thought you would definitely help me out!
Thank you, Kankichi!
You two are safe and sound!
Senpai!
What's wrong, Honda?
I heard a strange sound coming from inside...
The dimensional device may have started to operate on the fallen cover.
What?!
Hey!
I knew it!
You're weird!
Everyone, let's run away!
I'm going to fly like a flying dragon!
Huh? Senpai?
Senpai?!
Kankichi, where are you going?!
Rats!
I won't be able to make it out of here if I use the Sky Tree Elevator!
What's that idiot going to do?!
Oh, Kankichi!
I see!
The Sky Tree is 634 meters high.
Did Senpai go up the Sky Tree because he heard that the explosion was 500 meters long?!
So that's what it was.
Trying to stop the damage from the explosion to the minimum.
Kankichi, you're so...
I'll do my best, Kankichi.
I'm counting on you!
Ryosu, there's no time left!
I'll do my best with this!
I can't do this anymore!
I have no choice but to get back up!
Now all we have to do is throw it far away!
This isn't the time to be being pushed by the wind!
That's right!
What?
What?!
Taito wants to help Kuro!
And I'm here for you!
Kankichi!
There is no way Kankichi will die!
Please help me, please help me!!
Kaakichi!!!!
I'm not going to die.
I'm going to die.
You saved the lives of many people who protected the underground city.
Of course, it's heaven.
You're an idiot.
There are more evil spirits in the Noenma Town.
So, are you going to hell?
Don't decide that on your own.
Those who don't want you to go to hell are so desperate.
So, are you going to heaven?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
Heaven is also a human.
Where do you think you are walking around?
They drop their weapon.
I'm going to die.
There's nothing to be done.
Stay here.
I want to die.
I'm going to die.
*cries*
What's all of you doing here?
Kankichi!
Kankichi! Ryo-chan!
Senpai! Senpai!
*cries*
Kakuwa!
The power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the
power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of
Hey, Ryotsu! Don't you wait!
I won't pay even if I pay you back!
Hey, wait! Ryotsu!
I will never accept it!
I won't!
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black road of Akeidogai
I saw it
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
It's a politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You will meet everyone
Let's go!
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone, let's go to our town
Thank you!
After this, we have a message from Akimoto-sensei!
Akimoto-sensei's message
Did you enjoy it?
Thank you for everything!
See you later!