Inhabiting the "Masked Girls"
From inside I look up at my shadow
If I jump over the pebble I'll be on the Moon
From the water tank of a capricious hat
To the taishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow is already over
Katsushika, Shibamata, and happiness
I noticed it with a mark
Because I'm an idiot
Shibamata, Shibamata, and happiness
Lord Ryo, I'm going now.
Lord Ryo
Hey! Don't get in there!
No, Lord Ryo, you are embarrassing.
Please take care of us.
You're married from today, aren't you?
Is that so?
I'm happy.
I'm going to join you.
Ryo!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
It was a dream.
I had a terrible dream.
What?
Good morning, Ryo.
Maria!
Why are you here?
I see.
I'm still dreaming.
I'm sure it's a dream.
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up!
It hurts.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
I have nowhere to go.
What do you mean?
I asked you to come to the same dorm as Ryo.
But you said I couldn't stay here.
Of course.
You can go to the women's room.
I'm a man, so I was rejected.
I was rejected.
I decided to go to your room.
Don't make up your mind.
I can't do that.
Don't look at me like that.
Only you can rely on the police.
What should I do?
Don't cry.
I know. I know.
Do as you please.
That's enough.
I can't help it.
Ryo, I'm so happy!
Stop it!
I should return this book.
I've been borrowing it for a long time.
Senpai!
Hold on!
Did I go to the wrong room?
It's Senpai's room.
Who is it?
Um...
Hey, Honda! Come in!
Good morning.
Who is that pretty lady?
Get away!
I'm a member of the Katsushika family.
My name is Asato Iris.
My name is Maria.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Honda from Koki.
I'll prepare breakfast for you.
Go ahead.
Is it breakfast?
It's breakfast for you.
I'm sorry, I didn't know you were so good at cooking.
I can make sake right now!
What?
Don't be a friend.
Try it.
It's really tasty.
I thought you were very good at cooking.
And you are so pretty.
That's a misunderstanding.
Okay?
What? A man?
Yeah.
Please don't tell me such a lie.
Even if you're a senior, you're joking.
Senpai is so nice.
I wonder why I'm so selfish all the time.
Why does it always end up like this?
After all, I only have a motorcycle.
Senpai is so nice.
Don't be so mean.
Maria said you're a man.
Okay, come on.
What?
Maria.
Yes?
Ready, go!
It's so...
I forgot Maria was a former kickboxing champion.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, Mr. Honda.
No, it was my fault.
Maria, you can't fight anymore.
What?
Listen, you're a former kickboxing champion.
You're a walking monster.
To protect Ryo-sama?
No, you can't.
Okay?
Okay, I'll do as you say.
She's so cute and honest.
But I can't believe such a beautiful woman is a man.
I don't believe it.
I think so, too.
At least, once I thought we were going to get married.
I'm always okay with it.
I know it's a little too short.
But I like this feeling.
No, no, no.
Men can't marry each other.
Do you hate me that much though I love you so much?
It's not like I like or hate you.
Well, well, I'm not that kind of man.
Senpai, I feel sorry for you not understanding Maria's womanly heart.
What womanly heart?
It's a man's heart.
Because I'm a man.
There's a reason why men are attracted to manly hearts.
It has a different meaning!
Ryo-sama, you're so rude.
I made you cry.
I'm sorry.
I'll make you think you're a woman.
I'll try to make it work for me.
So don't cry.
I'm really happy!
I don't know if I feel good or bad.
Thank you for the meal.
Well, I'm going to go and get Maria's room.
What?
If you think you're a woman, you can't live with her.
In the men's dormitory, women are not allowed to enter.
But...
What?
If we fight, the woman's dormitory will be closed.
Leave it to me.
I'll rely on you, Ryo-sama.
Did you really see that?
Yeah, it's true.
That's for sure.
I think it's around here.
Nice to meet you.
I'll move in tomorrow.
What about that?
If I can get along with you, I'll stop listening to that sexual oxen.
Let me go home and tell Maria.
I'm sure of it.
Look, the iron-clad coach.
So he snuck into the police station.
What?
What are you guys doing here?
Want to be allies?
We finally found the iron-clad coach.
This is the hundredth iron-cladиныwaowe prominent town moments to people live with.
Iron-clad measles?
I want to ask you something.
Where did you hide the old man?
Old man? What do you mean?
I didn't hide anything.
You're just trying to cut my hair.
I'll have you answer with all my strength, Iwao!
Stop it! It's not me!
I'm not Gantetsu! I'm Ryo Tsukanki!
No problem!
It's Suhiro Ryoko!
Where?
You're disgusting!
I have 10,000 yen bills...
Wait!
You always get caught up in this, Gantetsu.
Stop it!
Gantetsu!
He's not Gantetsu!
If you're Gantetsu, I have my own ideas!
It's Buffy's Mia and Miu!
Idiot. You can't get caught up in this.
Ryo!
We're so happy...
We'll win, Ryo.
I'm so happy.
Ouch!
Damn it!
I'm sorry, you bastard!
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-sama!
What's wrong with your face?
It's nothing. Just a scratch.
Are you alright, senpai? What happened?
The 6 members of the Khenpo Gi suddenly attacked me and a man named Gan-tetsu Iwao by mistake.
He attacked me by mistake.
Is he the one who attacked Maria-chan?
Yes. He was my coach when I was a kickboxer.
I think his face looks like yours.
Yes. I think my father's school students attacked me.
School students?
My father is a budoka and he's running a dojo.
He must have come to find me.
Does your father know that Maria has become a woman?
He doesn't know.
You must be surprised, father.
He might be shocked and fall asleep.
Huh?
I found you!
I won't let you run away anymore.
I got a call from the chief.
You bastard!
Ryo-sama, help me! I don't want to go back to my father!
Don't worry. They haven't realized you yet.
What?
Come on, Gan-tetsu!
I won't let you fool the police officer!
I told you it was just a mistake!
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
Huh?
Oh, it's here!
The chief has come!
işi!
I remember this.
Isn't that a Wotosanri?
It's my father's car.
Huh?
I'm a budoka,
Asato-banda!
TAKAHASHI
Episode 2
They all appeared at a strange location!
What is that guys?
That was just a gank for us!
What an annoying nauce.
Danmuji, where are you?
I am not Danmuji!
This guy is not Danmuji,
I'm not a school teacher, I'm a student.
Oh no, they'll find out.
Mr. Fuku, what time are you working today?
If you don't mind, there's a French restaurant in Daikanyama.
Do you want to have dinner with us tonight?
N-no...
You're not taking the stickers with you?
I want your phone number too!
He's just making fun of me.
But isn't it normal to have dinner with your parents?
I feel like we've met before.
Didn't you go to Roppongi before?
Chief, please don't switch to Roppongi mode.
Go to Gan-tetsu first!
Oh, I forgot.
Hey Gan-tetsu, where's your son?
I told you it's not Gan-tetsu!
Your son is the one I just met!
What?
Ai, you've become a woman!
Yes, Father.
Oh my god!
Delicious spaghetti, lasagna, borscht, pizza, flatbread!
What the hell is this?
Chief, please be careful!
Please forget about me, Father!
What?
What the hell are you talking about?
I won't!
The one who made me the book is...
You!
Since I was a kid, I was a coach.
I taught him all kinds of martial arts.
Karate, judo, wrestling, kickboxing...
I trained him to be at the top of all martial arts.
Then...
He became the president of the Hon-dara-kenpo instead of me!
He fought Andy Trafford at the K-1 Grand Prix.
He defeated him with a kick and a kick!
He made the Hon-dara-kenpo spread all over the world!
He was the first kickboxing champion of the plan.
He didn't just leave the house.
He became a woman!
It's a big shock to see your son become a woman.
Of course.
I don't know why he made you expect so much.
Ai, go back to the dojo.
No!
You're the only one who can take Asato.
My sister, Rin, is there.
She's a woman!
No!
You look like a woman when you're close.
You're not my son!
You're a pervert!
You're right.
Ryo!
I don't want to go back.
Okay.
I'll protect you.
Ryo...
I can't help it.
He's an amateur.
But he's still a man.
I'll protect you.
Are you ready?
Ryo, what's your father's martial arts?
I'll show you my martial arts!
Tsubanomai!
I'm not done yet!
Did you see that?
Tsubanomai...
What martial arts?
Is this a fight between children?
I'm too embarrassed to follow you.
I don't want to fight.
What are you talking about?
Take my second sword!
Hon-dara!
Stop!
Did you take it off?
You're pretty good.
How about this?
Ryo!
Did you see that?
Hon-dara!
I'll show you what a son does!
Don't mess with your father!
If you don't show him face to face...
It'll be hard on him!
I don't like you guys,
I'll make you taste the Hon-dora sword.
Come on!
Ryo!
Sashimi!
Senpai!
Ryo!
I won't hold back this time.
I'm telling you!
I'll show you what I got!
My eyes!
How about that?
You bastard!
You used the old lady to make the Hon-dora sword!
You know what the Shutamachi way is, right?
Let's go, Shutamachi Kenpo!
I'll make you taste the Hon-dora sword!
Ryo!
My darling.
Ryo! What are you doing?
Ryo!
Don't get mad at me!
Ryo is fighting for me!
Hey!
Don't get mad!
So it's finally Ryo's turn to have a girlfriend!
Ryo, I'm going to use it!
Tenryu?
Aye!
Shutamachi Kenpo Oji!
Otankona!
Aye!
How's that?
Great!
How dare you look at me!
Let's go!
Okay!
Thank you, aunt!
Good luck!
I won't forgive you!
Sosui's eyes are burning!
Please let me go!
Sosui, please be strong!
Where's the iron-hide model?
Hey, you idiot!
You're not stupid!
Akabe!
Damn it!
Sosui!
Please defeat him!
This is bad.
What's going to happen?
Wait, iron-hide model!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hey, dad!
Did Omawari come in?
Today's the first time the guests have come.
That's not true!
It's all right.
Be like Kim Taku.
Hey, what are you doing, dad?
Our guests can't be caught like this.
Damn you!
Got it, huh?!
Let's go,
I feel sorry...
Well, the final is...
*Gasps*
*Giggles*
You're done for!
*Gasps*
-Where are you? -Ryo-sama!
-Boss!
*Gasps*
-G-gosh.
*Giggles*
-Boss! -Ryo-sama!
-Maria! -Ryo-sama!
You won, for my sake!
Thank you!
If I was a little more serious, it would be like this!
-Ai. -Huh?
I lost. Ai, I won't force you anymore.
Live freely.
Thank you,
Father.
*Gasps*
I'm glad, Maria.
Thank you, everyone!
I'm glad we talked in peace.
I'm glad!
-I wonder what's so peaceful.
-Geez.
However,
instead of that,
I, Ryo-san,
will have you
pass the Hon-dara-kenpo!
What?
-You all, get in! -Yes, sir!
Hey, stop it!
Ryo-sama!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it! Let me go!
*Gasps*
Ouch!
What? What?
What?
You've been through so much
Hon-dara-kenpo
since you were a child.
I won't do that!
*Gasps*
Father!
Maria, do something about them!
But I promised not to fight.
I don't care about that!
Help me!
All right, let's go!
*Screams*
Ryo-sama, let's go!
I don't want to go!
*Screams*
Oh, Chief!
You can't hide it!
You want Yuko Asada's autograph, right?
If you don't mind,
I can take it and give it to you.
But,
the first love of the great actress,
Yuko Asada,
is Kanki-sama Ryo-tsu.
Next time, "The First Love is Ryo-tsu!"
Please look forward to it!
*Music*
"I can't fall in love with you."
"I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle."
"I want to be free more than a bird!"
"My lady's dreams change with the speed of a magnifying glass!"
"The dream of love and the love of the heart."
I'm sorry, wait for me
The future of the panorama
is so bright
You know it, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me
Translated by Releska