『 Part 1 of Part 2』
♪ When you're watching TV♪
♪ Share the light in the room and let's go hard ♩
♪ As if somebody called me ♩
♪ After a heavy rain♪
I walked while looking back at the other side of the road
I was drawn to my mother
At that time I felt a strange feeling
So I walked only in the dark place of the Ake-dogai Tile
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
I'm hungry
When I hear the sound of Senpai's stomach, my stomach is getting empty
I agree
I feel like I'm going to die
Don't say anything
You're not the only one
Everyone here hasn't eaten anything since last night
It can't be helped, Ryo
Because it's a health diagnosis
Why don't you eat?
There are various purposes for testing
Please be patient
When the test is over, you can eat a lot
Then let's go to eat delicious food for dinner
Let's do that
We'll treat you
How about all-you-can-eat grilled meat?
Grilled meat?
Oh!
Chief
Let's go
Health diagnosis
All-you-can-eat Valium
Don't you feel happy all-you-can-eat?
Then let's take a picture of health statement
All together
"They're not freaks"
Hmm
Anyway, let's go early and go to the полез
Are you happy?
Ruotsu
If you find something wrong in your health diagnosis, what do you do?
Huh?
That's not true for me
which is absolutely true
This body is healthy
You don't know
You can't tell
Because you're moving to a place where you can't see the disease.
I heard that the most dangerous thing is to overestimate your body.
Yeah.
In Senpai's case, he has a terrible diet.
He always eats ramen, katsu-don, and curry rice for lunch.
When he has no money, he only takes a week off.
He eats grass growing on the roadside.
He's thinking about the balance of nutrition.
He might be in a department store with an adult disease.
It might be a department store with an adult disease.
It's okay.
If you look it up, you'll find out.
Okay.
Then, Ryotsu.
If you find any abnormalities in the test results,
you won't be allowed to eat grilled meat.
That's not fair, chief.
Why am I the only one?
Then, the chief is with us.
Everyone is with us.
If something happens to him during the test,
he won't be allowed to eat grilled meat.
Okay?
We'll have to go see the doctor.
Right.
I'll go to the hospital now.
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
The doctor is here.
You're not going to die?
Go back to the hospital.
You're in a lot of pain.
Say something.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
A man who has lived a life of a vending machine like a monk suddenly goes crazy.
No way!
Hey! Don't say stupid things!
A man who gets angry like a manager suddenly goes crazy.
Don't scare me!
That's right, senpai.
Nakagawa, you're a little bit of a glutton.
That kind of eating life is the most dangerous.
There may be a lot of diseases going on before you realize it.
You've lost weight recently.
No, I haven't.
You look pale.
The chief said you don't have appetite.
Apparently, I'm the only one who's healthy.
I'm not like those sick modern people.
I can't do anything bad.
Except for the head.
The head is the main thing.
I got drunk last night and rode a bicycle.
I hit a block with my head.
I'm talking about the inside.
I'm not drunk and riding a bicycle.
Please be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Please be careful.
The chief can't make a big voice at the hospital.
You're a jerk!
Hey, wait.
My pulse is getting faster.
I'm praying too.
Despite his
When do I get an injection?
I don't know. don't know?
Go all the way to the back.
I think I can do it. I think I can do it.
I don't want to go all the way to the back.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Teacher! Are you okay?
Teacher!
What's this white lump?
It's okay. It's a fat.
The monitor!
I just blew it as I was told.
It's not a human technique.
I'm not good at drinking this.
No one is good at drinking barium.
No, I think I was alone.
Wow!
It's a snack!
Snack?
Is it that good?
Anything is delicious if you're hungry.
As expected, there are times when you only eat the weeds on the roadside.
Do you eat weeds?
No, it's not just that.
When I'm hungry, I'll grab the insects flying around and eat them.
If you try to eat it, you can't eat it.
I heard that there is no such thing in this world.
That's right, I've seen someone eat beef eggs.
It's a lie!
No, he can't do it.
By the way, I also saw him hanging on the tree in the park.
You do not believe me.
You're wrong.
Move to the next room.
I do not believe you.
Heading to the Patient's Kit
Here you go.
Where'd Senpai go, I wonder?
Leave him alone!
He'd much better off staying healthy.
How about that!
This is terrible.
What?
Oh, me too?
Three people together, and you're leaving me like this.
Doctor, what's wrong with you?
Is it that terrible?
It's my time. Please be clear.
I'm not ready for this yet.
You should listen to me, Mr. Tenai.
No, wait, Nakagawa.
If you tell me that clearly,
I'll be in trouble, right?
Let's investigate this carefully and thoroughly.
Yes, sir.
Doctor, what's going on?
It's dangerous to go wild.
What's going to happen next?
That's...
What?
What's going to happen next?
It's a trap!
You made me feel better earlier.
You should feel better too.
It's a trap!
What's that?
Eh~?
Ryotsu...
What do you think this is?
I'm so sorry!
You're an adult.
Why do you do that?
I'm so sorry!
Unbelievable.
Professor.
What happened?
Well, it's because of the treatment by Mr. Kanji.
I can't believe this is real.
This is a big discovery!
Look! This is the skull of a modern man.
This is the skull of a chimpanzee.
And this is the skull of a lion.
It's like seeing the evolution process.
It's similar to the real human.
Myra, you're a real chimpanzee.
I tried to make the skull three-dimensional.
This is scary.
Is it a Jaua genji?
No, it's a European genji from 500,000 years ago.
Chromanion?
No, Neanderthal genji.
No, Chromanion has evolved even more than Neanderthal.
This is a living fossil.
We have to investigate this man thoroughly.
Are you done?
All we have to do is wait for the result.
I'm sure it won't be a problem.
Let's go to the grill.
What happened to the three of you?
I'm worried about the result.
Me too.
We have to do a re-check.
Hey!
My name is Luce.
Is that right?
We have still a test left.
Let's take a break!
What is this?
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry, but it's enough for me to see him again.
Don't be mad at me!
That's why I came to you.
What were you thinking?
The End
Where are we?
Are you awake, Ryo Tsukankichi?
W-What's going on?
Welcome to my laboratory, Ryo.
I am the head of this laboratory, Serizawa.
This is a laboratory!
What's going on?
I never thought I'd get a call from Kameari Hospital.
I've been looking into your body from end to end.
And I found out a surprising fact.
What?
Is there something wrong with my body?
I'm in trouble!
I have to eat meat after this!
I'll give you a more detailed test.
Here's the first test.
Yes, sir!
What?
A banana?
Use the fire to pick a banana.
What?
That's easy.
What? That's easy.
I'll do this.
Oh, my God!
It's so easy!
It fell off!
Clearly, it fell off!
Pull your gun!
What do I know now?
Now here's the next test!
Eh?
Huh?
Can you peel an apple?
That's how much you can do.
See? Is this enough?
I'm going to use a knife!
It looks like you're a good cook!
What the hell is this?
Then I'll move on to the next set.
Are you still going to do it?
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Why did you do that?
See? I told you!
You're making fun of me!
I told you!
I'm finally done!
I'll do the next test!
Yes, sir!
What's this?
T-this is...
This is my real simulation system, which I think is the pride of the research institute.
Now then.
For the next test,
Go and grab that torch there,
What?
Huh?
What does this have to do with the health exam?
This is the most important test.
What time is it now?
If you don't finish it quickly, I won't be able to eat yakiniku.
It's a miracle that you have a time concept.
Then let's finish this test as soon as possible.
Come on, do it.
Okay, I'll say no.
This is the last one.
I'll definitely get it back when it's over.
I'll get it back.
Yakiniku, yakiniku, yakiniku, yakiniku.
I'll throw it away in the trash.
This is a human banana.
Why are you preparing a lion?
Shin-chan climbed.
He's did it with a human banana.
Ready?
No, no, no, no, no.
Amazing! He's a real man, defeating the Thunder Dragon!
Grilled meat! Grilled meat!
If this goes up, it's grilled meat!
Grilled meat!
Wow!
Amazing!
Wonderful! Perfect!
Now, the examination is over, so give me back my horse!
Wonderful!
Kimiko,
I'll give you the fossil of life!
Look! This is your whole body.
This is mine?
Yes.
Your head is very similar to the human ancestor, the real man, more than 550,000 years ago.
The real man?
Not only the head, but also the whole body.
Furthermore, the muscles are developed abnormally,
and the body is as light as a gorilla and as light as a chimpanzee.
This was revealed in the test.
You!
You didn't have a medical diagnosis after all!
So what the hell are you talking about?
There's a process called the restoration of the fossil skull.
The skull is made of clay, and muscles are attached to it.
The height of the nose and the position of the eyes are calculated and the facial expression is added.
In modern times, it can be restored close to the real person.
So this is what was restored from your skull!
This is what was restored from your skull!
What?
Don't be silly!
How is it similar?
It's totally different from me!
That's the strange part.
It would be strange if it wasn't like this.
My face is like this!
This is the mystery of evolution.
It's a miracle.
You are classified by the evolution chart of humanity.
You are not compared to modern people, but to me.
In other words, you are evolving at your own pace.
You bastard!
If I let you say it, you'll be in a good mood.
You evolved at your own pace and you're a one-man army.
Stop talking!
I'm going home!
Hold it!
Don't let them escape!
A burglar has appeared!
It's a strong attack, so be careful!
I'm sorry.
What is this place?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
I'm going to the back.
I did it!
The ultimate medicine of the 35th year of the year of the season is finally complete!
The 35th year of the year of the season has also passed.
It seems that the sword man has escaped to Aichi.
I see.
I ran away into Aichi.
He will have a good time.
I'm now going to hand you hacechiku to Aichi.
Yes sir!
Oh.
The battle has begun.
Oh no.
I'm a little upset.
Achi, you guys, take this!
Why did you bring me to such a place?
I missed you, princess.
8th
10th
I'm falling apart!
Time for bed!
Excuse me?
Why don't you go to bed?
But what happened to Ryo-chan?
He was looking forward to the yakiniku.
Yeah, he's always the most lively one, but he's strange.
Is he still being examined?
As expected, he's been eating and drinking.
It doesn't matter. Let's start by ourselves.
What do you want to eat?
Yes!
We're on the way to the show, but we have news.
The real person who woke up from the sleep of 55,000 years has escaped.
Mimmy Mimmy Mimmy...
Mimmy!
Nico Nico Nico Nico Nico Nico...
Nico!
Nico Nico Nico Nico Nico Niro
Nico Nico Nico Nico Nico, Nico!
The message about Genjin in the 55 years ago has now come in!
According to the speculated story,
It seems that the current person is running while mumbling "meat! meat!"
It is said that it is in a very dangerous state. Please be careful enough!
Found the current person! Found the current person!
Running towards the Kameari direction! Running towards the Kameari direction!
The current person is currently heading towards the Kameari direction!
Please evacuate the nearby residents immediately!
Please!
Phew!
Well, I ate it!
Finally, Senpai didn't come.
I wonder what happened.
See? Hey, look!
What's wrong? No one's here.
Somehow, the outside is noisy, isn't it?
Um, what's going on?
It's a genjin!
A genjin?
It's growing and it's very dangerous!
Ugh, meat!
Let me eat meat!
Meat!
Go!
Get ready to drink!
Meat!
Let me eat my own yakiniku!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
The track that used to be so bright when I was little!
The sweet memories, and also the promised home run
Tokyo Stadium!
It was a dream and light for me
Next time, "The Light's Curse"
See you next time!
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!