Gengar's
When you are watching TV, make your room bright and look away.
If you have no money, come to me.
I don't have money, but I am worried.
See the blue sky, the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, you who have no job
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
Red clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
You know, don't you?
I know, I know
If you know, shut up and follow me
I was saved
If you know, don't remember
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
But now that you have an idea, you can't go back now
I can't even do anything
I don't have anything to do with anything
I'm going out
Don't follow me
Senpai!
What are you doing in someone's house?
This is a garbage collection place.
Oh, I see. You got drunk and slept here.
You were doing the 20th New Year's Eve party until the new year.
New Year's Eve is already in April.
But why is your uniform so worn out?
Don't you remember?
Dog hair. Oh, right. I remember fighting three dogs.
You're acting too much.
By the way, why are you wearing your uniforms to work?
Oh, no, Senpai. Did you forget?
The manager said to wear his uniform tomorrow.
Well, that's right.
That's great. Let's change into the locker's uniforms and throw them away.
What? Throw away the uniforms?
What? I don't want to be taken away for a few days.
I have no other choice but to let you all gather in uniform.
Recently, the Aki-su is in the Shokatsu-kannai of the Katsushika-shō.
I want you to patrol in your uniforms and be careful of anything suspicious.
Hey, Ryōtsu!
Yes?
No, you idiot. I'm not asking you.
Are you listening?
Yes, I am.
Don't make a loud noise.
It will echo in your head.
I woke you up because you were sleeping standing up.
Listen.
If you skip your uniform because it's your uniform, you'll be punished.
I know.
Yes, yes.
Listen.
How dare you!
I hate it when strangers step on my feet!
You are an outlaw.
What a mess.
What's wrong?
You're here too.
Again!?
It's so lame...
Ah, I still have to sleep like this.
With this I can get to work without worry.
What!?
Bad!!
Bad, bad! Someone's coming!
What's that?
A wet blanket?
Oh- I mean, s...
Wait, wait, wait.
Ah, it was wet after all.
Just a moment, okay?
Now, this is good.
Don't cry anymore.
It's not the time to change the toilet.
Hey, Yamashita-san.
I'm collecting the newspaper.
Eh, the key wasn't locked?
Yes, I knocked, but there was no answer.
What a good house.
Here's the newspaper.
For two months.
Ah, am I paying for it?
Of course.
Who else will pay for it?
Oh, of course.
Damn it.
Thank you.
Why am I paying for it?
Ah, the laundry!
Why am I doing this?
Damn it.
Oh, he kept taking out the laundry.
He came back!
It's raining and I'm sleepy.
I'm sure I'll have a good rest on this day.
I'm done for today.
Huh?
Let's have a drink.
Here you go.
Ouch.
I'm gonna die.
What's wrong?
You're so poor that you're sighing.
Huh?
I don't know what happened,
but if you look like that, you'll run away from the moon.
That's right.
I'm a great person.
I'm so jealous of everything I do.
I'm jealous of everything I do.
I'm confident in my skills.
But I'm a coward, so I've never done well.
Don't be so nervous.
You'll get better.
I'll get better?
Yeah.
Men need courage and sometimes recovery.
Recovery...
You have to act rather than worry.
Open the door and we'll have a straight fight.
Ah, but...
I always go to the good places and get in the way.
Well, there's always a way to get in the way.
But when you get over it and succeed,
you'll be happy.
I see.
That's so convincing.
I have to learn from it.
That's right.
If you're afraid of failure, you won't be a big deal.
Ugh, that's bad.
Huh?
I saw it.
That was Ryo-tsu.
Can I talk to him again?
No, just take a look.
Ugh.
You have to work hard.
You're awesome, Can I talk to him?
...
What, no.
I'm going to get back at him.
Excuse me.
Is that Tatsumiya?
What?
Oh, you're not Tatsumiya.
Oh, right.
There's a guy in the corner with fibers and glasses.
A male?
Oh, is he King Tatsumiya?
You saved me! You're a good person! I'm grateful to you!
I'm Ryotsu!
I'm Mameda!
My husband is related to that place.
Oh? Haha, well.
That's how I feel.
He has a strange name.
Well, I don't know anyone in this neighborhood.
I've learned!
I'm going to take a look at Mr. Ryotsu and have a manly fight!
It's that spirit!
Good luck!
I'll do it!
I'll succeed this time!
There's nothing that was taken.
I took the laundry and ironed it.
The dishes were also washed clean.
Oh, there's a strange man.
Did something happen to Kei?
No, nothing special.
How about Ryo?
Is he doing it properly?
Well, I wonder.
Well, he's a senior.
I'll do it!
I'll do it this time!
Oh?
He moved!
All right, I'll help him.
Yes, that!
Please give it to me.
Thank you.
It's heavy!
Is there something lighter and more expensive?
Oh, is this it!?
What!?
Uh!
Have you been frightened?
What?
Um,命績 Advice...
For acquaintances ?
No, it's ridiculous!
I see. No, no.
I'm interested in helping you!
Oh, it was like that!
I'll help again!
The noisy one is here!
Why are you hiding too?
Well, I was just caught by Ryouku-san.
You're going?
Yes.
Then I'll go.
Let's have another drink.
Yes.
I'll be good too.
I'll do it.
Everyone, take a break!
I did it!
I succeeded!
What's this?
It's a plum blossom jar!
Why did you steal it?
I'm such a bad guy.
Ryou's wife must be cheating on him.
Chiki-chan.
It's not safe to see you looking drunk.
By the way,
don't you know that we should be careful about Kisu,
or that we need to be careful about Ryou?
Thanks everyone!
When you move,
you can set up another thing.
Yes, I'll take care of it.
Hey, where's that plum blossom jar?
Well,
Eh? You don't have it?
Eh? You did! I don't know!
Maybe it was in the truck!
Why a plum blossom pot?
It's money!
It's not in the truck.
Eh?
No way...
Did you forget to fill it up?
Sorry.
Is there something wrong?
I heard he forgot to fill it up!
The plum blossom pot?
Is it that important?
There are 30,000,000 yen in it!
What did you say? 30,000,000?
It's money!
No, no!
The amount is too high...
I'm scared!
Hmm...
N-No, it's nothing!
Could it be... that guy?
Anyway, let's go back there.
If we don't have the money, what should we do?
H-Hey!
Huh?
It's a year's money!
You!
Yeah!
I dropped this memo case.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I found it!
You saved me!
How can I thank you?
N-No, it's nothing.
Then, I'll take this.
Wait!
What a shameless person.
Should I take it instead of him?
That's none of your business.
I knew it.
Ah!
How can I
make money with such a tiny tree?
I can't believe it.
Maybe next time...
I'll just catch up to him
after I get the money.
*Growl*
Who's this guy?
What's up?
Eh?
Um...
He's my father's friend.
I came all the way here to see him.
Your father's dead?
Eh?
Ah, y-yeah!
My mother's photo is also with another relative's cousin next to him.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Your mother is sick and is in hospital.
What?
Ah, ah, ah...
I'm a bit dizzy.
C-Captain!
I knew it would come to this!
How well do you patrol!
No, captain, I'm just a part of the team.
No excuses.
The patrol's over, so go to Mr. Tanaka's house and see how he's doing.
Only the children are in there after your mother's hospitalization.
Right?
Yeah.
*Squeak*
I see.
So that's why there are only the children.
It's been windy for a while.
Hey, is your home okay?
I don't know.
I'm just a little sick.
I'm sorry.
*Gasp*
Did you have a rain shower?
Huh?
Did you get wet?
R-Ryotsu-san...
Ah, I see.
You're the only one with children here.
Well, that's true.
*Bang*
We haven't heard anything since I left the prison.
Hey, is everybody in here?
Everybody gather!
Ichiro the eldest son.
Matsuko the eldest daughter.
Jiro the youngest son.
Takeko the oldest daughter.
Umeko the youngest.
Oh, Saburo isn't here.
Huh? Where is he?
He was at the kitchen earlier.
Huh?
*Dang*
*希*
You're a little too much.
I'm going to play with you.
I'm going to find a new clothes.
You wash these guys in the bathroom.
Mr. Ryo.
When are you going to work?
You put these guys in the bathroom.
Then you fix the roof.
Fix the roof?
The antenna is about to fall.
The roof is about to fall.
See you later.
It's raining and windy.
Really?
Everyone worked hard.
The postman in Akitsu was caught
by the police.
I'm glad.
Is the senior still here?
I told him a special mission.
Special mission?
Hold it tight.
My legs are slippery.
What's that?
Okay.
Tighten that wire more tightly.
Yes.
Next is the his head.
Oh, you're pretty good at this.
Mr. Ryo,
When will you start?
When?
Oh, when the kids go to bed.
Oh, I see.
You should cure your child.
Um...
Yeah!
Ah! I lost again!
Uncle is weak!
Hey!
Do you have any more rice?
Yes, I have.
Oh, a pot? That's nice.
Yes!
I made it with the right ingredients.
How is it?
Is it good?
Uncle, I'll take care of it!
I'll take care of it!
I'll go first!
Yes, yes, one by one!
Yes, everyone seems to be asleep.
Yes!
Let's do it!
Huh?
Hmm...
But the world is unfair, isn't it?
Hmm?
Even if we work hard,
we can't make a living.
Even if we work hard, we can't make a living.
I think it's good to cheat people
and cheat people.
But men
live positively.
If you have a naked body,
you can do anything.
I think so.
But...
It's important to change the world
before you say anything.
If you're born with a man in this world,
you have to do something.
Oh, as a man...
I'm going to sleep now.
Ouch!
It's 5,000 yen...
Men are stupid.
Sometimes you need to be healed.
Heal...
You have to act rather than worry.
Because if you eat the same yakis,
you will be eaten or eaten.
You have to eat or be eaten.
Police officer?
You look like a criminal.
Huh?
Where are you going, uncle?
To the toilet.
I'm going, too.
Take me.
Here.
Before she leaves...
What?
The stream is flooded.
Huh?
Wow.
Grandpa?
If this overflows, the children will...
I... I...
Grandpa!
Where are you, grandpa?
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Yeah.
Grandpa's gone.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, are you going somewhere?
Don't go!
I'm sorry. I'm not going anywhere.
I'll be with you forever.
Hey.
I thought you'd come back.
Mr. Ryozu...
Did you know who I am?
Who am I?
I'm a kind old man who likes children.
Mr. Ryozu...
Come on, come on.
If you stand there, you'll catch a cold.
Okay.
Great
No, you have nothing to lose, huh?
Yup.
As expected, a new uniform feels good.
Mr. Ryozu!
Yeah.
What is it going on?
The other day,
I finally found the perfect job for me.
Hahaha.
You're a home helper, aren't you?
That's right. I've never noticed that there's a job that feels this way.
I see. Perfect. Do it well.
Yes. Now, I'm going home.
Yeah.
You don't look like it, but you're a good friend, Ryo-san.
What? I'm just a drinking buddy.
Let's go home.
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
I don't want to be someone who's playing games with luxuries.
If you're blocking my way at the corner of the bend,
I won't share with anyone but you.
The moon has escaped
Now isn't everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat
You're helping someone, sometimes
Baby, do you know me?
I'm heading for tomorrow
With a nice breath
Don't be sick
I'll do what I have to do
A heart-pounding breath
What is hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than nothing
Ah, I'm sure it's a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!