When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and try to look away
I look at the sunset floating in the middle of the river
I look at the sunset
I kick the pebble and fly to the shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym I was working on
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I can't help but cry
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
To the Taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow
It ends like this
If I win or lose
I'll lose my happiness
I realized
Because I'm stupid
Ryo's Ambition
Time Slip Sengoku-den
How are you all spending the warm spring sun?
Even so
It's very easy to spend
That's right
Well, my son has been a freshman since this year
Itadakimasu
It was a celebration
It was a wonderful celebration
Well, that's all for this season's greetings
What's the topic today?
Well, there's a big commotion in the village in the northeastern region
Ryo-chan just got paid
It's a very delicious lunch
Next, Ms. Nagano
Mrs. Kanegiroshi
Reiko-san
What?
What's wrong?
You must have done a bonus with a pachinko
Ms. Reiko
What's wrong?
Oh, I got it
You're a stupid, Ryo-chan
That's why you're in a hurry
Ms. Reiko
What?
What's wrong?
It can't be helped that you're not selfish
Reiko, you guys
Let me tell you
Hurry up
Amazing
What?
How would you do it for 500 million yen?
This is Mr. Yamada who dug up 100 million yen liberty
Mr. Yamada, how did you find it?
Well, it!
The pot I'm buying in my home
They were high in the backyard
It's so noisy and loud
So when I laid out trees and dug it
Lying down, la hugging
I was really feeling cramped
I thought I would die with it
I thought so too!
What?
I said I was going to pay the bills, but you're kidding me!
You don't do that on TV, do you?
I can't stand this unfair thing!
I can't forgive you as a human!
There are some lucky people in the world.
Ryo, why don't you dig somewhere?
Maybe you'll find hidden treasures of the Tokugawa family and the Toyotomi family.
I used to do it on TV.
I searched for it in the library or the metal detector,
and I pulled it for 2 hours, but nothing came out.
Right, Senpai?
What?
Ryo, you're kidding me.
There's no way there's hidden treasure here.
That's right, Senpai.
You should stop it.
It's definitely a bone-carving zone.
I pulled the TV for 2 hours, but nothing came out.
I have to dig something to find out.
Ryo, I brought a guest.
A guest?
I'm busy right now.
Please leave it to me.
Ryo!
I found it!
What?
Is he a member of a ninja club or something?
Senpai's relationship is wide-ranging.
He might be a real ninja.
I don't know you at all.
That's terrible.
You're telling a girl who just came out of prison such a cold thing.
I really don't remember anything.
What a coward.
That girl at her age,
I don't know what she's doing if she thinks about it.
Don't say scary things.
I really don't know.
This is embarrassing!
I don't know.
Is that a joke?
Don't talk about it for a long time.
No one will.
What?
What happened to my grandpa?
I don't know.
He doesn't know about it, either.
That's why I got lost.
I didn't even know it.
If it's about a ninja club, I'll see.
It doesn't matter who goes there and who goes home.
I'm frustrated.
Because you don't go there or goes home.
G tiempo.
I'm sure about that.
He used to call me by G.
G time?
Then you are...
That Tengu's granddaughter!
Yes, I am Koume. Nice to meet you.
Weren't you a friend of Ryotsu, the cosplayer maniac?
There's no need to stand around here. Can I come in?
Sure.
I didn't know that Hanayama had such a cute granddaughter.
So, what are you doing here?
Actually, I came here from home.
From home?!
You went to the underworld on purpose from heaven?
Yeah.
If it's heaven, it's probably a better thing than the underworld.
That's not true.
Grandpa's discipline is really strict.
Shadow.
Koume, give me more slaps!
Yes!
Look at me! Look at me!
Kado.
Hi.
What did you do?! Say it properly! Say it properly!
Nihonbu.
Oh, damn you, you!
Ah!
Heh! I've got to beICKY, palabras, I've got to beICKY, and I'm still going to make mistakes!
If you really say so, then studying is your true desire!
And who knows, you might even suffocate!
Let's study-
But it's that old man Hideo.
Heaven also has exams, huh?
genauso
So it's the same in every world.
Let's play once in a while. Sometimes I want to go to the underworld to play too.
I'd love to, but I can't play in the underground. You don't understand, Heide.
I heard that a 16-year-old girl like me plays there.
So...
I understand. I have experience, too.
But you're relying on Ryo-san.
Grandpa always talks about Ryo-san.
I have a crush on him, too.
When I go to the theater, I always ask Ryo-san at the Katsushikaku Kameari Park Exhibition.
It's like a movie about a tiger.
I see. I see. That old man told me about it.
I've done a lot of work for him.
What did he say?
Well, I think...
He said he was a hopeless, hopeless man with no plans and a dirty life.
That old man! Did you say that in the theater?
Wait.
That old man said that?
That old man's grandson means that Koume-chan can use magic, too?
Yeah.
That's interesting.
Would you try it?
Sure.
♪ Over a mountain, a cliff, a cliff ♪
♪ Pui Pui ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ It's a dinosaur, a dinosaur ♪
You know that, don't you?
I'm hearing trees.
♪ It's gonna be a supernatural showdown ♪
♪ I'm
It's going to be a monster showdown.
♪ Over a mountain, a cliff, a cliff ♪
♪ Pui Pui ♪
♪ Hey ♪
*silence*
*sob*
That was a relief.
Chief! Please be strong! Chief!
You can even use a bigger one, like the Pronto-Zaurus.
Enough already!
I know that magic can be used.
But it's amazing.
Everyone in Heaven can use magic.
I'm going to learn it in class.
I'm still very young, though.
No, no.
If you can do something like that at that age, that's a big deal.
You can't even beat that old man.
Huh? Old man?
Old Man Rikao?
Oh, right.
I was just talking about Old Man Rikao.
But maybe, maybe,
that old man's name is Rika?
That's right.
He thought a girl was going to be born,
so he decided that name.
That's why he's called Rika Hanayama.
I'm Rika.
Nice to meet you.
Rika.
Rika-chan.
Ryo.
Harajuku.
Can I show you around?
Right now?
If you start from Kameari, you're going to take an hour.
Don't worry.
I can go there in a second.
Huh?
If you go up a mountain,
you'll reach Harajuku.
He disappeared.
He could teleport.
It must've been hard for many people to visit him.
Hey!
I'm working here!
Old Man Hanayama!
Ah!
Koume is coming, Koume!
Where is Koume? Where is he hiding?
I'm here, Hayayuu.
What? That man?
I'm here, you seduced my cute grandchild!
You too! Why did you stop?
I'm here, Koume.
Then, where is Harajuku? Where is Harajuku?
Hayayuu...
I think it's here.
No, it's here.
It's here.
Which one is it? Which one?
Which one is it?
Well, here is like this. And here is like this.
No, but it's here.
And here is like this.
Again?
Oh, it's here.
You two are completely different!
I'm sorry.
It's not here.
It's here.
Come back!
What?
Mr. Pochii.
Uncle Tenbatsu.
Koume!
What is that outfit?
It's disgusting.
Change your clothes!
No thank you.
It's my money.
It's my right, right?
What are you talking about?
A human from the PI security office?
Don't talk about that.
It's okay, why do you say that?
I'll tell this stubborn old man some respect.
You are useless for the go.
Shut up, you!
I'm Kouji Kouji!
This feels so bad!
What are you doing?
She's the one who's getting in my way.
I'll put you back.
You're a real bastard.
I'm Jinmen Ken!
You're so weird!
What are you doing?
What the hell is this?
I'm Kouji Kouji.
I'm Kouji Kouji!
How's that?
You bastard!
You're playing with my body!
I'll beat you to death!
Hey, Ryozu!
I don't want to lose!
You're a rock-a-mole, you're a cockroach!
Come on, Koume.
Let's go back to Heaven together!
No. I'm not going!
You're a good boy.
Go home!
No!
Don't make things up!
I don't want to!
Don't try to be a shield to your grandchild!
Rika-chan.
D-You...!
How did you know of my name!?
You've been investigated properly.
Rika-chan.
You Papaya,
went to school
and ate poop in school.
Well done.
Rika-chan.
Yeah! And her nickname was Omo-rasi Rika-chan.
I can't believe it!
They froze the secret of the big brother!
I just answered because they asked, isn't that dangerous?
No, if it's dangerous, that's...
But I'd like to share my opinion on it!
It's a masterpiece to say an apology for the dialogue that got Rika-chan to her grandmother!
Root!
Hey, Mr. Yaochi!
You're so kind.
You're always working hard.
It must be hard for you, Ryozu.
It's hard for me, too.
I'm in charge of the store,
so please understand.
So, I won't say anything else.
Right, Ryozu?
Then, I'll listen to what you say.
Just one week until the spring break is over.
You can stay in the basement.
However, the air in the basement is dirty.
There are many bad guys.
It's not a place for humans to live.
Thank you very much.
Because everyone says that the basement is fun.
I want to buy cute clothes and walk around Shibuya and Roppongi.
Everyone is lying.
In fact, the basement is...
the scary place where demons from hell come to eat humans.
Don't say such a thing.
It hurts. It hurts.
I'm educating my children like that,
so I'm going to do it at home.
I'm going to do it at home.
Shut up! You're a big-ass!
I heard you cried and asked me to do it.
If you don't marry me,
I'll cut your balls and jump to hell and commit suicide.
I understand. I was just talking nonsense.
All right.
I'll take care of it with responsibility,
so don't worry.
But...
You're telling the cute children to go on a trip, aren't you?
We're with you, so don't worry.
It's okay.
Mr. Hanayama.
I understand your feelings of concern for your grandchildren.
But what do you think?
Your grandchildren are 16 years old.
I think it's a good chance to develop their self-esteem.
Mr. Hanayama.
Can't you entrust your grandchildren to us?
I understand.
Then it's okay.
Thank you, grandpa.
If anything happens, I'll call you right away.
I'll come to pick you up right away.
I got it.
And then...
This is your grandfather's money.
Yes!
This is a secret from my mother and father.
Thank you, grandpa.
You're acting like a wizard in heaven, but you're acting like a human.
You have to be careful with your health, Koume!
Yes!
Bye-bye, Rika-chan!
Rika-chan, stop it!
Bye!
Koume-chan, you can do anything with magic, right?
Yes, roughly.
I'll give you soft cream, so come with me.
I'm so happy!
I'm afraid of your kindness.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm going to go out for a while.
Don't take your eyes off Ryotsu.
Okay!
Look, there are a lot of horses running.
Yes.
This is a video of the horse sports event, isn't it?
Look at this horse called "Billy No Hope".
It's always Billy.
Don't you think it's pitiful?
It's pitiful.
I want to make this horse the best once.
Koume-chan.
Then, I'll make you the best with Koume's magic.
But, is that okay?
Of course!
If Billy gets first place, the big hole will be full of money.
No, the horse will be happy.
Then, let's go back to the past together and go to the sports event.
Then, let's go back to the sports event.
You idiot!
Grandpa!
Have you not returned to heaven yet?
If you think this is the case,
you're right.
If you change the past, the future will change.
If you try to make Koume do that this time,
I'll make you go to hell.
I've seen that on a school trip.
It's so scary.
It's not a hell trip.
I'll take you to the real hell.
Remember that!
You're right.
I learned in class that changing the past
is a crime of time violation.
Then, there's no magic.
Wait.
I see. You have to change the past.
Koume, can you teleport to the future?
I can.
I learned it last month.
Next Sunday.
Can you do it?
I think I can.
Then, let's go.
Let's go to the mountain.
Let's go to next Sunday.
Ryo and the others are so quiet.
I'm worried.
Koume!
Senpai!
Huh? He's not here!
He's gone again!
You're changing Koume into the taxi.
I should have helped him.
I did it!
I came to the future of a week.
But it doesn't feel like the future at all.
Six days won't change anything.
What?
I'm standing here.
It's Ryo-san's appearance after 6 days.
He's still skipping work, huh?
This is so creepy.
He's stretched his nose and reading an etch-book.
But he looks like this to others.
I'll be careful from now on.
Look at yourself and fix my behavior.
Koume, go buy a news paper about the race.
Me too.
If I go and find him, we'll be in trouble.
That's true. I'll be right back.
I'll be waiting outside.
I'm sure he'll be on the race results on Saturday.
He's going to be a big deal.
Pull! Pull!
Shoot!
What? A mirror?
I'm such an idiot.
I'll go take a look.
Senpai!
Huh? He's not here.
He disappeared again!
You're using Koume as a taxi driver, aren't you?
We have to solve this, though.
What?
Senpai! Koume! Where have you been?
I went to see Mirai.
Mirai?
But why is he going to see Mirai again?
Ta-da! I bought this.
A news paper about the race?
This has the results of the race on Saturday this week.
Are you going to make money out of it?
You idiot! Why?
You're going to get a thousand times more than what you've earned in the last five races.
Even if you spend 10,000 yen, it's still 10,000.
If you spend 1 million yen, you'll get 1 billion.
But what are we going to do with the money?
That's right, Senpai.
You'll lose a lot of money with the pachinko, and you won't get a thousand.
You're out of your mind, Gagawa!
You're going to lend me 1 million yen, aren't you?
Kei, you can't lend me money.
I know. I won't lend you money.
The manager also said that lending money to you is forbidden.
Don't say such harsh things.
If you make money, I'll double it.
No, you can't.
Then I'll give you a hundred million.
No, I'll give you a hundred million.
That's a very good story.
Chief!
Is that what you're talking about?
Yes, I heard everything.
No, it's all a joke.
It's a joke, of course.
Please don't be serious.
You idiot!
What is he thinking in the hands of a policeman?
It's a joke.
Are you really safe?
I'll drive you far away.
You can't go where you're going.
You should pay me.
Hey, enough gurgling.
What's a gurgling?
He's going to take me with him.
You are not going.
That's rude.
You are going to be imprisoned.
Don't judge me just because you haven't experienced anything.
I don't go to military.
I'm going to test the power of the paddles.
He's a man.
I will do my best.
Damn. I can't believe I'm going to get a chance to play with the super manba sword.
I understand. I'm sorry, Chief.
What the hell are you talking about?
Hey! If you don't do this...
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Hoi! Hoi!
To the crossroads of yesterday morning!
It disappeared!
What should we do?
Koume, can't you call your grandpa?
I see. Grandpa!
It's a big problem! Come here right now!
What's wrong, Koume?
Grandpa!
No, it's just that I was enjoying the rest of the vacation.
It's a big problem, Grandpa! Actually...
What?
I told you that you wouldn't go back to the past, but that idiot...
I think it was yesterday.
I was going to go to the crossroads of yesterday.
I understand.
When you say crossroads, it's the time when the pachinko shop is disbanded.
I see.
I'm going to transfer the money that I was going to lose at the pachinko to the field.
All right! We'll follow you right away!
What?
What are you doing?
Hey, Ryo! Ryo, aren't you coming?
Who are you?
Koume!
You'll be home tomorrow.
I don't know if you'll be home by tomorrow.
I see.
Ryo!
Hey, Ryo!
You're not coming tomorrow, are you?
What kind of nonsense are you saying?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I'm back!
I'm going to make a lot of money today!
It seems like the senior isn't here at the moment.
What?
What's wrong?
Come to think of it...
Ryo, you were wrong about the spell.
What would you do if you got the wrong spell, Koume?
I'm sure Ryo went to a different era!
What?
It's cold.
It's cold!
Who are you?
What are you?
Where are we?
A castle?
What? Nikko? Edomura?
No, it might be the movie village in Kyoto.
I was in a hurry, so I was looking for a magic spell.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
Don't be so serious.
You're working part-time.
It looks like a real sword.
Lend me a little.
Shut up!
It's real!
What's going on?
Come on!
The bad guy is here!
It's the bad guy!
We didn't find the bad guy yet!
By the time you get bigger, the boss will be caught, no matter what!
We didn't find the bad guy!
It's like we're in an extraordinary era.
Anyway, this is not good.
Let's dress up for the sake of it.
Let's dress up.
What's this?
Did I pronounce your spell wrong?
Let's see.
Oh, no!
I was wrong again.
What was it?
I was right!
I was wrong again.
I don't doubt this.
Hey, monkey.
Monkey?
Where's the monkey?
What are you talking about, monkey?
It's about you.
Me?
What are you doing here?
Oh, no.
I was looking for it because it's hiding in the tree.
I see.
Anyway, monkey.
It's about time that Lord Nobunaga will rise.
Lord Nobunaga?
You can stay here.
Go back to Zori Tori.
Oh.
Nobunaga?
I've heard of him somewhere.
I'm in trouble.
I'm not good at history.
Hey, hurry up!
Yes, sir!
That's the way.
Watch out.
Look.
Huh?
What a race.
I can't see anything at all.
Honda, I'm glad you came.
Hey, what's wrong with that suit?
If you talk about it, it will be long, so I'll bite it.
Ah, Lord Nobunaga!
That's right.
We are living in the era where that Nobunaga lives.
Hey, you shouldn't be here, too.
You can't fool me.
I'm not lying. Take a look.
Isn't this a castle?
Is this Nikko Edomora or Kyoto's Eigamora?
Don't make the same reaction as me.
Anyway, you can definitely be cut with that outfit.
One Yamato, and Honda will be safe.
Honda will be safe, too!
This is Yoshito.
Wow, senpai. You're like a magician.
What's wrong?
If I talk about this, it'll take longer.
Oh, maybe this is a dream I'm having.
Dream?
Wait a minute.
If I keep it as a dream, it might be more convenient.
That's right. This is in your dream.
What? Then you should have said that first.
I thought it was strange.
By the way, you must have loved TV period dramas, right?
If it's about period dramas, leave it to me.
People are about me.
What?
I'll call you a period drama professor.
I'm counting on you!
So, Honda, who is Nobunaga?
Oda Nobunaga is famous for his military service in the war.
He tried to unify the country.
Oh.
But the one who actually unified the country was Hideyoshi Toyotomi.
Hey, I've heard of his name.
Yeah.
Someone's here.
Everyone's having a big fuss over a weirdo.
But he's not one of those old-timey guys.
Hey.
Oh.
What?
Is it a mirror?
Don't be stupid!
It's not a mirror!
Who are you to say that?
Don't you mean a twin brother from the dead?
Nothing at all.
And who are you?
I'm Hiyoshi Maru, who has become totally stranding with Lord Nobunaga.
Hiyoshi Maru?
What?
Did you know him?
He's the name of Hideyoshi's childhood.
What?
So is yourka the one who is going to be Hideyoshi Toyotomi?
That's right.
Dream is like story.
It's cool.
It's a very interesting story.
By the way, the samurai I met earlier called me a monkey.
I'm sure he mistook me for this person.
Monkey is Hideyoshi's nickname.
But, rather than a monkey, a gorilla suits you.
Stop talking nonsense!
Um, what are you talking about that I don't understand?
You're a man who can't stand it if you're a man who takes over the country.
That's right.
Are you really Hiyoshima-ru?
Y-Yes.
Kyo-chan, why don't you dig somewhere?
Maybe you'll find some hidden treasures of the Tokugawa and Toyotomi families.
Hmm...
Huh?
Honda!
Do you have a lot of money?
Well, I guess I had a lot of money because I was a man who took over the country.
I see.
A lot of money.
Oh...
I might be better off than you if I make a living in the field.
Kyo-chan!
Thank you for letting me be a maid.
Well, I'm going to go out of my way.
Anyway, we can't find you here.
No, we can't find you anywhere...
What is it this time?
The history hasn't changed so far.
-Because it's okay. -I don't get it!
It's too late that the history has changed.
Anyway, let's just scrape past each era and look for them!
Scheme 3 An explosion of an additional century.
-You mean, I'm going to be a
-Yes, that's right.
-Hey, hey, hey, just kidding. Just make it eyebrows.
-It's not a joke, huh, Honda?
-Yes. You will be called Hideo Toyotomi in the future and you will become a white-eyed.
-Hey, hey, why do you know that?
-Even if you ask me why, Senpai...
-Anyway, it will be.
-It's Lord Nobunaga!
-Do-sha!
-I know the way Lord Nobunaga is.
-Oh, what should we do?
-What are you talking about?
-Lord Nobunaga is a very short-lived person.
If I go on like this, I may be cut off.
What should I do?
My life ends up here.
-Okay, leave it to me.
You two are hiding.
-Hot-moth.
-Nobunaga.
-Good morning.
It seems that he was awake.
Oh, damn it!
That monkey was on my back!
Wait!
I'll beat you to death!
That monkey was on my back, so it's not warm.
Then why is it warm?
It's because it's cold because of the snow, so I put the tent in its place to warm it up a little.
What?
Is that so?
Monkey!
You think you can do that for me?
Yes!
You're a loyal man.
Monkey, enough of this.
You're going to be my slave from today.
Thank you.
Mr. Ryotsu, thank you very much.
How can I thank you?
If you're going to thank me, you should give half of your property to me when you take over the country.
You're joking again.
I'm not joking!
Listen.
Help me to become a man.
I'm sure half of your property is cheap.
All right, I'll give it to you.
OK. I promised you.
Then I'll go.
Where?
Come on!
Hurry up.
OK.
I'm going, Mr. Ryotsu.
Go!
Bye!
Don't forget your promise.
Where are you going?
What's happening?
You'll see.
It's an era of the white man, Hideyoshi.
Then, I'll play the role of Hideyoshi!
OK.
Let's start!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Go to Osaka castle!
That's enough!
This is...
What's going on here?
Were you planning to come to Osaka castle?
That's weird.
I wasn't wrong.
Hey!
You!
What are you doing in my farm?
What are you doing in the middle of the night?!
Hey, I want to ask you something.
There should be a castle built by Hideyoshi Toyotomi around here, but I don't know.
Hideyoshi Toyotomi? Who is he?
He is Hideyoshi, who conquered the country.
What are you talking about?
Lord Yoshimoto Imaga is the one who conquered the country.
Yoshimoto Imaga?!
Who is he?
He is the great warlord who defeated Oda Nobunaga in the battle of Okehazama.
What are you talking about?
Oda Nobunaga is the one who lost in Okehazama.
That's not good.
Then, there's no way that Hiroshima, who hates Nobunaga, can conquer the country.
Honda! Let's go back to the battle of Okehazama!
Hey!
Help!
What are you doing?
Oh, Mr. Ryotsu. Mr. Honda.
You're going to fight the Imagawa army, aren't you?
What are you doing?
The Imagawa army has 40,000 soldiers, and I have 3,000.
I don't have any chance to win, so I thought I might as well run away.
Idiot!
You're so childish, so you can't follow the history!
No way!
Take off your armor.
I'll change my clothes again.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Please don't run away.
You're a hundred percent right!
Hey there, nobunaga.
Get down.
What are you doing?
Stop.
What?
You're going back to the battle of Okehazama.
Stop.
What are you talking about?
You're physicallyント these墓 Onosaka.
What? What should I do? What should I do?
Please calm down, sir.
As far as I can see, there are 3,000 enemy soldiers.
This is a large army of 40,000.
It's not enough for us to be afraid.
Y- yes, sir.
I was in a hurry, so I did that.
Please calm down, sir.
Look at that, he's a Nokibe!
Now, it's the time to стали Mr. Miyo!
What is that?
It's Lord Nobunaga's vassal, Hiroshima!
Is that the one called Yoshimoto Imagawa?
There are two enemies!
Even if they die, we'll protect them!
Yeah!
It's time to taste the power of the Great Shogun's sword!
I'll show you!
Yahoo! Yoshimaru did it!
Hey! Hey!
Looking at the pathetic appearance of Yoshimoto,
the Koshinuke of the Imagawa have left the Kumonos.
Everyone,
you've done well!
Yes!
However,
the one who played the most important role in this war
is you, the monkey who stole Yoshimoto from the main camp!
Yes!
Therefore, from now on,
the monkey will serve as the kitchen of our castle!
From now on,
you will be called "Kinoshita Tokiro" again, Hiroshima!
Yes! Yes!
I'm so grateful!
Lord Ryotsu, thank you so much!
I can't thank you enough!
So, don't forget half of your property!
Yes, I know.
It's a promise!
Hmm...
Next is Osaka Castle, right?
Yes!
One mountain,
two parks,
three towns,
and then,
we're going to Osaka Castle!
What?
What is this place?
It's the same as the last time, right, Senpai?
It's strange...
You guys again!
What are you doing?
Hey!
What happened to Hideyoshi at Osaka Castle?
I told you not to know about such a thing!
Huh?
Senpai, what's going on?
I can't help it.
It's time to go back.
Again?
What should we do?
Hey, what are you doing?
Huh?
Lord Ryotsu, Lord Honda!
You're still here,
so you can't go back to the old way.
But, Lord Nobunaga
is going to attack Mino,
so he's telling me to build a castle
in the middle of the night.
It's impossible.
It's not impossible.
It's just a matter of history.
I think he's going to use
the Hachisuka Koroku
and the Nobushi Corps of 2000
as his childhood friends.
I see.
So that's what happened.
I can't help it.
We'll help you, too, so please do it.
Really.
Yes.
Sorry for always.
Mr. Honda has disappeared?
Yeah.
He's on his bike while he's training as a newbie.
It must be Ryo-chan's doing.
Oh, no!
It's this!
It's a textbook.
I wonder what happened.
Look.
This page says,
"The Battle of the Okahama"
Look at the two in the middle.
They're riding on the white horse.
They're Ryo-chan and Mr. Honda.
What?
Senior!
What do you mean?
Ryo-chan is going to be Hideyoshi?
If this continues,
Japan's history will be messed up.
I'm getting a headache.
"The Battle of the Okahama"
What's up with the 2,000-person Nobushi?
I used to have 2,000 people,
but they got stuck in the river.
Ryo-chan is such an idiot.
It's gone.
We must make more than this.
No way.
How can we make more than this?
We'll use "Kakivari",
"Kakivari"?
Kakivari?
Do they make the building or the soldiers
in the movie?
That's right.
-Alright, let's start the operation! -Yeah!
That's...
That's Tokichiro Kinoshita, who's selling out in the Oda Army.
This is bad! Mino's soldiers are attacking!
-No way! -No way!
Don't worry. I've already taken care of it.
Stop!
When a war breaks out on the land, one open pan will solve everything.
One of the special police officers, Sanbagarasu, open pan Dekanosuke,
is here to help!
Let's have the moon energy be on our backs, and the stick of justice break through the darkness!
We'll leave the war to the sky!
The messenger from the moon, Dekko Dekanosuke!
Just like that, Dekasaburo the Venus!
I'm back!
I love the ocean and protect justice. Who called you, Poseidon?
Leave the water war to me, Dolphin Degaemon!
I'm back!
Here I come!
From now on it won't take us a single step further!
Everybody, start the attack!
Stop being silly for a moment!
That's not what I'm talking about!
No♥
We're poor, poor!
There's so much loot in the city.
Now!
D- d- d- d- d- d- d- d-
Fake!
Ad膩の5人でか!
I'll find it quickly!
You would-on-dose give in!
-Game over! -Gold!
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I
Oh...
W-waaah!
This is it!
A finishing blow!
Go, go!
Waaah!
Okay, let's start!
What?
Tokishiro, you got a big gift!
Yes!
You'll be Oda's chief from today!
From now on, you're called Hideyoshi, the god of the Chikuzentai!
Yes, yes!
Yes.
You'll be Oda's chief from today!
If this continues, Japan's history will be messed up.
My head is starting to hurt.
Look!
This is...
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Aren't these people from the Special Police Department?
They're the comrades of Hideyoshi, who made the Sunomata's night castle.
Japan's history is going to be messed up!
It's a big deal.
Mr. Ryotsu, thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
How can I thank you?
So, don't forget half of your wealth.
Y-Yes, I know.
It's a promise!
So, next time, we're really going to Osaka Castle, right?
Yeah!
♪ One Yamako, a picture book, a picture book ♪
♪ Let's go to Osaka Castle! ♪
What is this place?
It's the same as before, right, Senior?
That's strange.
It's you again!
What are you doing?
Hey, what happened to Hideyoshi in Osaka Castle?
That's why I told you not to know about it.
Why?
I'm sure he took the throne this time.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Nobunaga Oda took the throne.
What?
Nobunaga was killed by Akechi Mitsuhide in Honnoji.
Huh?
That's not true.
Nobunaga is still in high spirits and is a royal servant.
Huh?
What do you mean?
What do you mean, that wasn't true?
I-I know nothing bad about rice.
No way.
We're going to fight you again.
Again...
Funeral
Uh, what should we do?
It's time to make a vow.
What are you doing here?
If you keep talking about that...
What can I do?
I am sorry.
Stop it.
Let's get rid of this enemy.
Oh, you said it already. Oh, you said it already. Oh, you said it already.
If you don't cry, I'll kill you.
Nobunaga!
Hideyoshi! You're supposed to be going to take care of Takamatsu Castle.
Why are you here?
That's because...
No questions asked!
I can't do this!
No! No! No!
Let's get out of here!
I-It's a fire!
I'll attack. I won't attack.
I'll attack. I'll attack.
Mister! I have something!
To be continued...
I'm so lucky! A prize!
Hey, hey! Let's say that this prize is ours!
We'll name it "Honnojirohen".
That's what we want!
-Honnojirohen! -Honnojirohen!
Huh? Where did you get "Nobunaga"?
I don't know. We got it last year, so I don't know where it is.
But now there are some traces of history.
Well then, this time...
Yeah!
Let's go to Yama Chong E Honno-Daratte Pui Pui Osaka Jyo!
I've done it, Mr. Ryotsugo.
I'm a rich man now!
I, Kanpakutai-ko, am ready to receive you!
Ryotsugo...
Mr. Yaguchi, Mr. Honda, please raise your heads.
Hideyoshi, you've become much more handsome!
No, it's all thanks to you.
You didn't forget your promise, did you?
I know.
Big and small, they're all around!
What's that?
Ouch!
That's all you've got to enjoy!
Ryozu!
Senpai!
That's terrible, Ryo-san!
Ryo-chan!
You guys!
Ryozu Kankichi!
You're trying to change the past and make money!
You're a total moron!
You're not going to go to hell!
Get lost!
That's a nightmare!
I'm going to the place that's more terrifying than hell!
I'm going to the mountain!
I'm going to Honda!
Where is the place that's more terrifying than hell?
I'm going to the mountain!
Help! Help!
You're in this age!
Monkey, it's all your fault!
It's all your fault!
Isn't this too realistic for a dream?
Damn it!
I hate time travel!
Next Episode
I feel like we're melting together
I want to shoot you down
For some reason love is so cowardly
Don't hide everything that's too strong
I want to be loved someday
I want to show you that I'm a child who can't go out
I want to hold you tight
I want to shoot you down
Always
I must give you a sad message today
My name is Ryo
That Ryōtsu!
He's going to star in a movie!
This is the movie "2000 Year New Year's Anniversary" by Kazushikaku-Kameari Park.
I'm not listening!