Please be careful when you watch TV!
When you watch TV, light up the room and look away!
Come to me, you penniless!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky!
White clouds!
I'll manage somehow.
You know it! You know it! You know it!
If you know it, come to me quietly!
I'll manage somehow.
Ryo-tsu and Ryo-tsu?
The End
I broke the Miracle Cracker!
Chooooooooon!
Oh, it's a mirror.
I'm surprised.
I'll sleep a little longer.
You idiot!
Who are you?
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi, too.
What do you mean?
My birthday is March 3rd.
I ate natto-chahan soup for dinner the day before yesterday.
What did you do yesterday that made you angry?
I skipped work and slept at a manga cafe.
Why do you know such a thing?
Why are you so familiar with it?
Are you me?
Am I you?
Are you Ryo-tsu?
Well, for the time being, it can't be helped that this happened.
We're together now, so let's think about it a little more positively.
Yes.
As expected of me.
You say good things.
So what exactly do you do?
That's right.
For example,
I work in two shifts.
Oh!
Then you can take a break in the shift and increase your holidays.
Then I'll take a break today.
I proposed it.
Why don't you hold back a little?
Why don't you look forward to it later?
No, no, you're the one.
You're the one.
You say that, you're the one.
Hmm...
This bastard, Egoist!
I'm embarrassed!
It's not like you're the only one who wouldn't want to be called!
Hmm act cheeky me.
That's not what it means!
Ryo went away.
What time is it now?
At what time is it to change that attitude?
I'm going to do it again.
That's not the problem, is it?
I'm the one who's in it.
Shut up! Don't scream in the stereo.
I'm not surprised at all by what you're doing.
As expected of the chief.
You're not surprised at all.
Even so, I really only see the same thing.
I've always thought you were a mysterious person.
No, I didn't think I'd be able to do something like this.
You're impressed, aren't you?
But you're great.
If you have two people, you can take a break, but you come to work together.
No, I thought so at first.
Thanks to this idiot.
What did you just say?
I said you were an idiot.
It means that the two of you have doubled your labor.
You're working two people because you're slacking off every day.
No way.
Then, Ryo-chan.
I'm going to work.
What?
Every time you call me Ryo-chan, it's confusing to react with both of you.
It's true that both of you seem like seniors.
All right.
Well, then.
If you do this,
It's done.
If I were Ryo-A,
I'll call you Ryo-B.
Wait a minute.
Why am I B?
Because you're the second me.
So I'm A and you're B.
No, you're wrong.
There's no evidence that you're the first one and the second one is me.
I see.
I thought you were a copy or a fake.
But from what you see, I look like a copy or a fake.
That's right.
Anyway, I'm also me.
It can't be helped.
Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors.
All right.
Here we go.
At first, I'm good.
What?
I said I'm good at first.
You're the first one.
Then I'm not good at first.
It's a game.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Don't play hard to get.
You're a human scum.
If you can't decide by yourself, I'll decide by myself.
You're A and you're B.
If you understand, get to work.
All right.
Then I'll decide by myself.
Why am I working at the orange box?
Senior, do you mind?
What?
I'm fine alone.
Then I'll help you.
Do it yourself.
I won't die.
Ryo, help me.
I'm calling you.
You're the one who was called.
But Reiko said Ryo-chan.
You're Ryo-chan, right?
You too.
I'm not convinced of Ryo-chan and B.
The chief decided, so I can't help it.
Why am I working at the orange box?
You're B.
If you don't like B, you can choose Ryo-chan.
It would be great if you two split up.
At least you two should work as one person.
You're a criminal.
A criminal?
What?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
I'm in the toilet.
It's a coincidence.
I'm in the toilet too.
The toilet is not that way.
Ryo-chan.
I can see through your behavior patterns.
It's about time you want to skip it.
Damn it.
It's because you're standing up on purpose.
You're a liar.
You're lying.
What did you say?
You're B.
What?
Stop it.
Yes.
It's patrol time.
Chief, you're not skipping it.
It's my turn today.
Yes.
You two can't go.
You stay here and organize the documents.
I can't help it.
I have one thing to do.
Fight fair and square.
It's fine.
I'll decide.
Ryo A, you stay.
Ryo B, patrol well.
Yes, I'll go.
I like being alone.
I'm not good at it, Ryo A.
How's it going, Ryo's boss?
What's up, Honda?
What's wrong?
It looks like you're having a lot of fun.
Well...
I see.
All right.
Damn it.
Why only me?
I found you, Senpai.
What?
Nothing.
Give me back the money.
Money?
What are you talking about?
I told you to come get it later because I'll give it back soon.
I don't know.
I don't borrow money from you.
It's my first time meeting you today.
Don't be silly.
Give it back quickly.
I have to pay for the bike parts.
I won't die.
What?
Ryo, Kikanki.
You're already at your limit today.
Did I do something?
Don't play with our pato car.
When I first ran into you, why did I cause trouble?
You're out of your mind.
You must give me my money back.
You want to give me money back?
Why don't you get along?
Stop it.
Not my business.
I want my money back.
You're not going even if I pay you back.
Hey, Eiko, what are you doing?
I'm trying to find a way to get your money back, or learn some new Kentucky.
What are the mom and dad doing?
I them how you get theirs?
I got my money back because I couldn't give you money back.
I see...
Why are you here?
I'm going to help you.
You're wrong!
Senpai!
Damn, B! You did whatever you wanted because of me!
Huh? Wait, I should do it too.
Hehehe, A must be having a hard time right now.
Good for you.
How about that?
Huh? What?
You did whatever you wanted, didn't you?
I'm sure you're prepared.
What are you talking about?
Hmph, you're so stupid.
But that's it.
Look at that.
How dare you do that to my Samba!
How dare you do that to my dog!
Give me back my dog!
What's that?
Just like you did to me,
I'll do the same to you.
I did a lot of things because of you.
What?
You're running around and reflecting on yourself.
Oh, I remember!
Yay, idiot!
Just watch me!
Hehehe.
I'll do the same to you!
No way.
Everyone's doing the same thing to that dog.
Damn it.
I was the same.
Hey!
Yaaaaa!
Haha, what a dumbass!
You're the one who did it!
You should be the one to blame!
I called you B or 2 for nothing!
What a loser!
What?
You bastard!
Yaaaaa!
Hey, you!
It hurts.
Oh, crap.
That was mean.
I've been beaten up.
You're the one who did this.
Let's stop it.
Let's sleep.
This is a nightmare.
Tomorrow will be the same as the day before.
The End
Don't tell me...
What's going on here?
The End
I don't know why this happened...
But we are six now.
What are we going to do?
Hmm...
I knew it.
If we take a day off, we'll be free for six days.
Hooray!
I knew it.
I know what you're talking about.
I failed yesterday.
I'll do my best today.
I'll take a day off today.
I'll take care of it.
Idiot!
What's going on here?
You've been living like a policeman for days.
That's why you're like this.
I'm sorry.
You make me angry.
What do you mean?
I don't want to be a policeman.
Wait.
"Welcome!"
"I'll start with the food."
"I'm hungry, so I can't start anything."
"It'll be 17,502 yen."
"What?!"
"You guys are buying too much!"
"You're the one who's buying!"
"Don't start buying manga in the morning!"
"You're buying the same manga!"
"Wait a minute!"
"I found it!"
"I just realized that we're six people now, but we have six wallets?"
"So we only have one wallet."
"So we only have one."
"It can't be helped. I'm not rich enough to pay for food for six people."
"That's true. But how do we split it?"
"That's right."
"Oh, we have pig's feet!"
"If this happens, we'll lose quickly!"
"Oh, you guys!"
"The croquettes are mine!"
"I'll take the food! Winner!"
"I won't give the food to anyone."
"Thanks to you, we're all rich now."
"It's going to be tough from now on."
"But we're six people now, so we can do our jobs well."
"I see."
"So, let's do it."
"Come on!"
"Come on."
"Come on, Come on. Come on."
"Come on, Come on!"
"Come on!"
I don't know what to do.
Well, then...
Yesterday, we had a fight.
Don't complain.
Just get to work.
Yes, sir.
Well, it can't be helped.
Anyway, let's do our best under the same roof.
Yes.
Okay, let's go to bed.
I'm going to bed.
I'll patrol well today.
Don't bother me.
I got the top.
What's this?
Don't bother me.
You're going to do it again.
I'm at my limit.
I'm going to take it.
Cheese.
let me eat.
What's this?
You ...
is it good?
Go!
You're going to die!
You're a big person!
You know what to do!
After a few days
I'm tired.
The manager was really busy.
Anyway,
let's have aaga.
Thanks to your kindness, I was able to get a lot of bread.
Wow!
It's been a while since I had a feast.
I'll eat it!
What's that?
What's wrong D? Aren't you going to eat it?
I... I can't wait anymore...
I can't endure it anymore!
What's wrong D?
I was supposed to be living a comfortable life by myself.
But now there's more people living together,
I can't eat well, and I have nowhere to sleep!
I don't want this anymore! I'm leaving this house!
Hey, D!
I guess it's true what D said.
I used to live with six people, but it's not normal.
I can't do this anymore.
This is not the life I wanted!
Hey!
I'm leaving too!
I've been taking care of you until now!
Hey!
You too...
If we live together like this, there will be problems again.
If that happens, it's no use fighting with the same people.
So we're leaving too.
See you!
Hey! Wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Hey, wait!
Wait!
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
Hey, wait a minute!
Well, it's not our fault.
Let's see.
I can't do this anymore!
I'm going to the bathroom!
Let's go!
Sorry.
It's not there.
Here's the weather.
It's a strong wind from the continent.
The Japanese archipelago is in a typical winter-like pressure arrangement.
It will be especially cold tonight.
Next is the weather in various places.
What? Did you come back after all?
You always do your own things.
You came back well.
I'm sorry. The person next to me is on leave, so I'll take my luggage.
Oh, yeah.
Good day.
Hey, you can't pick it up again.
Then I'll take it.
Damn it.
It's time-consuming.
If I have a day off, I'll go to the pachinko shop first.
Damn it.
I'm not going anywhere.
What should I do from now on?
Hey.
You look like you're going to lose.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to laugh at me?
Come back.
It's going to be cold tonight.
It seems to be.
But I...
What are you talking about?
That room is our room, right?
Yes.
Damn it.
You idiot.
I'm never going to come back to this house.
Where are you going?
If you do something like this, you'll catch a cold.
Come back, D.
You're very helpful.
I went out of that room.
I can't go back now.
Come back.
It hurts, right?
You're in pain, but it hurts me too.
I'm a Ryotsu, and you're a Ryotsu.
That room is the room of Ryotsu.
In other words, it's our room.
Don't get carried away to come back to your own room.
Go back, D.
D...
A...
D....A...
Line 3 is now entering the train.
What should we do? We have no money to eat.
Why don't you come back?
You guys!
We're not playing any games!
It's true! We're not playing any games!
I don't have to say anything.
Come back.
You guys...
...have no money.
Only F, huh?
I don't think we can go that far anymore.
Oh, hey, hey...
Oh, oh.
Hey, F!
Huh?
WHAAAAAT!?
WHAAAT!?
Wh-what are you doing!?
Where are you going?
You came home, right!?
N-no!
No! I'm talking about that thing you forgot!
I see. You forgot it.
Then shall we eat hot pot?
Hot pot?
Yes. We're celebrating the reunion, so we're all going to eat hot pot.
What about you?
I guess I can't help it. I'll eat it since I'm in a hurry.
Alright, everyone's here.
Itadakimasu!
Eat more!
So good!
Anyone want some?
Yes!
Me too!
What's up, Abe?
It's nice to be with everyone.
How about that?
Alright, let's toast!
Cheers!
A
*Groaning*
Man...
*Groaning in pain*
*T FEELING UNREAL CONFUSED*
*Groaning pizza*
*Groaning spicy pizza*
What the heck is this!
What is this?
Why is it?
Why does Ryo's eyebrows look like black hair?
Why does it?
Why does he run fast with sandals on?
Why does Ryo always do arm wrestling?
Why does he?
Why does he fall in love with everyone?
Why does it?
It doesn't matter
Bon Bon Bon
The title of this anime is so long
This is Katsushikaku, the first appearance in front of Kameari Park
Why is it?
Everyone, let's sing together!
Why?
It's
Why is it?
Feeling
"Jig Full Husk"
Thank you for watching!