"The Greatest"
From a bottle, to a Freedom Check
The sunset goes down
Tomorrow will also end some day
But I'm still so happy
I'm just me who gave up, and I realized
Huh?
I can't drink anymore.
I want to work for you.
Don't make such a loud noise.
It's been a long time since I've had a bad day.
Me too.
Why am I sleeping here?
I don't know.
One more time.
Good.
I remember the 5th Izakaya.
I don't remember the 3rd one.
Where is my senior?
Senior.
Excuse me.
What?
You're great.
Did you go to work already?
Ryo Hananoko.
What?
Do you like my face?
Yes.
It's funny.
I see.
What's wrong?
Oh, Mr. Maori.
Yes.
That's right.
This is your job.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh.
Everyone, say bye-bye to Mr. Maori.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Today seems to be a good day.
Yes.
Thank you.
Next time is kindergarten, to my grandparents, to his aunt and grandpa.
Ryo is very popular, it looks so great.
I guess saben…
What's on your mind?
Congratulations.
What are you doing?
Is this a punishment game?
Sometimes, our faces don't suit each other, that's great.
Hey.
Why are you yelling in here?
Well, I feel like...
I'm wondering what you are up to.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
What?
I'm going to submit my final statement by the end of this afternoon.
I'll tell the chief, "Well, it's hot, so give me tea."
I think it's better to give him some water than tea.
I guess so.
Huh?
Wow, what a beautiful flower!
Ah!
It's cold!
What are you doing, Reiko?
Oh, no, it was Ryo-chan.
I can't see the top!
But, it's on Ryo-chan's head...
Head?
Hmm?
Huh?
Flower?
Hmm?
Huh?
There's a flower on my head!
So he didn't notice.
Now then, at the Showa Memorial Park, the flowers of the cosmos are in full bloom.
If you take a look at these flowers...
I think the person who went wrong will laugh at me.
This flower is firmly rooted in your head.
It's really rare.
Rather, I've never seen someone who has a real flower blooming in his head.
Ugh, my head is so dizzy!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
Why are you pulling it out?
You've been burning it for a long time, so you've got a flower on your head.
It's disgusting to see it outside!
Ah!
It's fine, right?
Even if you don't pull it out.
That's right.
It's so pretty, but it's a waste.
It's surprisingly good-looking, Ryo-san.
You're kidding me!
If a boy put a flower in his head, it's over!
Is that so?
What?
What's wrong with having flowers?
Isn't it cute?
Cute?
Can I ask a policeman like this for help?
The policeman with the flowers wants the citizens to help him!
I'll guide you.
Me too.
So that's not what I mean.
But you don't usually guide people, do you?
Where is the post office?
The post office?
Ask the post office.
What?
Ryo-san!
So at this time, it doesn't matter how you guide people!
It doesn't matter!
That's right.
By the way, let me tell you this.
The main task of the police at the police station is to guide people, organize traffic, and...
That's nonsense!
I know it!
The theme of the day is, "What is my head flower in today's world?"
What kind of flower is this?
Reiko, do you know?
It's not a tulip, it's not a gable, and it's a flower you've never seen, right?
What kind of flower is it? I don't care.
But it smells really good.
It's true.
A memory.
Hey, don't just pass it by.
I'm...
Can I take it?
Yes, cheese!
Hey, hey! If you want to take them, give me 100 yen each!
But why are there flowers on your head?
Don't you have any around here?
I don't have any!
Oh, by the way, I haven't taken a bath for two weeks.
Ryo-chan, you're here!
Maybe it was because of the blood.
This skin...
Ouch!
He really put his eyes on my head!
Damn, I almost passed out!
Look, this flower is already wilted.
It's because I couldn't get the nutrients from Ryo-san.
Poor thing.
Don't look at me with such an angry look!
Anyway, let's take a picture of this flower.
Let's try it.
I'll send it to the plant research facility in Nakagawa-Bussan and let it investigate.
Damn, thanks to that flower, I've passed the time I promised.
I wonder if he's angry.
Why are you all looking at me?
What's that?
No, it's like an idiot.
What?
No way!
I found it again!
What are you wearing, you primitive?
It's a little cute.
Where?
I just took it out, and now it's growing again. What the hell did I do?
I'm sure the deadline was today, Ryo-san.
Chief!
What are you up to?
I just came back from writing the deadline, Chief.
I was wondering what was that bamboo stick-like leaf on your head?
You're asking me what it is.
It means, I mean...
You're trying to make me lose my temper by writing the deadline, right?
No, I'm not, Chief!
Are you going toagus a case of Katsushika?
I grabbed it without permission to even smell it, and now it's solve with something like a bamboo stick!
I don't think so, you idiot!
How much are you going to make me angry, or are you gonna go mad?
No way, master, I'll just have to be disappear from your mind.
A flower!
What?
-The flower is blooming! -Ouch!
I told you! It's really growing! The flower is from its head!
-The flower is from its head? -And it won't come out! The flower is from its head!
-Amazing! -Amazing!
It's really growing. It's so weird.
-You idiot! -Why?
Because you're drooling, the flowers are blooming. Get a grip!
-You're so annoying! -Okay, do something about it by tomorrow.
Okay!
Let's go!
-Oh! -The needle doesn't work.
It came out easily this morning, but it's getting stronger and stronger.
-It's so weird. -Shut up!
It's because you left me behind that the flowers are blooming.
Take responsibility!
I'll take responsibility!
-I'm a little hurt. -It's okay. Do it.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Next, next!
-Arab? -Arab?
Yes!
-We got it! -We did it, confirmed.
Really? Did we?
Once again?
-It was fruit. -What?
Let's not give it a hard time after all!
All right.
Alright!
Let's go, Mr. Ryozu!
Alright, Honda! Do it with all your heart!
Support me with all you got!
Alright!
Ride on!
Let's go!
Take this!
Come on, come on!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Move, move, move!
I'll crush you!
Did you get through, Mr. Ryozu?
Just a little pain and I'm not going through!
I'll do it!
Let me go!
This is the flower that Mr. Nagagawa contacted me about this morning.
This is the ancient flower that was supposed to be extinct!
André the Giant Amigo Yamato!
Take a look.
It's the same Ryozu Kankichi as before.
Hmm, I guess I'll just have to live with this guy for a while.
Hmm?
Huh?
Ah!
It's a bee!
That's dangerous, that's dangerous!
Ah!
What's wrong?!
Damn it!
I got caught by the sweet scent of this flower!
You stubborn bee!
You're still chasing me!
If this happens...
Uwaaah!
Grrrrrrr--!
Huh?!
Huh?
Man!
What is it?!
Uwaaah!
Hwaah!
Hwaaaaaaa!
Hwaaaah!
What are you doing?!
Just like that, the bees blew away!
Hwaaaah!
What--what?!
W-what are you doing?
Hwaaaaah!
Oww!
What are you doing?!
Don't make yourself plastic!
Hey!
You've seen it before!
I've seen it, too!
Hwahhhh!
Dr. Serizawa
My name is Dr. Serizawa.
I have thoroughly investigated your body and head.
And the surprising fact has been revealed.
Ah! I remember!
The fake doctor who has investigated my body!
Fake?
That's enough.
It will be a problem if it is damaged by a precious flower.
Flower? Is this the flower you want?
Fine! I don't need it.
Please pull it out quickly!
I can't do that.
Why?
This is your skull and brain.
As you can see, the root of the flower is wrapped around.
I see.
Eh?
If you pull out the flower, the brain will surely be removed.
No, no, no! I don't want the brain!
Well, that's right. So I can't pull it out.
Why do I have such a bad eye?
That's the problem.
This is the fossil of the flower that was in use about 550,000 years ago and the fossil of the flower that was in use at that time.
Liar. There is such a solid fossil in such an old time.
Oops, there are still...
Sh*t!
Various of them, I guess.
This is a very accurate model that has been reproduced with detailed data of a small amount of fossil.
Huh? I am me?
Yes.
It has the ingredients of the flower
It's really a miracle.
There is nothing else to say.
It's just a disaster for me.
You have a duty to preserve the flowers, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
Wake up early, take a walk in the afternoon, eat light natural food, and don't drink alcohol?
What the hell is this?
From now on, you will be able to think about the health and safety of the flowers and take a thorough approach.
You will be able to think about the health and safety of the flowers and take a thorough approach.
I'm not kidding!
Why are you doing this for the sake of the flowers that I don't know?!
You have no right to choose.
This project is already a national project, Ryo-tsu.
So this is the flower that was here 550,000 years ago, Ohara-kun.
Yes, it seems so.
I'm glad I didn't have to pull it out.
Well then, from today on, you will be the guardian of this flower.
Hey, Chief, this one is stiffer than me, so you can leave it alone.
Ryo-tsu!
This is an order from the Minister of the Police, Jikijiki.
The Minister of the Police?
Please take care of it, Ohara-kun.
Yes!
Excuse me.
It's unfair.
I can't take care of it alone.
If you push it while I'm away, the Chiefs will get angry with me.
What did you say?
If this happens, we should get rid of it before it gets discovered.
Don't be silly.
I'm protecting this flower because I think that you've taken care of the important guest.
Don't say that!
Yes, I will give you a week's refreshment for the important guest.
If you go to Minami Island and give it to the important guest, I think you will be happy.
No.
Why?
If you let go, you won't do anything good.
You're just playing games and playing prams in your room,
and you're living a life of a slacker who's going to turn the tables.
It's more obvious than seeing the fire.
To live a regular life,
the best thing is to continue working as a police officer.
Instead of a vacation, you won't be off today.
Huh?
You're the worst.
It's okay, Ryo-chan.
You're still in a daze.
I'm hungry.
I've taken all your fun away.
I don't need your fun.
So let me eat.
A little pickled radish and miso soup.
It's hard for Ryo-san, who's always on a diet,
but vegetarianism is good for your health.
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
The flowers will rot too.
Is that okay, Ryo?
Ryo-chan may be disappointed,
but the flowers are in great condition.
You've done your job well, Senpai.
You're to blame.
You're the one to blame.
I'm living on rubble because of you.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat something rich.
I want to eat something fatty.
And give my stomach a massage.
Right in front of the park.
A Chinese restaurant in front of the station?
Chinese food?
Chinese food!
A car with a fine of 3 million yen!
Hurry up!
Is it dangerous? Please step back!
If you don't want to get hurt, step back!
Wait!
What's the situation? Did you find out who the culprit is?
The culprit is a former employee of this restaurant.
All other employees and customers are evacuated.
Okay. We'll make sure the culprit doesn't notice us and dispatch an emergency.
Yes!
That's Ryo-tsu, isn't it, Ohara?
It's me, Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu! Don't be hasty!
What happened to the bomb case?
What are you going to do if something happens to the weird flower?
It's not a Chinese dish, it's not a Chinese restaurant of the host!
I'm going to kill myself!
The chicken duck is calling for help!
Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu!
It's him!
If we don't hurry up, the host's life will be in danger!
Hurry up!
Help me!
The smell of the aroma is like a firework!
I'm going to die!
What? What?
What is it?
The flower moved! The flower over there just now...
Flower?
The flower is moving! The flower!
The flower?
That's strange...
Are you sleeping, you idiot?
The flower is dying and the energy is running out...
Senpai! Ryo-san!
It hurts!
See? It's moving after all!
Brother!
What?
Nothing is moving.
Are you okay?
What?
Hmm...
That's the smell of fire.
An iron-capped man?
There it is!
Wah! My Chinese food is...
See, Brother!
The flower's moving, after all!
Brother!
The flower is moving, after all!
What if something happened to the flower?
Then what was you going to do?
When that time comes, I'll take responsibility.
The rest will be up to you, Ohara.
Son of a gun!
You're not getting no union!
If you do, Gyoza!
Come in!
Enter!
Ryosu!
Ryosu, where did you go?
My meat...
My shumai...
Left herring!
Rei!
I knew it!
You imbecile!
To Be Continued
Ryouto-san...
May I help you?
I hate flowers!
♪ I'm a sea fish with a sharp head. ♪
♪ I don't care about sandals or scandals. ♪
♪ I play with a tunnel every day. ♪
♪ I throw my boredom in the trash can. ♪
♪ I'm a fool with a full-fledged instinct. ♪
♪ I just play like how I want to. ♪
♪ I act the way I want to. ♪
水魚 水魚松 雲魚松 グーライバ 作う寝るところに住むところ 煮油麹 蒸ら麹 バイコ バイコ バイコの シューリンガン シューリンガンの クーリンタイ クーリンタイの ポンポコキーロ ポンポコなーの 超久名の貯すけい!
Hey everyone! I'm the idol of Katsushika Prefecture, Kumawari!
If you copy me, you'll be a good boy!
When you're about to get scolded, say, "Captain, I'm sorry!"
Next time, "Fight, Kumawari-kun!"
See you!
Thank you for watching!