Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I looked at the sunset floating in the middle of the river
I kicked a pebble and flew to the end
I was laughing at the taiko singer who was jogging
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only get angry
The cityscape that never changes is kinder than the evil
The moon is setting because the crows are crying
I'm a yakitori hobari
o
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end soon
But, I'm happy again
I'm relieved because I'm an idiot
Papa is the young captain of the camp
What?
Don't be so surprised
I'm joking, Tera-i
Tera-i is an out-door?
Nakagawa is a newbie
Camp is a game
Outdoor is a game
You can also do auto-camp
Tera-i seems serious
Of course I'm serious
Because I made a promise with the children
I will send Tera-i to the mountain
In these mountains, the mobile phone is not connected
I can't play games on TV
Is it ok?
Yeah
It's so much fun
I caught so many fishes
Enjoying camping in nature
It was a family family
The appearance of a parent and child
My friend said,
I'm going to the eggplant campsite with my family
Camp? We're not going anywhere for summer vacation again, are we?
I guess we should write a diary.
I don't mind if you write one. I'll do the same.
I'll take you to camp.
Really?
Let's go to camp and make memories of summer vacation.
Make memories!
Making memories of summer vacation.
I thought I'd show my father's will to this opportunity and make the kids see it again.
Mr. Terai, have you ever been to a camp?
Not at all.
But kids can't show their bad sides, right?
Actually, I was trying to get Ryo to tell me a lot of things.
What's your father's will to see people?
It's a shame to spoil the children's mood.
Stop it.
Ryo.
Don't be mean.
You should teach him.
That's right, Senpai.
You want me to give him the knowledge of Outreger I've been teaching for years for free?
I'm not kidding.
Ryo's knowledge is not about Reger, but about survival.
It's not good.
It's the result of my blood, sweat, and hunger.
Of course, I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about the life of a sender.
At the expense of Omi's will, I can't over것
I can't even think about giving gratitude.
How about you bring my wife's lunch for ten days.
That's the idea.
Of course.
It's great some time, Ryo.
A lunch console is always a good thing.
Well, you're good, but your lunch is good.
Then, how about you bring me a dish for ten days?
By the way, do you own a car yet?
My car?
It's a Subaru R2.
You have to be careful.
Your car is over 40 years old.
And it's a K!
It's a lot of luggage.
Four people in a family...
I don't think it's possible.
At least it's a four-wheel drive.
Is it a new car?
If you're a man, buy it!
What?
That's amazing.
Four families.
That's a lot of space.
Yes, the kitchen is big.
There are toilets and showers.
It's cool.
The children will be happy.
The father's shares will rise.
It's a deal.
That's right.
So how much is it?
Yes.
It's 13 million yen at the current discount price.
What?
13 million yen?
I'm taking a loan for 30 years.
I'll take it for 30 years.
30 years of loan?
Please wait a moment.
I didn't think we'd be making a 30-year loan for a camp.
Then give up the auto camp.
If you want to run away, now is the time.
I'm working hard on this...
But I have to pay the loan.
But the monthly payment will increase a little.
But if it's a 30-year loan, I'll do my best.
I keep asking for it.
The loan for the life-saving band that collapsed still remains!
Life-saving band?
Ah, the one I named "Your Cruiser"!
It collapsed after riding on the top of the Gansho in the first public show, right?
I can't! I can't buy such a high car after all!
Then, give up auto camping, and have a barbecue in your yard.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry, but I still have a loan...
Well then, how about the rental car?
What, there's a rental car?!
Sure. This one.
These RVs here are very popular too, and it's called by a very long-term deal.
That sounds nice. My kids must be really happy to have one of this!
Okay! I can take it!
Very boring.
Wait, Ryo-san!
In the end, we have to buy a cheap and cheap family camping set after all!
Right!
I don't need it.
The car is rental, but the camping supplies are going to be given out one by one.
I'm going to put them all together.
I'm begging you, Ryo-san.
Then, please pay for dinner.
I see.
Are we really going to camp?
Of course, I'm not lying.
It's a camp!
Write it in the summer vacation diary.
I will write it.
Now, you two, go take a bath.
Yes!
Now, even if the kids go up from the bath, don't let them in this room.
What are you going to do?
It's a rehearsal.
Apparently, there are many fathers who go to the campsite and then go to bed.
Ryo-san, how about you?
I'll take care of Yamamori.
Yes, yes.
But, if it's so big, I can't go home.
Ryo-san, please.
Thank you.
There's a lot of miso soup, so I'll take it.
I see.
If I said that I would treat everyone to dinner in the world,
they would say that I could earn one seat with the high-class kappo.
I often say that I would pay three times more for a large serving of rice.
It's still the same.
I thought it would be more difficult to set up a tent,
but recently it's so easy that I'm surprised.
That's good, Terai-san.
I didn't expect to be taken care of by Ryo-san.
You're so naive.
The inside of the house and the camp site are different.
If you are careless, you will be in trouble.
I know.
I'm going to try fishing with my sons.
I'll fish and fish and fish.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to catch fish just by watching the fishing video.
I want to be happy.
There are no tuna or tuna in the river.
I know.
I'll grill the fish I caught with salt and eat it with my children.
It must be delicious.
Terai-san is a good father.
I'm sorry to stab you in the water,
but it may rain in the afternoon around the camp site where Terai-san goes.
It may be a storm.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, Terai.
It's okay.
The weather forecast I saw this morning said that the chance of a flood was 50% and that the storm could be stopped.
Is it really okay?
I wonder if it's okay.
What do you think, Senpai?
Leave it alone.
I don't know if it's a good sign.
Ryo-chan, don't say that.
It's okay.
Don't worry because the storm will blow it away with its spirit.
That's it.
It's a camp.
I'm happy.
I'm okay?
Don't talk to me now.
We'll talk in the next service area for 15 minutes.
I've spent a lot of time on taking care of my cómo.
If we don't move on according to our schedule, our plans won't get results.
All right.
We need to follow the schedule.
It's a camp.
I'm happy.
I'm thirsty.
How's the tea?
The next service area will serve tea.
Please like or subscribe!
Alright, it's finished!
Wow!
You did great, Dad!
You bet I did!
I should have practice more, too.
Sssh.
The End
Daddy, I'm hungry.
Then, let's go fishing for the dinner.
What? Are we going now?
I'm already tired.
Tired? You just came here.
Besides, you're doing everything on your own at the camp.
Let's go, Kenji and Koji.
Yes.
Be careful.
Damn, I taught you so hard, but you're going in a different direction.
Mr. Ryoichi?
Did you follow me because you were worried about the temple?
Daddy, I'm going to catch it.
It's dangerous to slip, so watch me catch it from behind.
I don't mind just curry rice.
Daddy, can you really catch it?
Of course.
I trained myself so hard to catch it today.
I'll catch it for sure.
Here it is.
Daddy, you're amazing.
I'm going to catch it, too.
Me, too.
Okay. I'm going to catch it.
Yes.
I feel it now.
The...the fishing rod...
I...the fishing rod...
It can't be helped.
I'll get it for you.
Hold it, please.
Okay.
Kenji, you're going to catch it, okay?
Yes, Daddy. Be careful, too.
Okay, it didn't come out.
What?
It's shallow.
Phew, you saved me!
Oh, I did it! I caught another one!
Papa, you're amazing!
I did it! I caught it with my rod!
Let's say Koji caught this one!
Yes! I caught it! I caught it!
It's shallow! It's so shallow!
I caught it with my rod.
You didn't notice it yet.
You should catch it as soon as possible.
You're amazing, Papa! You're good at fishing!
It seems so.
Papa, I got a pull!
All right, pull the line slowly.
Oh, Papa, me too!
Oh, that's a lot today!
I'll do my best too!
Look, look, Papa! I caught another one!
Wow, this is the tenth one!
All right!
I caught a big one today!
I caught it!
Papa, you caught a lot, didn't you?
Yes! Let's stop fishing and go back to the tent.
Mama will be surprised when she sees this!
That's right! There's a lot of fish!
They're going to fish so hard.
Are they going to do something at the fish shop?
But the fish we caught are also very big.
This is the headquarters.
Ryo, can you hear me?
Yes, this is the river fishing area.
Over!
Senpai, Bulba, thank you for your hard work.
It's really hard!
I caught all the fish I caught.
Go back quickly and have some coffee.
Roger!
It seems that the weather will be just right for this.
I wonder if the new year of the Terai Papa has won the storm.
That's right. Oh, the children have come back!
Mama, we caught a lot of fish!
Isn't that great?
Senpai, the children of the Terai-san,
we're very happy!
Fish are good for the long haul.
Me too.
It's strange, I can't see the Terai-san.
Ah, there he is!
I wonder what he's doing.
Ryo-chan, come back quickly.
The Terai-san has started something again.
What is this?
It's a stove.
You cook the rice here.
The rice cooked in the stove is very delicious.
I'm confident.
All that's left is to light the fire on the firewood.
Now, I'm ready.
All I have to do is cook with the stove.
Oh, you're going to fall.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm about to light the fire.
It's broken!
Mama, I'm hungry!
W-wait a minute!
Papa is making a stove right now.
Mama, I'm hungry!
Oh, that's not good.
It's not a stove, so you have to open the direction of the wind and go around the rest of the way.
Oh, I can't look at it.
At this rate, when will we be able to eat?
Can you make it with a stove?
It's a basic basic.
Oh, the children are eating grass.
Oh, my God!
Look, over there, my wife is making cup ramen.
What are you going to do, Terai?
The Terai-san is suddenly trying to light the fire on the firewood.
I'm trying to light it.
Can you light it?
I can't.
Terai, didn't you buy a solid fuel?
No, I should have brought a solid fuel and charcoal.
Then why don't you use it?
I've been up and down and forgotten.
I'm sure.
I was persistent about buying a cartridge gas burner that is easy to handle even for beginners.
But the Terai guy said, "It's impossible for beginners, so make it a stove."
But I'm going to camp, so I'll make a stove with a stove made of stone.
I want to show the children where to light the firewood.
Even if it looks like that, it's more stubborn than Chief Ohara.
It's hard.
What?
What's wrong?
It seems that gasoline and charcoal were put in the furnace together.
That idiot has a degree in ad-lib.
It's an SOS signal from the wife.
Where is the fire extinguisher?
I have to call number 119.
Wait, I'm sure this car is also a hose.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to put you all in danger.
I'm just a child.
You, be strong.
Hurry up and light the firewood.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
As it is, move up 30 degrees.
OK.
OK, pump OK.
Roger.
Mr. Golub, ready.
Maximum output, fire.
Honey.
It's raining.
It's disappearing.
Senior, it's OK.
Please pull the pump up.
Roger.
No.
Mr. Golub, the operation is over.
Go.
The ingredients are...
I'm almost done.
Let's eat cup ramen, honey.
I love cup ramen.
Don't you, Koji?
Yes.
I didn't want to eat curry so much.
Honey.
Papa.
The fish I caught are gone.
I'm such a hopeless, unreliable father.
Mr. Terae is moaning.
Poor thing.
I'm just thankful that I didn't get a mountain bite.
It smells good like curry.
I also made curry for dinner.
Oh, curry.
Wow, looks delicious.
That's the same pot as Mr. Terae's.
It's a recommendation from Ryo.
I was sold one too.
Are you making a fortune by selling a pot that was purchased at a low price somewhere else?
Don't say anything bad about it.
That's right.
I thought of something good.
What?
What is it?
It's called "The Animal of the Forest."
Honey, let's eat cup ramen.
Yes.
What is it?
A bear!
A gorilla!
No, this is my home.
Hey!
Don't let my family touch my finger!
I'm going to eat you!
Honey, run away!
The animal's stomach is bad.
If you can eat it, try it!
Dad!
Honey, stop it!
Mr. Terae's wife.
Dad!
Ms. Reiko!
It's curry.
Everyone, please eat it.
Well, maybe that too.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll be happy to eat it.
I did it!
Dad!
Dorya!
Ouch!
It's gone!
Mr. Volvo.
Curry's replacement has succeeded.
Hey!
Mr. Volvo.
I'm bleeding.
I won!
To the gorilla and the bear!
Dad!
Good, you're safe!
Where's mom?
Over there.
Here you go.
It's curry!
I got have a cold, and I'm hungry.
Eh?
I remember the curry's
that had just...
Oh?
Look.
The star that has the most stars.
Wow!
... Really?
Wow, the star with the most stars!
Damn, Terai really hit it!
It's done.
Thanks to Terai, dinner is instant.
Try it. It's a military meal, but you can eat a lot.
It seems that Terai and the others are also calm.
How is it? I'm glad I came to the camp.
Yeah.
Dad, Mom, thank you.
No, it's not that much.
Dad, it's getting red.
That's not true.
I have nothing to forget.
Okay, let's go.
Dad, I want to play more.
The road will be jammed if you get late, and you have to return the car by 5 p.m.
So get on the car quickly.
Yes.
Mom, will you look over there?
You're only 5 cm away.
What?
Damn it.
Your tires are about to fall.
It's okay.
You have to go back once.
I know.
It's okay.
Watch out!
Hey!
Protector!
You're there, too!
What?
Th-that is...
Ryo!
Everyone!
They found us.
Well, it's very troublesome.
I recommend you to carry it on this way.
I'll take you to the north, so be quiet!
Thank you, Ryo! I'm glad you came by!
Wow! They're flying!
They didn't find out about yesterday.
I'd rather let them know everything.
Let's hurry! The car will be back by 5 o'clock.
The Diary of the Children
Yes. The Diary of the Children's summer vacation is back.
Is there a problem?
It's about fishing a lot of fish.
The fire went out in the middle of the stove.
The Sigma and the Gorilla were thrown away.
The helicopter was hit by a bell.
It's a fun Diary of the Children, isn't it?
But look at this.
The teacher commented, "Let's stop lying!"
It's true that all the episodes are fake.
But they're all true.
That's right. At least we did the last episode of the car.
That's right. But the children are sorry that we wrote it as a lie.
Well, Terai, how about this next?
What?
I'll write a Diary of the Children's summer vacation.
I'll become Santa and bring the Sola and the Toecai to that summer vacation.
JuGAME JuGAME
Go! Go! No!
Sh clarity
Kajari Suigyo
JuGAME JuGAME
Go! Go! No!
Sh clarity
Kajari Suigyo
竹子竹子
Mew Mew
And Mewy
"No, I don't."
I play the tunnel every day.
"He-he-he-he-he, handy!"
I put my boredom in a
"No, I don't."
I just do it the way I want to do it.
"That's amazing!"
The lightningting of my model car.
Smoke from my head.
When I run and escape, I take a picture.
That makes me so happy.
To the flower bed...
A mass day break.
I can take off...
"Welcome home to my town!"
And certainly...
I just have to keep working.
8:00 am.
I put my food at the grill.
9:00 am.
8:00 pm.
Burakoji Burakoji
Baiko Baiko Baiko
Shurinkan Shurinkan
Gurindai Gurindai
Ponpoko Hiro Ponpoko
Naano
Choukyumei no Chousuke
Chief, do you want to go golfing?
Then leave it to me
I'll let you play real golf
Play with your life in the nature
This is golf, isn't it?
Oh, Chief, it's dangerous
Next time, "Golfing on an uninhabited island"
Thank you for watching