Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Subtitled by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle of the river ♪
♪ I fly to the corner of the stone ♪
♪ and jump to where I'm going ♪
♪ I wonder if I'm going to the place where I joked ♪
♪ I was laughed at for being a brat ♪
♪ Even if I try to cheer up somewhere ♪
♪ I can't help but get mad ♪
♪ The cityscape that doesn't change ♪
♪ even when I yawn is so kind ♪
♪ The fire is burning because the crows are crying ♪
♪ The yakitori is full ♪
♪ The beer is also full ♪
♪ From the drink of a sparkling water bottle ♪
♪ to the taishakuten ♪
♪ The sunset falls ♪
♪ I wake up tomorrow and it ends ♪
♪ I'm sure I'm still happy ♪
♪ I lost it ♪
♪ I realized ♪
♪ I'm such a fool ♪
♪ I can't believe when I'm in the middle of nowhere ♪
♪ I will never be able to forget this lair ♪
♪ where the bird is flying on its wings ♪
♪ I'm tired of waiting in the long car ♪
♪ I won't forget tomorrow ♪
♪ I will never forget tomorrow ♪
♪ When everything is over and I'm back ♪
♪ I will finally get to know ♪
♪ theomere of this land ♪
...
I'm sure it'll be tomorrow!
I can't do this kind of secret work!
Damn it! I failed the second act, too!
Nakagawa-kun!
What is it?
...
Don't push people.
Hey, Reiko-chan!
What's wrong with your disgusting voice, Ryo-chan?
...
Don't catch people with your own hands.
You have to do it yourself.
...
I can't get over it.
My room's dirty, so I can't concentrate.
That's right!
...
I'm sure!
Alright, give it to me.
Here you go.
Alright.
No, I don't think this is my room.
Alright, I'll do the report with this momentum.
Here you go.
I've cleaned up the mess.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it's better to be messy like this.
I feel like I'm working.
The atmosphere is important.
The atmosphere.
Oh, yeah.
I thought something wasn't enough, so I'll have a late-night snack.
Let's eat and do it quickly.
It's Ryotsu-special instant ramen.
It's just vegetables.
What else?
Oh, char siu, menma, and Naruto.
It's quite a lot if you look for it.
It's tuna.
Let's put this in.
I'll put it in.
It's pepper to finish with.
What are you doing, senpai?
It's a good place.
Do you want to eat?
I'm fine.
Really? Then I'll eat it.
It's good. As expected of me.
As expected, he's so different from a human.
Maybe I should have made it a little more voluminous.
I forgot!
Come to think of it, I haven't washed for a while.
I've been eating so much.
Wash, wash, wash, and then all at once.
All right, well...
I have to clean up the storage room.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I'm a boy, aren't I?
I was going to put it in the resource collection garbage.
Whenever I read it, the other side is interesting.
Oh, no, no, I have to get to work soon.
Clean up, clean up.
Oh, this is...
Model gun.
Colt Python 357 Magnum 4-inch.
I'm always in love with this mirror.
It's a little rusty.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Oh, I was in the middle of cleaning up.
Oh, nostalgic.
I got it at the fast-food competition in the shopping street.
My arm isn't weak.
It's a jigsaw.
It's a masterpiece of an illusion.
It's a rakuda that breaks through the Sahara Desert.
The ultimate 12,000-piece.
I bought it when I was busy with puzzles.
It's nostalgic, it's nostalgic.
Here, here, here.
This is difficult.
This is here.
All right.
I did it!
Oh, my God.
oh, my God.
I'll do it.
So, after this is over, I'll do it.
I don't like it, Ryo-chan. Did you start something again?
Oh, Reiko, well, if you notice it, this escape room is pretty dirty.
Eh? What are you saying to the super-man who always messes with things?
Get out of here. Get out of here. I don't want to write a report.
I'm sorry. Here, too.
Good morning.
What's going on?
Oh, Chief.
Ryo-chan, today...
Ah! Come to think of it, the front wall...
Wall?
No, this...
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
I haven't written my report yet.
You're forcing yourself to find another job and do it later, aren't you?
What?
A little...
200...
Let's do something about this!
Yes, yes.
How about this every day?
Wait.
If you don't like the paper work, then you can always give them paper work.
Wouldn't it be possible to keep this condition always?
Okay, perfect!
You're still here?
Ryo-san, what's the list like so far?
Uh...
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ah, by the way...
I knew it.
The list is...
Start!
Good, good.
Good, good, good.
Just like I thought.
As long as I give you the document, Ryo-tsu will work.
Ryo-tsu!
You're clean now.
Well, that's fine.
Because the report is full today.
And I'll take this one, too.
And this one, too.
And then,
I'll give you the report you need to finish tomorrow.
Gah!
All right!
I get it, Ryo-tsu!
Then, I'm counting on you.
I'm going to the office.
Damn it!
Ouch!
You're going, too?
Yeah, to the patrol.
Then, Ryo-chan,
get on your feet!
Well, bye-bye!
I'm off!
Do you want to keep this?
Yeah, Ryo-san.
I'm going to the police station.
You don't want to go in there with a full face, do you?
This doesn't "the police station."
So just keep the collar on your head.
Ah, wow.
Oh.
Hey!
I'll just give it a try and start with the new one.
Hm?
A survey?
Huh?
An application for a baseball tournament?
An old people's association?
A primary school student?
What is this?
I got it, Mr. Ohara!
Oh, Mr. Ohara! You prepared something like this to make me clean up, didn't you?
Damn it!
Did you write down the documents properly?
I wonder. I think he's into cleaning.
Well, I guess he's a good-for-nothing, but I can't believe he's a clean-up.
Huh?
What?
Ahem.
Chief, look! I've cleaned up everything so nicely!
What?
What's this?
You wanted me to clean up, didn't you?
So I've organized the entire station by material!
Good job!
Idiot!
Because you started it first, didn't you?
I didn't do it after all.
Please believe in me!
The friend of justice, Mr. Ryo!
Ugh, I don't have any money!
If this goes on like this, I'll have to find a new part-time job.
Ryo, you're here again?
Senpai, it hasn't even been a week since the day you got paid.
Oh, there you are. Mr. Ryo.
Huh? All my neighbors.
Ah, actually, I was looking at Mr. Ryo, so I couldn't talk to you.
I'm busy.
It's a job that only Ryo-san can do.
Huh?
A job?
Come with us for a bit!
What a great tree!
I didn't know there was a tree like this.
It's been over 180 years.
In the past, this place was like a paradise for children.
But...
The number of children who play here has decreased, and the land is being sold.
Finally, this tree has become the only one.
I'm really sad.
Huh?
Then, let's enjoy the land until we feel like it.
Ryo-san!
Don't go back!
It has nothing to do with me.
It's Ryo-san's job from now on.
This land has been taken over by the strongholds.
That's why the company is trying to cut down this tree.
Ryo-san, that's a terrible story!
Hmm...
It's a disturbing tree, so shouldn't we cut it down?
Uwaaah!
What the hell!
It's a treasure for us!
Oh, really?
Ryo-san!
If you protect it, we'll give you a reward!
So, how much is it?
30,000 yen per day!
Hmm...
Uwaaah!
What a happy neighbor!
If I were not here, this huge tree would be...
Thank you, Ryo-san!
So, how do we protect it?
We should watch over it on the tree and get the construction workers back.
Okay!
Listen to me!
Ryo-san!
It's not good to be in uniform!
Ahaha!
You can't be a policeman in uniform!
I knew it!
This is what a good-for-nothing does!
Hehehe...
Hmm...
If you dress like this, people will think you're joking!
Huh?
This is what a good-for-nothing does!
Awakening equipment, helmet, and a life jacket are perfect!
Oh, I knew it!
I knew it!
I'm counting on you, Ryo-san!
Just leave it to me!
This is quite a relief.
I'm sure you'll be fine!
I found a good part-time job!
Hehe, I found a good part-time job!
*Sigh*
Hey, don't cut the tree!
Oh, what's that?
Go home!
Go home, you guys!
What is it, Ryo?
It's okay.
Let's get to work for now.
Damn it, it's an insect!
Okay, if this happens...
Ouch...
*Sigh*
You guys!
If you cut it, you won't be able to go home!
If you don't go home quickly, I'll keep on shouting!
Be prepared!
Dad!
Your own family is going to die!
What stuff did you just eat?
I was about to go home to heal myself, but I was a mess.
It's you Heidou!
He wanted to wash his pocket!
You!
Oh, wait there.
Hey, Tatsumi!
He's back!
Tatsumi!
Sorry for being late. Eat more.
It's a special bento made by everyone in the school.
There's also tea and juice.
Wow, so much. I did it!
Let's eat.
I heard Ryo-san's voice chasing them away.
Oh, I see. It's useful, isn't it?
It was the right thing to ask Ryo-san.
Then, do your best.
If you want anything, just say it.
Three meals and snacks.
I'm going to do a part-time job like this.
You're here again. Go home.
You please get off.
The permit for harvest is out.
Get off and shut up.
We're taking care of our lives.
Life?
Our lives are also taken care of.
Here, here.
Here, in the complete residential area of Katsushika,
the locals work.
We're trying to cut down the trees that we love very much.
TV? Okay.
Everyone in the country!
These cruel people are trying to cut down the trees.
Can this be forgiven?
Look.
To protect the trees, the allies of justice are doing their best.
Those with common sense.
Justice will always win.
Let's go!
Wow, this is amazing!
What's going on?
This is Ryo-san's gift.
We've been receiving support gifts from all over the country.
We did it!
I didn't know we'd get this much for free.
Keep up the good work, Ryo-san.
Yes, yes.
Here's something for you.
This feels like a secret base.
Things have been increasing and my life has flourished.
Alright.
Let's appeal to the allies of justice.
Increase the number of things we can bring.
I'll be the one to protect this tree!
Let's go!
I won't lose!
I'll be the one to fight alone!
I'll be the one to support you!
I'm here to help!
Where did you bring that costume from?
I brought it from the library!
He seems to be a senior at demanding things.
My friends of justice! Here's your gift!
Good work!
It's really growing.
There's no space to put it anymore.
This branch is in the way.
It's a big tree, so I cut it a little.
I don't know if it's because of the bottom.
It's getting wider.
I'll spread the floor as well.
If you distribute it from here,
the electricity will be okay.
Ryo-san, it's over.
Good work!
What?
This tree was helpful.
Thank you.
You're so stupid.
But if I'm gone,
they'll come for sure!
This morning,
there was a notification of the construction stop.
You can't believe it.
That's their trick.
No way.
It's not coming anymore.
No.
This is the mountain range.
I can't go down there yet.
Ryo-san!
Then bring me some rice.
50 kilos.
There's no water,
so 100 liters of mineral water,
please.
Please!
Hmm.
Hmm..
I think we're screwed.
It's getting harder to get through Ryo-san.
It looks like a devil's tree.
Let's watch this tree.
If the workers don't come,
we'll stop our part-time jobs.
They're going to watch us.
It seems they really gave up on the workers.
They're so clueless.
If we don't do something about it,
they'll end up getting fired.
I'll use that trick.
Get out of my way!
I won't let you cut it!
If you don't cut it,
then cut me!
What?
I'll cut you!
You're not getting away!
I can't let you go.
I'll get you out of here today.
I really got a job.
I got a job.
You're protecting the tree
with your whole body.
Hmm.
Good job.
One for 3,000 yen each.
Yes.
Thank you.
You can be a little more rough.
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
The pay after work is a special one.
I can't believe I quit this easy part-time job.
300,000 on the 10th,
600,000 on the 2nd,
900,000 if I work for a month.
All the money I've earned
will be spent on this job.
You're a goodством guy.
Is this part of this job a working-day job?
Since you're very busy,
The flame!
No no no no!
This way too!
That's a waste of gas.
That's the mineral water, though!
I can't do this anymore!
Get out of here!
I...I realize the threat...
Not me! It's you!
You're an accident!
Hey, Ryōsan!
You're original,
What's wrong?
You cancelled your part-time job?
I told you at 8am
I'm paying you for three thousand yen
I mean, that...
Ryo!
I mean, get out of here!
We'll wait!
Help me!
It must have been a strange feeling
That I felt at that time
So...
I climbed up the
A-G-D Gai'sνaddile
And I walked around
Everyone was a kid once
But they forget
That they were girls
A politician with a big face
And a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a camera over there
Ah, there's definitely a camera
Come on everyone, let's go to our town
There's a camera over there
Ah, there's definitely a camera
Come on everyone, let's go to our town
Thank you!
Damn it! Naoko!
How dare you post my embarrassing photo
on the newspaper!
Thanks to you, I'm a funny guy!
If this happens, I'll take a picture of Naoko's embarrassing photo
on the newspaper!
Next time, "Naoko's Unexpected Day"
Please watch it!
There's a camera over there
Ah, there's definitely a camera
Come on everyone, let's go to our town
Thank you!