Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I laughed at the captain of the taiko who was jogging ♪
♪ He said it was fine as it was ♪
♪ Even if I feel good somewhere, I have no choice but to win ♪
♪ The unchanging cityscape is very kind ♪
♪ Because the crows are crying, the mochi is coming ♪
♪ The yakitori is full, and the beer is coming ♪
♪ From the tap on the cap ♪
♪ To the taishakuten ♪
♪ The sunset falls ♪
♪ It will end tomorrow as well ♪
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I'm a fool who got hurt ♪
=The End=
Hmm... you're right, it's a turtle.
Because it's a turtle-slaying park...
It's for me, but I think a deer should be better.
Even so, the director gives us
quite an absurd command to think about a new character.
I've got work, too.
Ryo is going to be late every day, getting reside in the office.
He's not convincing at all.
I'm cut.
Yeah, I got it!
You're really quick, Sasugawa-senpai!
How's this? This is my new mascot in the Katsushika office, Kuma-wari-kun!
Huh?
I've made a new, soft character that's more like a police officer and a lovely bear,
and I've also made a new, soft character that's more like a police officer and a lovely bear,
and this will make the president very satisfied!
The people of the city will definitely like it!
I'm a genius, after all!
Ahahaha!
Kuma-wari-kun, huh?
I'm sure everyone will like it.
I'm sure everyone will like it!
Fight, Kuma-wari-kun!
I'm Kuma-wari-kun!
I'll protect your city, Kuma!
Please take a look.
This is Kuma, the police officer of Kuma, who has just become the new mascot of the Katsushika office.
Nice to meet you, Kuma!
Kuma-wari-kun is very popular among the children.
I'm looking forward to his future activities.
Look!
You're quite handsome, no matter how much you say it.
No, thank you for the compliment.
You're really popular, aren't you?
The costume was hard, wasn't it?
Ryo-chan, you're wearing it, aren't you?
Yeah.
I didn't want to wear it, either, but there was no one else.
But I won't wear it again.
The children are so pretty, and the costume is so pretty.
It was hot and terrible.
It's proof that the children love you, isn't it?
You have to be happier.
That's right.
The Katsushika office has been fully backed up.
Kuma-wari-kun's popularity will continue to rise.
Kuma-wari-kun's height, weight, favorite food, special skills, and even the name of his friends.
Did you think of all this?
Of course.
To pursue reality.
And recently, children are used to such settings in games and comics.
I didn't notice that.
Well, if I get a little serious, it's that simple.
It's impossible for the chief to talk about it.
What's wrong with me?
Chief!
I told you to come to the office, but what the hell do you think your job is?
I'm sorry.
Everyone listen to me.
The chief ordered me to go to kindergarten with Kuma-wari-kun.
Kindergarten?
Yes.
Kuma-wari-kun is going to campaign for public safety.
Listen, Ryozu.
Kuma-wari-kun is not only the mascot of the Katsushika office, but also the hero of the children.
Don't ruin the dreams of the children.
What?
You mean I'm going to wear a costume again?
I don't like that.
Idiot!
You're Kuma-wari-kun's father, aren't you?
That's ridiculous.
I'm giving you an order.
I got it.
No, you're not.
I'm not going to give you a rude greeting.
I got it, Kuma.
Kuma-wari-kun is going to campaign from now on.
Okay.
Everyone, Kuma-wari-kun is here today from the Katsushika office.
Let's say hello to him.
Yes.
Hello.
Everyone, hello, Kuma.
I'm Kuma-wari-kun, Kuma.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, he's real Kuma-wari-kun.
Wow, he's fluffy.
He's bigger than I saw on TV.
Let me touch him, too.
Everyone, Kuma is fine and healthy.
It's troublesome.
He's hot and his children are annoying.
Ouch!
Hey, don't pull me.
Who kicked me?
Ouch!
You idiot!
You're a mascot loved by children.
You can't be serious.
Ouch!
Kuma-wari-kun, are you okay?
Don't worry, Kuma.
Kuma-wari-kun is very strong.
He can do anything, Kuma.
Amazing.
Then, let's learn traffic rules together, Kuma.
Okay.
I'll go.
See you later, Kuma.
You're so popular.
You're like a big kid.
That's true.
Kuma-wari-kun, we brought you a present.
Hey, everyone.
Yes.
Really?
Kuma?
I'm so happy.
For the cabbage.
Yes.
It says here that your favorite is the cabbage.
I know Kuma-wari-kun.
I know everything about you.
I want to eat a lot of my favorite cabbage.
I want to do it with everyone.
Eat it.
I don't need anything.
Wait a minute.
Is Kumari's favorite cabbage?
I think I've thought about that.
Don't think about it.
If this happens, take responsibility and eat it all.
It's too much.
Are you trying to break the dreams of the children?
Look at those children's eyes.
I don't think there's anyone in there.
I believe that he is a creature called Kumari.
Do you betray such a pure feeling?
But...
You're a big animal.
Thank you, bear.
I'm impressed, bear.
I'll enjoy it.
Remember that, boss.
The car has stopped, so I'll cross it quickly.
Chikuwa.
You're wrong.
You have to check your left and right and raise your hand to cross.
But I've never seen a man cross like that.
What are you trying to say?
You are the Hero of the Children.
I understand.
Then, let's cross by raising our hands.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
You have to stop while raising your hands, bear.
In the same way, there are some people in the city who do not follow the traffic rules.
So be careful, bear.
Yes!
But, Kumawari-kun is strong, so he's stronger than a car.
Huh?
That's right.
It says here that Kumawari-kun is strong enough to lift trucks easily.
No, no, that's just a setting.
Amazing! I want to see it!
If it's a car like that, you can lift it with one hand, right?
Huh?
Let me see it!
Kumawari-kun, let me see it.
Huh?
I know, Ryotsu. It's for the children.
I-I understand, Kuma.
Why did you do this?
How is it, Kuma?
Kumawari-kun is very strong, Kuma.
Just kidding!
Here, a reward.
Thank you.
Alright, I want to see the next Kumawari kick!
Kumawari kick?
It's your special move, right?
It's also written here.
You can defeat a bull with a kick, right?
I want to see more!
Me, too!
Can you beat me with a bull?
Kick! Kick! Kick! Kick!
Well, as long as your kick is good, I guess.
It's just your same move.
I'll show you my special technique that crushes concrete.
Chana-sensei, come here.
Chana-sensei.
Who is it?
Chana-sensei is doing kickboxing.
Chana-sensei is ranked third in the world.
What?
Chana-sensei.
Nice to meet you.
I'm not kidding. I can fight with this.
Don't run, Ryotsu. The children are watching.
I can't win.
But you're a true hero.
Come on.
Don't leave me alone.
Chara!
Chara.
No.
Don't leave me alone.
Let me see.
Chara.
I'm counting on you, Kuma.
Damn, you're so selfish.
Hey, hey, onee-chan,
is Tanooki-kun not coming today?
Eh? Tanooki-kun?
You don't know him? He's Kumawari-kun's subordinate.
He always makes mistakes and
always makes trouble for Kumawari-kun.
He's a pain in the ass.
I want to see Tanooki-kun too.
I want to see him! I want to see him!
Leave it to me, Kuma!
Tanooki-kun will be here soon, Kuma!
Really?
Really, Kuma! I'm waiting for you, Kuma!
What?
What is it?
Well...
Everyone!
It's Tanooki!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Kuma!
My subordinate is always a pain in the ass and
always makes trouble for me!
It's Tanooki, Kuma!
R-Ryosuke-sama...
Hey, hey, Tanooki-kun, you have a small voice, Kuma.
Then you won't be heard by everyone, Kuma!
What did you say?
Tanooki-kun!
Are you sure?
Your dream of being a child will be broken.
Then everyone,
let's go!
I'll call Tanooki-kun with a loud voice, Kuma!
I'm sure Tanooki-kun will answer with energy, Kuma!
Now, one, two, three!
Tanooki-kun!
Tanu!
I'm so happy to meet you all today, Tanu!
Let's study the traffic rules together, Tanu!
Yes!
Chief Okinoda...
Ryo-chan gets on my nerves right away...
I had fun today, Kuma!
I-I'll come play again, Tanu!
Are you leaving already?
I want to play more!
Hey, hey, it's okay, right?
It's a shame, but we have to go back to the secret base, Kuma!
The secret base?
That's right!
It's written that we live in a secret base somewhere in this town!
That's right, Kuma!
Then, everyone, see you again, Kuma!
Bye-bye! See you later!
Bye-bye!
Ehehe...
Chief, you can take it off now, right?
No, not yet.
I need to get away from the kindergarten a little more.
Okay, that's enough.
Yay!
I can finally say goodbye to this hot and painful costume...
Huh? The jacket...
Huh? Huh? Huh?
I'm finally relieved.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
It was so hot.
But it's for the children.
This is also inevitable.
Hey!
Hey, Renko Nakagawa!
Help me out, too!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Huh?
Ryo, wait!
Look!
Huh?
Oh, I found you, Kumaori!
Hurry up!
Hey, you!
You can't run away like this!
Damn it!
Oh, he ran away!
Wait!
Damn it!
Why?
Let's play again!
Why should I run away?
Wait!
I'm sorry, Kuma!
Oh, no!
I'll be out of here soon!
I ran from here for the first time in a long time!
But I have no idea what happened to me!
What should I do?
What?
Oh, Ryo?
Just, do not run after me!
No, Ryo.
Ryo, my sweet boy, just run or I'll kill you!
Okay, everyone,
Ryo, take my sister to go.
Yes! He's very cute!
He's cool!
He's strong!
He's a hero!
I see. You like him that much.
Do you want to play with me that much?
Me?
What do you want to play with? Do you want to play with me? Which do you want to play with?
I want to play with you!
Then come with me, bear!
Yes!
My name is bear-bear.
Bear!
Everyone protects this town.
When I'm buried, I'm a bear-bear.
Bear!
Everyone's hero, bear-bear!
Wow!
Bear, you're watching well.
This kind of hard to grab doll is aimed at the thin part, bear.
Wow! I got four!
I, I've never seen anything like this before.
Bear-bear is amazing!
He's a little boy.
But there's nothing about the fact that he's good at crane games.
This is the real me, bear!
Today, I'm going to play with you guys.
I'll show you how to do it, bear!
No!
There are more rice balls than other restaurants in Taiyaki.
Bear, remember this.
Yes!
My name is bear-bear.
Bear!
Everyone's hero, bear-bear.
Hey, Ozaki! How are you, bear?
Oh, I'm...
I'm Zenzo!
I'm the first idol of Shikasha, bear-bear!
Are you Ryu?
I'm Ryosan!
Bear!
I'm Kumaari-kun, now!
I don't know those people!
Got it?
Yeah!
Everyone's happy, bear!
This old man will give everyone a present!
Bear!
What are you talking about, Ryosan?
It's Kumaari-kun!
Put Daikin on Katsushika-cho!
Got it?
Y-You get it.
The unbalance of a smiling teddy bear and a loud voice is scary.
My name is Kumaari-kun!
Kuma!
Everyone in this town is protected by Kuma!
Ah!
You idiot!
What are you doing, you bastard?
I-I'm sorry...
Aiki-sama, what are you doing to a child?
W-what are you?
My name is Kumawari-kun!
What is Kumawari-kun?
Uwaaah!
Damn it! I'm angry!
I'm done for!
Done for...
No!
That's so cool!
As expected, Kumawari-kun is our hero!
Ahahaha!
My name is Kumawari-kun!
Ah!
Everyone in this town is protected by Kuma!
Protected by Kuma!
Kumaari-kun, bye-bye!
Let's play again!
Bye-bye, Kuma!
Hey, I'm tired.
I've been crying all day because of Kumaari-kun...
Senpai!
I washed Kumaari-kun!
Oh, sorry.
Please dry it for me.
Okay.
It was hard to put this on all day.
Oh, but...
Well, it's okay.
Sometimes, that kind of outfit...
Ah, it's morning already.
Ah, I'm going to sleep a little more.
Huh?
What?
What's wrong?
Ah!
Kumaari-kun!
No!
Don't die!
Oh, no!
Ah!
Kumaari-kun is...
He's dead!
Senpai, what should we do?
I think Kumaari-kun is dead.
Anyway, we have to take it back and fool him!
Damn it!
I'm gonna break it!
What?
Ah!
It's falling!
I got hit.
Ah!
Kumaari-kun is dead!
No!
We can't help it!
Found you again!
You!
Wait!
Ah!
Where did he go?
I think he should have come here, no?
He's so sad!
What's wrong!?
Kumaari-kun is...
Huh?
Damn it!
Senpai!
Take it!
No!
Honda, we're counting on you!
Please be careful.
Here I go!
Good luck, Senpai!
It's Kumawari!
Don't go!
Kumawari!
Revive, Kumawari!
You're alive!
Wow!
As expected of Senpai.
Idiot!
We've been hearing that you're in trouble since this morning.
What were you doing?
I was just chasing after the toys.
You're not in control.
The Chief said that you're not the same as you are now.
What are you going to do?
I'm not the one who was blown away by the wind.
Don't make excuses.
Come on, improve your image of Kumawari.
If you fail, you'll have to go to the constitution.
I can't do that.
Why are you doing this?
If you can improve your image so easily, you won't have to suffer.
You keep saying things that the Chief wants you to do.
It's Kumawari!
What are you doing?
Let's play together!
Sorry, I can't get used to it.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Actually...
I see.
You failed.
I always fail when I'm perfect.
Cheer up!
Kumawari, you're so poor.
Okay, okay.
Thank you, Kuma.
But it's not good to do this.
We have to improve our image somehow.
What do you mean?
For example, we have to show people that we're working harder.
If we help everyone, we might be popular.
That's right.
If Kumawari catches the culprit, everyone will be surprised.
Are you going to give us a chance?
But are you going to be that good?
You have to try it.
I have to try it.
Good luck, Kumawari!
Good luck!
Even if you say that, it's not easy for a criminal to show up.
Thief!
That's right.
A thief suddenly...
What?
Oh!
Isn't that a thief?
It looks like it.
It's a chance, Kumawari!
Good luck!
Leave it to me!
Look at me!
I'll show you the real power of Kumawari!
Hey, don't let it go!
What's going on?
What's wrong with you?
What does Kumawari look like?
It's not just Kumawari!
It's Kumawari!
What?
That's bad!
I'll arrest you!
You're so small.
You'll be in trouble!
What are you doing, Kuma!?
Oh, no...
Oh, my!
I won't let you run away!
If I don't do that, I'll arrest you, Kuma!
What?!
Oh, no!
I found you, Kuma!
り
Kumawari!
What's going on?
Wait for me, bear!
Looks like they ran away.
That was close.
But what was that bear doing?
What was that voice?
I think they came here.
Oh, that's...
That's Kumawari-kun's...
Kumawari-kun!
Everyone, you did it, bear!
That's scary!
That's not Kumawari-kun!
Mom!
What? Why, bear?
You idiot!
What's this picture?
I-It can't be helped!
I was so obsessed with arresting the culprit!
That's why I was told to take a picture like this!
You idiot!
This picture is really terrible.
It's impossible for a child to cry.
Hey, Kumawari-san!
Where's Kumawari-kun?
Hey, you guys!
Ta-da!
Wow, so cute!
You guys!
Kumawari-kun's costume set!
From today, we're also Kumawari-kun!
We're going to be Kumawari-kun!
I was a little scared, but...
Kumawari-kun is our hero!
Wow!
You guys!
See you!
Bye!
What's going on?
Chief, I'm going on patrol!
I'll be waiting, bear!
I'll play with you today, bear!
Yay!
I'm going this way!
Your
dashing
puppy
It's okay to be poor
Isn't that right?
Just do it the way I want to do it
Nice!
No.8
0:28:47.940,0:29:01.elen
That's better
All right
0:28:38.400,0:29:40.000
I am
Yes
Mr. Hiroshi
Baiko Baiko Baiko's Churin-gan
Churin-gan's Churin-dai
Churin-dai's Honpoko Tea's Honpoko Nado
Chosuke's super-savory Chosuke!
I know it all now!
The one who needs me now is Maria!
You taught me a lot of important things!
One last thing, okay?
Listen up! What is that strange bunch of people?
Next time on Aishenshi Ryotsu Kankichi!
See you next time!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!