Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the river ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was laughing at the captain of the taiko who was jogging ♪
♪ He said it was still a good show ♪
♪ I'm fine somewhere ♪
♪ Even if I'm a man, I have a strong will ♪
♪ The cityscape that doesn't change even with a single nightmare is strangely kind ♪
♪ Because the crows are crying, the rain is already falling ♪
♪ The yakitori is running out ♪
♪ The beer is running out ♪
♪ The Hoshino Shisui is running out ♪
♪ The Taisyaku is running out ♪
♪ And the sunset is falling ♪
♪ I'll wake up tomorrow and end it ♪
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I realized that I'm an idiot ♪
♪ That I can't keep it at all forever ♪
♪ I don't want to give up, but I can't stop ♪
♪ Oh, I've got a problem with my mind ♪
♪ It's not natural ♪
Nature is also a relaxation.
You guys, golf doesn't have anything to do with nature.
Oh, why?
We harvest the forest that we originally had, plant the grass on the front, and make artificial ponds and bunkers to make it more difficult to hit.
Where in the golf course is there nature?
That's true, but...
Where is relaxation?
As you say.
Who are you?
I'm the golf director of our company.
Nice to meet you all.
As Ryotsu-sama said, the current golf is said to be natural.
Originally, golf was a game where the sheep were hit by a rock with a bow cut in the corner and played in the rabbit's nest.
Now, the golf course is originally called a golf club, and it's made of aluminum and titanium.
It depends on the thing.
It's a high-tech thing that costs hundreds of thousands of dollars.
In this case, it's no use saying it's natural and big.
Don't be so mean, Otaku!
No, I thought so before.
How about this, Keiichi-sama?
This time, we're going back to the origin, and we're going to play golf in nature.
Yeah, that's good!
Let's do that!
Then I'll leave it to you.
Thank you very much.
Then I'll help with the competition project.
Captain Settai, let's talk here.
It's golf, after all.
Senpai has always said that golf is a money-growing paradise.
He has a great jealousy for money-growing.
I'm scared.
By the way, where are you heading to?
To the island of Saiko on the
Great Island of the South Pacific.
I'm surprised.
Surprised?
I've never heard of it.
There's no way.
Since the beginning of time, humanity has never stepped on an island.
Is that where you can play golf?
That's why I told you.
This time, we're going to play golf in the nature.
We're almost there.
Let's go.
Welcome, Dajoubu!
We're glad to see you.
Hey, what are you doing with the golf bag?
We didn't bring it from the start.
Huh?
If we didn't have the club, we wouldn't be able to shoot.
The club is ready. Let's go to the hall.
It's a big nature.
This is a golf club.
What's this?
It's a red-leaf pine.
It's a natural material.
What's a red-leaf pine?
It's a year-old tree with strong stems from China.
It's a cane that thousands of people have.
Oh, that cane.
If you make a head of the root, it can be used as a club.
I see.
And...
Use potatoes in the ball.
Potatoes?
The lost ball is usually the same no matter how many decades have passed.
Potatoes grow roots there and eventually return to nature.
It's true that it's 100% natural material.
In that case, it's better to make it round.
But it's hard to hit everything with just one ball.
This one is also pretty big.
Well, let's get started.
Before that, I'd like to announce the winner of this competition.
The winner is...
This one.
It's a pair ticket for the world tour of the luxury line provided by Nakagawa Group.
Oh!
I'm getting motivated.
It would be great if I could go with Jody.
I wish I could go with Nana-chan.
The winning product can be made in cash.
Of course, that's fine.
If we win the world tour, we'll get 10 million yen.
All right! Let's get started!
Here is the first hole.
There is a hole on the beach where the jungle is located.
It's called the Meerkat.
That's the cup of the first hole.
The hole is also natural, isn't it?
It's a long hole of a par-5.
We'll find out the order when we hit the goal post.
I'll be the captain.
Somehow, it's not easy to hit it.
V Omomomo!
Hurry up and hit it!
All right!
Yes.
Oh, it bent!
Reiko-san, potatoes tend to bend.
I'll be careful.
Now to the left.
To the left.
What?
Senpai, potatoes are impossible.
That's not true. Look closely at the potatoes.
You need to calculate the irregular bulge.
If you rotate it, it will fly straight.
Push it from the wind and extend the distance.
Furthermore, this part of the stick is the impact spot.
This angle is good.
If you shoot at this angle,
at the same time as the impact,
it will rotate to the right and fly straight.
That's just a theory.
It's impossible.
Then let's try it.
In nature golf, the basics of golf so far are not applicable.
It's about 300 yards.
Good.
It doesn't bend at all.
It's not bad.
It's not bad at all.
I don't get it.
With this tool ...
Then let's go!
What should we do with the ball in the jungle?
I think it's a lost ball.
What?
There is no way that it will be a lost ball.
After this, these two dogs will play the role of caddies.
What?
What do you mean, Captain?
I've already made them smell your smell.
so you can find the ball by relying on it.
I found it!
Thank you, One-chan.
One-chan, please go down a little.
It's difficult, but we have to get out of that gap to get to the fairway.
Eek!
Oh, dear...
In a place like this?
It's impossible to get out of here, right?
I'll move it a little bit.
Ouch, it itches!
What? I just cheated!
If you cheat, you'll be bitten!
I'm sorry.
I'm paying for it, so let me shoot from a distance.
I shot ten bullets just by getting potatoes out of the jungle.
All right, all right. Good job.
There are a lot of birds.
This island is called Bird Island.
There's a hole in the end of the meerkat.
Who is it from?
It looks like my potato.
All right, go!
Yes, sir!
All right.
I'll give you this ball and you can shoot his legs!
That's a good shot!
Oh, dude!
First, it's an vale!!
Woo-hoo!
Why again?
It must be a lost ball.
It can't be right!
Fucking golf.
I don't get it.
Hmm.
You must be surprised.
You're surprised? I'll definitely get 10 million!
Alright, now it's my turn!
I'm going to get 10 million!
So that's where you're aiming for.
Alright, I'm aiming at it!
Ryo-chan is really good at this.
Just hurry up!
I failed!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
That's a lot of them.
That was scary.
Thanks to the birds, it's a lot easier to shoot.
My ball is...
Huh?
Ah! My ball is being eaten!
The shape of the pit has completely changed!
Damn it!
Nice!
Thank you very much.
It's certainly easier now.
I managed to get into the bogey.
Hmph! I'm aiming for the eagle!
Ouch!
It's...
Oh, no!
What the heck! I'm a bird!
This is the Par 3's shortfall.
Hmm...
Hey, Tanma.
I'm going to go clean up, so you shoot the inside first.
Come on, Ryo-chan.
Hehehe...
Ouch!
This is my...
What was that just now?
Ah!
I'm not sure if I'm getting better or not,
but the lower part of the hole
is a trapping course.
I can feel it!
Just throw the ball away!
Super easy!
T-that's not it!
My...
Where?
Huh?
Use your head a little!
What do you mean?
You can aim from where the waves don't come.
This is dynamic golf!
Come on!
I did it! It's a hole-in-one!
Huh? Ah...
Ah...
Uh...
Senpai!
Are you okay, Ryotsu?
Ah, damn it! What is this?
Ah...
It's really dynamic.
That's also the natural snow, so I can't complain.
Ah, sen-sen-senpai!
Huh?
Yeah!
Wow!
It's an ictiosaurus!
It's really so natural!
Yah!
Is this a white rabbit from Inaba?
Yah...
What a順ing life!
Really...
You did it! It's a hole-in-one!
You did it! It's a birdie!
Do your best!
Damn it!
You two have excellent athletic ability.
There's a better course in the second half, so I'll pull you out of the hole in the first half.
I'm sure that's...
Nice kick!
If I use that rock, I can get a hole in one.
I will also get a hole in your back!
Dinosaur!
T- Tyrannosaurus!
Begone!
Why did Tyrannosaurus...
It's not distant human form?
My leg!
Senpai, what are you doing?
I'm the one who gets 10 million!
What?
I'm going to eat Tyrannosaurus and give up!
Yay! Another hole-in-one!
W-what?
Hey! Even though it was a hole-in-one, you bastard!
You bastard! Come out, you bastard!
All right, there you go.
You bastard!
This is of no use in the wilderness.
Yay!
Hole No. 17.
Ouch ouch ouch!
Idiot!
I'm sorry, senpai. I'm sorry.
I'll have to try again with the OB.
OB?
If he gets a +2 with the OB, he'll get caught up in the middle.
I'm not kidding.
Ryo-chan, you can't do it! Come back!
What? There's no OB in the game.
It's not OB. I'll shoot from below.
I won't let anyone get the win.
I'll take it.
The prize money...
is 10 million yen!
Oh!
Amazing.
He's got it.
What a terrible habit.
He's the kind of man who gets caught up in the money.
I-I'll do it.
I'll get the prize money.
Next, the final hole!
It's finally time.
This surprised man, Mou San's outfit is the cup of the final hole.
And, by the way, this is the "super-long hole" of par 80.
Par 80? Stop talking nonsense.
It's that big of a cup, so it's easy.
The hole is big, though.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's said that it's the fastest to climb the right route.
It seems like they're doing it seriously.
As I thought, it's impossible to climb the jungle.
No, you don't have to climb the jungle here.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Damn! I was just a little bit further!
It's hard to see what's ahead at the next stage.
Yeah, that's why he's carrying a magnet.
What's going on?
What's this?
It's a snake's big movement!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It seems like it's common in this season.
But it's not that bad.
The local staff says it's not that bad, so I'm not worried.
I'm going to pay the penalty and go on a trip.
Me too.
They're so stupid.
This is the shortest route.
I'm going.
Hey, Senpai!
Leave me alone, you idiot.
It's in the way.
The ball is hard to see.
Okay.
It's about time.
Hey, don't get caught in the air!
It's hard to shoot!
It hurts so bad!
Damn!
Ouch!
I'm marvelous bitten.
Are you okay, Ryo-chan?
I've been too tired.
And I'm so hot.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
The local staff might be poisonous snakes.
Huh?
Idiot.
I'm at my limit. I'll give up.
I won't give up, but I've already hit about 200.
But I can finally see the past.
I can see the past.
It's 76 so far.
If you put this in, you're an albatross.
Okay.
Something's shaking.
That's the nature golf!
It's the final hole lift!
Idiot! That's not the time to say that!
It's dangerous!
Hurry up!
Let's go down!
Run, run!
This is the end!
Okay, clear!
Go!
I did it! I'm in the cup!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Senior, are you okay?
Don't worry.
He's stronger than a cockroach.
To be continued
I really got in the cup just before the lava came out.
But no one has seen it.
Senior, unfortunately, it means there's no winner.
I really got in the cup just before the lava came out.
That's 10 million yen!
I bet you'll play the nature golf
next month at the golf course
in the next golf course in the next month!
What?
Even if they don't tell us the nature?
Heads and heels.
5 ski slates,
andkalimbo and inquiry!
Head and heels.
♪ Let's play the game. ♪
♪ I'll scratch my head and write a poem. ♪
♪ I don't care about the scandals. ♪
♪ I play the game every day. ♪
♪ I throw the ball into the trash. ♪
♪ I'm stupid. ♪
♪ I'm stupid. I'm stupid. ♪
♪ I'm stupid. I'm stupid. I'm stupid. ♪
♪ I'm stupid. ♪
Digging, diving, waiting for the swarm of parrots who have their eggs
At the Noel's sleep-walking place
Yabura Koji, Burakoji, Paipo, Paipo, Paipo
Suriingan, A decline of Suriingan
Pompoko Land, Pompoko T, Pompoko You
The 98-year-old Josuke
A major incident happened at Honda's home
His sister Eve is going to Africa.
Honda, be strong.
It can't be helped if you're with your brother.
It's impossible to stand between that ugly father and Eve.
Next time, the Honda family.
Thank you.