Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle ♪
♪ I kicked the pebble ♪
♪ Fly to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ In the middle of a taiko ♪
♪ I laughed at how much I was a mess ♪
♪ I'm fine somewhere ♪
♪ I'm fine even if I'm alone ♪
♪ I'm fine in the middle of a taiko ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ The sun is already setting ♪
♪ Are the yakitori and hobari here? ♪
♪ I'm going to the water tower ♪
♪ From the top of the Tongari Bridge ♪
♪ To the Taishakuten ♪
♪ The sunset is falling ♪
♪ It's going to end tomorrow too ♪
♪ I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I realized I was a fool ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Ryo-tsu the King of Invention
Sauce.
Soy sauce.
I don't care who says it, it's the sauce.
I'm not saying it stupidly. It's soy sauce.
Good morning, Kanchi.
What are you making a fuss about in the morning?
I'm talking about what to put on the fried egg.
You're making a fuss about that in the morning?
Matoi is the sauce, right?
I'm the soy sauce, right?
I'm the salt, though.
What?
Lemon is...
The sauce, right?
Soy sauce, right?
I won't put anything on it.
Huh?
The best thing is to taste it as it is.
So, it's decided on soy sauce, right?
It's not decided, right?
Then, I'll put soy sauce on my fried egg!
I'm the law here.
The sauce has been decided on the fried egg for a long time!
Hey!
Kanchi!
Hmph, even if it's not super simple sushi, there are places where you can eat other food.
Ryo-tsu is not here.
Really?
Are you late again?
I can't help it.
I'll squeeze you when you come out.
Damn it.
I can't get close to the starting point.
There are bicycles and bugs in my stomach.
There must be something in Ryo's dining room.
W-what's going on?
Oh, Ryo-san!
What's going on?
Ryo's construction is starting today.
I wrote it on the bulletin board a month ago, right?
I didn't know.
I put your luggage there.
I'll be taken there by mistake.
I wrote your name on it.
That's not it.
What's wrong with the food in the dining room?
Is there something wrong?
I used it up yesterday.
It's going to rot.
I'm going on a trip from now on.
See you, Ryo-san.
Hey, wait a minute.
What's going on? Food?
Food!
I said so.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry and my bicycle won't burn.
It's Naruto.
I can't pick up anything as a human.
But I can't go home hungry.
Hey!
Food for humans!
I didn't have time to be lost.
I'm going to disturb you.
Welcome.
Do you have a cankichi?
If you are Ryo-chan...
I'm working here for a while.
You have a cankichi here as well?
You're working here for a while.
I've been working here for a while.
I fought with my grandmother yesterday and ran away.
I was worried about you.
I searched everywhere and couldn't find you.
I thought you were fine.
I'm a little worried.
I have to use my hands.
I'm hungry.
When I'm hungry, I feel the autumn wind.
What?
It's cold.
That car...
It's a coincidence.
If we meet in a place like this...
I knew it.
It's a coincidence to be in a park on a helicopter.
It is a coincidence.
We've searched the room back in the events of PHS.
Who asked you to do it?
Are you the leader?
No, it's not because someone asked me to do it.
I really did it by chance.
I'm sorry.
I was asked by Lemon .
Too bad.
We're having a party at my home from now on.
You're not coming? There's a lot of food.
I didn't ask Lemon-san to let me eat.
I got it, I got it. I don't care about the reason. Let's go.
I'm at my limit.
I ate it, I ate it. I'm back to life.
That's good. Clean up.
What?
You don't have to clean up.
It's a high-tech house.
The machine moves just by ringing the button.
I'll do it too.
Show me the TV.
Is it broken?
It has a sound of a finger.
It's not responding to other finger patches.
TV.
It's broken, isn't it?
No way.
I knew it.
TV. TV.
What's going on? TV.
It's broken.
I don't care. I'll use the ultimate remote control.
The ultimate remote control?
Switch on.
It's just a stick.
Next news.
Super electronic machine.
Isn't this your company?
No.
Super electronic machine announced that it will pay a part of the sales of the actualized product to the developer as a compensation.
What?
Is this true?
What's the point of lying?
How much is the part of the sales?
It depends on the sales amount, but if you develop a big hit product, you can get one million.
One million.
Is this a 100 billion yen project?
No.
100 billion yen.
If I have 100 billion, I will never regret it.
Let me do it, too.
What?
I have an idea for a big hit item.
I have it.
Is it done?
Yes.
Use the title. Safety Box.
safelybox.
Pudding can be eaten.
What's this?
♪♪♪
In a family with many siblings, they have had the experience of eating the pudding in the refrigerator.
That is the cause of the development of sibling quarrels.
This is how to solve it.
If you do not enter the number, it will not open.
The pudding is completely protected, and the sibling quarrel is gone, and it is two birds with one stone.
If you press the registered number, it will open like this.
It's a big invention, isn't it?
Who will buy it?
If the siblings go and buy pudding,
The number of siblings in the family is decreasing year by year.
How much did the material cost?
It's cheap. It doesn't cost 100,000 yen.
How many houses have such a large amount of money for 100 yen or 200 yen pudding?
But maybe there are 100.
It's not a story.
There are still many ideas.
Next time you can expect.
Next is this.
Safety box.
No manager.
You see the product development.
How is it different from the previous one?
The opening of the lid is faster.
It's not a story.
I'll show you the real product development.
Product development is like this.
Super small batteries are being developed here.
If this is completed,
All battery-powered machines will be small.
The battery revolution will occur.
Of course, sales will be enormous.
This is a selling product.
I see.
Of course, it takes time to develop.
It's not something you can do in one go.
That's right.
If you understand, go back home quietly.
From now on, I'll stay here and develop the product.
It's okay. I'll develop an overwhelming product.
Then I'll lend you this room.
If you lock it in this warehouse,
It may interfere with the people in our company.
What's this?
It's a talking translation robot.
Talking translation robot?
If you talk in Japanese,
It automatically translates to English and speaks to you.
You can also make English into Japanese.
What?
It's not theoretically wrong,
It didn't work well and was suspended.
What a waste.
If you complete this,
Can I get a reward?
If you can complete it.
Okay.
I'll give you a reward.
Let's get started.
Well, making is rough.
It's impossible to make one up by a clumsy man.
For the time being,
I remodeled as the design figure with the ability that I had in making plastic models.
There it is, the switch.
I'm tired and sleepy...
Stripping.
What?
Didn't you talk to him just now?
Yes, I did.
My name is Ryochi Kankichi.
My name is Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I-I didn't know this was completed...
Yaaay! I'm gonna be a millionaire!
I got it! I can be a millionaire!
Yeah, yeah!
Hm? Wait a minute.
I can't tell if this guy really translated correctly.
I'll have to ask them.
Translation by: Katsuhiko
All right, the chief isn't here.
Hey, Reiko Nakagawa!
Ryo-tsu!
Senpai!
Where have you been? You've been working all day.
Chief, you're so slow.
There's a lot going on.
Could you talk to this for a bit?
What's this?
What is this?
Is this a translator?
Is this translated?
It's a talking translator I made.
Is the English correct?
It's perfect!
All right, next, English to Japanese.
Let me do it.
Oh, please. The Chonektai is the switch.
This?
How about some tea?
Oh, it's perfect!
The perfect talking translator is probably the world's first.
It's a global invention, Senpai!
Oh, I see!
Ryo-tsu!
Hey, Chief!
You! What have you been up to?
I've been talking for a long time.
This time, you're out of your mind.
Get over there!
Wait a minute. I've made a great invention of the century.
Don't say that!
I'm telling the truth!
What's this?
What is this?
I spoke!
It's a talking translator robot.
A perfect talking translator has not yet been developed by Docomo.
It's a great invention!
Really?
Yes!
This is the world's...
Oh, right!
Speaking of the world, tomorrow, a party will be held to invite police officers from around the world.
The chief and I are invited.
I'll take you there, too.
Huh?
I'll show you the translator machine I just used.
I'm sure people all over the world will be surprised.
The world's famous person.
The world's famous person?
Not bad.
Ryotsu!
Yeah?
I thought you'd do something great someday.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
As a boss, I'm sorry.
The switch just now was turned off.
Good morning.
Huh?
Didn't you just say "good morning"?
Just in case, I'll adjust it later.
Okay, I'm done adjusting.
Good evening, I'm Ryotsu Kankichi.
This is a pen.
What?
No, where did I get it wrong?
It should be as planned.
Okay, I'm okay now.
Tomorrow will be a windy day.
Kameyari, good boy, come here once.
What?
Why is my Japanese coming back?
Okay, I did it.
I'll go to the police station.
I'm a brave policeman.
Stupid, stupid, idiot.
I can take it tomorrow if I keep doing this.
So this is the address.
Reiko, Nakagawa.
Ah, senpai, good morning.
You're not going to the party, are you?
You guys have a favor to ask.
It looks good.
Hey!
Ryotsu, this way.
Hey, chief.
Wait a minute.
I'm going now.
Thank you for your help.
Did you bring it?
It's not here.
Chief, this is the translation robot.
Oh, then let's introduce it to everyone.
Before that, let me eat something.
I haven't eaten anything in my life.
Eat as much as you like.
Then I'll be spoiled by words.
Thank you for the meal.
With this, can you really translate?
Nakagawa-kun and Reiko-kun have confirmed it.
That's a relief.
Well, all right, let's do it with that person.
Hello.
Translate.
Oh, it's okay.
Oh, yes.
It was this switch, wasn't it?
The switch is in.
It cannot transform by this machine.
This machine.
Can you translate it really?
I wonder if I can translate it.
It seems that you have been able to translate well.
Yes.
You are surprised.
It seems that you are deceiving me, but I can feel it.
Eh? You want us to replace the translator machine?
Please.
I accidentally broke it while adjusting last night.
This looks like yesterday's translation robot, but the inside is modified into a transmitter.
You can receive the conversation here, translate it, and talk to me.
Please.
Just today is fine.
If you have time, you can fix it.
It's a big deal.
Let's cooperate today.
Where is your favorite city in Japan?
It's the director's voice.
This time it's English.
Fairly the town, number one police in Japan.
Oh, amazing.
That's right.
What a wonderful machine.
Thank you.
Oh.
It's a really good first impression.
I want to go back to the old days.
Wow, this is pretty cool.
I want to buy one, too.
I'm clueless.
Thank you.
I see.
In this case, we should answer in French.
That's right.
Andou.
Mes bordeaux, ne?
Ohara-kun, I feel like it wasn't English just now.
Well, it was somewhat French.
Can this machine also translate German?
Reiko-san, it's German now.
Ohara-kun, can this machine also translate German?
Well, Ryotsu was just talking about the translation machine.
Well, I think it's okay.
Please talk in various languages.
Translation takes a long time.
The boss and the staff have been waiting for a long time.
Boss, what's going on?
Ryotsu, what's this translation machine?
Did you get caught up with me because it's a fake?
How could you think it was a universal translation machine that could translate all languages?
Huh?
This machine is really something!
It's a wonderful machine.
Who made it?
Oh, it was made by this Ryotsu Kan-kichi.
The man who made it is him, Kan-kichi Ryotsu.
Thank you very much!
Mr. Ryotsu.
Here is something.
I have something to tell you.
You want to be the Prime Minister?
I would like to ask you for your cooperation.
From today, the Main Meeting with the President of the Republic of Shimagoka will be held.
The topic is the all-purpose translator produced by the Ryotsu-Kankichi-Junsa-cho of the Katsushika-cho.
Until now, the translation of the Shimagoka language into Japanese was necessary for all of us,
but Mr. Ryotsu said that if this was the case, the translation would not be necessary.
The all-purpose translator will be displayed at the lunch meeting tomorrow.
What should I do?
I managed to find the homepage of the Republic of Shimagoka on the Internet,
but what is written there?
I don't know.
I don't think there is any Japanese who can understand the Shimagoka language.
Wait a minute.
Does that mean that no one can understand even if I translate it properly?
Then I have an idea.
For the time being, I will choose a phrase from this homepage and create some patterns.
This is the meeting of the Main Meeting with the Republic of Shimagoka and Japan.
Mr. Ryotsu seems to have arrived.
Hello.
I am the All-purpose translator.
I am the developer of this translation robot, Ryotsu Kankichi.
I entered the data in a hurry to support the difficult Shimagoka language, so there is a slight time lag.
The robot will operate on this computer.
No, I thought I would like to talk to you two like this.
Okay, let's put out the third language for the time being.
Oh, finally, I'm glad I got a log.
The Shimagoka translation machine was not completed, right?
What's going on?
If you start talking in Japanese, the Shimagoka language on the homepage will appear randomly.
It seems that the Japanese that corresponds to the Shimagoka language is also typing in the appropriate phrase.
Eh? Then it will be a mess.
The Shimagoka language that comes out of the translation robot is only the words on the official homepage.
Senpai says it's okay, but ...
What? Something is fishy about Kumoyuki.
That's right. It seems that the face of the president is dragged.
Senpai saw it.
This is the official homepage of the Shimagoka Republic called Shimagoka, right?
I don't know what's written there.
Wait a minute, Kei-chan. There is also an English page.
Oh, it's true.
If you click on English ...
What? Kei-chan, this ...
It's not an official homepage. This is a meeting site for Shimagoka language.
Meeting site? Then, Ryo-chan, are you translating what is written on the meeting site to the president?
Yes.
I wonder if you can translate properly.
It's okay. My all-purpose translator is perfect.
I wonder if it came out with bad words.
Anyway, the lunch meeting is almost over. If you go on like this, there will be no complaints.
Genra.
I ...
Sokunto-kun.
What?
You can use the translator.
Yes, yes. Even so ...
Sokunto-kun. Sokunto-kun.
I said you can use it to make fried eggs, but I will choose this one for now.
I leave it to you.
You can use it to make fried eggs. Do you want me to leave it to you?
Then, please use it.
It 's a source when speaking of fried eggs.
But there are people who put soy sauce like gepalt, and there are people who only have salt, like Matoi.
Kei-chan, look here!
Here, at the end of the dating site, there's a regular Shimagoka homepage.
There's something like this...
Um...
Shimagokajin is very particular about medamayaki.
You can't just put sauce on medamayaki!
Um...
It's sauce, Ryo-chan!
This is definitely sauce.
Excuse me.
Ah, that's not it!
Huh?
There's a secret ingredient.
Soy sauce.
In other words, soy sauce!
Ryo-chan!
No!
That's not what I meant!
I said no!
No, I wasn't.
I was just picking randomly.
It's pretty good.
It looks like you're angry, but...
Hahaha!
Shimagokajin has a strong expression of emotion.
President, which is your favorite city in Japan?
Hatayu-no-Yasen, Kata-Sanpai.
What's wrong?
There are too many, I can't choose.
No, no.
Your country is wonderful.
I respect you from the bottom of my heart.
I support your goals.
Shimagokajin has a strong expression of emotion.
So, are you overworking the country?
Is this what I can do?
No, no.
It has nothing to do with me.
Hahaha.
You're humble.
There's something I can do to change you!
I will keep a close eye on the ties of both countries.
Maiden T traveller Seki Harukas
Marudou
Nishio
This is it!
Japan!
I'm the king of Japan!
What's going on?
I guess he didn't understand.
The 500th episode.
The separation of the island and the Republic of Japan.
Why did he put the sauce on it?
He's trying to fool the world with this piece of junk.
He's the king of Japan!
Where did he go?
I'm hungry.
I'm going to eat something.
Act 5
♪いつでもスケンダル気にしないって ♪
♪いくつでもスケンダル気にしないって ♪
♪局寝る遊ぶのエブリデー ♪
Oh gosh…
Dance now!
♪ 退屈なんて始末書に まるめて放り投げた ♪
♪退屈なんて始末書に まるめて放り投げた ♪
♪ 丸出し本能 むき出し本能 馬鹿になって ♪
♪丸出し本能 むき出し本能 馬鹿になって ♪
Isn't that right?
Just do what you want to do the way I do it
Amazing!
Wow !
The lightning to each value
The smoke from her head
She runs but the camera Kiriyoshi: The camera
Well, it's that much better
Really?
At the edge of the flowers
Great we go
There is a big mass typhoon
Can't escape
Atar gathered up once,
The water game, the water game
Take care of ourselves and become our own company
Water мы
水魚末
雲魚末
風雷末
汲れる所に住む所
家村工事
村工事
Paiko, Paiko, Paiko, Shurinkan
Shurinkan's Kurindai
Kurindai, on popo, on popo, pee, on popo, na, on
The super-famous Chosuke!
Nakagawa's been hospitalized?!
It's not a big sickness, of course!
The disease is called "power"!
You just have to laugh, laugh, laugh to the death!
I just need to laugh!
Nyaa!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Right?
Next time!
"Don't laugh, forgive, and please don't!"
There's a turtle there!
Ah, there's a turtle for sure!
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!