Hikari
When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away!
Those who have no money, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll be able to do something about it.
Hahahaha
Hikari
Those who have no work, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
Look at the red cloud burning.
I'll be able to do something about it.
I know, I know, I know.
If you understand, then shut up and follow me!
Ryo-san's Long Day
Hmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Idiot! Hurry up and give me the silver coin!
Uuughhhh! Aahhh! Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Shouldn't I apologize to you?
Huh?
Idiot! Hurry up and give me the silver coin!
There's a trick like this? Damn, I thought the chief was crazy about giving me a present.
Ugh, I guess I can't help it. I'm not going to wake up.
I didn't wake up because the chief woke me up. I woke up because I was too hungry.
I finished eating something.
Hm? There it is, there it is. Rice balls and natto.
I don't remember when I bought them, but I'm sure I bought them at a convenience store.
What is this smell?
The expiration date is July 5, 1999.
It's impossible for rice balls from the 20th century to rot.
Natto is fine.
This is Showa.
But, but...
Wait, wait.
It's black!
It's natto fossils.
I can't eat this.
Damn, I'm getting even more hungry when I realize I can't eat it.
I'm hungry and I don't even have a chance to eat.
Mochi, mochi!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Don't eat it!
You're a dog, but you're a canazuchi.
Oh, it's Omori-chan.
Hm?
Omori-san, help that dog!
Hm? I'm going to work from now on. I'm late...
Omori-san!
Hm? If I'm late, the boss will...
And I'll be hungry...
Ah, damn it!
Kids, get out of the way!
Ah!
Bad dog!
My bad!
Ah, thank God!
Aren't we done for today?
See you again!
Wow, you lost so much.
We lost so much!
Hey, what are you doing?
I've done a good job, but I can't do it again.
I can't do it.
Hey, hey, you're following me, aren't you?
If you take the stray dog to the country, what will the chief say?
Hey, hey, stop it.
Please stop it.
Good morning, senior.
Chief Ohara, I gave you a alarm clock, but you were angry at me for being late.
I was angry.
Where is the chief?
I went to the chief's meeting.
Oh, I see.
I'm glad.
It's not good.
You're late for ten days in a row today.
I can't help it.
I'm on my way today.
Well, I'm here.
I saved this stray dog because it was drowning in the river.
So that's why you're so affectionate.
Well, yeah.
Isn't it a cute puppy?
Do you want to eat a biscuit?
Eat it.
Give it to me.
It's gone.
You were hungry.
I ate the whole box.
You're so strong.
I haven't eaten anything since this morning.
If I have breakfast, I'll go on a patrol.
So, can you lend me a thousand yen?
He he he.
I borrowed 1,000 yen from Reiko.
Now I have a beef bowl, rice bowl, miso soup, eggs and a butt.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I went too far.
I'm not careful.
Hey!
I borrowed 1,000 yen from Reiko!
I found it!
Hey, wait!
How far are you flying?
Fly and get it!
On top of the building.
Wait there.
I'll go get it now.
My precious rice bowl.
Catch it!
Are you licking it?
Wait!
I think I got it!
Damn it!
I'll let you get away!
Watch my threat!
I did it!
Damn it!
I'll catch anything and everything.
I'll put it in the cauldron!
I won't let you!
What is this?
You can see it.
It's 1,000 yen.
Oh, it's 1,000 yen.
Wow!
Then I'll get a beef bowl, rice bowl, miso soup and eggs and a butt.
Excuse me, could I have the meal ticket?
Ah, yes, of course.
I'll take care of it if you force it.
Damn it, I can't get in.
What?
Are you okay?
Bakco.
Hm?
What?
I'll borrow the police!
You're going to catch me by bicycle?
What?
You're a thousand years too early to run away from me!
Damn you!
But, wait!
Sorry!
No!
You're not getting away!
You're too slow!
Damn you!
Get out of here!
That was close!
I'm so hungry I can't get any strength in me.
But I think I can get away from this Ryotsu Kankichi!
Ouch!
Alright!
Damn you!
You're too slow!
I can't!
I'm so hungry I can't move anymore!
You're really good at this, Senpai!
I think I can catch the criminal if I'm not hungry.
I found this before the park.
I need to eat something before the park.
Senpai,
we have something to do at the library,
so please take us to the office.
Senpai, we have something to do at the library, so please take us to the office.
Yeah.
I can't move a single step.
What?
You're still here?
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry first.
Go over there.
Shut up!
I'm hungry too!
Bite my shoes!
Don't bite me!
What about you,でも,
Ouch.
My legs are on fire!
It's much faster than usual.
Didn't you say it was a big rush?
Even so, it's too fast.
Could it be that the customer left it?
It's not that, it's just freshly fried.
It's suspicious that it's not cooked.
Please forgive me.
Even so, it's very thin.
Is there meat in here?
It's in here.
It's a masterpiece when it comes this far.
It looks like it's transparent.
It always looks like this.
Ryo-san, don't tell me you put it on.
It's a bad blow.
If it's money, it's fine.
I don't need a fishing rod.
Take it.
Every time.
What is this?
It's a 1,000 yen bill.
It's a little dirty.
It's dirty?
Is this a bill or something?
Well, wash it clean.
There's no doubt.
If it's not a bill, I won't admit it.
It's okay.
It's a 1,000 yen bill that's true.
Then I can finally eat...
You!
You bastard!
I know, I know, I...
Don't think you can escape alive!
Ryo- шооо.
No, never.
I'm hungry and my eyes are blurry.
Damn it.
If the chief sees this, I don't know what he's going to say.
I don't know what he's going to say.
There was a scene in a movie that I saw a long time ago where I ate shoes.
Maybe I can do it.
Shoes are like beef jerky.
I think if I cook it thoroughly, it will return to the original beef.
It's looking good.
It's starting to look like meat.
This is a roast beef.
I'll have it with soy sauce.
It smells good.
This looks delicious.
I'll eat.
It's a little hard to cut.
Well, how does it taste?
It's still hard.
It's a little chewy.
But the more I chew, the more it tastes.
It was a solid skin.
Damn it. I'm hungry.
I can't help it.
I'll clean it up to distract myself.
This is pretty good.
I'm hungry one by one.
Excuse me.
I'd like to hear what you have to say.
What is it, Tomichi?
I'm sorry.
No, I'll become angry if I'm too hungry.
I'm a normal person.
What a persistent guy.
Can I eat lunch here?
I wonder if I can eat it.
Oh, you're a businesswoman.
I'm busy.
Do it yourself.
Thank you.
I'm glad to eat under the roof.
That's good.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm sure you can tell by looking at it.
It's Sukiyaki.
I'm carrying a heavy luggage.
I have to take care of it.
Don't do it in the exhaust.
Oh, are you hungry?
I haven't eaten anything since this morning.
But it looks delicious.
Do you like Sukiyaki?
I like Sukiyaki.
Then look at what you're eating.
What are you doing?
This is one serving.
I'm hungry.
I'm tired of it.
I'm tired of feeding the扇
of my chest being arant.
I got a bad stomachache.
You want to try a bite of this meat?
I have a bad stomachache again.
I'm going to eat meat.
How do I eat it?
How do I eat meat?
You bastard! I won't forgive you anymore!
Get out of the way!
It's all your fault for thinking like that!
What is it?
20 servings of jumbo omurice.
If you eat it in 20 minutes, you'll get a 5,000 yen reward!
You're so generous, Lago!
I can eat 20 servings of jumbo omurice in 5 minutes if I want!
Doesn't it look delicious?
If you eat it in 20 minutes, you'll get a 5,000 yen reward.
I don't care! I'll eat it in 5 minutes if you want!
You're kidding!
I don't care! Just let me eat it!
I understand.
Alright.
I'll eat it!
You're so mean!
Hey, you're not even starting yet?
You're not even getting there.
I'm being mean, sir!
Now, at a time like this...
I got it! You just have to eat it!
Pick it up! The omurice!
Which one is it?
Over there!
That's...
That's him again!
Wait!
It's that policeman again!
Darn it!
No, no, no, no!
My eyes are getting blurry!
What? What? Did you follow me?
Jumbo omurice!
Alright! Hold on tight so you don't get thrown away!
Hold on tight so you don't get thrown away!
Is it just a fun livin up there?
Isn't this a pizza restaurant?
Hey, what's going on?
Jumbo Omurice!
Hey!
Pizzazo!
Where'd you get that!
I knew you were gonna get hit by a pizza!
command!
Commander Jumbo Omurice!
Commander Jumbo Mirage!
Damn it!
You bastard!
Get ready for this!
I can't do this. My stomach...
I can't get my strength back.
Omelette rice!
Dad, the problem is solved!
Let me eat omelette rice!
But, the customer's omelette rice is...
What?
Then, make it again!
But, the one he gave me is gone.
My omelette rice...
I can't do this. I can't do this anymore.
My strength is gone.
Oh!
What's going on?
How much trouble do you have to cause trouble to people?
I'll make a house for the old lady at the business school!
I'll make a mess of the kitchen!
I'll bring the stray dogs into the kitchen!
It's really pathetic!
Chief Ohara!
I know my place is a mess but I'll change it!
What?
Entertaining!
Not all dogs are happy in the world.
So, how about we work together?
I see.
What are you doing?
Does she know why you're here?
I don't know...
Braggart.
She's aware she's a drugľr!
What about it?
This smell is cake.
Eat.
Give it to me.
Thank you for the meal.
Senior.
He's eating while crying.
It doesn't matter if the other adult doesn't cry because of the cake.
The boss doesn't understand my feelings.
This is my cake.
I'm not going to give you my strawberry cake.
You're eating the cake without telling me.
You didn't eat anything because of me.
Give me that much.
After this, Hard Boiled Deka came back.
Hard Boiled Deka
It's Kamaro.
Is he in here?
It's Hoshi from the capital.
People call me Hard Boiled Deka.
You're Hoshi, of course.
All right, everyone.
Let's go to the scene.
It's Hard Boiled Deka.
What's this work?
This is like a daily comedy anime.
I can't show my Hard Boiled charm enough.
It started again.
This background is NG.
Change.
This is a background that suits Hard Boiled.
Next.
You guys have to be more realistic.
You have to be realistic.
Use the from here.
She becomes realistic.
This is not real.
Where is she?
It's real.
I've beenut they told me.
This is an amazing opportunity.
Hard Boiled Deka
This is How I look realistic.
My time is up.
Why don't you say something?
I'll show you what you're capable of.
It's too much.
We have a good opportunity to do this.
With the three of us.
Alright, then let's start the Hard Boiled Dekka scene, take 2.
Ready, start!
It's Kamalo!
Could it be that...
I'm Hoshida, from the main office.
People call me the Hard Boiled Dekka.
Why is it suddenly over?
It just started!
What's going on, Director Takamatsu?!
Sorry,
the broadcast time is...
I'm running out of time,
so I just asked you to come and adjust the time.
What?!
You can go home now.
No way...
What's going on?
My place to show up is...
Damn it!
I'm definitely going to show up again!
Hey, I can't do this anymore...
I need to help him, Hoshida-san.
Okay, I'll go and get him too.
The cast and crew are all here,
a new guest.
I can get away-
I'm not a bad person
Don't be so indifferent
Even if you lie and cheat a little
Sometimes you're helping someone
Baby do you know me?
I'm heading for tomorrow
Nice breath of my heart
Don't get sick
I'll do what I have to do
A cute breath of my heart
What's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than seeing it again
Good morning, Ryo-tsuku
Well, this time it's your mission
To find the police office
The model of this 50 tower ordered from the police
It will be completed by the deadline
This trailer will be automatically eliminated
Next time
The secret command
Mission in 50 towers
I wish you success
There is a turtle there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you