When you're watching TV
Make sure to keep your room light and keep your distance
It's like someone's calling you
After the rain
You look back and walk
Hold your mother's hand
That's when I felt
A strange feeling
So
I walked on the dark side of the arcade
Just a bit
Everyone was a child once
But
Everyone has forgotten
The politicians with a big face
And the blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle over there
There's definitely a turtle
There's a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Hyper President's Family Service
Hello!
I lost again!
I'll call you when I get there
That's funny
That's right, Manchi-san was a good kid
That's right, that's right
You were a little different from when we were kids
You're not a bit of aä»”
Didn't you have a turtle?
You have a turtle?
I do know you
I'm a little bit supposed to be a turtle
But with this turtle
It is
There's something I want to say
There's a turtle
Not a turtle
I want to be a turtle
There's a turtle
A turtle
That's a turtle
I want to have a turtle
Do you have any money?
I don't have any money.
I'll pay you with a taxi ticket.
Hey! Don't do something like a working man!
I don't have any cash.
I only have cards.
You're so cheeky!
Why do you have a credit card when you don't have any money?
No, I have money.
I have a bank account for the game software I'm thinking of.
I earned about 20 million yen last year.
20 million yen?
You're a kid, but you earn more than I do.
You're a cheeky kid.
Calm down.
His father is the president of a super electronic engineering company.
He's good at computers.
What are you talking about?
You're a kid, but you earn more than I do.
Excuse me.
It's me.
What?
I'm at my parents' house in Katsushika.
You talk like an adult.
Do you keep the test questions in your mail?
OK. I'll download it and send it to you.
A high-tech land cell is out.
It's much thinner than the land cell I saw before.
High-tech devices are evolving day by day.
What are you doing?
I'm connecting it to my cell phone and downloading data from my partner.
I'm downloading the data I saw earlier.
You're copying the data to the electronic notebook this time.
I hate elementary school students.
It's done.
But when you show the land cell, you'll go back to normal elementary school.
What?
What are you going to start next?
What are you doing this time?
I'm going to play a video game.
It seems to be navigating.
He seems to be doing a navigation.
Well then, I have a specification.
I'll excuse myself.
Hey! What's a specification?
Is that a job question?
You're a junior, but you use a professional term.
It will appear from the corner soon.
Sir, please hold this.
Flas, why are you here?
I got a message from my father.
My mother took the minus and left home.
He told me to stop him.
Well, if you come by yourself,
you can't let your son do that.
My mother won't go home.
It's useless for my mother to run away.
The car has a transmitter.
You can easily navigate the location.
Well, then I'll go here.
I have an idea.
Let's go, Minus.
Mother, it's useless.
Minus has a transmitter.
Why?
You're scary.
Calm down, mother.
Let's go to the station and talk calmly.
I can't stand it anymore.
Look at this.
What's this?
It's like a kindergarten goods.
By the way...
A computer.
It's the age of information.
You have to have a kindergarten card.
Flas, keep your mouth shut.
Yes.
It has DVD player,
mobile phone and TV.
It has a lunch box and a mini microwave.
And it has a gas for safety.
It has a gas for safety.
It's a small version of the high-tech land cell.
Yes.
Like Plus, Minus is trying to use it as a monitor for a new product developed by the company.
I think I can understand why you want to stay home.
Right?
I don't want to be Minus like Plus, who is completely high-tech and has no emotions.
I don't want to be Minus.
The area of this platform is...
Look, your mother and brother are trying to do it at home,
but you don't take classes online.
Don't get too excited.
I'm the one who's bothering you in the couple fight.
I can't do anything about it.
I'll download the class content for my friends later.
Banji is like this.
She doesn't have any childish emotions.
She's been like this for a while...
Look, Plus.
Look at this.
This flower is beautiful.
Wait a minute.
The correct name is Campanula, Mom.
It's a herbivorous plant.
Plus has no normal feelings that are beautiful just by looking at the flowers.
All you have is information and knowledge.
R-right.
Right?
Okay, I'll meet Chishuya and complain.
Really?
Yeah, I'll tell him.
Right now, I'll get back to work.
Yeah.
S-sorry.
Where are you going?
I have a job.
My wife is in town.
Let's go back.
Hello.
The store is closed.
Please give me a ride.
Thanks.
It'll be fine.
That's right, cheat code "Unlocked".
Oh, Mom! You're back!
Good work, Plus!
Honey, I haven't said anything about going home yet.
Huh? Really, Plus?
Yes, Mr. Ryochi. I'll be in your care from now on.
Oh, Ryochi. Who's that?
It's Mr. Omari, who used to monitor the Super Electric GX 767.
Oh, Mr. Ryochi. Thanks to your monitor, the problem of the Super Electric GX 767 was solved.
I had a hard time back then.
Now, the Super GX 777, which has improved the problem and has been sold worldwide, is selling.
It's a hit product with a sales of over 2 million units.
Oh, it's thinner than before and cooler.
Mr. Ryochi, you're really smart.
Yeah.
Hey! I'm not here to hear that kind of bragging!
Stop using your own sons as monitors!
That's impossible! If you try it with money, the development will be exposed!
I'm doing this to research better products, so I'm making my heart a demon.
You're a criminal, so you don't have the guts to complain!
Shut up! Is it okay for you to lose your elementary school-like emotions for that?
Ugh...
Plus, you're an 8-year-old elementary school student.
You can't laugh or cry at all!
And it's all thanks to you monitoring your own company's products!
At this rate, you'll grow into a human who has no blood or tears, and you might be kicked out of the company, and Plus will become the president!
Hmph. That's pretty good.
What?
The future of the high-tech industry is an era of downfall.
If Plus can be that strong...
I'm satisfied.
My wife, you can't do this. You should get a divorce.
Yes.
And you?
I'm going to go back to my parents' house.
Mom! You love her so much, but you can't do that!
Hmph.
R-Ryotsu, what should I do?
Just treat her like a normal father, and treat her as a plus.
Even if you say I'm a normal father...
For example, you can play catch ball on your break.
Catch ball?
You've played it a lot, haven't you, Plus?
Yes.
What? I've never seen it.
How fast can you go?
About 130 km/h.
Okay.
Here I go, Dad.
Nice ball!
Now it's your turn, Dad. Let's go, Plus!
You idiot!
What?
Is there anyone who can play catch ball virtually?
I'll go back to my parents' house.
M-Mom...
R-Ryotsu...
Is there any other way to interact with Plus?
That's right.
Tomorrow's Sunday.
How about forgetting about studying and work and playing in an amusement park?
Then the virtual amusement park software is here.
No!
It's not a game.
You actually play by touching each other's skins.
I see.
Then, Plus and I will go to Kazushika Wonderland.
Yeah, that's fine.
That would be a problem.
President, Mr. Smith will come to visit tomorrow, so...
No!
I'll go to the children's school tomorrow.
You finally understand.
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
I promise!
That's good, Plus.
Let's go back to the school.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
President, we finally got an hour's time to talk to you.
I have to make a contract with you for tomorrow afternoon.
Yeah...
President, your father and I are really struggling.
That's right.
Contract!
*whisper*
I see...
That was good.
Yeah, but I think it's impossible for them to enjoy the amusement park like normal parents and children.
I agree.
Ryotsu-san, can you keep an eye on those two?
Eh?
I'll pay you back.
Thank you.
Thank you?
I got it! I'll leave this place to you, Kankichi!
According to the navigation, it's a traffic jam.
It's Sunday, so it can't be helped.
Dad, if we go at this pace, it'll take 72 minutes to get to Wonderland's parking lot.
Yeah, plus, that's a bit different.
Let me show you.
The capacity of this parking lot is 1,500 units.
According to the internet, 120 units will be filled.
If they're full, you can't enter.
If you're at this position, you have a 52.63% chance of entering.
I see. I forgot to enter the entry regulations in the data.
Yeah. I forgot to enter the entry regulations in the data.
I forgot to enter the entry regulations in the data.
You guys, cut it out! We're not here to calculate! We're here to play!
Poshu!
Sorry, I just got here this week.
Geez, what a parent.
Let's go, Plus.
Wait a minute!
Huh?
You don't need a land cell to go play, do you?
But my friends might e-mail me.
Plus, you're going to play a lot with me today, so leave that out of it.
Okay.
Nagagawa!
Let's go, Poshu.
Okay.
Well, I'll leave it in the car.
Haha.
Let's play a lot, Plus.
Again!
Cool.
W-What is it?
I only have a video camera.
Why are you wearing a suit when you're playing?
N-No reason. I love suits.
Change into this.
Do I have to change?
That's right!
I can't help it.
I have to change.
What's that?
It's a hyper business suit developed by my company.
It's a revolutionary suit that includes all business tools in a suit.
T-This is amazing!
Don't say that!
It's also Poshu!
That's it.
I don't have any complaints.
I don't have anything else.
You're right.
Yeah.
Nakagawa Metal Detector.
Yes.
Hmm?
Huh?
There's something in the belt!
Y-You!
I think the metal detector is a foul play.
Tsk.
Oh, there's a Pokebell in the buckle.
What else?
A TV in the soles.
The clock is on the internet.
This Mamey-su is a radio.
You're James Bond!
Hahaha.
Are you talking something?
You can't be so serious.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Are you playing along?
Don't touch me.
Oh, is it?
Anything?
ð’°ð’·ð’¾ð’¿ð’¸ ð’©ð’ºð’¾ð’¹ð’±ð’¸ð’¸ð’¬ð’¸ð’¸ ð’¢ð’¸ð’±ð’½ð’·ð’¸ð’¸â†—
It seems like you finally become like your father.
What do you think?
I can't get any closer.
You guys, listen up!
Let's make a line and shoot one by one!
Dad, the video is fine.
No, I'll do something. Just wait there.
I have to do something as your father.
Alright!
I brought Macky here!
Look, look!
Now, Plus!
You're with Macky.
It's fine. I don't really like Macky.
You're really happy to hear that, right?
Look, smile!
Where's your father?
Plus, what do you want to be with next?
Choose what you like.
Dad, it's fine.
Then, let's ride a ride next.
How about that?
Looks like your father has gradually become your father.
That's so normal!
A job is like nothing else!
The longer you play with your father, the richer you become!
It seems like he finally woke up.
Yeah.
Hm? No!
It's time to have a talk with Mr. Smith.
Ah, Plus!
What is it?
Let's take a video in front of the fire place.
Stand in front of it.
Understood.
Let's take a video in front of the fire place.
I'll do it.
Mr. Smith is negotiating.
Okay, show me the supplies.
Yes.
This is the paper work of a paper that has solar cells.
How about 10 meters for $10,000?
Hm. It seems to be of good performance.
But $10,000 is expensive.
Hey, where are you taking it?
Plus is over here!
Oh, that's right!
Why is there an antenna on the video camera?
There is an antenna on the video camera.
This is better.
Hm?
Oh, this flower is really beautiful.
I want to put a flower cut on the camera.
Ryotsu seems to have noticed.
I'll contact you later.
What did you do by saying something to the video camera?
No, I recorded it with Hesse.
It's suspicious to hide.
Video is also confiscated!
Ah, that's all.
That's all?
Ah, no.
I wanted to take a lot of plus.
Don't just shoot videos.
Enjoy some attractions!
Yeah.
According to the information I saw on the Internet,
the jet coaster is relatively easy to ride at this time of day.
I see.
Then let's do it.
It's a mess.
I kept Smith waiting.
If this continues, the deal will be a par.
I can't help it.
I'll call you with a good response.
Hm?
Oh, here it comes.
It's my helicopter.
But how do I contact him?
Hm?
That's it.
Plus, let's play that game together.
Yes, that's fine.
Dad was beaten.
Dad, you're not good.
No, not yet.
Bang! Bang!
You finally became a normal dad.
It seems so.
Oh, Mr. Okuchi.
I was worried after all.
I guess I'll go for it.
I'll shoot down that helicopter.
Ba! Ba! Ba! Ba! Ba!
10,000 dollars is expensive.
8,000 dollars.
Tell me.
Keep your word.
Yes.
Yes!
Ah!
Ah! Plus!
Got it!
Yes.
Hmm?
Hey, wait!
Ah!
*Screams*
Senpai!
Senpai, please hold on!
The culprit is...
Over there!
Damn it! I won't let you escape!
*Screams*
I'm coming!
Hey, you can't escape!
How about that?
*Screams*
*Laughs*
The helicopter is coming soon!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
What are you after?
I want all the data of the Hyper Learning Model
that your company is developing!
What?
If you want your son's life,
I'll send you the data!
I can't do it now!
The data is in the company!
Shut up!
I know you're carrying the important data in a disk!
What?
Are you serious?
Then give it to me!
Uncle, it's useless!
You're more important to the company than your family!
Don't ever get involved in any transactions!
You idiot!
I'm sorry, but I want the disk from my Super Suit pocket!
I understand!
You're the one who should be ashamed!
Mr. Nakagawa, please wait!
What?
Please bring my land cell!
Hey, you!
Don't say unnecessary things!
Mr. Nakagawa, do you think your father will give you the secret?
What?
It could be a disk that contains nothing.
I'll check it out.
What did you read, Plus?
I'm not that cold-hearted!
Shut up!
You said something good!
Bring my land cell!
Get out of the way!
The helicopter is coming!
Please wait.
It seems to be real!
I'm glad!
You're so clumsy!
The helicopter is coming!
Get out of the way!
Plus!
I'm glad you're safe!
Dad.
It's so sweet to give you an important business secret like that!
Plus!
But I was very happy, father!
But Plus is over, Kazan!
Plus!
Hahahahaha!
You're a pretty good father, aren't you? I've seen you again.
That's right, senpai.
Plus-kun, you're a good father, that you're the president of a big company, and you forget to work and play all day.
You two are praising me too much.
Please look at the new product next time.
Wonderland Navigation?
If you put this software in your pocket computer and carry it around,
it will tell you what attractions are waiting for how many hours, and what is the target during the parade.
What? Did you get that information in there?
You really are a person who doesn't waste your time.
Hahahaha!
If you put this software in your pocket computer and carry it around,
it will tell you what attractions are waiting for you next time.
It is fall.
It's time to get ready for the parade.
It's time to get dressed up and set up.
Can't wait up to work.
Well, I'm going to bring Koko.
And with a lot of energy.
Well, Koko the captions, what is she saying?
She is angry, isn't she?
Hm!?
Oh, Koko!!
Let's get rid of the annoyance and cleanliness
No problem every day
If you go through the hot shower
Recover your health with a sleeping pillow
No problem every day
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
Monday
Eh? The chief was fired?
And he said he couldn't do anything else in his 10-year police life?
It can't be helped, it's for the sake of my former boss
I'll find him a part-time job
Next time
There's a turtle over there
Ah, it must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town