English Subtitles:
From the top to the bottom, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
If you win or lose, you lose happiness again
I realized it, it was an idiotic me
Taikichi! Beauty! Nippon Zuri!
You got it! Hurry up and get it!
Yes! I did it! I got it, senpai!
It's not the time to be happy!
Line tension is high! You'll be cut if you don't do it!
What should I do?
Loosen the drag and pull the string!
The drag button is...
You're bad, you got the line cut.
Mr. Honda, it was a pity.
It was a big one, but it was a pity.
It's not that I caught it.
Come to think of it, Senpai caught a 23-pound big one.
Well, well.
Even if the fishing is bad?
Well, well, it doesn't matter.
Good job!
Yes!
What's hiding you now?
Good job!
I know, I know.
I'm sorry. I was playing a fishing game.
A fishing game.
Is it true that the chief is also a fisherman?
Well, I'm a herabuna expert, but I caught a 50-centimeter fish.
When I went to the chief's house, there was a tall fishing rod.
That's a product made by a famous craftsman.
If you like fishing, why don't you go fishing with me?
It's a toy. I'm a toy.
Chief, that's not what you're making fun of.
When you catch it, it vibrates like a real thing.
Oh, and the reel is also attached properly.
That's not all. You can choose the lake and lure where the bass is.
It's a great feature that can be found at the depth of the sonar and the water room and the lure.
It's pretty serious. How do you do it?
I'm here, chief.
Which lake do you want?
Oh, this one.
Next is the boat.
Look at the sonar and aim for the place where the bass is.
The depth of the lure will also come out.
What? Then it's easy to catch.
Oh, man.
The most important thing in lure fishing is to choose the lure.
The bass cannot be caught unless the proper lure is used according to the weather, water and depth.
I see.
Beginners are good at eating.
It's safe to catch a spider jig brown.
Then I'll leave it to you.
Now, please cast.
It's here.
It is amazing that it is large.
You got it!
Itacion Channeling
I did it! I were able to cast it!
The bass is 25 pounds long.
That's awesome.
It's my first time to catch a bass for the first time.
Ah, is it?
I'm a genius in fishing.
By the way, Ryotsu, what's your best record?
I forgot. What was it?
You said 23 pounds.
What? 23 pounds?
You're playing games all the time and you're saying 23 pounds.
I'll be the first to do it and it's 25 pounds.
What's with that ridiculous laugh?
You're so stupid that you caught it by chance.
Lend me your money.
I'll catch a bigger bass.
Let's get the boss closer to the rock.
Alright!
That's a good fish. It's definitely a big one.
Really? It's a big one, but it's not that big.
This is why you should be worried.
You're pretending to be weak and you're playing games all the time.
I caught it.
What? It's a bluegill.
How much is it?
5 pounds.
I can't win a game with fishing.
I've been fishing since I was a kid.
I've been fishing from herapuna fishing to Christmas tree.
I've never lost to anyone.
What? Christmas tree?
I've been fishing and I've been fishing.
It's a joke from your father.
Ryo, this is a talent.
No matter how hard you try, it's not going to work for me.
This is a life.
Remember that.
Where are you going? I'm working.
I don't think you'll come back for the rest of your life.
The chief is to blame.
He will hurt Ryo's pride.
He's in a bad mood.
I'm sure he's thinking of revenge for Ryo.
Kumoyuki is getting suspicious, so I'm going home.
Excuse me.
You're not coming back.
You're drinking Yakisake somewhere.
Who's drinking Yakisake?
Ryo.
Where have you been?
I went to a toy store.
A toy store?
Yes. To get this.
Chief, let's play again.
What? Bus Fishers again?
This is not Bus Fishers.
It's a new game machine in the works.
It's Gal Fishers.
Gal Fishers?
It's a game where you get a gal instead of a black bus.
Idiot!
I'm going to quit my job and borrow something like that.
I don't care what you say.
Let's see who can catch more gal.
You're stupid.
I don't play such a stupid game.
What's this document?
You're running away.
No.
I'm not going to play a game like fishing for a gal.
You said you'd never lose a fish, but you were lying.
I don't want to play such a stupid game.
I don't want to work under a boss.
I'm a real man.
Is there a bill of two balls?
I can't do anything about it.
I can't do this.
Shut up.
All right.
If you say so, I'll do it.
Let's do it!
Chief!
As expected of the chief.
He's a man after all.
Tell me how to fish, Ryotsu.
Fishing is similar to the bus fishers, but
It has a digital camera and real gyaru can catch it.
I'll try it, so please watch.
Oh, the reaction is over immediately.
This game machine has a fish-based detector instead of a fish-based detector.
Oh.
It also reacts to women who are actually alive.
It's a pretty cute little gyaru.
Next, choose a lake that seems to be alive.
It's not a lake.
The prey is not a bus, but a gyaru.
Well, the current child is a little gyaru.
If you're going to play, choose Harajuku.
Next, choose a car instead of a boat.
She seems to be active in short cuts, so she's an outdoor fan.
4WD Range Rover.
As expected of the senior, you have a sharp reading.
Next, choose a lure.
The lure is also quite different.
Well, it's realistic.
The gyaru is choosing what she wants to be presented.
Well, since she's a high school student, Tiffany's ring is suitable.
OK, the setting is complete.
Well, the gyaru is choosing what she wants to be presented.
Oh, yes!
I didn't know that.
What is it?
It's a gift.
Let's go.
All right.
I got it!
Look, look, look!
What's this?
If you lift it, the picture of the girl appears.
The computer will compare the face and body of the girl with the beauty score.
And the girl with 70 points of beauty score will wear a swimsuit.
This is so cool!
Do you know how to use it?
Yes.
But it's not fun to just compete.
That's right. How about this?
Let's bet on the most precious treasure.
What?
I bet on this.
I don't need this.
This is 350,000 yen.
I don't have such a high treasure.
You have.
A rod for a herabuna.
No, that's not good.
Then let's have you admit your defeat.
You'll show up in front of me and say you won't brag about fishing anymore.
And lower your head.
You don't have confidence in winning.
What?
You don't want to bet on this because you don't have confidence in winning, do you?
What do you want to do?
A game of rock-paper-scissors?
Which do you want?
Okay, I got it.
I'll bet on the rod and show you.
Boss?
How can we decide who will win?
Well, let's decide who will win with how many points you get within an hour.
Okay, that's good.
Then, follow the position.
Ready.
Start.
Start!
I found three of them.
I think it's Komachi and Naoko.
Okay, I'll go with those two.
I can't expect a high score even if that blue animal is the one.
I'll go with the flashy girl next to it.
I'll go with Komachi first.
I remember Komachi often went shopping in Ueno,
so he bought a place in Ueno.
Komachi's appearance is like a small gyaru,
but he has a unique style.
This is the car, and this is the lure.
Ready, set, go!
Miss, would you like to drink some tea with me at the Togenuki Jizo?
Chibu~i!
If you date me, I'll give you a Bill Search outfit as a present.
I like you, Mister!
Let's go on a date!
I'll go with you!
I did it! I got it!
40 points!
I thought it was a higher score.
That's just how Komachi is.
Okay, it's my turn this time.
Ready, set, go!
One, two, three.
Stop!
Get out of the way, all right?
Whenever I see a car, I drive it.
Don't tell me...
Doc.
Is this the real corner?
I'm going to drive!
Fish on!
90 points. No doubt about it!
What? I'm not going!
How about the Kimijita brand suits?
Great! Naoko, let's go!
Fish on!
I did it! I caught it!
You're definitely below 50 points.
I'm not!
I did it! 70 points!
What? Naoko got 70 points?
What's the point of making this game?
Damn it! I'm going this way!
I did it!
Come out, 100 points!
25 points!
Why is it 25 points? I can't believe it!
What? You can just watch it!
But the violation is a violation!
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
You're so stupid.
What?
Yeah!
I'm sorry I'm stupid.
What's wrong with you, you bastard?
Yeah!
I've got 25 points.
Change the point, Ryoza.
Get out of my house, Ojiya!
Oh, no!
Uchyo, how's it?
Huh?
What's going on?
I'm going to my house, Ryoza.
It's more useful to have an artificial Whale
which is familiar to you
rather than a whaling who can't even hear women.
Of course, I have a trip to the blue sea, too.
Oh, come on!
You're trying to escape by yourself!
I'm coming with you!
Fish on!
-Captain! -Yes, Oryosu!
Too bad. I've caught all the fish that are currently in the club.
I might be a big killer!
You're right. You're all just old ladies.
That's ridiculous! You caught only a woman with 25 points!
Unlike you, I'm not a big fish. If I caught both of them, I'd be in the opposite position.
That's...
A young girl with a strong sense of propriety!
-Yosha, itadakii! -What? I'll catch her!
-Captain, it's my prey! -The fast one wins!
-Are you serious, Oryosu? -Indeed.
If the game has the same prey during battle mode, the one who catches it first will get points.
-You're not confident, Oryosu! -What? I'll catch her first!
-Rua will use a powerful bass bait. -What's a bass bait?
It's a device that makes the lure spin on the surface of the water, and makes the fish excited.
It's a BGM.
-Go! -Go!
-The next day. -The next day.
Lady, would you like to go with me to the National Fair?
No, Lady. I'll go with Odaiba.
I see. What do you want?
I'll give you this watch.
This is a ring of Garche. And...
This is a new Sharanpi song.
How about a drive while listening to the new song?
No! I want to see it!
Drive smoothly!
Sharanpi!
Eh? The BGM is off.
You're quite a drag, Saotome. The tension of the line is severe.
Ah, cut it out! Cut it out! If you get caught, I'll take it!
What the hell!
I did it!
Look! It's 85 points!
Hehehe! What's going on?
-Heh... I won't lose! -Wait, you!
Oh, it's Reiko! I bet she'll get a high score.
I'm sure Reiko will get 100 points.
Good. If I fish for this, the gap will open again.
It's so easy. The more beautiful you are, the more difficult the conditions are.
The weather is rainy and the water is cloudy.
It's okay.
Reiko, the rich man, won't be able to find a luxury car or a branded product.
It's a sure thing to simply attack.
Will it really work out?
Alright!
Yeah!
Reiko!
"I! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Reiko! Whooah!"
This is a fastest race!
It's such a cool feeling.
Reiko!
I love simple presents like this one.
So, where should we go for lunch?
What do you want to eat?
I know, French food would be nice.
Oh, French food.
The shop is in Paris.
Paris?
Are we going to France just for lunch?
French food is the best in France.
What's this?
The thread is getting loose.
It's not getting any closer.
It's not easy to catch a super-big one like Reiko.
What's that?
Maria?
Maria has nothing to do with Reiko.
I know everything about her.
I can easily catch her.
I won't let her make any difference.
Go!
Maria, where are you?
Maria!
wilt state
Maria, would you like to eat this?
This is made by me.
Maria, I am so happy.
I'll save you.
Maria is jealous about me.
She doesn't care about me.
Ugh...
My hands are getting tired...
Uwaaah!
Oh, no! He found me!
Damn it! I was going to a good place, but...
Too bad, Chief.
This way is easier.
Here you go.
Get!
What?
Minus 100 points?
This game machine, Marian, is a man, isn't it?
Hahaha!
You're so stupid, Ryo-tsu!
This is mine!
Ehh...
Watch this!
Come on, come on.
Eat this.
I'll give you all of it for free.
You're so considerate of a gorilla!
Give it to me too!
This is amazing!
What are you doing?
I'm the one who brought the food.
These are all my fish.
Please look for others.
Here you go.
I'm going to eat you now!
Eat my food!
Eat my food.
Damn it.
He's going to turn the tables if I keep this up.
This is amazing.
100 points at once.
What?
Nice Buddy Gal.
Alright, he got it!
It's dirty, Ryo-tsu.
This is my prey.
I'm body-wrecking you.
I'm not getting any more!
You're in trouble.
I did it!
Why did I get minus 50 points?!
No way!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's wrong with you?!
It's killing me...
I'm sorry...
Damn it, I have three minutes left.
I'm gonna lose if I keep this up.
I found a big fish!
Alright, let's go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you wait so long.
Here...
You idiot!
You're not supposed to sneak into a girl's classroom!
I'm really sorry.
It's a draft!
Draw it yourself!
You're lucky to live in a draft.
Shut up!
I've worked as a cop for thirty years.
This is the first time I've ever drawn a draft!
This guy's pretty tough.
Here you go!
Oh, I see.
I see.
How you've suffered.
Are you all kidding?
That old man is crazy.
He's been a fraud-punisher since the moment he built the school library.
You pushed this annoying old man all over me.
Next time on...
Grandpa and the Bomberman!
I'm counting on you!
♪ It's rumored that I'm a girl who can't fall in love ♩
♪ But I have a lot of things to do ♩
♪ But I have a lot of things to do ♫
The changing lady's dream
My love, I'm sorry, wait for me
The future of the panorama
The dazzling light that shines
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me