Japanese presup累
I was looking forward to a day in Nakakawa
If I kick a stone, I could soar
I wonder if I'm going to go to the gym where I was saving money
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
Katsushika is a one-way street with a single grumble
The cityscape is just as gentle
From the waterfront of Tongari-boshi
The sun sets to Taishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
Katsushika
But I lost my happiness again
I realized it
Because I'm an idiot
The stormy baseball tournament
Isn't this Aikawa Yuki?
I'm a big fan
What?
I'm coming to the charity concert at Kameyari Bazaar in two weeks.
Lucky
I got my autograph
I'll get it
That's my senior
Please look at this
What?
You're doing a charity concert at Kameyari Bazaar?
Lucky
What?
I have to come two weeks later?
What do you mean?
What?
I heard that he double-booked the office for misunderstanding.
Kameari Shopping Street and Minami Shopping Street are not very good friends.
What are they going to do?
They are going to settle the score with a soccer game.
A soccer game?
Speaking of which, the people from Kameari Shopping Street were practicing earlier.
What?
Ah, it doesn't matter if I beat one or get to meet Yuki-chan.
No, I can't!
I want to forget that Yuki-chan brought me here.
Hurry!
Is your reservation still okay?
You're welcome.
He picked up the tree.
Kiyohara!
Are you really Kiyohara?
Why are you here?
Actually, my son's classmate's father's,
the president's wife's,
and his grandmother's distant relative
played against Kiyohara in the Little League.
That's why they're helping out the store.
Now he's a member of the shopping street.
I see. I'll do my best in the next match.
I see.
It's obvious that Kiyohara will win.
I'll root for you, president.
I'll ask for your autograph.
Leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you.
What?
It's Kiyohara?
Yes.
I saw it on TV.
Mizuhara is so cowardly.
He's playing baseball and playing baseball.
What's he going to do?
What are you going to do, Ozaki?
He's playing baseball.
He's got no chance of winning.
If he's a substitute, I'm a substitute too.
I can't lose to him in the next match.
Still, he's not a substitute.
I guess there's no one who's good at baseball.
Well, I'll do it.
I don't know how I'm going to win tomorrow.
I must do what I thought was right.
What if Kiyohara does it now?
Yes.
He's a substitute.
Another such a shame.
I never thought I'd be this good at baseball.
He's a substitute?
Next time you come here, this place will be a shame.
He's the only one who can fight against Kiyohara in our town,
with his strong physical strength and life force like a cockroach.
Ryochi Kankichi!
Hey! Go home!
You idiot!
You can't even fight against a member of the Kusaya team!
If we win, we'll be able to see Aikawa Yuki-chan up close.
Even if Minami Shopping Street wins, we'll be able to see her.
I knew it. He's not going to let us win easily.
Let's use our best move.
This is the total amount of debt we owe the shopping street.
You have to pay it back immediately.
You're so annoying! I told you I'd wait for the bonus!
Well, what do you think?
Pay it back now!
That's right!
I get it! I get it!
We can pay it back!
You're going to pay it back, huh?
However, if we win the match, we'll have to pay off all of my debts.
That's the condition.
What?
At least 20%!
No, 50%.
No!
Then 80%!
No, no, no!
What?!
I'm going to pay it back now!
Alright! I'll pay it back!
I understand how you feel about the shopping street being rebuilt.
We're going to do our best for the shop.
Paying off all of our debts.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Um, why am I coming on board?
The traffic in the shopping street is making me worried.
I've never played baseball!
Let's do the game of Aikawa Yukihai-Kameari Shopping Street Versus Kameari Minami Shopping Street!
We'll have a match!
On the first floor,
Kameari Minami Shopping Street.
Number 1,
Carl Lewis,
in Sarashina Soba.
Come on!
Nice!
The superstar of the field,
Carl Lewis!
It wasn't just Kiyohara!
My daughter's friend's cousin
met Carl through the internet.
Hey, come on!
Come on!
Even if 100 meters and running is the best in the world,
baseball is a man of the field!
It's a must!
Nice!
I got it!
What the?
Nice!
Number 2,
Kamiho Date,
This time,
he's a female tennis player!
I wonder if he also knows Mr. Mizuhara.
No, I don't!
Hey!
Don't make fun of a tennis player!
I'll shoot!
Team!
Good! You've won!
This time for sure!
Number 3. The part-time job of the Sekiguchi Kometen. Takanohana.
Takanohana, do your best!
What? There's still more?
Senpai! Look!
That's the professional soccer player, Maezo,
and the professional basketball player, Michael Jordan!
There are only top athletes!
You're so dirty!
You're using a professional player
for a match against a store!
You're breaking the rules!
What are you saying?
We're all people working at the store!
You're not a clerk, Ryo-san.
You're the one who's breaking the rules!
You're making up excuses!
You're the one who's making up excuses!
If you hit your body and make everyone stand up,
I'll shoot you!
Dead Ball!
Oh, it didn't work at all.
I practice hitting my body every day.
Number 4. The part-time job of the Mizuhara Gang. Kiyohara.
Kiyohara, do your best!
Number 5!
Hit me!
Professionals don't use that kind of deep ball!
father!
Son of a bitch!
Four!
Dad!
What's wrong with you?
I've never been so beaten in a single round.
There's too much power difference.
I should quit.
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm in debt.
I can't give up like this.
But, Senpai, look at that.
What?
It's the great league's NOMO.
Honda, even if you die, come out on the ring!
No way...
Grable!
Strike!
Hey, break the hand!
Excuse me.
Hey, hey, that won't make it into the match.
Let's take a break.
Yes, sir.
Come on!
I can shoot with this!
It's a right-mine hit!
Maezono!
What?
That's a right-mine hit!
Oh, no!
I'm...
A home run!
Ha ha.
Ah!
Is that the Bo Takatobi's Bouboo?
No, it isn't.
Out!
Three outs change!
Come on, come on!
Brrr!
NEGGIE!!
Ta-da!
Ha!
Whoa!
♪ ♪
Huh?
Rain?
Listen, it's finally raining now!
This game's over!
What?
What's going to happen?
We win.
Our game's worth 23 points.
What?
Or are we playing
Can we turn the tables?
Let's give up already.
That's right.
We can make another chance to call Yuki-chan.
No!
At this rate, the dream of zero debt will disappear.
Well, the match ends here.
Wait!
The match is still halfway through!
The engine is finally running!
Ryo-san, I understand how you feel, but...
You guys!
You said you would never lose today's match!
Is that what you really wanted?
And the other pro athletes!
You can't say you're a true sportsman if you can't escape this rain!
You're a pro, so you have to fight to see what the conditions are!
What are you talking about?
Think about the situation!
It's okay, Mizuhara-san.
We're also pro athletes.
We have the will to win.
I understand.
Let's do this until the end.
Don't stop no matter what happens!
But if we continue...
No, it's about you.
You might have a plan.
If you're in a bad condition, it's my fault.
For now, let's just run away.
And...
Hurry it up.
If you're in a bad condition, you're no match for me.
What's the time limit?
30 seconds in the air!
Don't give up!
Let's have a look...
If you're faster, we're more than happy!
You're faster, have a proper fight.
You're slow and then you want to miss!
It's the end.
Chisato...
Ah!
Ah! My hand slipped!
What was that?
Of course, it was intentional.
He immediately showed his true power.
What's this?
It's weird.
This skinny...
Turn, turn.
I did it! I got one point back!
I won't lose another point!
A Bunshin Makyu!
Strike, Buster!
It's dirty!
The mud is also thrown up!
Is there any proof that I did it on purpose?
I'm sorry, Kiyohara.
I didn't mean to,
but I'm sorry.
I just got mud on my hand with this rain.
Please forgive me.
Yes, we both have bad conditions.
B...
In this situation,
Senpai is so lively.
Oh, no!
What's going on?
It's not easy to win.
Friends, come here.
Will we be able to win?
We have to win this battle.
Buster...
It's okay.
We won!
After this,
we should work together to turn the situation around.
Right before we leave this mess.
There is no escape.
Please.
Then we'll be able to win.
e...
The end.
Don't be discouraged.
Why?
Yes!
A big storm and a stormy storm warning has just been issued.
If you are in a car, please evacuate to the emergency shelter!
The river is overflowing!
We can't keep on racing!
Let's end this!
If you're okay with losing, then let's end this!
Don't be silly!
We're still winning!
But the game is still on our side.
We've been chasing them up to the third point!
I told you we wouldn't stop the game no matter what!
We're not done yet!
Senior!
Mr. Honma and the others are going to be swept away!
I don't care!
Even if we're not enough for two or one, we can still play baseball!
Hey!
Mr. Honma!
This is a decisive victory!
Please evacuate!
Calm down!
Just move forward!
Help!
Mr. Honma!
We're being swept away!
Save us!
Mr. Honma!
Are you all right?
Mr. Ronda!
Well, I was swept away by the waves on the 8th floor.
Are you still playing baseball?
Help me!
What a bunch of people.
Running in the middle of the night! No, I mean, a swimming home run!
Iwasaki, I'm counting on you!
Yes!
Iwasaki, the best swimmer!
Ronda!
Oh, my God!
I did it! I'm in the top!
Ryo!
It's dangerous there!
Please evacuate immediately!
Don't be silly!
I'm in the top!
I've been chasing you for 15 years!
You can't stop me here!
What?
Help me!
If the pitcher is gone, we win!
I'm still here!
The pitcher has experience in high school.
As expected, you have come out, Kiyohara!
Kiyohara Kiyohara
Ginga!
Gross!
Kiyohara!
Ginga!
I'm here!
Hi!
Kiyohara!
How about you?
Hi!
Mr. Kiyohara!
Kiyohara!
The two directors are being dragged away!
Hurry up and save them!
They're still fighting.
By the way, what happened to the match?
I don't know.
Ryo...
Here I come!
Come at me!
Yaaay!
You fools!
We did it and goodbye!
He really said it. He really did say goodbye to the homerun!
OK, OK. I believe what Ryo said.
So that makes it the final decision for Yukiyuki Aikawa to come to my Kameari Shopping Street.
Wait a minute! There is no one who can prove what Ryo said!
There's no one who can prove Ryosan's home run.
The judges have all been thrown into the 9th floor.
You can't believe what the police officer says.
You're the one who always says not to believe what Ryo says.
My debt is on the line!
It's a big problem!
Thanks to the heavy rain yesterday,
Yuki couldn't come home from school.
Then, what about today's event?
It's the same thing.
Let's go home.
Let's go to work.
Hey, wait!
What about my debt?
Ryosan, I'm sorry, but please forget about this.
No way!
At least 50%...
No, 20% or even 10% is fine.
Please make it cheaper.
The court has been decided on Nakoto,
and he's given his relatives an invitation.
What are you thinking, dad?
Maria!
You're a man!
You can't get married!
You're preparing a parade for the Samba Carnival!
Next time on Dengeki Kekkon!
Ryotsu Kankichi!
See you!
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ It's said that a woman who can't fall in love is a woman who can't fall in love. ♪
♪ There are many things I want to do. ♪
♪ I want to ride a bike through the vast desert. ♪
♪ I want to be more free than a bird. ♪
♪ A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a full moon. ♪
♪ It's my love, sorry, wait. ♪
♪ The brightness of the future in the panorama ♪
♪ You can see it. You can see it. ♪
I was able to get a lot of points.
I'm glad I was able to get a lot of points.