"When you watch TV, please light up the room and look away."
Come over here, you cheap people.
I don't have money either but I'm worried,
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, you jobless one
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
You know what to do, don't you?
If you do, just shut up and follow me!
Teacher!
Teacher is Hachamecha Grandpa!
Dolls?
Yes, the head of the department asked me to deliver 15 of them to the Katsushika office.
Why do I have to do such a troublesome thing?
Ryo-chan, you know a delicious restaurant because Asakusa is your hometown, right?
That's right. The person who gave it to me will also be happy with the name of the restaurant.
You guys are leaving all the troublesome things to me.
Don't you try to make me cry?
Don't say anything and just buy it.
Look, there will be a fish of about 2000 yen.
That is your Oda-chin.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I'll go!
Ryo-chan, when you get Oda-chin, you are different from the way you are.
Senpai's energy source is to earn.
I'll go.
OK.
It's a familiar restaurant, so I just let you lose a lot of money.
It's an unexpected temporary income.
I don't know anything, but I'm just a manager.
The grilled doll looks delicious.
There are only these. I don't know if I can get one or two.
It's delicious!
One more.
Isn't it Kankichi?
What are you doing suddenly?
It's me.
What?
Kankichi.
Did you forget this face?
Oh, it's from elementary school.
That's right. I was a senior in elementary school.
It's nostalgic.
How many years has it been?
Was the teacher still alive?
Of course.
It's just like this.
I think the teacher was quite old at that time.
Yes, this year it will be 90.
90?
I'm 70 or 80 years old.
I'm on the verge of youth now, Kankichi.
How long do you plan to live in youth?
Did you say something?
No, no, I'm fine.
Please stay healthy forever.
By the way, Kankichi.
What kind of work are you doing now?
What kind of work?
As you can see.
I see.
That rascal who always broke something in the classroom.
I feel strange when you say that.
Did you become a stewardess?
What?
Stewardess?
I'm a man.
Are you wearing it properly?
Of course.
Show me.
Can you show me at a place like this?
I can show you.
What?
It's a man's proof.
I'll show you now.
Ouch.
It hurts.
Here.
What is this?
This is my name.
Read it.
"Omagari Daisaku"?
It's a man's name.
I was brought up to be 90 years old.
No matter how old you are, you're still a bad student.
Why did you walk around the store?
I was walking around.
I live in a mansion on Shisago Street.
You live in a mansion in that city?
That's unfair.
I can stay in such a large store for a little while.
What?
Is it eel?
Don't worry.
This is my hometown.
Don't tell me that.
To be continue ...
Damn.
You're good at it.
If so, let me teach you how to have it.
You paid so much.
You didn't say wow to me.
What?
That's why I didn't have the money to treat you.
I can hear your narrative.
What do you have?
I can't hear you.
I don't have enough money to pay you back!
What?
I see, I see.
Sir, two more shirayaki.
What?
I'm telling you, it's not fair.
I said it's not fair! I don't have any money!
How about the temporary income?
Huh?
Or just be a manager?
That's what you heard?
Do you want to eat?
Yes, yes. Sir, beer.
What?
Sir, you're in a bad mood.
You're too good.
What? You're in a bad mood?
Sir, two more shirayaki.
It started again.
Give me the money for that.
Sir, there are many students who have been teaching for a long time.
They make the class hours go by one hour and finish the class early.
They mess up the class lunch.
They try to drink water from the cup in the classroom.
I kept it a secret every time, so it's good.
But I didn't think...
That kid is a police officer.
Sir, let's drink.
Today is my treat.
Oh, it's nostalgic.
Right, right.
Well, even if you grow up to be an adult, you won't forget the old king.
It's gorgeous.
Please order whatever you like.
Damn, I lost.
Thank you.
Oh, it was delicious.
Damn, I spent a lot of money.
Well, sir, I'll have this.
Don't say cold things.
I've been teaching for 30 years like this.
And there was a student like you.
It's not something that happens often like this.
But I have to deliver the doll roast that was asked by the chief.
Oh, doll roast.
That looks delicious.
No, no, no, no.
That's right.
I wasn't good at mathematics.
How's that?
I wonder if I can do it.
What's the sudden question?
There are 15 kids here.
I need some snacks to get through all the kids.
How many are there?
I wonder.
It's a lot.
5 people.
It's possible now.
How many do you want to give them?
I think it's 15.
Then 15 is enough.
No way.
One box is one person.
So, there are 8 in it.
What will you do with the amount Kankichi ate earlier?
Eh?
I will reduce one person's portion.
I know.
If you make one person's portion into 6,
you will have 2 in each.
So, 2 x 15 = 30.
You are more clever than me.
So,
I will take one box from here.
This dollhouse is the best.
Thank you.
It's a good lesson to have.
You are on the right pace.
Today was fun, Kankichi.
See you again.
See you.
What a bad luck.
Oh?
That face.
Yo!
You must be Tompi.
Oh, yes.
You are the maid at elementary school.
Long time no see.
Oh, Mr. Maid.
It's a coincidence.
Is this your shop?
Yes.
You are a well-known person.
I am happy.
I am glad to see you.
I'm looking for experience.
You are all smart.
It's the luckiest are you ever.
But you have great skills.
As your good teacher,
I really like you.
There are about 2000 people in this neighborhood.
After being scolded by his wife, he went out when it was troublesome to cook for himself.
He's been scolded by one of the teachers, so he's been beaten.
But you remember the face of 2000 people.
It's not 90, it's memory power.
I'll pretend not to know even if I meet you from now on.
That's good. If you're on that pace, you'll lose.
It's a scary 90-year-old.
Welcome.
Hello.
I'm Mugitsu. Please come in.
A foreigner?
It's Tachibana's god.
We got married recently.
Where did you meet each other?
In fact, I was at the last year's Asakusa Samba Carnival.
I was pulling the dashi from the god with a horse at the youth conference.
I didn't know that the god of the Gokukuya had a foreign god.
Asakusa is the same.
I've been internationalized.
See you later.
Yes, please do it anytime.
Tompei, Chinkichi, I'm going to drink soon.
Yes.
See you.
I'm here.
I'll take a look at the house.
Oh, there you are.
What?
It's dangerous.
Jump out suddenly.
No, it's Kankichi.
Oh, teacher Omagari.
It's been a while.
I just met him the other day.
Really?
Do you want to talk while drinking?
I can't do it anymore.
Well, where should I go?
No, no, no, no.
I pretended not to hear.
The teacher's house is...
What?
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
Teacher!
Don't scare me.
What are you doing?
Well, what?
What?
Welcome, Mrs. Murasame.
Is there anything good about the obidome?
Obidome?
Yes, sir.
It's beautiful.
It's like a pure white lily if you compare it to a flower.
What?
You have a big head.
You're 90 years old, aren't you?
Are you going to fall in love at that age?
What are you talking about?
Kounosuke Matsushita, who was called the god of business, said,
"Youth is the youth of the heart."
Oh, really?
So, did you confess to him?
That's...
Not yet.
What?
You're not like a teacher.
Why are you afraid of one or two dates?
But...
Look, it's out.
Hurry up and apply for a date.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not ready yet.
It's okay.
Men are shy without saying anything.
Go away.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Mr. Omawari.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
This is good.
It's a good weather.
Yeah, that's right.
I wonder if it's going to work.
Well, then.
Be careful.
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
How was it?
Huh?
Was it no good?
It's a great success.
I made a date.
Oh, my God.
Don't be surprised.
I did it.
But there's only one problem.
What's the problem?
I was lying to you.
Huh?
When I met you before,
I said I had three of the best companies.
What?
Why are you lying to me?
It's just profit.
Please, Kanki.
If this gets out,
I'm going to get hated by Tokiko.
Please do something about it.
Even if you say you're asking me to do it,
I said you applied for a date.
Hey, Kanki.
Please.
I'm going to get hated by Tokiko.
I just thought you'd come.
I just wanted to save me as a donor.
I got you.
Really?
That's great.
Kanki.
This has become a huge mess.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, it's nothing.
I know.
You're going to do something for yourself.
I'm sorry you're telling me to do nothing at all.
No, i'm not.
I told him what you told me to do.
But...
I need to talk to him.
What do you want?
I'm sorry I couldn't park the car.
Pierre.
Huh? Me?
This is the sheep, Pierre.
If you need anything, just say it.
No, no, Pierre.
No, I'm the sheep... No, I'm the sheep, Pierre.
Nice to meet you, my wife.
How funny.
I'm Murasame.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go.
When I think about it, I remember when I was studying in Paris.
I often went on walks in Seine.
In Paris?
You were an artist or something?
Well, that's right.
When I was young, I wanted to make a living by painting.
But my father passed away, so I had to move on.
That's why I came back to Japan.
If I had stayed in Paris at that time...
Nowadays, the world is changing.
I may be getting used to this country.
Haha, but I never had the chance to meet a person as beautiful as you here.
That's how people's destiny works.
You don't have to keep lying about it.
I also remember the gondolas in Venice.
Venice, the city of water.
Ah, the days when I was young.
I'm envious.
How nice. I have never been out of Japan.
If you get on a gondola with someone you love, it will be very romantic.
Of course. Oh, right. This is Pierre.
Hey, Pierre!
Then it's me. Yes, what do you want, sir?
What kind of classic gag are you doing?
Get me a gondola.
Gondola?
It's the same as the one in Sumida River and Venice.
Get me a gondola right away.
What kind of gag are you doing?
It's the same as the one in Sumida River and Venice.
Get me one right away.
All right, sir. I'll get it right away.
Gondola, gondola.
Shaken by the waves, gondola.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
What?
I have to dance with a real man.
Here, two rivers are divided.
Harumen is the other side.
The bridge ahead is the bridge.
Tohiko, look.
It's the Kaji Toki Bridge.
It's nostalgic.
It's been a while since it's opened again.
There's Tokyo Bay.
I smell salt.
It smells like a sea.
Rainbow Bridge.
I've never seen it.
Where are you going? You'll go out into the sea.
Look, I can see it.
It's the TV station I bought last year.
What?
It was cheaper than I thought.
Isn't that right, Pierre?
Yes.
Next, I'll rent Queen Elizabeth and go on a cruise to Tokyo.
A cruise to Tokyo?
But I want to go on a cruise to Tokyo.
I see.
Pierre, get me a carriage.
A carriage?
What?
You mean the carriage we used at the Sanba Carnival?
You mean the stock?
Yes, I think I got it at the Youth Conference.
Where is it?
It's probably in the warehouse.
Alright, show me the way.
The store...
Leave it to God.
But...
Don't worry.
Here we go.
Hold on tight.
I'm counting on you, Pierre.
There!
Pierre, don't fly so far.
Tokiko is scared.
I got it, sir.
I'm Kabukiza.
Let's go see Kabuki next time.
Okay.
If we go on a cruise to Yamamoto at this speed, the sun will set.
We have to be horses, not turtles.
I really had a great time today.
I'm glad you were happy.
It was really fun.
Tokiko?
Yes?
I...
Um...
How are you feeling about me?
I think you're a very nice person.
Eh?
So...
Tokiko?
I...
I'm too late.
Eh?
I'm not.
I…
I don't…
I...
I'm not.
I don't see anything.
It's just a…
A super deep pit.
Almost frozen.
It's so deep, it's too strong.
It's just like a rock to me.
I don't even have a even weigh.
I'm just like a clay.
Like...?
I want you to collect all the money.
But, Senpai...
I'll talk about it later.
I'm in a situation where I don't know if I can get the best happiness in my life or fall into a pit of misfortune.
I'm begging you to do something!
I understand. I'll try to do it.
Yes.
I'm a good person, too.
It doesn't cost a penny, but why do I have to suffer so much?
Tokiko, I'll make a miracle happen.
So, so, I...
I'm happy to hear that, but it's impossible for you to do that.
No, there's nothing I can't do.
What do you mean, "I"?
I...
I don't measure the value of that person with money or social status.
Tokiko...
There are some people who can be respected even if they don't have much.
There are people who are admired by people even if they don't have much.
I think that kind of person is the best.
I...
Tokiko, I'm sorry.
Omagari, what are you...
I lied to you.
I lied about running a large company.
I'm the worst man.
Please stand up.
I've tried to be loved by you somehow,
but I'm much more than your pure heart.
I'm a narrow-sighted man.
Please raise your face.
I knew it from the start.
Then,
Then you knew it was a lie and went out with him?
I'm embarrassed.
But I lied to a lie.
I'm not good enough for you.
Thank you for your trouble.
Mr. Omagari, please wait. I...
Sensei! No, Mr. Owner!
Kankichi, it's okay.
I took care of you today.
Sensei, don't say that. Please wait a little longer.
I'm Ryotsu, a teacher at a elementary school where Mr. Omagari worked.
You were a teacher at a school?
Yes, but now I'm a man who is obsessed with those teachers.
You're not like your usual teacher.
Please be more confident.
Kankichi!
Here he comes.
Sensei!
Mr. Omagari!
Everyone!
Even them...
Yes, everyone is his teacher.
These people live next door, and they're cheeky to Mr. Omagari.
Mr. Omagari!
Susuman...
We're all looking forward to meeting him from time to time and having some food.
That's right.
Sensei was so much loved by everyone.
It's wonderful.
Oh my!
Hey! Oh my!
Oh, I see!
That's right! A miracle happened!
Kankichi, did you do this?
It's a miracle, Sensei!
Sensei, a miracle will happen!
Let's make a miracle happen too!
No, I don't...
Mr. Omagari!
I was just about to say it, but...
I was happy to hear that you were willing to do something for me even though you lied.
Mr. Tokiko, will you forgive me then?
Yes, if you don't mind being such an old lady, I'll go out with you.
Mr. Tokiko!
Banza!
Hey, Flan!
You're too old!
Idiots!
The snow's not cleaning up the area today, and the traffic is in a big mess!
It's this heat! If you leave it alone, it'll melt away!
Idiots!
What?
Look!
What is it?
This will clean up all the snow!
What?
Don't come back until it's cleaned up!
You're a jerk!
It's impossible to keep it clean!
Yeah!
Welcome to my house!
I say, "Welcome to my house!"
Welcome!
Ah, that's right.
Do you have California Macchi?
California Macchi no yo.
This is not America.
Sorry.
Um, well, excuse me.
Hi, what's up?
Then, Kushiage, Kakiage, Katsuage, whatever, Ageage, what was it again?
What do you recommend?
Just be careful with Katsuage.
Oh, that's my father's gag.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I have no idea either.
Huh, huh, huh?
Seriously?
Welcome.
Welcome!
Where am I? What am I doing here?
Who am I?
I don't remember at all!
By the way, why do I call myself "I"?
Someone, please tell me!
Next time, "Who am I?"
See you!
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!