『Fantastic Girl』
中川に浮かぶ 夕日をめがけて 中川に浮かぶ 夕日をめがけて
砥石を蹴ったら 靴まで飛んで 砥石を蹴ったら 靴まで飛んで
居たすけど 辿り着くのかしらに 居たすけど 辿り着くのかしらに
楽器のまんまだと 笑われたのさ
どっかに元気をクコとしても ぶつしくためあり 悪夢も非常
違わらない街並みが 妙にやさしいよ
トンガリ帽子のシュ geldiと バラバラと
トンガリ帽子のシュasmaと
From the east to the west, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness because I was happy
I realized I was stupid
Yay! Meichu!
Okay, let's go!
Yeah!
The children just now didn't have a ghost competition.
They're not interested in anything.
Yeah, that's right.
The children who are used to the recent movie SFX
They laugh at the first one.
What is that SF something?
There's something special about it.
Don't put seeds here, Ryo.
But when we were children, we were looking forward to the ghost competition and the test of the liver.
We're going to the shopping street.
I wonder if the traditional events of the past are also abandoned.
I feel lonely.
In short, there are two.
As long as there are some tricks that make the children happy.
Do you have any other ideas?
Well, it's impossible if you leave it to me.
How about it?
Can't you give me all the sales of the stalls at the shopping street?
Idiot!
It hurts, this bastard!
Chief!
Good guy!
Are you going to make money to help the citizens?
You idiot!
Come on!
Chief!
Why are you so angry?
I bought it at this sports exhibition for the sake of my subordinates who are burning.
Yeah, yeah.
The citizens are free to give it to them.
It's our job!
Do you understand, Ryo?
I got it.
Yes!
I can't believe I'm just working in this hot weather.
And I don't think the modern children are surprised by the first child.
Don't worry.
Leave me alone.
I have confidence in my make-up.
This is the latest special make-up material from Hollywood.
The result will be surprisingly realistic.
Well, let's get started.
Yeah, whatever you say.
The ingredients you need are:
cast iron, silicon and foam latex.
Let's make them.
First, apply silicon to the face to remove the mold.
Next, apply cast iron and silicon to the face.
Make a mold and then make the face of the first kid with clay.
Then take the mold out of the mold and throw away the unnecessary clay inside.
Next, make sure to mix the latex foam well to make it even.
After filling the mold with the latex foam, bake it slowly in the oven.
It looks like you're making a cake.
When you open the mold, it's done.
All you have to do is to stick the glue and paint it.
That's all.
It's easy, so please try making it.
The end.
It's pretty realistic.
All right, I'll try to scare the chief.
I'm home.
Who are you?
You are...
You're a loser!
Stop it! It's me!
I'm your cute subordinate, Ryo-tsu!
You're not getting away with this!
Chief, that's really Ryo-chan!
Reiko made a special make-up!
I can't believe it!
Really?
Please take a look.
It's over there!
What?
It's a 5-yen coin.
Well, I'll take this.
No doubt.
That's why I said it.
My head is spinning.
What are you doing?
I'm going to the ghost festival tonight.
I don't really want to do it, but I'm wearing this.
Don't get too close.
I'm sorry.
Senior, I have to go to the venue soon.
Is it that late?
Are you going to go like that?
I'll drive you there.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to get in trouble.
Hey, are you okay?
Did you notice me?
Ryo-chan, go ahead.
What?
Look!
That's Mr. Nakagawa's Ferrari!
Really?
Yes.
I'm so lucky!
Let's go drive it together!
Let's do that!
Mr. Nakagawa!
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
It's a 5-yen coin.
Let's win!
It's a 5-yen coin!
Mr. Nakagawa, please stop messing around.
They just called me.
I'm going to look around.
Wait a second, please.
All right.
Until you arrive, go back to bed.
Oh!
Oh, no!
I didn't think I'd get a Ferrari.
I'm sure it'll sell well.
I think I heard a moan.
I'm starting to feel bad.
The driving is rough.
Idiot!
What was that?
I saw something weird.
What is it?
Who are you?
Are you a car thief?
Hey, car thief!
Don't let me get away!
Don't catch me!
Help!
Help me!
I got it.
What?
I got it!
Don't leave me!
Damn it!
You stole my property!
I have to hurry.
The ghost competition is about to start.
It's closed.
I'm coming!
I made it.
Did I have any change?
I've been collecting my money since last time.
Is that it?
I can't believe it.
No.
I made a ghost.
If you break the rules in town,
you'll be punished by the president.
But no.
We need to...
You... you...
You can't take that!
There he is!
G-gosh!
Geeeees!
This is bad! If I get caught, I'll be caught too!
Yellow, orange, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue...
It's over!
Let's try it again!
You monster! You can't run away!
Hurry up!
Get out of here!
You monsters!
Stop resisting and come down!
Hey! Where are you?
Hey!
I managed to escape.
What should I do now?
Taxi? I can't help it.
I'll try going back and forth.
Hey, driver, don't be surprised.
What is it?
See?
But if you look at this, you can tell it's makeup.
Everyone's in a hurry.
I'm glad you're a good driver.
Which one?
I'll take you to Manpuku-ji.
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm late.
I'm so tired.
It's over, isn't it?
What? What's that taxi?
I haven't paid money and it's already gone.
Never mind.
I'll just look around.
It's so dark you can't see my feet well.
I don't know who it is, but I'm curious.
Oh, sorry for being late.
Who are you?
Oh, you're the old lady from the candy shop.
You're wearing such a thick makeup, I can't see your face.
Ura-meshi...
Hmm?
Your hands are a little different, aren't they?
About this much?
Ura-meshi...
Oh, you're a person who likes to participate in the competition, too.
That's the way it is.
Oh, come on, come on.
Everyone has a great makeup.
I don't think it's a competition for a gift at a shopping street.
Okay, I'll hide over there.
I'll scare you a lot.
See you.
I'll get rid of you right away.
Where were you last night?
That's my line.
I've been waiting for you all the time.
But no one came.
What?
Manpukuji?
Ryo, the ghost festival was not called Manpukuji but Bunpukuji.
What?
You're lying!
I'm not lying.
Look, it says it here.
What?
Huh?
It's true.
But I've met other ghosts.
Manpukuji is a temple, and there's no one there.
What?
Then I've met one.
I don't think you can say you've met a real ghost.
You can't say you've met a real ghost.
They're too realistic to be a group of people from a shopping street.
No way.
There's no way a ghost exists in this modern science.
Stop it, Ryotsu!
I'm late, so I can't lie about it.
Oh, there was a ghost festival yesterday.
What?
You're not lying, are you?
No, I'm not.
But what I said is true.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
There's no way a ghost exists.
If there really is a ghost, I'd like to pay for it.
Huh?
I see.
If we use those ghosts...
Well, well, welcome.
120% fear.
We can shake hands with everyone.
It's a game that doesn't wait!
Thank you!
Hey!
Here's the entrance!
And there's a two-shot camera that can take photos of ghosts.
Let's take a picture!
My sis will be at the rice paddler's tomorrow.
Hey!
As you said, it's a little dark outside.
Maybe that's why we need these three ghosts?
23 ...
24 ...
Y-you're the one who's scary!
You're not the one who's scary!
It's me!
The first kid you saw yesterday!
But...
You were putting on makeup for a special show!
See, that's him.
Guys, come over here!
Jake!
Come on!
"I'm sorry, I thought you were human."
"I thought you were just a friend."
"I don't want to!"
"Why are you guys standing here? You're a ghost!"
"If you have time, why don't you go out and scare people?"
"But, you know, these days, wherever I go, it's bright even at night."
"I can't stand behind those who play mobile phone games or play games."
"I can't even notice them."
"You're too stimulating."
"Really, this is going to make my business go up, right?"
"I'm sorry."
"Oh, you're pathetic, I'm Sueda, but you guys are still ghosts."
"You know, ghosts are scary and mean."
"I'm sorry."
"Okay, from now on, I'll train you to be a ghost and not be embarrassed."
"Okay?"
"But..."
"Do you have a problem?"
"No."
"Okay."
"My eyes are spinning."
"I'm going to wait for you."
"Don't look at me, you idiot!"
"One, two, three, four..."
"Four, four, four?"
"You idiot, I can't do four!"
"There's no way you can do it!"
"Five, six, seven, eight..."
"Five, six, seven, nine..."
"You idiot. Fives..."
"Five, six, seven,"
"Five, six, eight, nine, ten..."
"Five, six, seven, point."
"Five, six, seven, two..."
"Five, six, seven, one..."
" eternally."
"Five, six, seven,"
"Five, six, seven, two.
" purpose?"
"Five, six, seven, nine?"
The first stage of the game.
500 times in a row!
I can't do it anymore...
Shut up! Do the Kuchiko-Tensetsu!
It's finally time for tomorrow's night's party.
The Okuman Chouja is right in front of us.
Huh? Ryo-chan?
Ryo-chan?
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
You look pale.
Are you sick?
I'm fine.
I'm not sick, but...
You're not sick, but...
Really? You look very pale.
Besides, you left half of the katsudon.
You're eating katsudon and ramen and yakisoba, aren't you?
I sometimes eat tandoori, too.
What? I just don't have the energy for food.
I just don't have the energy for food.
It's hot every day.
I guess you should talk to the director.
It's...
Anyway, today is the first day tomorrow.
Right. I should go with him.
Yes.
Listen, it's the first day tomorrow.
We will show you what you've learned.
Today is the last day and we'll be harsh.
It's... it's the real ghost.
That's a ghost!
What Ryo-chan said was true.
Senpai is possessed by a ghost.
He might get killed by this.
What should we do?
What did you say? I'm possessed by a ghost?
Yes.
That face already has a secret.
Secret?
If you go to the ghost tonight,
you'll be killed for sure.
This is bad.
If the plan is revealed here,
Motomoko will be gone.
You have no idea what he's talking about!
You idiot!
Our Gachon Temple has a good evil spirit.
That's right.
Listen to me, Ryotsu.
It's for your own good.
No matter how much you hate it,
you can't abandon it.
As your superior, as a man,
I will protect you.
No.
Today is an important day.
I have to go.
Everyone, get in the car!
What are you doing?
You pervert!
You're a bad boy!
What are you going to do with a man?
I'm going to spell the spell of the devil.
You're so annoying.
Stop it!
Be quiet.
You can't spell it well
unless you're focused.
Well...
Don't look up the characters!
What is it?
Hear my spell.
I'll show you how I spell magic.
I'll do it.
I'll give this spell.
Who's trying to make an excellent monster?
I'll give them all a spell of terrible evils.
I'll use magic to Peters.
I'll give it a spell that cubes,
so you don't have to watch the game anymore.
I'll just do what he's doing.
Gachon.
I had no other way.
Gachon, Gachon.
Pay for this.
♪!#$%#&&'&#&#'&#!
♪!#$%#&&&#'&#!
♪!#$%#& &&#!
Hold on, Ryosu!
♪!#$%#&&&&#!
Kue Kue!
Shai-ya Shai-ya-cho-wa-no
Kue Kue Kue!
Gachon! Gachon!
It's here!
Gachon!
Gachon! Gachon!
The evil spirit has been destroyed!
How could you do this?
I've borrowed all the money from the haunted house!
Senpai!
Wait! Senpai!
Oh, so you guys came to pick me up?
Alright, alright.
Senpai. Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan, come back!
Alright, let's head straight to the venue!
S-save me!
That person is scary.
Wh-what?
What's going on?
That person is not scary!
Um, we came to refuse this job.
I know you're working hard, Ryo-san.
But we're not coming with you.
I'm really, really tired.
Then you guys must be stuck with Ryo-san.
No, no.
He's the one who's stuck with us.
He's the one who's the real king of money.
What?
What are you going to do with the $122,500 I borrowed?
I'm going to get fired!
Wha-what?
Wait, you radish rascal!
Ryo-chan!
I'm going to get fired!
Speaking of!
The patient I called at the market at midnight
was the classic beauty driver
Maria's mother!
Is he that Honzaraya's daughter-in-law?
Even if the agency approves,
Ryo and Kan-kichi won't forgive!
Next episode: Bossy Lady is Super Intoxicating!
Y-Yes, sir!
♪ It's rumored that I'm a woman who can't fall in love ♩
♪ But I have so many things I want to do ♩
♪ I have so many things I want to do ♩
♪ I want to ride in the huge desert with my motorcycle ♩
♪ I want to be freer than a bird ♩
♪ A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a telescope ♩
♪ It's love ♩
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♩
♪ The future of the panorama ♩
♪ The dazzling light that dives ♩
♪ You understand, right? ♩
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♩
"It's nice to meet you, really."