Translation by Releska
"Nagakawa ni ukabu yuuhi wo megakete"
I kicked the pebbles and I flew to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym I used to save money
I was laughed at for being a coward
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win
The cityscape that doesn't change even one of the bad things is strangely gentle
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
I'm going to the taishakuten
The sunset is falling
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness in Katsushika and Shibamata
I realized
I'm such a fool
I don't want to change
I heard there was a car operation there
That's the director
It's not like that
How's the cake?
Not bad
It's not bad.
Please do your best to keep the fire burning.
Thank you.
What's this line?
What do you think?
Ohara.
Yes, I'm listening.
Excuse me, what is this line?
It's a cheap program.
It's a picture of a favorite idol.
I'm going to take a picture with Nagase.
What?
Is it a picture of a favorite idol?
What? A picture of a favorite idol?
Yes, it's a picture of a favorite idol.
It's also the latest model that can take a picture with five idols.
Oh, a picture with an idol.
It's a picture of a favorite idol.
I can take a picture with Ryouko Suihiro.
That's right, president.
I can take a picture with Aurore Teruyo.
Oh, a picture of a favorite idol.
Oharu, president.
Are you going?
Yes, I am.
I'm going.
Oh, there's only half a minute.
It's a picture of a favorite idol.
I want to eat a food of color.
I have to take a picture of it.
You're welcome.
How do you use it?
It's my first time.
It's easy.
Stand in front of the machine, choose your favorite frame.
And your name is?
I'm Suihiro Ryoko.
I'm Orore Teruyo.
That's Suihiro.
Ryos!
Chief and Boss!
What are you doing?
What?
Can you do that kind of work during working hours?
Well, that's...
We want to experience what it's like to be young.
That's right!
What are you doing?
That's...
It's a public service.
You go to work for the public every day, don't you?
Oh, a public service?
That's right.
Then you should pay me.
What?
I said that I could take a picture with an idol.
I'm sure you've got permission from the agency.
Well, that's...
Not yet.
That's nonsense!
That's illegal.
If you take that, I'll arrest you.
Everyone, this program is free from now on.
Even if you pay me, I'll give you money.
Oh, you're not giving me anything.
I'm here to careful.
Oh, you're here to careful.
I'm going to make some trouble.
I have to use the public service.
Oh, the public service?
You're going to leave yoursleves behind, right?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Have a good day.
Bye.
Hehehe...
I'll revenge.
Even if it's the chief or the chief,
I won't let this grudge last!
So, I feel like I'm ten years younger now.
And this is the "Purikura" I got at that time.
The chief and the chief are so cute!
Really?
Hehehe...
Look at this.
I'll make a picture of them in the "Purikura"
and post it everywhere.
I know, I know.
I was surprised by that popularity.
I'll go to the library.
Yes, sir!
Alright.
You're not going to take a picture of me, are you?
Turn around, turn around!
You!
There's a place on the right, on the second street.
Thank you very much.
See you.
Ouch!
This time...
...is my chance!
Oh, there's a lot.
Here, let me help you.
Sorry.
What?
This is it.
Let me explain.
What appeared beyond the wall is a spy scope, right?
The outside view is reflected in the mirror inside.
If you attach this in front of the digital camera,
the chief's stupid face can be taken.
Hehehe...
This is perfect.
What's this?
This is in the way.
You idiot!
Stop it, you idiot!
Hey!
Are you alright?
I'm fine!
This time...
...um...
Oh?
Oh, it's a spy!
It's a spy!
Hey!
The spy has appeared!
It's a spy!
What's wrong?
That's a spy?
It's a spy that can be Academ skipping me?
There's not enough.
No more.
I've learned.
I don't believe you.
It hurts.
What? What? What?
Now it's OK.
I'll let you know what will happen if you make me angry.
I'm hungry.
Who is it? Who did this?
What is this, boss?
I don't know. I don't know, Jimmy.
I'm hungry.
Who did this?
You don't remember taking this photo, do you?
Of course not. I've never done anything like this before.
I see. I see. I see.
What? Really?
Look. Look at these two faces.
No, no. They look exactly the same.
This is a composite photo.
A composite photo?
This is a trick to take a composite photo with an idol.
That's their trick.
Damn it.
Prepare yourself, Ryosu.
What do they look like now?
Look at them.
Where should I put the rest?
I'll put this on.
Bastard.
Give it to me.
Not just anybody, but me, too.
Here.
Say, "Heave ho!"
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Double-cross?
Heave-ho.
Neru.
Thank you.
I can get two.
Are you serious?
My boyfriend was really worried about me.
Are you sure?
He's so crazy about me!
Work is done!
Br Forever: Congratulations young
Br Forever: Good work and please keep working hard
Maaf
Why you guys are always so mean?
Episode 1: The
Hey, did you hear about the Puri-Kura incident?
That's terrible.
That's also the work of the primitive people, right?
Who are the primitive people?
Oh, you're doing the poll again.
Huh?
A poll for the police in the 23rd district of Tokyo?
The poll for the police in the 23rd district of Tokyo?
The man who doesn't want to marry is the first to enter the first place, Ryo Tsukankichi!
It's a great top again.
And the difference between the second place is spreading.
I didn't get to see the Ogeretsu seal the other day.
That's right.
Mr. Honda!
What's wrong with you?
Do you have a problem with me?
But look at that.
I'm ranked 7th in the Worst.
That's right.
Hahaha!
You're as unpopular as me, aren't you?
Come on, let's do it!
No, I'm not.
I was hated just because I was good friends with my seniors.
Hmm?
Come to think of it, you were completely out of rank last time.
Tch!
Huh?
Wow!
What are you doing?
You bastard!
It's a good time!
It's not a good time!
Huh?
You guys did it anyway, right?
I can't stand it!
What kind of guy is he?
Wait a minute.
I'll show you the proof.
How long are you going to keep me waiting?
Tch!
Ah!
How is it?
It's still this time.
The man I don't want to marry, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The reason is, he's mean, vulgar, and I hate his face.
The man I don't want to marry, that's Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The reason is, he's a human.
So, Ryo-tsu Kankichi, do you know what you're doing?
The man I don't want to marry.
Yes, I'm going to marry him!
No!
Wait!
Can you see?
Don't worry, I'll tell the director.
Just do it.
Katsuo, are you okay?
That's it!
Sir.
I can't believe it.
I don't know who you are.
I just wanted to make sure I was sure that I was up at the right time.
I don't know you.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, I don't know.
The president named me either.
Nobody told me about it.
There's also a game contest.
The first one is the computer game that my senior wanted,
Fight the P...
What? Is that true?
Of course it is.
It's you again.
I'm sorry.
I can't invite you.
Anyway, Reiko,
I wonder if you have any ideas.
I'm not sure about the event.
It's just a karaoke and a game contest.
I see.
I think Ryo is the best at this kind of thing.
What?
What's with that look?
Ryo, do you have any good ideas?
Who's doing this for you?
Senior, you should have a good time here.
You can have a feast.
By the way, I'm in a bad condition because of the Pricula.
I have a chance to eat.
The game software is also attractive.
How about a firefly show with your fiancé?
What?
Firefly show?
Firefly?
In this season?
I have some friends.
I can get about 50 fireflies.
That's great.
Let's go.
The moon and fireflies are romantic.
But...
If you invite such primitive people,
they will be so happy.
It's okay to talk about fireflies.
And Ryo is strong.
If I invite you,
the preparation of the party will be very helpful.
Hmm...
In exchange, if you can't eat fireflies,
I will go home soon.
Let's shoot them together.
What?
Have some fun!
Come on, go for it.
Come on, good boy.
And now I'm gonna have a dinner party.
I don't think you can really do something like that.
Then I'm gonna work hard.
This is so cool, I can't believe it's working.
Okay, then I'll go to the firefly.
I'm so sorry.
Ryo, come on.
Hey!
It's your turn now.
Goodbye.
What?
This isn't the party!
Huh?
I'm not joking!
What are you talking about?
I already paid the fire bill!
Hey!
You just said it was canceled!
What's wrong?
Komachi and Naoko haven't come back yet.
They didn't respond to me, no matter how much I called them.
They were acting weird, so I thought I'd go look for them.
I see.
Did something happen?
Do you have any idea?
By the way, a car from the
What kind of car?
I think it's a Knight Rider.
Knight Rider?
They're bad guys with a badge.
Come on, Honza!
Oh, no!
I'm counting on you, Honza!
Leave it to me!
Are you okay?
If there's a Knight Rider involved, there are more than 100 people.
What?
I'm sorry.
Honza, do you know where they're going to get away with this?
Take care of those guys and let them go!
Hey!
You didn't pay for that.
You bastard!
What did you do that for?
What are you doing, regimes?
No, no.
You can't do that.
Hey.
You're so annoying, Ama!
I'll teach you a lesson about how to fight us!
Hey, bring her here!
Do you know who this guy is?
I'll use this to seal your nude and get you out of town!
No!
Come on!
Come on, pull her back!
Who are you?
Looks like you made it in time.
Mr. Genji!
You're my friend? Get him!
Is that all you've got?
Honda!
No need to hold back!
Just go at it!
Get him!
We've got pretty much everything.
Now, what do you want to do?!
Damn you!
This is what I'll do!
Komachi!
You!
Get out of my way!
Shut up, you coward!
You're so mean!
I can't even talk to you, you know.
What the hell are you talking about?
Don't underestimate me!
I'm gonna do it!
You idiot!
You came all the way here,
and there's no escape!
Move, Komachi!
Komachi!
Go away!
I'm not...
Who are you, Chyurepi...
Hey, stop...
Stop!
Stop, why?
What's going on?
Don't, don't! Smile more!
Here, butter.
Listen, you guys.
If you do anything this time, I'll give this sticker to the rioters all over the country!
That's all we need!
I'm surprised!
He defeated dozens of people by himself!
He'd be a good example in such a situation!
I've looked him over.
I'm impressed by his wildness.
Yeah, he's kind when he's married.
He's better than a weak person.
Ryo seems to have gained a lot of weight.
Yeah.
48, 49, 50.
Okay, I'll give you 50.
A firefly in this season.
Can you give me that firefly?
I'm not kidding.
I got it tonight because I needed it.
I'm not saying it's free.
One.
1,000 yen per one.
No, 2,000 yen.
What should I do with it?
3,000 yen!
Plus consumption!
I won!
You sold it!
At last, I've earned 157,500 yen.
But I don't know how I'm going to fool Mikai.
I see.
Ryo-chan, you're late.
Yeah, I'm late.
You're here at last.
Hurry up, Ryo-tsu.
The chief came to see the firefly.
Well, well, Ohara-kun.
Yes, yes.
Don't rush.
It's beautiful.
It's romantic.
We've been misunderstanding you.
I'm sorry.
As long as you understand.
That's weird.
This firefly doesn't blink at all.
You're right.
Ryo-kun.
Gen-chan, look.
Look, isn't it beautiful?
It's a cockroach!
What?
It's a bug!
It's painted with fluorescent paint.
Hey, Ryo-kun.
What?
Wow.
I'm a little scared.
Are you in danger?
It strange.
Ryo-chan.
W, what!
What?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Ah, no!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh!
If it's a cockroach and a firefly,
that won't change much, does it?
Seem to be a peace of mind.
Hey, hey, old man! What kind of flashy life are you living?
You're eating such a greasy thing!
It's already 106, right?
Even if you think a little about your age and come to the second challenge, I don't know!
Next time, "Sakuretsu Old Man Power"!
Thank you!
♪ You can see the brightness, right? ♪
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♪