Seed
make the room a bit lighter and let's get away from each other
Necklace
That's what I'll say
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be all right
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Come to me if you don't have a job
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, there's a burning dragonfly
I'm sure it'll be all right
You got it?
You got it, you got it!
If you got it, then keep quiet and follow me!
W-What's with the real thing?
What are you talking about?
Yes. On the day of the Hina Festival on March 3
We will make an actual Hina doll and display it at a nearby cats' park
I see
The picture will be broadcast on TV all over the country
It will become a huge image of the cats' park
But if we want to make a set of the human size
It will take a lot of work
Don't worry, O-Hara-kun
I have one in my book.
Oh?
A man who is only useful at this time.
"Hina Sanzan's Birthday"
What?
You want me to hold a Hina festival?
On March 3rd?
It's the director's order.
You're good at this, aren't you?
There's a TV broadcast, too.
You have to do it well.
Wait, director.
I can't hold it for March 3rd.
This is the director's order.
And he said he would allow other tasks.
Then at least make the Hina festival on March 2nd.
It doesn't matter if it's on the 4th.
What do you mean?
The Hina festival has been decided on March 3rd.
Director!
If you fail and embarrass the whole country,
you won't get a bonus.
Hello!
Ryo-chan.
Senior.
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
You don't want to make Hina dolls?
No, I don't, Tenai-san.
If it's March 3rd...
What?
March 3rd.
If you say that, it's something.
It seems...
It's my birthday.
Oh, I see. Ryo-san, March 3rd was your birthday, right?
You were born on the day of the Hina festival, right?
On the day of the girls!
Shut up!
By the way, I don't remember having a good day on my birthday.
For some reason, I have a sad day every year.
I was mistaken for a mobile unit and was put together with a hellish Moutoku.
Before I knew it, I was taken to the North Pole and fought against a Shirokuba.
And there was a time when a tank came down from the sky!
March 3rd is the biggest holiday for me.
You're right.
I thought I'd sleep at home for a day so that nothing would happen this time.
I can't refuse the order from the director.
You're so selfish.
What's that?
Hmm?
Oh, Ryo and Kanchi!
You're acting like a bad guy again, aren't you?
No, it's the director's order.
I heard you're going to make a doll for the Hina festival.
Yeah, I'll ask you to help me.
But you have a bad jinx on March 3rd.
Yeah, so I'm going to finish it by March 2nd and take a day off.
It's a good chance to be on TV.
Too bad.
I'm sorry, but I'll watch it on TV at home.
I'm going to die.
Ryo, you too!
Senpai!
Ryo!
Are you okay?
Ah, it's nothing serious.
I'm so glad.
But you're not even cold.
No way.
No?
No, it's just-
What should I do?
I'm scared.
It was someone's fault.
I'm sorry.
Bwahahahaha!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
That hurt!
Hey!
Ouch!
Aaaaaaah!
What, I'm stuck.
What are you doing?
Huh? The power's out?
Yuzu!
Senpai!
You! Are you trying to kill me?!
The End
Senpai! You're hurt!
Ryo-chan!
It's just a bruise.
The misfortune that should have come on the 3rd of March is coming at me.
No way...
Can you think of anything else?!
You're just standing there with your eyes closed!
Seki! Seki!
What's with you?!
Yuzuka!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
It's gonna sting! It's gonna sting!
Senpai!
You're right.
It's a series of bruises.
Poor thing...
How about we have you pay for it?
That's right! Let's have you pay for it!
We have a good reputation for having a great arm!
That priest of mine is sitting next to us.
Yeah...
I see...
Paying for it, huh...
Huh?!
Mie?!
You know the cause of my misfortune?
Huh?!
The cause of your misfortune on the 3rd of March.
It's all because of the cursed doll!
Cursed doll...
You mean the cursed doll?!
You! You must have done something terrible to a Hina doll in the past!
Hmm... I have... I don't have...
Ah! That's right, you have!
That was when I was still in elementary school.
I went to a place where the same class girls were having a Hina festival...
...and challenged a Hina doll in the GI Hall.
I had my opponent annihilated.
There's no doubt about that.
-That's right. -I knew it!
The Hina doll, who suffered a terrible blow, resented that...
...and took revenge on you on March 3.
This year, you have forgotten about the old blow...
...and are trying to make a Hina doll. That's why they're angry.
You know that?
The Tōnins said so.
Hey, do something!
Don't be so flustered! I'm a professional! Leave it to me!
Oh, how was it? Did you finish the cleaning?
Yeah, it was perfect.
I think so, but...
I don't know yet. I don't want to see the work actually resumed.
Let's start!
Huh?
Let's knock on this guy first.
Oh! I got 500 yen!
Hey! You're lucky, Ryōtsu!
You got paid well, didn't you?
No, I don't know yet.
Something terrible might happen after this.
It's empty.
Oh!
It's Hercules the Hedgehog!
Wow!
I don't have money!
I got some, Ryōtsu!
No, you haven't.
Look at this!
It's for you!
Just for you.
This is the Tiger戦車 you sent me!
So, I got the price for a magazine I sent you now!
Wow, there you are!
Yeah!
Did you do your cleaning?
I guess so.
That's right!
That's great.
Yay! Yay!
And with that, we bid farewell to the 3rd of March!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
There's nothing else I've read about you.
I'd like you two to host the festival of the real things.
Eh?
Us?
You two represent our school.
Please join us.
Please, I beg you.
I don't mind, but...
Me neither.
I see.
Well then, let's get dressed.
Wait a minute.
What is it, Reiko?
I have a suggestion.
A suggestion?
I think it's around here.
Ah, there it is.
I have to use real sake for my rice wine.
What?
You're giving the rice wine to the director?
Hm?
Yes, he's the most important person in this festival.
Hmm, but I don't know if the world will approve of him as the director.
The 3rd of March is my senior's birthday.
So if I give him a birthday present...
That's right.
Everyone will approve.
I'd like to do the same.
Please, President.
Hmm.
Got it.
If you're going to say that, then I'll do it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure Ryo-chan will be happy.
Me being the director?
Not bad.
Huh?
That's right.
Why don't you keep this a secret from Ryo-chan?
Let's announce it the day after and surprise her.
Hehehe.
As soon as I finished the cleaning, I got lucky.
I was
What's that?
It's not a bad idea.
I was impressed by the way it was made.
It's good.
Trash.
You're looking for girls?
Yeah.
It seems that you are making a doll.
Boys!
I will measure the size, so come!
Yeah!
Yes!
Hmm. Finally, my agent's costume.
Yes Yes!
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
What?
What does that mean?
Hello, I'm from the TV station.
I said that I would like to make a doll as a woman as possible.
The five-person forest is a man!
I said to make it a woman.
What about the minister and the minister?
I also said to make it a woman.
Anyway, it's a request to make everyone a woman.
What is that?
What does that mean?
The minister should have decided with me.
Then why did you call us?
That's right!
I called you because I thought you would be sorry if you didn't appear on TV at all.
How?
This is...
You have to paint your face three colors.
Ah, ah, ah!
Pea flower.
Daidai.
What is this?
You want me to show my womanly appearance to the whole of Japan?
That's too much!
Oh, you're so noisy.
I got it.
Then, I'll make you a five-person forest.
It hasn't changed at all, right?
Then,
If it's the gold industry, there's no problem, right?
It's not that kind of problem!
I can't talk.
Can you go out with me?
I'll go home.
You're so mean.
What? I thought I'd show you on TV.
It's okay. Let's do it alone.
There's one thing I want to confirm.
What is it?
The minister is actually a man, right?
You know?
I knew it.
The minister decided it beforehand.
That's right. I should have decided it.
That's what I wanted to confirm.
See you later.
What's wrong with him?
All right! All right!
I think it's a really wonderful firework.
Thank you, Ryo-chan.
For making such a wonderful firework.
What? What?
What?
As a secretary of the Katsushika office,
I did the obvious.
We'll rehearse in 10 minutes.
I repeat.
The rehearsal will be in 10 minutes.
Well, now...
Oh, it's refreshing.
If you want to go to the bathroom at the top,
you can do it.
What's wrong with you guys?
You're pathetic, Ryotsu.
You're such a male secretary,
but you're asking a woman to help you.
What are you talking about?
You're not like the usual seniors.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
It depends on the situation.
I don't get it.
Huh?
What?
What's wrong?
What do you mean?
We are angry.
You traitor.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm also upset about their attempt.
But think about it.
Even if the law and the system are reformed,
Japan is still a male society.
There's no place for women to play an active role.
What?
The day when women can play the leading role in Japan.
That's the day of the Hina festival.
It's not a big deal.
We just decorate the Hina dolls and add Hina Arale and Amazake.
I think it's okay to make their faces on such a day.
Ryotsu.
You've thought that far.
As a man, it's a matter of course.
5 minutes before rehearsal.
No.
This is not the time to do this.
Sir.
Are you there?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm changing.
You have to.
What do you mean?
Why?
It's natural for Nakagawa to be the clerk.
He is the most suitable for the clerk in the Katsushika prefecture.
I should have been the clerk.
Eh?
Is it a joke?
If he can make you the clerk,
he needs to leave you alone.
doesn't he?
Don't mess with me.
3 nurses, please get to your seats.
Okay.
I'll get you.
I knew I would be your clerk.
I've had enough of you.
I will crush you.
I'll get it!
Oh, Ryo-chan, where are you going?
I'm going back to the office. The show is tomorrow.
That's right. You'll be surprised at the show.
That's right. I didn't expect you to be the assistant.
What are you guys doing here?
What do you mean?
I'm going to put flowers on the festival tomorrow.
I'm making flower of peach.
Don't make such a thing!
You guys are so stupid for making the festival.
Aren't you frustrated?
But...
You said you were going to make a girl's set tomorrow.
That's a general story.
Look at my girls.
They are always making a big face.
We boys are having a narrow view.
Do we have to make a face now?
Tell me, Bull.
If you say it's a festival, they will be more and more stupid.
It's a festival, so we have to be smart and smart.
Is there any way?
I have an idea.
Tell me.
First of all, they are making flowers.
What?
Are you sending it?
It's very difficult to make such a thing for the festival.
But this is a festival that I came here today.
That's a small show.
I say, a festival the big has to be together with other festivals.
But now you're cutting it into two.
I'm inside.
You?
What's wrong?
N-nothing.
I-I thought he hadn't come yet.
The priest is looking for him right now.
The broadcast is about to start.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Listen up, everyone!
The women in the neighborhood are too good-natured!
It's one of the reasons why men have become weak!
We just need to show them the strength of a man around here!
And then, we'll destroy the women's festival, the Hina Festival, in this manor!
Yes!
Okay! I, the chief of the Kirikomi, will report to the teacher!
You guys wait here!
Yes!
It seems like he's not in the book.
I searched all over the place, but...
Huh?
Where did he go, Senpai?
He's in trouble. The broadcast is about to start soon.
I-I knew it!
It's Nakagawa-san, just like during the rehearsal!
There he is! It's Ryo-chan!
Eh?
Senpai!
Tch!
Hey, you guys!
Ryo-chan! I've been looking for you!
Eh?
Senpai!
Happy birthday!
W-what's this?
It's Senpai's birthday today.
I was just about to celebrate with you.
Is that so?
And then, this is a birthday present from everyone.
It's the costume of the chief.
It's exactly the size of Senpai.
So I'm the chief?
I'm sorry for not telling you.
I thought I'd surprise you a bit.
Y-you guys...
Thank you! I've never been this excited before!
Broadcast 10 minutes ago!
Now, hurry up and change!
Because I'm the chief today!
Ryo-chan, you're back in time.
What are you doing?
Here.
What's wrong?
Ryo-chan is really becoming a big boss!
What?
Ryo-chan, you betrayed us!
We're going to get married!
Ryo and his betrayal will be put to death by the Hina Festival!
What?
Ryo-chan, you will get on well!
Re-so-perfect.
Broadcasting 10 minutes now!
3, 2...
In this Katsushika garden,
a lady from the Katsushika branch shows us a real-life Hina.
She prays for the safety of the children's transportation,
We wish you a safe trip.
Your costumes and the Hinadan are also made by the people around you.
It's wonderful.
I'm curious about Ryotsu.
Of course, the guests and the Hinadan are also made by the Katsushika...
What?
What's that?
Doki doki doki!
It's a men's Hinamatsuri!
What is that?
Oh no! I totally forgot about them!
They're coming this way!
Wait, Ojaru!
Get ready!
Wait! I can tell if you let me go!
Men's Hinamatsuri!
Get ready!
What is this?
My head!
Oh, director!
I defeated you!
You're really良ling!
Not only do I want to fight, but I don't know who will take me down.
Youсеll.
That's right.
What's special about you?
I have more strength than Minato!
I will protect you!
You often talk about it.
What's wrong with youse, Minato?
Stop it, yousse!
Me?
What?
I hate March3rd so much!
Ryo-san's "Why?"
Ryo-san's eyebrows look like black ants, why?
Why?
He wears sandals but he runs really fast, why?
Ryo-san always has his arms around his head, why?
Why?
He's so fast but he's so popular, why?
It doesn't matter but
The anime title is so long
Katsushikaku Kameyari Kouenmai, first release
Why?
Who the hell are you?
You're the same as me, right?
Did I become a part of you two?
But I don't know who's who
Do you understand?
I became Ryo-A from now on
And you became Ryo-B
Next time, Ryo-an and Ryo-A
Let's split up!
Next time, Ryo-A and Ryo-a
Thanks for watching to the end!
Please subscribe!
Thank you!