Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Watching the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ Flying to the point ♪
♪ Where the love stone is broken ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ While fishing ♪
♪ I propose a parting call ♪
And I'm caught laughing
♪ I'm fine so I don't need any help ♪
♪ But I'm imprisoned in a bad mood ♪
♪ The street isn't changing ♪
♪ That's the good part ♪
♪ The crows sing ♪
♪ The sun is up now ♪
♪ I'm all pale and feeling tanned ♪
♪ My soul ♪
CAPTIONS PREVIEW
Granny, what are you doing here?
Knifes, pressing and holding a ruler.
Shh, wait a sec.
You never take any.
-You mean Kanchi? -Yeah, I've been waiting for this.
"Choukanda Sushi"
"Norenwake Taiketsu"
Ehhhhh! What's going on!
K-Kankichi, don't show your feelings!
U-um... I'm sorry.
Your skill as a sushi chef is at its peak.
Why don't you take over the shop?
U-um...
Don't make a loud noise!
So, which shop is it?
It's a shop inside the Sky Tower that Nakagawa-san's company completed this month.
Huh? The world's largest high-rise building that will open next month?
Yes. With Nakagawa-san's support, we decided to open as tenants.
I see. A private store. Amazing!
It's my shop!
I can't believe you have a private store!
The rights to the store will all be mine.
That's a promise, too.
It's a very specific one.
There are certain conditions.
Huh? What are they?
The condition is that Nakagawa-san will take over the store.
All fish and seafood will be given an IC tag.
The production, freshness, price, and quality will be managed by Nakagawa-san.
The management will be in charge of the management, and the sushi will be eaten without any worries.
So, it's a high-tech sushi.
That's what Kankichi is good at.
It's not a private store. It's an independent store that can't be used.
Do it well!
Even if I have a shop, the operating budget is not even a single yen...
I'll leave it at 10 million yen for free.
What?
I'll return it in three years.
Yay! As expected of Gepard!
I'll make it my favorite shop!
Grandma, are you sure you want to leave it to Kankichi?
Don't worry. I have the talent to make money.
But if it's for making money, you have to lower the quality.
There's an IC tag there, so it's fine.
I'm looking forward to it! It's my store!
Manager?
What's with that surprised face?
You guys are bothering me because I'm the manager?
No, not really. But that store is a very important store for Nakagawa Group...
Nakagawa! How about I own that important store?
R-Ryo-chan is worried about lowering the quality to make money.
Gepard and Matoe told me the same thing.
Why don't you all trust me?
You told me that you want to fill in the IC tag and look up the operating data.
I see.
That's a good idea. Let's do it.
But Ryo-chan, what are you going to do about the police?
Of course!
Are you going to quit?
We're going to aim for the best sushi restaurant in Japan...
No, the best sushi restaurant in the world!
You guys should come and eat!
I'm going to go now.
I'm going to go now!
Huh?
Bro!
It's been a while, Matoi.
What's wrong, all of a sudden?
Don't be happy, Matoi. We just finished our training in Kyoto and we're back.
Yuzu, hold on to the orange.
Come on, orange. Come on.
It's expensive.
So we're going to live together for the first time in years.
Yeah. This will give us a chance to catch some fish.
Grandma, Bro is back.
So we should leave the Sky Tower to Bro, not Kankichi.
We were just talking about that.
If we could have Yuzu do it, we wouldn't have to.
But, you know, we told him we'd leave it to Kankichi.
Oh, right.
That idiot made a mistake.
Lemon sent an e-mail.
He said, "Please give us some advice."
So we're going to leave the Sky Tower.
We have no choice.
What are we doing here?
What?
You guys are not following your promise!
We're going to leave the Sky Tower!
You can't leave it to us.
We're not going to leave it to you.
Huh?
What?
We can't afford to leave the Sky Tower.
We want to do our best.
Let's open two stores.
What? Two stores?
We'll split it into two stores.
The Sky Tower grand opening is next month.
Until then, we'll open for a week.
We'll leave the store to the one who makes the most money out of the two.
I don't mind.
But Kankichi...
I don't care what you do.
My future depends on you.
You have to accept it.
I've been training in Kyoto.
I'll fight with all my might.
I'll help you, too.
I'll win.
I'm going to fight against him one day!
I put a sign up on my account in advance.
So the customers are line up.
You're so energetic.
What about Kankichi?
Kankichi, are you okay with two people?
The purchase is managed by Nagagawa Water.
I can't cut it.
I have to save the human rights.
I see.
But you look like an amateur.
That's right.
I was taken a week off and I paid 1,000 yen for the day.
Don't you think it's terrible?
Don't say that.
I promised you that I would give you sushi for the rest of your life.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Welcome!
Today, we will give you a special service.
We'll give you a special rice ball and a flyer.
And we'll give you a discount of 500 yen.
It's that cheap?
That's crazy!
500 yen?
That's half of our price.
Don't worry.
500 yen is not a big deal.
We'll just keep going.
A special flyer.
I'm back.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Leave it to me.
I'll do it.
I'll give you a flyer.
I'll give you this.
The price is right.
I got it.
Who comes to play with me?
This guy.
I know who it is.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
That's a big plank.
Thank you for the service.
What?
You idiot!
I'm not cooking a picnic lunch.
Sayori, we're waiting for you.
This is Kohada.
He's really good, but he hasn't washed his hands yet.
Don't worry, it'll be clean in a few minutes.
Huh?
Ah, it's a foreigner.
I can't speak English at all.
Is this a sushi bar?
It doesn't matter. We have customers.
Do something about it!
Just a little bit.
Please...
What's wrong?
I don't understand English at all, so I went to the next door.
I see.
You have to get foreign customers from the place.
Is this a sushi bar?
It's a foreigner.
Bro, I can't speak English.
Don't worry.
There were a lot of foreign tourists in the Kyoto Ryotei.
Yes! Sushi bar! Sushi bar!
Please sit down!
Oh...
Please, please! Japanese tea, please!
What?
What? Same profit?
We make overwhelmingly more profit in Kankichi, but the profit was small.
Damn, I've gone to all the foreign customers in the room.
Huh?
Dis swatр
Honda, master all of them by tomorrow.
Yase-senpai, I can't.
I make sushi that satisfies foreign customers.
I'll think about it.
We made this tonight. A menu for the foreign guests.
You mean by that, I'll just have the pictures taken and you'll know, right?
Yeah.
Good afternoon.
Please, please.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
Here you go.
I wonder which country he's from.
Maybe he knows English.
Indian.
I wonder if there's any sushi that's Indian.
Don't worry. I've prepared it for that.
Hey, wait.
Curry sushi made with dry curry.
Oh! Very, very good!
He he, I did it!
Oh, it's refreshing.
I don't know what refreshing is.
It's okay.
It's said that it's good to enjoy the refreshingness of the dried bonito with snacks.
He he, I'll try it then.
No, let's go with the Italian style dried bonito carpaccio.
What? You can do that?
No problem.
I've made it in Kyoto.
Hey, wait.
Oh, delicious!
Gyo Gyo Gyo!
What? You said you lost a little?
If it's a sale, I'm completely winning.
It's true that there are many, but the cost of materials is double.
There are too many made in Kankichi.
Hmm, if this happens, I'll make a more impactful store.
Matoi, we have a lot of customers in our store, but no repeater at all.
R, right.
That's right.
Everyone is the first customer.
Is it just because it's rare?
Yes.
The customers will be sold out.
It's a store that makes me want to come again.
Okay, let's go back.
Wada, let's attack with the atmosphere of Japan.
Hmm, you're coming.
I'll wear a kimono.
Yes, let's do that.
Oh, no, I won't lose either!
Really, he is a noisy man.
Oh, of course!
Okay, I'll shoot at the base
The offensive rate is low.
I'll let him be.
Well, he's a little of a man.
Let's go carefully.
What is this?
What is this fuss?
Don't push it! Don't push it!
Buy the ball properly and then hit it.
Where is this called a sushi shop?
Hey, look closely!
I did it! I got a big tuna!
Congratulations!
Here, a big tuna.
I did it! It's a sea!
I got a sea too!
Hey, congratulations!
It's a slope again.
I want to eat a tuna.
Hurry up when you finish.
You can use it later.
How about this?
If you're a good customer, you can be full with 100 yen.
Well, there's no such customer.
It's like Kankichi, but do something about the noisy music.
I got it. I got it.
Even so, it's a great customer.
Hey, the tuna won't come out.
Ah, I got it.
Hey, I got it.
This is a sea!
It's a sea!
Kampuchi, it's a sea!
A tuna, red sea bream, huge tuna, all in one.
Hey, Kampuchi. Congratulations.
Senpai, look at this.
Huge tuna sea.
It's all over the place.
What's up?
It's gone?
The people who are selling this place ate it all.
Who's selling it?
It's still the sea, the sea and the green onion and the tuna.
Not yet.
Hey, you're the Pachi Pro on the Pachinko magazine!
Hurry up!
I'm back!
I'm out of ideas and ideas!
I ate it, I ate it!
It's an Amaridama present. I'll come again tomorrow.
Senpai, if you come tomorrow, we'll be in trouble!
I'm in trouble.
I'm not going to eat Pachi Sushi!
Wait a minute, sir.
They're trying to start something again.
Headmai Sushi Get Racing!
Explain the rules!
Pull out the sushi you want to eat!
Let's start!
All right, I'll aim for the expensive ones!
It crashed!
Game Over!
Now I'm the best!
You know, F1 racers have a difficult course.
How many times are they set at 95,000 steps?
I don't manage sushi.
Nacağım!
Damn you, Guts!
This can't be happening!
Come on!
Wait a minute, Guts!
It's the Egg and....
I can't keep up!
So fast!
But I'm a pro in this world too!
I can't afford to lose!
That's a great run!
Is he going to dance?
What a technique! Amazing!
As expected of Otaro.
He doesn't seem to be a one-man team.
He's not really a pro.
But you're too confident in your own story.
Otaro is too heavy!
If you're as light as me, you'll be able to get through!
I won! I can't lose!
Otaro, get!
It's a legend! This guy's a legend!
Thanks for the dream!
Wait, this isn't a sushi restaurant!
Not again, Otaro!
Wait, guys! Get!
It's a bad game!
Senpai, you're out of your mind again.
No way!
Hey, who are you?
I'm Shono Gotsudo.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
It's the F-1 driver's shoe!
Right?
Why is the real F-1 driver's shoe coming?
I quit this too!
The fifth day has made a big difference.
If this continues, the store will be in a gloom.
No, there's still two days left!
I'll show you a real gloom!
Senpai, just the renovation fee for the store alone...
But I'm out of 100 million yen of operating funds.
All the fish and fish I've ever eaten are in the fridge.
I can't win against Yutsu-san's store.
In this case, I'll have to use a real hand.
A real hand?
What are you going to do about it, Senpai?
I'm going to leave only the tail tag with the IC tag on it and sell it later!
If I do that, I can't hold on to sushi.
I'll buy you cheap fish with the money I sold you.
What's going on?
What? 300 yen?
It's even cheaper than the service on the first day.
Kankichi's going to be burned to death!
Tomorrow will be a comeback home run!
What do you expect from me?
Um...
I'll call you when I leave.
Okay!
What's wrong, Yutsu!
Ready now!
One, two!
Three!
They came to the survey room, and they came to the end of the session!
What?
Of course.
Hey, it's only 1:00.
Well...
Hmm...
Grandma, what do you think?
The profit is exactly the same as both.
That's ridiculous!
Damn it! I was winning because the customers were still there for 5 minutes!
You're cheating! You can't make a profit with 300 yen!
I'm not kidding! I'm using the IC tag of all fish from Nagagawa!
Then show me the remaining fish!
Too bad. I've cut all the fish.
What's with these tuna? Aren't they flounder?
Flounder? They're supposed to be real tuna.
You're right, Lemon. I think it's because of the heat.
That's not true.
Kankichi, bring me the bones of the fish you've cut.
What's that?
Honda-san, bring it to me.
Okay...
Look! It's got the IC tag, right?
It's a fish, as I thought!
You're stupid!
Kankichi, what's this?
It's a fish, as I thought!
But it has a tail.
Eww!
It's suspicious. Show me.
It's a glue!
You idiot! I told you not to make such a mistake!
I knew it.
It seems like it was a game.
I'll have you pay back 10 million yen.
No way! I worked so hard!
Ah, Nagagawa-san! Reiko-san!
Good evening. I was just worried about the game and came here.
Matoi-chan, what happened?
Kankichi cheated and the older brother won.
Yuu-san, congratulations!
Thank you.
Give it to me.
Let's celebrate the new manager, Yuu-san!
Kankichi, Batu-chan, grab the sushi!
Yes, yes.
Everyone, please eat more.
Mmm, it's really good!
Yuu-san, you can do this as a representative of Japan.
Thank you very much.
Kankichi, are you still eating?
The sushi is ready.
Here, take it.
OK.
Here, Kobachiro.
Let's eat!
It's good!
Mmm, it's good!
The thickness of the fish, the texture of the sushi, and the texture of the sushi.
It's perfect no matter which one you eat!
What?
It's better than the sushi I ate.
I lost.
Your sushi is really good!
It's really good.
You're good, Ryo-chan.
Grandma, I'm going to Kyoto again to do my training.
Then, everyone, good luck.
Brother!
Yuu-san!
I went there again.
Damn it.
If you do it normally, you'll win.
Wait.
If Yuu-san is gone, I'll be the manager.
You can't say that!
I'll return the Yuu-san that I returned years ago to Kyoto.
What?
Why is this always like this?
"Yuu-san, I'm going to Kyoto again."
"Yuu-san, I'm going to Kyoto."
"Yuu-san, will you do it?"
While I walked with a look back.
I was drawn to the lamp.
I felt a strange feeling at that time.
I walked on the black side of the Akeidogai
I was a child once, but everyone forgot
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above my eyes
Look at that corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Come to our town
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Come to our town
Thank you!
A great person wants to see the flowers?
And it's a legendary cherry blossom that has been blooming all year round?
Is that really true?
I can't help it. Leave it to me, the head of the Katsushika-cho flower viewing club.
Next time, "Sakura's Big Change."
"Heisei Romance and the Cherry Blossom Storm."
See you in summer.
Don't forget to subscribe.
Next time, "The Lest Santa Claus Has Gone."
See you.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!