Especially setting the dog by the side
When I watch TV, I always
"If you're watching TV, make your room bright and let it be free."
When I watch TV, make your room bright and let it be free.
Tell me
"It's the same thing, but there's more than enough."
"There's more than enough."
Tell me
"Come to me if you've got no money."
"I don't have any money anyway, but I'm worried."
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
They'll be all right eventually
You understand, don't you? You understand, don't you?
If you understand, then come to me quietly!
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Water...
Where am I?
Hakodate...
I'm sorry...
Who am I?
You don't know who you are?
Yeah, I can't remember why I'm here at all.
You're losing your memories...
You don't look familiar in town.
I...
Why am I calling myself as "I?"
Anyway, I'd like to call the police.
Police!
Policeman!? What's wrong?
When I hear "policeman" I feel somehow nostalgic and...
It's so painful.
Okay, okay.
Then, I'll leave the police.
Really?
Yeah.
Then, do you have anything that you can understand?
Why do you have so many things?
I don't know.
Is there anything else?
What?
How is it?
Nothing.
I see. No clues.
Then, what are you going to do from now on?
What should I do?
For now, let's come to my house.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
I'm Ryoji Kano.
My house is nearby.
Thank you.
You saved me.
Hey, Ryo!
Yeah?
What?
I told you to come back as soon as possible without Aya-chan.
Did you understand?
I understood.
See you.
You just replied, didn't you?
Yeah.
I just...
Maybe you were called Ryo-san, too.
Maybe.
Then, your name...
For example, Ryo-suke.
Hmm...
I think it's different.
Then, Ryohei.
Ryozo.
Ryota.
Ryo...
They all have the same...
I see.
Well, there's no need to be so impatient.
Yeah.
Just remember it slowly.
But, with that outfit, the people at home will be surprised.
Why are you wearing a suit?
Well, I don't know.
Oh, really?
I think this is the most appropriate.
I see.
Memory loss?
Yeah.
I'd like you to stay at home for a while.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Hey.
Yeah.
I don't mind.
Hey.
The radio is out of service.
What's wrong with this girl?
She said the customer was coming.
Oh.
Welcome.
This is my sister's Ayada.
Good afternoon.
Bro, don't make me do this.
Don't say this to me.
Say this to your dad.
Can you show me that please?
Bro, is that person at the electric shop?
Yeah.
- Here you go. - Thank you!
- Here you go. - Thanks.
So, you really don't remember anything?
No, I don't remember anything at all.
But you were called Ryo-san, right?
Probably.
I wonder what it is.
This kid suddenly started to use the service.
I was told to fix it a little, so I'm a good boy.
I see.
Because it's a big difference from your brother.
But why did you fix it?
Maybe he's an electrician.
Well, I don't know myself, but my hands move on their own.
What?
Ryo-san hasn't come today?
No, he hasn't returned to Ryo's side either.
It's always Zuru Yasumi, but I can't contact him at all.
He's a bad guy.
If this happens, I'll consult with the director and fire him for his job.
But I wonder what really happened.
I hope nothing happens.
Just leave it.
I don't know where he is and what's going on.
I'm going to go.
Bye.
See you later.
You've been waiting, Ryo-san.
Ah.
Let's go home then.
I'm sorry.
I have to take care of him.
Don't worry about it.
If you want, I'll help you too.
I'm happy to help you, but...
I'm also happy that you're helping me on your ship.
Don't you have your own ship?
You don't have a boat?
I have one, but...
Hm?
It's this one.
I've been using it since my dad's generation.
I don't have to buy a new boat or spend money on it.
Can I borrow some tools?
Huh?
Yeah.
Can you repair a boat?
I don't know.
I don't know, but I feel like I can do something.
Maybe you were a carpenter or something.
Yeah.
I always feel like I'm making something smaller.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Hm.
Wow.
You can even repair a boat.
Yeah.
You call me "Big Boss" from now on.
Huh?
Please, Big Boss.
You're kind of embarrassing.
It's all right.
Yo, Big Boss!
Nippon Ichi!
A game of tug of war!
Don't mess with me.
My face and body can't stop moving.
I don't need to go on a black and white journey at night.
I've inherited the power of drift and versatility.
The
Well, it's a lot.
My father would be happy to see it.
Does your father not board the ship anymore?
Since I got my back hurt.
I'm working at a pachinko shop in front of the station now.
My father actually wants to board the ship.
Ryo!
How was it today?
Oh, it's a lot!
I see, it's a lot.
Ryo, thank you for everything.
Ryo.
Yes.
No, no.
Let's drink this.
Good, good.
Thank you.
You're a good drinker.
Let's go.
Dad.
I'm happy, too.
Shut up, Ryo.
Ryo.
Here, Ryo.
Yes.
By the way, Ryo.
I need to talk to you about something.
Can you stay here for a while?
I'm serious, Ryo.
I don't mind if you stay here forever.
Please do that, Anki.
I'm grateful for that, but...
I...
That's right.
Ryo, can you be my maid?
What?
Maid?
Yes.
I'd be happy if you could be my maid.
What?
Hey, Aya.
I'm Ryo, right?
You're not a maid, are you?
You're an idiot!
Who is he?
I'm telling you, he's an idiot!
What?
He's an idiot.
Don't call me an idiot!
Stop talking about me.
It's been a month since we talked.
Have you got any news from Ryo?
No.
I left the store because he said he'd be back soon.
But it's been a month.
Forget about him.
That guy.
If he's not here, there will be no problem.
We can go home in peace.
Um, sir?
What?
The file is upside down.
So, we came to Hakodate's Uojishiba.
What's up, Terai?
Oh, that...
Hm?
This program is...
This is Tsukamoto Tetsuya.
The person in the corner on the left.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, Ryo-chan!
What's with Hakodate?
①Leave the
Sayonara!
Hey, sister!
Why don't you go somewhere nice with us?
We have little time, we are in a dilemma.
Why don't you play with us?
No!
Don't say such nonsense.
Hey!
- Hey! - No!
- Hey, stop it! - I said no!
Who's there?!
Ryo-san!
Who the hell are you?
Don't get in my way!
You're disgusting!
You're a big man, and you're with two guys!
Shut up! Don't try to act cool, you bastard!
Get down.
You bastard!
I did it!
You're a big man, you bastard!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I see.
Ryo-san!
What's wrong?
I was scared.
I almost missed you.
Ryo-san, do the memories not return?
They don't.
If they do,
what?
do you want to go somewhere?
Brother said
that he'd be able to buy another ship thanks to you.
He'd be able to work for you anytime.
Ryo...
Don't go anywhere! Stay here forever!
Aya...
I...
I've been thinking about you...
Aya!
Wait, wait...
Ryo, go home first.
Yeah.
Hey!
You came to see Ryo?
Yeah, she was a pretty girl.
A girl...
From what I saw, she looked like a woman who came to find her ex-boyfriend.
See you later.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I'd like to ask you something.
I'm looking for this person.
Do you have any idea about him?
What is this person?
His name is Ryo Tsukankichi.
Your husband?
No, actually, I...
Did this person do something?
Well, a little...
So, do you remember anything?
No, I've never seen him before.
I see.
......
...
Aniki!
Big brother!
Big brother, that's...
Yes, it's mine.
It seems I'm being chased by the police.
If I stay here, I'll be a nuisance to everyone.
I want to disappear from here.
Big brother...
A policeman is looking for you at the port.
I see.
Run away, big brother!
Ryoji, you...
I don't care if you're being chased by the police.
I'm a big brother!
Hurry up!
Ryo!
He's leaving.
See you later.
Ryo!
I finally found you.
Who are you?
What are you talking about?
I've been looking for you.
You've been looking for me?
That's right.
Who are you?
Big brother, don't be fooled.
He's a policeman.
A policeman?
What are you talking about?
Come with me.
I won't let you go from here.
What are you?
Move!
What are you doing?
Big brother, now!
I'm sorry, Ryoji.
I'm sorry, but...
Be careful.
He's an old man, isn't he?
Ryoji!
Can't you understand?
I don't want to be aå
I'm sorry, but...
You can learn very good Japanese.
He says this is bad.
What the hell is he talking about?
Master, I'm going to show my brother a joke.
Kei?
Senpai, stop!
W-what?!
Run away!
Senior, why!
Move to the ship infront of you!
Ryo, please stop!
Super Duran
What?!
What have I done?
I see!
Yes, that's right.
That's true.
It is said that if you pay a lot of money to the shop, you will be fined.
If there is a chance that you will get a lot of money, you will be sued.
What?
This year, the price of crab water is low and the price is rising.
This is it!
If you take the crab and sell it, you will get a lot of money quickly.
I went to the crab market after the fishing boat chartered, but there was a big storm.
I was thrown into the sea and was in the port town when I realized it.
That's right, I didn't let go of my sword, so I didn't let go of my sword.
I see.
I remembered everything.
That's good.
What?
Not good at all.
After all, I couldn't get the crab, so I can't pay you back, and it would be a big deal if the director found out about this.
No good.
I'm sorry.
It's definitely bad.
What should I do?
He went, Ryo-san.
Yeah.
Ryo-san lost his memory?
According to Reiko-kun's report, it seems so.
So he didn't contact me for a month.
I'm back.
Ryo-san!
Who are you?
Do you really have a memory loss?
Don't you know me?
I'm sorry.
I can't remember.
If you can't remember where you went without telling me that you were going to the crab farm, I have a request form for the fishing boat.
Do you really not remember?
Well.
Ryo-san.
I'm sorry.
I can't remember at all.
I see.
Ryo-san.
It seems I have caused you great trouble here.
I will leave this town.
What?
I don't want to cause you any trouble anymore.
Please let me go this way.
Wait, Ryo-tsu.
It's not trouble.
You are the necessary person for the fishing boat.
That's right.
Don't go, Ryo-san.
Yeah.
I feel lonely without Ryou.
Senpai!
You all are so...
Then, I...
Can I stay here?
Of course.
Thank you, Chief!
Chief Ohara is such a great person!
Chief Ohara?
Why do you know my name?
Huh? Why do I know it?
I can't remember.
Ryou!
Your memory loss was a lie from the beginning, wasn't it?
No! It was true at first.
But I finally remembered it.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I will never forgive you!
Hey, Ryou!
When I remember, it's like this again!
Yes.
Hello!
Welcome!
Welcome here!
Come Sir!
Welcome!
Sir!
Oh!
Excuse me!
No!
Come Sir!
splendesty, splendesty, splendesty!
Are you the selling type?
I'll do whatever I want.
That's right.
I'm the California Parece.
Can I have a drink?
Oh
California is not for you
This is not America
I'm sorry, sir
Excuse me, excuse me
Come on in
Then
Kushiage, Kakiage, Katsuage
Whatever it is, what is it?
What do you recommend?
Be careful with the Katsuage
Huh?
Is that a gag from my father?
Yes, I'm sorry
I don't understand
Huh?
Eh?
Ah, that, that, that, that, that, that
Really?
Yes, welcome
Welcome, please
The captain is on leave
and the Nishiki gui is
The Japanese god who was asked to take care of the child
I thought it was just a small part-time job to feed the child
Koichiro, the leader, who was the most adorable, ran away
Koichiro come back
Hey, if this happens, that's the only way
Next time "Nishiki Goi Panic"
Thank you