Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Inside the river slope
I've been gazing to some day
When I kicked the pebble
They came up from high
I wonder if I'm going to save money
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is only a single bad habit
The cityscape that doesn't change even one bad habit
It's strangely kind
From the fountain of the "Tongari-boshi"
To the taishakuten
The sun sets
Tomorrow is over already
I lost my happiness because of the number of times I spent
I realized
I'm such an idiot
The First Love Story of Asakusa
Oh, Ryou!
Ryo, you're so stylish. What's wrong?
Well, I'm a little...
Ryo! What are you doing?
It's okay. Just a little.
This is a cream for removing hair.
Isn't this a mousse or something?
No. I'm going to use it for other people.
Senpai, you're going to meet someone you've never met before.
You're going to meet someone you've never met before?
Ryo?
Yeah. I have one or two memories of my first love.
Oh? Hey, let me ask you something, Ryo.
What kind of person is your first love?
Where did you meet her?
I met her in Asakusa, where I was a kid.
The zaver who burned up the community building in the end of the war will revive.
Sensoji, Horaku Center. New World.
Jintan Island 12th Floor.
Asakusa, where Hanayashiki is located, was exquisite.
At that time, the Hanayashiki was free.
It was like our backyard.
I knew it! The coasters have such a good thrill to them!
Urgh!
That's right!
Compe! That was just a blip!
You're so mean!
I'm not mean!
Let's ride the Spitfire next time.
Oh, there she comes again.
What's she doing alone?
She's studying.
I heard she's an actor of a rock band.
Actor? Really?
That's so cool!
Huh?
No! No!
No!
How many times do I have to tell you?
How can you be an actor?
Why can't you just act like a real person?
I'll change the way you stand.
Huh?
I'll change the way you come to work.
Boss!
Can you do it again?
I'll do it one more time!
You're doing your best, aren't you, Kotone?
Move!
You're my daughter, aren't you?
Actors and the stage don't have parents and children!
I'm always ready to help you.
I don't know who you are, but thank you for your friendliness.
At least, at least, tell me your name.
I'm Kan-Kichi Ryosu!
What are you doing here?
Wow!
Look at this!
It's a real script!
The rumor is true that you're an actor of the Rock Band!
Yeah!
You've been here...
Go over there!
Let's go, Kankichi.
I can't talk to great actors.
But, they're the same age as us, and they're actors.
I've never seen a play script before!
Wait!
Wait, I'm an actor, so I called you?
It's not a joke.
We're meeting a real actor for the first time, so I thought we could talk.
Right?
Yeah!
But I'm not a real actor yet.
I'm not good at acting, and I'm always scolded.
We're scolded at school every day.
Right?
Yeah!
I'm Ryotsu Kankichi!
I'm Tachibana Kotone.
You're so cute!
And sometimes you're evil!
What are you talking?
Are you understerreichize or something?
Haha!
I read as "kyu" in my man field.
Oh!
Hey, show us the example.
Miss, you can't do that.
Sometimes you have to be gentle.
Let me handle it.
You should leave.
I-is this too foolish?
Hello.
Wow!
That's cool!
Kotone-chan is like Okawa Hashizo!
Look! This is it!
Kotone-chan will become as handsome as Hashizo someday!
That's cool, Otoneemon!
G-g-gah...
I guess it was bad luck for you, Kankichi Nosuke!
I'm on my way!
I 다니!
I guess it was bad luck for you, Kankichi Nosuke!
I'm on my way!
You two wait, you wait!
Wait, Kankichi! Kotone!
Huh? Where did they go?
This way!
Hey, Kankichi! Don't steal!
Run away!
There!
Yeah!
I got you!
You're amazing, Kotone!
What do you want to be?
The best actor in Japan!
My dream is to become the best actor in Japan and play the whole country at once.
Kotone, you can do it!
Yeah, I'll try! What about yours, Kankichi?
I love arts, so I want to be an athlete.
An athlete?
Not really. I want to be an airplane pilot!
You're amazing! An airplane pilot!
Not really. I want to be a director of "Katsubo Shashin"!
I want to be a cartoonist!
I don't know which one!
Sounds like you, Kankichi!
By the way, where are Chin-Kichi and Tonpei?
Those two are staying at the school.
Because they're stupid.
Damn it!
Remember that, Kankichi!
I'm not stupid!
You're my type, so I'm embarrassed to be alone with you.
I also like you, Kankichi.
You like me?
You're so annoying!
Kankichi, watch out!
A samurai!
I don't know who you are,
but I'm sorry for your trouble.
I'm sorry for your trouble.
You're very honest.
You're a true hero.
I'm glad I made good friends.
Kankichi!
Kotone!
My dad said I could be on the stage next week!
I'll be in the front row!
I'll do my best!
This is...
New vehicle!
It's great to see an artificial satellite fifty meters apart from Tokyo at the same time.
You have to get here with us as soon as it's completed.
Let's do this!
Kankichi...
Kankichi,
You'll be fine.
It's okay. Come here, Kotone-chan.
The satellite is already ready.
Because the stars are stars, let's make a reservation for this gondola.
I secretly signed the reservation.
Oh, Gosunkuni.
Kan-kichi-ta.
No one will notice if it's here.
Then lend me too.
I'll lend you.
I changed the umbrella.
It's a waste.
Don't be shy if someone sees us.
Hey!
You can't enter the warehouse.
Run away!
They look good.
Yes.
It's too late, Kotone-chan.
Is it over today?
But, but, the show is scheduled until next month.
As long as the owner of the park said it's over, we have to obey him.
If you're a person of this world, you know what's going on.
No way.
If the opponent is Bunji, it's impossible.
I'm not going to do the show suddenly because I'm recovered.
I'm not worried about the popularity index.
I felt sorry for Kotone-ojo.
I was so happy to be on the stage in Asakusa.
I have to stand here tomorrow morning.
I can't.
Kan-kichi-kun.
...Kotone-chan...
Chapter 2: The End
Episode 1: The End
K-Kotone-chan... are you leaving?
You're always like this...
Even though we became friends...
Even though we were able to perform on stage thanks to you, Kankichi-kun...
Even though I thought you would watch my plays...
You're always... always...
Kotone-chan...
I don't want to travel anymore!
I want to stay here forever!
I want to stay in Asakusa!
But... then you can't become the best star in Japan!
Is Kankichi-kun okay?
Even if I say that...
You idiot!
Kotone-chan!
...
I...
I don't want you to go either!
Why did you leave?
Even though we became friends!
K-Kotone-chan...
Kankichi-kun...
H-hah...
Let's ride together!
I'm looking forward to it!
- - Since
we have to go to Kyoto by the end of the day... let
's hurry. - Yes.
- Kotone, let's go.
Kotone...
How long are you going to keep this up?
Enough. Stop it until you're tired.
Kotone!
Kankichi!
What's wrong, Kankichi? You're so dirty.
Mister, please!
Give me some time!
I really want to show Kotone something!
Please!
Hey, Kankichi, what do you want to show me?
It's almost time.
Kankichi!
I like you too, Kankichi.
I like you, too.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I promised to ride with you at the beginning.
Kankichi...
I'm sorry.
K-Kankichi...
It's been so long.
Once I hit him with my machine gun...
I'm worried about his inauspicious state.
HanKichi!
You know...
When I was a little kid...
I was worried that Kankichi was yourself.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Right in front of you is Sumida River!
The big building in front of Azumabashi is Matsuya Department Store!
There's the Asakusa Park over there!
Next to Sensoji, there's the Hanayashiki Ferris Wheel and the airport!
The artificial satellite will soon reach the summit!
Ah, Asahina was there!
That stupid Kankichi! Make it better!
K-Kotone...
I'll never forget you...
The Asakusa River, and Kankichi...
Kotone! So far, I've brought you here...
You're the only one left!
KanKichi-kun...
You will definitely become the best star!
Kozune-chan, I will always support you!
Goodbye.
Hang in there, Masane-chan!
Goodbye!
The next day
What about the satellite tower?
It was replaced by that Beater.
Ryo-chan, you had such a first love, didn't you?
It's not like that.
I'm not embarrassed.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Well, I had a boyish era, too.
Kankichi-kun?
Kankichi-kun, isn't it?
K-Kotone-chan?
Yes.
I knew it!
Kotone-chan!
Long time no see, Kankichi-kun.
How do you feel?
Are you disappointed to be an old lady?
Yes, I feel beautiful.
No, I mean, I'm surprised to be an adult.
Kankichi-kun is the same as before.
He hasn't changed at all.
Ichizawa is very popular in Kansai.
It's all thanks to Kankichi-kun.
For the play he sent me,
Shin-Kichi and Tonpei can't come to work, so...
I brought my colleagues to work.
Hello.
Asakusa has changed a lot, hasn't it?
Of course.
There's no manpower now,
and nothing is the same as before.
Oh, there is!
What?
There is!
The satellite from back then!
He's gone.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm going to put the satellite down!
Be careful.
Wait a minute, Kankichi!
Shouldn't we put another rope on it?
All right.
Let's put it inside.
My eyes are spinning!
We're going to need a rope.
How many times do I have to tell you that?
None of your business!
So, even now,
you've got criminals to shoot!
All right, work!
It's a senior-like ending.
Really?
Thanks to you, I was able to get the tension before the main show.
You're really my savior.
Thank you.
This is enough for breakfast.
Kankichi.
Yes.
Then I'll go back to the theater a little earlier.
It's a dream national park.
Do your best, boss.
I'm very nervous when I think that Kankichi is watching me.
No!
If Mr. Osamu...
If Mr. Kotone was here all the time,
I wonder if he would have become Ryo-chan's wife by now.
Well, I wonder what happened.
Even if you lose, there are times when you get into trouble.
I'm sorry.
Well, leave this to me.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I got the money!
Hey, Kotone-chan!
Let's go to Japan!
Let's go!
Hey, Sakonji!
Why are you listening to the way to capture Doki-Memo?
You were an expert at fighting game, weren't you?
Huh?
Anyway, you got caught to the game!
You can't hide it!
Hey, which child does you like it?
Next time on Doki Gamer Sakonji!
Good luck!
The story of a woman who can't fall in love
But I have a lot of things I want to do
I want to ride on a bike in the desert
I want to be more free than birds
I want to be a lady who changes at the speed of a mangue
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait
The future of the panorama is a dazzling light
You understand, right?
I want to be a lady who changes at the speed of a mangue
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait