Maiden's Wife
Make the room brighter and get away when you watch the TV!
The people without money, come to myplace!
I don't have anyone either but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
You'll be able to do something somehow
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
You who have no job, come to my place
I don't have one, but I'm worried
Look, it's burning
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
You who have no job, come to my place
You'll be able to do something somehow
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
You'll be able to do something somehow
You know, you know!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's the same as your mom's!
You're wrong.
I know, I'm not wrong!
It's a little different.
Roadside trains run on both the river and the rail,
but this one runs on two poles only.
It's cheap because there's no need to draw a track,
and it's a "ecology car" that's out of the question.
What?
Actually, I've driven a trolley bus before.
Really?
What do you mean?
Let me hear it.
It's a story from when I was a elementary school student.
The
Tokyo sky a long time ago was full of electric wires.
At that time, the foot of the common people was the railway, the bus, the roadside train, and the trolley bus.
The roadside train was convenient because it could carry a lot of people at once,
but the construction cost was high to build the railway.
That's where
the
The
That's why.
This is a special seat.
It's just a sandbag.
Is it a stopped station?
No, the pole came off the river.
You guys are not on a ride?
No, we have a real ride.
It's not a ride.
If you want to ride, pay the ride fee properly and ride.
What if you get hurt riding in such a place?
It's fine.
I'll help you if you fix it.
Hey, get off the bike.
600 volts are flowing.
It's fine.
We're used to riding on a 20,000 volt pole.
About 600 volts.
Idiot.
It's hard to power the pole even with 600 volts.
I told you it's dangerous.
You guys are not afraid of anything.
The driver is Ken.
He is a good-looking guy who is faster than the driver.
He has high driving experience.
It's not easy to break the pole.
The road construction is rampant in this area.
The number of sliders is decreasing.
It's about time to replace the pole.
Oh, no.
The road construction is rampant.
It's about time to replace the pole.
This is great.
It's shaking a lot.
There's a lot of construction work in Tokyo.
They're planning to build a highway.
Ah, I can't do it!
It's you guys again.
Sorry!
Thank you very much.
What's wrong, Grandma?
It's strange. I can't find my wallet.
I found it a while ago.
I'm sure it was when Kanchi was making a firecracker.
Yeah, I lost it because of the commotion.
Alright, I'll look for it.
Hey, you guys, help me!
Sorry.
Grandma, what kind of wallet is it?
It's a Hibikawa Gamaguchi.
Hibikawa Gamaguchi? Hibikawa, Hibikawa...
What?
I found it!
Huh?
This isn't a Hibikawa wallet. It's a snake toy.
Damn it. Where did it go?
Wallet, wallet...
Oh, it's here.
This is it, right?
Oh, that's right.
Oh, thank you for your help.
You're welcome.
I'll thank you from now on, kid.
Kid.
Hehe.
See you, kids.
Hey, go to my elementary school next time.
On this bus.
Hahaha.
Sounds good.
I'll go wherever there's a river.
See you!
Goodbye!
This loop at the end is powerful.
But it's weird when you think about it.
The plus and minus are one turn at U-turn.
No matter how you think about it, it'll be short.
I'll make it go through the loop.
Look.
The plus and minus...
Oh, they switched.
At the same time, I'm converting the motor and the song.
I don't understand at all.
Chinkichi is a railroad maniac, after all.
That's right.
Chinkichi might be able to do it.
Huh?
Pull the power cable for the troll bus to the school.
Did you really put the power cable on?
Of course.
I'm a man who does what I say.
Huh?
I brought the power cable that I didn't need in the middle of the night from the waste disposal area.
I dug a hole in front of the school gate at night.
I put a fire line and just let the current flow.
Then it became morning.
I was found by the teacher and removed immediately.
Of course.
Hahaha.
The adults were happy, but Ken was just smiling.
You're right.
That's what happens one day.
Oh?
Mr. Ken.
Is it near here?
Yes.
There's a bath at home, but it feels better when it's bigger.
My house is near the troll bus garage.
Huh?
Oh, you came out first.
I've been waiting for you.
No.
This is Ken's...
Yes, my wife Chieko.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
I'm Ryozu Kankichi.
I like troll buses.
I became a driver because I was opposed to my parents.
If you say this person, it won't work.
I was opposed to marriage and I was impressed and I was surprised.
A baby will be born soon.
This person is going to be restless from now on.
I'm definitely a boy.
I don't know that.
I'm a good girl.
If you're a girl, you'd better not be like Ken.
I told you.
Hehehe.
Well, it doesn't matter if you're a boy or a girl, if you're fine, you're fine.
That's for sure.
I'm moving well every day in my stomach.
And I'm getting along with Ken.
Are you good, Kankichi?
Yes.
Oh, Kankichi.
Mr. Ken.
Here I come, Mr. Ken.
Go, Kankichi.
If you can shoot, shoot me.
Got it!
Be serious when you're playing for a child.
What are you going to do if the ball is gone?
I'm sorry.
When you can't find the ball, I will compensate.
You like baseball, you like children, no matter
I was a fan of Turo Bus
This is the auxiliary engine switch
That is the fire engine
But such Turo Bus was pushed by the so-called micro-car boom
It was about to disappear
What did you say?
Mr. Amano and Mr. Miyata are fired because of the limited number of employees?
Is there such a stupid way?
Both are the most influential to the company
It doesn't work for the company
Both are old
I'm going to be fired from now on
Are you kidding?
I'll go to the president
Good, Mr. Ken
Go
President, can't you ask me this much?
No
Turo Bus
Turo Bus is a car that is a long time ago
From now on, it is the era of micro-car
I'm not going to be a Turo Bus from now on
I'm going to start a new business
That's more money
What are Mr. Amano and Mr. Miyata going to do?
It's too bad if you suddenly get fired
I can do other jobs at my age
Turo Bus and those old things
There is no choice but to disappear quietly
Turo Bus is only a car
If you understand, hurry to work
What are you doing?
I'm the president
Call the police
I'm a thief
Mr.
Let's go, Ganchi!
Yeah!
Oh, nice!
I got as many as Ken-san!
Again?
K-K-Ken-san!
What?
What did you say?
It must be a mistake!
No, it's definitely Ken-san!
Let's go check!
That's right!
Alright, let's go!
Yeah!
Is there really no mistake?
He just got caught and killed.
Ken-san is a short tempered person.
Uncle, can't we do something about this?
That's right.
I feel sorry for Ken-san!
Even if you say that...
I see.
That's right.
If he's a president, he got angry and went home.
Alright, let's go get Ken-san!
It's a private chat between the president and me!
Follow me!
What?
You took away Chiba's head?
Yeah, Ken-san's going to have a baby soon.
I feel sorry for him.
What?
That has nothing to do with me!
You can't say no!
Go home!
Because Ken-san went to lecture on behalf of the troll bus driver, right?
It's strange for Ken-san to be responsible for one person!
Yeah, yeah!
It doesn't matter what you say!
In general, troll bus is no longer needed!
No driver is needed!
What?
Why?
Sales are decreasing and revenue is increasing!
The maintenance fee of the vehicle is increasing, and the city's beauty is also ruined!
It's fine even if there is a river!
It's cool, right?
Shut up!
Anyway, there is no need for such a modern thing!
That's terrible!
We ride it every day!
Shut up!
Do you understand that children are business?
Go home, kids!
Go home!
If you don't go home, I'll call the police!
Damn it!
Stop it!
I hate you!
Even if I have money, I don't want to be such an adult!
Damn it!
What happened to Ken-san?
Has he returned from the police yet?
No time to say it!
第4回
You're not there yesterday, Ken!
Ken-san's not home, so I'll call you back!
Right?
Ken-san?
I didn't expect him to get it?
Come on!
Get out of here!
Dad!
The next day
I understand how you feel, but it's not good to hit.
It's just that my will doesn't pass.
I know, but I just cut it.
Well, I have some reasons to say that I'm a new job.
I have a child and I can't play with her.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Detective, you can go home now.
My wife is alone.
If I go home, the car and the train won't move.
Then run home.
Don't say nonsense.
Well, now is the worst time.
Just wait a little longer.
If it goes on for a while, the storm will end.
It's a huge storm.
Yeah.
Just stay here until it gets better.
What's wrong with my wife?
It's probably about Ken, so get on the train immediately.
What do you mean?
I didn't mean to keep it a secret.
What happened?
It's all because of that stupid president.
I see.
You're right.
I understand.
My parents made me die because of that stupid president.
For sure, you were worried and made me go home.
That way, I won't have to worry about her.
Well, we should be very grateful for that.
Just take care of yourself and send me back home.
Yeah, I know.
It's okay, Monami.
It's good to have a baby and be able to share a full responsibility.
What?
Well, I don't know what to do with that baby.
The baby is going to be born?
Oh no!
Chikichi, call an ambulance!
Where's the phone?
I don't have a phone. I have to call an ambulance.
The water is like a river.
We can't go like this.
It's an ambulance.
What should we do, Kikichi?
That's it.
We have to take it to the hospital.
Okay.
The water is like a river.
It's perfect for the electric line.
As expected of the railroad maniac, Chikichi.
Kikichi!
Chikichi!
Hurry up!
Okay.
Go, Chikichi!
Turo Bus, go!
What's the problem?
I want to show the bad guys who made fun of Turo Bus.
Okay.
We have to stop the train.
I'm going to the hospital.
Okay.
Okay, Chikichi.
No, no.
We have to take care of the baby.
Okay.
We have to go.
There's no fire in the hospital!
Leave it to me. The electricity is up to here.
Lower the trolley pole.
This is the latest model with an auxiliary diesel engine.
Oh, I see.
Pole storage completed.
All right, change!
It's working! As expected of the latest model!
Kankichi, hurry up!
I got it!
If that idiot president doesn't have a house, it's a shortcut.
I don't have time to sing.
Somehow I'm going to cut the garden.
The baby is more important than the president's house!
It's time for real estate sales.
I'm sorry.
What's that?
Hmm?
Drive more safely!
I know.
Eh?
What?
Ah!
Yaah!
Wow!
Yaaah!
Yaaaaa!
Yes!
Kyaaaaa!
Yayaa!
Ah
Yes, here is Asakusa
What? The child got on the troll bus and ran into President Akashima's house?
What did you say?
Hmm...
Hey, Kankichi!
Huh?
Mr. Ken!
Are you guys alright?
Yes!
Mr. Ken, a baby will be born and we will...
What? Really?
It will be born?
It was born...
Congratulations, Mr. Ken!
You did it!
Mr. Ken, it's your dad!
Hahaha
Congratulations, Mr. Ken!
Wow!
Here, you're a healthy boy!
A boy! You did well, Mr. Ken!
It would have been dangerous if you had been a little bit later.
It's all thanks to these children!
Hehehe
If that's the case, it can't be helped!
Wow!
Hehehe
You did it!
Kankichi made him look like Mr. Ken!
Hehehe
Phew...
No matter how urgent the situation is, he can't get into the house on a troll bus.
After that, it must have been hard.
Yes, that's right!
It's a great thing from my father and my teacher!
But that incident was in the newspaper, and the people in the city were on my side!
Hrm...
Well, that president has been paying his insurance bills and has rebuilt the house.
Well, even so, the trolley bus was a gentle vehicle in the global environment.
The sound is quiet and the exhaust gas does not come out.
I feel like it's a vehicle that is needed in this era.
That's right. But it was different back then.
The number of minibuses and taxis increased, and most of the passengers did not get on the trolley bus.
The traffic jam is getting worse day by day.
The trolley bus is no longer the foot of the common people, but a lazy and annoying being.
The trolley bus was driven out from the road and was dropped off one after another.
Is today the last day?
I want to run more.
Hey, you guys are here too?
K-san!
You're here after all.
Yeah. I have to see the last flower road.
Huh?
That's the 50th-generation 77 vehicle K-san was driving.
But the slider is worn out...
You don't have to take it back, do you?
Also, the trolley bus is too slow.
Never again.
Ken looked very sad at that time.
I think the world has become richer than before, but I wonder if that's all right.
That's right.
Chief.
Ryotsu sometimes says good things.
There are many good things that people have lost in exchange for wealth.
I almost forget about it.
Chief, I won't forget.
In your case, you won't forget, but you won't progress.
You won't be rich, and you'll be poor in your head.
You're still a child when you drove a trolley bus.
You guys are also...
Well, humans don't have to force themselves to change.
No, in your case, you should change a little.
No way!
Chief!
The afternoon after the rain, as if someone was calling me
I walked looking back
"Mom, let me hold your hand."
I felt that strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black tile of the arcade
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgets
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above his eyes
Look up at that corner
I can see everyone
There is a turtle, there must be a turtle
Come on everyone
I'm done
To the town of the future
Thank you
"3.3.3"
3.3.3 is my birthday
However, I am in trouble each time
I thought this year
Where am I going
Next time, "Hisan San Zan Birthday"
Thank you
"3.3.3"
There is a turtle there
"Akito Kameari"
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!