"Beyond the Wall"
When you're watching TV, try to keep the room bright and away from the TV.
Come to my place if you don't have the money.
I don't have money, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I wonder what will happen in the meantime.
Come to my place if you don't have the money.
I don't have money, but I'm worried.
Look at the red clouds that are burning.
I wonder what will happen in the meantime.
I know, I know, I know.
If you know, come to me quietly.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
I don't have money, but I'm worried.
Angel 7 vs. The Wild Japs
This is the new mini-PATO.
You can control the bike with this.
For example, the recent mini bike incident
You can't chase the mini pato in the alley
But this pato can chase you anywhere
I see
The scooter is automatic and has mobility
I understand that but it's too much to buy a uniform
And this is the new uniform
The female pato team, Ladies Riders Angel 7
Take a different pose
Raise one leg and swing
It's very popular
It's like a motor show
It's something that Companions patrol as it is
It's more flashy than Race Queen
But why wasn't the white-collar member Otohime chosen?
I was told to become a member
But the costume...
Well, it's not that
Well, that's enough for the shooting
Let's do the actual performance of the criminal arrest
Please come over there
These thieves are...
Dato!
In the 21st century
Don't think of me as a thief
Please come over here
I'm not the one who's being kept
I'm a giant that was made up of a joke
Well, what are you going to do?
If you're going to run away with a motorcycle, you're going to have to
A professional motorcycle, a Honda
No, me!
And I'm a man who knows how to escape the city
I'll run away with you
Mr. President
I think that's good
I wonder if it's okay
No problem
We'll catch you in 7 people
Don't you have a hard time later?
A professional white-collar member is the culprit?
It's going to be a good article
No, I'm not the culprit
It's okay, you can escape
No, you guys
I'll catch you
Okay, I'm running away
I'll catch you in a costume scooter
Bye
Good job
We're both great
I wonder if you can really catch me
Angel Seven, line up
We'll follow you in a row
Yes, I understand
I'm going to catch that one right away
I'm going to arrest him
I'll catch him right away
Okay, let's go
Angel Seven, it's time to go
The car chase is starting
See you
The enemy is approaching!
I see!
Two criminals!
Detect!
Roger!
Auto-cruise on!
Marking!
What?
A rifle?
What's that?
It's a benton!
L-System, respond!
Turn left and stab him!
Roger!
It's so conspicuous!
Damn!
I can't believe they're using weapons!
You two over there, stop!
I'm going to stop when I'm caught!
Even before that!
Damn!
I'm going to get you!
He's not going to stop!
Oh, no!
Stop the force!
Fire!
I'm going to stop you!
Damn!
Ouch!
My eyes!
Be quiet!
I caught him in 20 minutes.
I told you I didn't want to!
Why do I have to be caught like this?
It seems that the fact that you caught the senior has become a propaganda.
Damn!
I didn't expect to cooperate with you.
Well, there are so many beautiful girls like models.
I want to catch them, too.
It's a great reaction.
It seems that the applications for the photo book are coming one after another.
Hey, look!
The figure is also scheduled.
It's like an idol.
All right, we'll do it too!
We'll do it!
Wild Yano-Tai?
Why do you make such a thing?
I can't leave it to only girls.
Does the president accept it?
No.
I just made it today.
But I'll make it great and let them admit it.
Oh?
The contact.
The Kittakuri group is tracking.
The location is Kanna-no-homen, Kameari-kousetei.
It's right around the corner.
Angel Seven, go!
I'm going to do it!
Awesome.
Let's do it.
Let's do it!
I made it so that this is bad.
I'm going to make this greater.
It is so bad.
I'm going to make it worse.
I lost my back.
Yoon Shun-tan, I'm not going back.
Twice the fast rate.
I think it doesn't matter to me, the low combat rate will be approximately here.
So I'm going to come on to the slope of Kamikaze, and I'll return with this.
Hurry up!
Resonance is fine.
I'll be like a human being after all.
Yeah, wait a minute.
Help!
Help me!
Damn you!
C-cake!
Sorry!
Let's get him!
My eyes are spinning!
No way!
How cruel.
He did too much.
Damn! I managed to get a hand!
Maybe you were a little too rough.
Hey, did you see that?
Angel 7 is being animated!
What?
It's so gorgeous out there.
All right, I'm going to make it wild!
Wait! I'm going to punish you!
You're just running away from the situation.
One, suck the lifeblood of the human world.
Two, the evil business of our people.
Three, the evil of this world.
I'll beat you up!
Varva!
Let's make a deal!
I will execute you!
I can't believe it.
He's too much!
Idiot!
A bunch of villains.
My lord!
We regret that we haven't done enough, so please accept this stage as official.
Will we accept such a thing?
Then I'll dismiss immediately!
Sorry...
Speed violation?
No way!
Hey you, dark-skinned bike! How long are you going to drive!?
Stay behind me and stop!
You don't remember the culprit?
*sigh*
I couldn't see his face with the helmet on.
Or rather, aren't you the culprit?
W-what?
That's right! You made a Wild Yaro team and made us your enemy!
Don't be stupid!
You're not as bad as you think you are!
Huh?
Yes.
Huh? He attacked me again?
Huh?
Okay, I'll be right there.
What about the bike?
I wonder if Angel Seven's team members were attacked again.
Yes, I'll be right there.
Let's go!
Yes!
Erika, are you okay?
What kind of guy is the culprit?
The bike is an old Honda 7-Hand.
CB750?
Yes, it was black.
What about the license plate?
I tried to look at it, but it was bent over.
So, it was the Wild Yaro team's fault.
Probably.
How did you find the bike?
It's not that difficult to find out!
Let's leave it to him.
It's been a while.
Do we have any time to think?
No, it's been a while.
To I soldier.
You're the one who knew it, right?
Ah!
The Kanto...
...Man...
...Union...
The Kanto Man's Union?
Do you know?
Eh?
What?
Is that the bandit group you were heading to before you joined the police?
I think it's a bandit group.
W-wait a minute!
It's definitely a bandit group, but...
...I don't think the Kanto Man's Union would do anything to hurt people.
Don't bring the matter to the investigation.
Let's go.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Tell me.
It's not me!
It's some mistake!
Don't take a picture!
Don't be so rampant!
H-Honda-san!
I won't do it!
Please help me!
You don't lie to me, Hijikata.
Let's go.
So you're the one.
I'm the one.
You're the one, aren't you?
You're the one.
What are you doing?
Don't worry about it.
There's no need to kill me.
What do you think?
It looks like the same bike that the Angel Sevens witnessed.
Senpai, look!
What's wrong?
The culprit said that he had the number reversed, right?
But, didn't he fix it?
Look closely. There's no trace of him having it reversed.
There's no trace of him having it reversed!
That's true.
I think the elbow is white.
Now we can patrol without any worries.
Yes! Then, let's head over there.
Eh? The Miwa and Sato units were attacked?
Ohare-kun went to the hospital.
What do you mean? The culprit was arrested?
That means the real culprit is somewhere else.
The elbow was in the investigation room when they were attacked.
It seems that the real culprit didn't know that the elbow was caught.
The real culprit attacked the Angel Sevens.
The Angel Sevens are slow.
It seems that they were aiming to push the crime onto the elbow.
But, they ran away and hid themselves.
I will definitely catch the real culprit.
Sakai-san, I think that the real culprit will attack the remaining two of you.
I... I will stop the Angel Sevens.
Please wait, Sakai-san!
I will definitely protect you, so please be a thief.
A thief!?
You must be joking!
Anyway, I will stop.
S-Sakai-san!
I-I can't be a thief either!
I will be a thief.
Nana-chan...
If you wear a helmet, I don't think the culprit can tell who is the real culprit.
B-But...
If you protect me, I won't be afraid.
Nana-chan...
Alright!
I will help you to rebuild the Wild Yaro team!
Please wait, senpai.
I'm sorry, but please let me do this job alone.
What?
I will go and save the three of you!
N-no!
I will do it on my own!
Come on!
You two!
The culprit has appeared!
Get on the sidewalk and stop the scooter right away!
Yes sir!
Tch! He noticed us!
You too, CB750! Stop right there!
That's funny.
Interesting.
Damn it! He's driving like a normal person!
Honda-san!
Don't worry.
Honda's white bike has a starter.
I'm getting excited, bro!
He's playing a joke on me.
I'm going to beat you!
I can't believe I can do this!
You can do it, Okita!
Follow me, bro!
I'm going to beat you!
Okita, I've decided.
After me, you'll be the second head of the Kanto Men's Federation.
Bro...
I wanted you to follow the head of the person who loves bikes and the wind.
Okita, will you follow me?
Yes!
I'll make the Kanto Men's Federation
into a men's rebel!
No doubt about it.
It's Okita.
Okita!
You're Okita Ryuuji, right?
I knew it!
Why did you do such a stupid thing, Okita?
I couldn't stand the mess of the Kanto Men's Federation!
They're going to run around with women on their asses
because I quit!
So I'll becomes a Nampana-bosougoku.
You should've just said so!
I did!
So what did Hijikata always say?
Okita,
you're not like your okay.
What?
Mices are for having fun with girls.
The time when men loved the wind
was over now.
I understand how you feel, but it's not good to have Angel Seven involved in this.
Okita, please do it!
You can do it after I win, bro!
What?
You're a coward!
Okita!
Ah! Honda-san's white seal disappeared from the navigation!
What did you say?
Honda-san...
Honda-san!
H-Honda-san...
He'll never die from his favorite bike!
There! It's Honda!
Honda-san!
Hey! Honda!
Are you okay? Okita-kun?
My leg... I think I fell.
Honda!
Honda-san!
You did it, Honda!
Are you okay, Honda-san?
Yeah...
Honda!
Ah...
You're like my little brother, Okita.
Please take care of me, Senpai!
Hmm?
Hmm...
So that's how you are.
Looks like you won't be able to walk anymore.
Now, rolled over here!
I want to help you.
Ouch!
Brother...
You weren't anything like you used to be.
I'm so glad.
Thank you, Sutan.
Don't say that, you idiot!
Konda-san...
Otohime!
Leave her alone.
Next Episode
"The End"
What are you guys doing?
You're being underestimated by the Nostalgia Club.
-Go and take care of Koda. -Yes, sir.
It seems like Honda has finally recovered.
Yes, it's the usual Mr. Honda.
Mr. Honda, I've made a sandwich.
Please eat it.
Nana-chan!
I'm happy, I'm happy.
Well, it's the usual Honda too.
Looks delicious.
Let's eat it together, Nana-chan.
What's wrong?
Ryo-san's "Why is it?"
Ryo-san's eyebrows look like black black eyes
Why is it?
He wears sandals but he runs really fast
Ryo-san always has his arms around his head
Why is it?
He's so fast but he's so popular
It doesn't matter
The title of this anime is so long
"Why is it?"
Why is it?
Kankichi, Mikan is so cute
Let's take her for a walk
Oh no
Mikan is so hot
Lemon is following her for a walk
What should we do, Kankichi?
Next time, Lemon's raising a child
Please watch!
There's a turtle over there
There's a turtle for sure
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!