Translated by Releska
When you watch TV,
try to light up the room and look away.
I look at the setting sun,
floating on the riverbank,
and look at the sunset.
When I kick the pebble,
I jump to the foot.
I wonder if I'm going to the gym
where I was jogging.
I was laughed at
as if I was a baby.
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere,
I'm not sure
what to say.
You don't know
where to turn.
The reason why you are
stirring up is
that the setting Annyeong
can't be turned off completely.
I don't know
what to look for but
Tomorrow will be over like this
I lost my happiness because of Kazushika Shiba
I realized it, because I'm such an idiot
This is my favorite person
Let's go!
Wow, this is great
I can see the beautiful view of the city
Look at the number of tombo
There are many tombo and hotaru in Komachi's country
Really? I'm looking forward to it
Kei is like a child
Right, Komachi?
Hmm?
Ah, that's right
I'm glad you kept it a secret from Ryo
Even though the nature is so luxurious
It's a game, a karaoke, it's noisy
Reiko, if you make a rumor, it will be a shadow
Behind you
Eh? Eh?
Do you need anything?
No, nothing
I'm really sorry
You're surprised, right?
I just got scared
I have to do something
I'm getting closer to home
Hey, mom!
What are you doing?
Mom, what is this?
What do you think, Komachi?
Did you like anyone?
I didn't like anyone
I don't want to get married yet
I'm going back to the summer vacation anyway, so it's fine to have a date.
No, I have one or two lovers.
That's a lie.
It's not a lie. I have a lover.
Then bring him to my house.
If you can't bring him, I'll talk about the wedding here.
I'll take you there.
I understand.
I'll take you there for the summer vacation.
Don't be surprised.
I don't want to have a date.
But what should I do?
I have to hurry up and make a lover.
I made up my mind.
If I want to make a lover, I have to find Nakagawa.
I don't care if it's not a real lover.
At least, I want to be a lover while I'm in the countryside.
I'll go get a lunch.
I need you to take care of me and Nakagawa.
Um, Nakagawa.
What are you doing here?
So you're staying here.
Keshijin.
How did you get here?
What?
I was sent to the station the other day by a Honda Bike.
I heard it's a countryside, but it takes three and a half hours from Tokyo to the bus stop.
I have to take the train and bus there.
It takes six hours.
I can go abroad in six hours.
What are you doing here, Keshijin?
You can't do that if you want to make me a lover.
I can't do that even if I want to be a beast!
Hey, Reiko! Did you buy my part?
Ryo-chan, you really followed me.
This is not a joke! Are you really going to follow me?
Of course! I don't know what mistakes will happen if I am young!
We won't make a mistake!
That's right! You are the one who followed me!
Don't talk like a kid!
You are a gorilla who grew up in a jungle.
You are the one who fooled the city on your day off and dressed like a high school girl!
You should dress properly on your day off!
Come on, Hesho!
I'm getting a nosebleed.
Ouch!
I won't take you!
I will definitely follow you!
Well, well, Senpai.
It can't be helped that you have followed me all the way here.
If you are with a man like this, it would be better to die.
I'll follow you like a cockroach!
We will soon arrive at Oyamakawa.
Oh, we have to get off next.
Please be careful.
Next?
Here.
You'll take the train again from here, right?
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.
It's actually the next autumn.
So I told you not to take me.
Hey, Kobachi!
You fooled me.
I'm not a man who gives up on things like this.
Alright!
Go!
Okay,
Here I come!
Ouch!
I'm so happy!
I was so happy when the genius came to give me a present.
But I don't think you can give up so easily.
That's right.
Oh, I'm going to make a call.
If you can make a call, it's now.
Um, Nakagawa-san.
Oh, that...
I caught up.
It's mine now.
Oh, it was a good chance.
You idiot.
Shut up!
I'm going to fly, Nakagawa.
What?
Well, then, please.
That's Ryo-chan.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Could you go over to the里?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Well, that's it.
I'll see you in less than a day.
What's the next bus?
"Before the school, before the school..."
As expected of Ryo-chan, he can't keep up with this.
I don't know.
If you say the senior's persistance, it's really more than a cockroach.
Finally, I got to the point where I couldn't shoot.
Go! Run!
Come on!
No, hurry up!
I'm home!
You've come a long way.
Thank you for your help!
Dad, Mom, Reiko-senpai, and me...
It's Ryo-tsu, the senior!
There's really nothing here.
Ryo-chan!
Did you really catch up with us?
Of course!
Mom, I'm glad the watermelon is cold.
Mom?
Tsu-tsu-shi, Mom, is that okay?
I'll put you to sleep in the cow's den.
Cow's den?
Stop it!
See? That's what a cow says.
Shut up! Do you understand cow language?
As expected of the rural people, they're different.
You're so annoying, Shinmachi Shoto!
It's all because of theEh?
These two are always like this.
They're good at breathing, aren't they?
I guess the more they argue, the more they get closer.
Oh, I'm Nakagawa.
Really?
Let me go!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Let go of me!
I'm sorry!
Stop earlier.
The watermelon is cold, and I've just picked some tomatoes.
Huh? Watermelon?
Thank you, mother.
Master Koraken! Don't be so dirty!
You're taking it easy. I'm glad you came.
You're right.
You're manly.
Huh?
You're a nice person.
Y-Yeah.
I can't take it easy.
I have to ask Nakagawa-san to act as my lover soon.
I wonder if we can be alone somehow.
The corn has been boiled. How is it?
Here you are.
Thanks.
Ryo-chan, you're too kind.
That's better.
You're more kind.
We might be together for a long time.
You're right.
There's a river nearby.
That's right. Isn't it cute?
That's great. Let's go!
That's it! That's where we're going!
He's running away!
Here!
He's gone.
That way!
Let's catch him!
What should we do?
There's a hole!
I've got a chance!
Leave it to me.
Alright.
Please, Ryo-chan.
I've got a chance!
There!
There it is!
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
If he plays with fish, we won't catch any thieves!
It's alright!
There!
Who are you?
Oh, sandals.
Don't lose, Nakagawa! Go!
Kei!
Thank you.
It's hot!
He's a bother, after all.
What? Are you still bothering me?
I'm serious.
I told you he's a bother because he's a bother.
Don't wear that hat, you're a man and a woman.
It's a big show!
Oh, it's pretty good, isn't it?
I wonder if I can be alone with Nakagawa-san.
It was fun!
It's nice to be out in the countryside.
Hey, hey.
Right now,
I've come up with an idea.
Why don't we go to the Kimo Dameshi?
There's a good place nearby.
Kimo Dameshi?
Is this the place?
To do the Kimo Dameshi?
It's a pretty old tunnel.
Yeah.
It seems to have been abandoned decades ago.
This tunnel is said to be run by a ghost train.
A ghost train?
Really?
Yeah, it is.
It's about the Pacific War.
There was an air raid.
The tunnel collapsed due to a bomb.
The train was destroyed.
It seems that all the people who were on it have died.
It seems that no one is living here.
It had been launched.
Theziehen and I went with the train.
It was the last train.
It wasn't the last train.
But after that, there was another.
the last train.
It was the last train.
And one thing led to the end.
Ya, it was the last train!
It was the last train.
Nakagawa and I will compete who can go further and get back home.
Sounds fun, right? Let's go, Nakagawa.
Hey, hey. Are you seriously going to test your guts?
What?
It's fine. This way, Kei-chan and I can be alone.
What are you going to do if we're alone?
I thought Komachi-chan was acting weird.
What are you talking about?
It has nothing to do with Ryo-chan.
I'm sorry.
I'm finally alone, but I can't hear anything.
I have to hurry up and tell him!
U-Um...
Nakagawa-san...
I have a request for you...
It's like you're confessing your love.
Please tell me.
N-Nakagawa-san, you're so bold...
What is it? Tell me.
U-Um...
It's fine if you're here, but in front of your parents,
can you...
Can you...
Can you be my lover?
I-I can't...
This weakness...
Show me your heart...
Is this supposed to be...
You can't.
You don't have to play after me.
relationships here...
Answer me.
Say, okay?
No.
My eyes...
Gyaaaaah!
That's Komachi's scream!
Oh! Oh!
It's you!
Huh. You know me well.
Piece of cake.
What?
Congattoryu Ninjutsu Saigo Koganemaru?
Nice to meet you.
Then what was Nakagawa-san's voice like?
"Ninpo, talk to me!"
"Let's kiss our love, Japan!"
"That's terrible!"
"Who made a door here?"
"Be quiet!"
"N-N-Nakagawa-san!"
"Sorry, it's not him!"
"Kissing our love..."
"What?"
"No, he did it again!"
"Ow, ow, ow!"
"What the hell was that?"
"I thought it went well."
"You're Gormo's grandpa, aren't you?"
"What are you doing here?"
"I'm training for a camp in Ninjutsu."
"I'll find you! Farewell!"
"What are you doing, Gormo?"
"I'm training for a camp in Ninjutsu."
"How dare you hide from me!"
"I don't want to!"
"How dare you!"
"So maybe you're in this tunnel, too, Volu?"
"That guy's scary. What if there's a ghost train in this tunnel?"
"A-a-a-ah!"
"A-a-a-a-ah!"
It's Borubo.
I ate the sand.
Borubo!
Idiot!
It's me!
Ryotsu, why are you here?
I see.
But is it true?
There's a ghost train in this tunnel?
If something like that happened, the tunnel would be destroyed.
Grandpa.
By the way, what time is it now?
Well...
It's just 0 in the morning.
I don't want to.
I'm getting scared all of a sudden.
Hey, let's go back.
Yeah.
Why are you scared?
You said you'd try it yourself, didn't you?
Even if you say that...
Ghost train is a story of creation.
The tracks are vibrating.
Again?
You can't scare me.
I'm not lying.
Put your feet on it.
Oh, it's true.
But why?
Something's running on the rails.
What do you mean?
Do you know?
It's coming.
It's the real ghost train.
No.
No way.
I can't believe it.
I can't understand how.
I'll cut you off later.
Huh?
I'm not scared of you.
The grass on the road is against us.
Get lost!
Nobody's talking to me anymore.
What special issue do you need here?
Yaaay!
Not this one!
It's a diesel locomotive!
What?
What were you doing here?
What are you doing?
We're growing mushrooms!
Mushrooms?
It's wet in the tunnel, so it's perfect for growing mushrooms.
We'll harvest it by night to get it in the right place.
You're making things so confusing.
What's that sound?
What?
It's the missile from before!
Oh no! It was an automatic pursuit!
That's ridiculous!
What?
Yaaay!
What's that sound?
What?
You guys...
What is it, Dad?
Ryotsu-san, I'm a mischievous child...
Please take care of me.
They're all misunderstanding me!
I'm not a spoiled child like you, you can't blame me.
You can turn me into a spoiled child!
What did you say?
There must be something fishy going on...
There must be something shady going on...
I don't know about you, but it doesn't seem to be us.
Please stop right there.
I hate you so much!
If you think you're a stiff skeleton,
you think you're a meteor from space.
Then your body will get lighter.
Then you'll get heavier.
It's you again, Professor Ezaki!
Next time, "A Gift From Space."
Don't send it!
The End
kameari no hoshi ga kururi to wa o kai sa
Kore de ii darou!
ii wake nee darou!