Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you watch TV, ♪
♪ light up your room and look away! ♪
♪ Baby! ♪
♪ "Hello!" ♪
♪ "Goodbye!" ♪
♪ "If you're done, you can go home right away!" ♪
♪ Don't panic! ♪
♪ In this small town, ♪
♪ where are you going? ♪
♪ Hurry up and turn around! ♪
♪ Maybe, ♪
♪ there's someone better than me, ♪
♪ someone better than me, ♪
♪ if you're here, ♪
♪ let me hear it! ♪
♪ Let me hear it all night long! ♪
♪ I don't hate waiting, ♪
♪ because I'm a woman on the throne! ♪
♪ I don't want to lose, ♪
♪ I'm a woman on the throne! ♪
♪ I've loved you for ten thousand years, ♪
A谷洞犯罪
A new type is discovered using computers!
Younger boys are getting cheeky!
But the number of policemen has definitely reduced to deal with them!
But the number of policemen has definitely decreased to deal with them!
We predicted the situation of today and prepared a countermeasure.
Mr. Ohara.
Yes.
This is the ultimate police officer created through the 30 years of destruction and 500 million of money.
Go!
Robot officer!
What? The robot officer is coming?
Yes. The chief and Mr. Terai are heading here together.
It's not a place where a police officer called Mr. Robot would be.
No. It really is a robot.
It was created through the 30 years of destruction and 500 million of money.
I'm looking forward to what kind of robot will come.
That's right.
I have a bad feeling.
It costs 500 million.
There's no way such a strange robot would come.
Yes. Ryo-chan is thinking too much.
Shut up!
It's a robot designed by us, the chief.
Do you think we're expecting something like that?
It might be a robot that was put on a drum in the drum kit considering our age.
But it might be a giant robot.
Could it be that the vehicle has transformed?
It would be fun if it was such a robot police officer.
Why are you imagining all that trouble?
It's not strange to have a robot like that.
It's something we came up with.
Here it is.
Hello, everyone. Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is the 30 years of destruction and 500 million of money that the police officer 001 spent.
I knew it.
I see.
Then let me transform it right away.
What do you mean?
This vehicle will transform into a robot police officer, right?
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
Hey, Tera, give it to me.
Yes, sir.
How was it? Were you surprised?
It's just a human being.
What is this human being?
It's made by anyone, no matter how they look at it.
Don't be rude.
The 001 was made by 30 years of destruction and 500 million of money.
Oh, you guys.
You can say that because you haven't seen the 001 move.
All right. Let's move it.
Tera, please move it.
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
What kind of switch is this?
If you kick the hip, it will stop functioning.
It's the same as us.
It's a robot made by 30 years of destruction and 500 million of money.
It's better to have a human part like that.
It's just like that.
That's what it is.
Chief.
Let's put it in for the time being.
Yes, sir.
Let's start again.
Hello, everyone.
He spoke.
I'm the 001 of the Robot Police Force.
You guys heard me, right? I spoke Japanese properly.
How was it? You were surprised, weren't you?
It's not surprising.
I can talk on my computer now.
That's more fluent.
Don't put the computer with the robot made by the destruction of the 30 years and 500 million of money together.
Don't worry about what he says.
I welcome you.
Chief, if you want to shake hands, you should say you want to.
I see.
You're a bad guy.
Shut up. Robots are like that.
Let's shake hands, 001.
Yes, sir.
This is what happened, so I'll take a break for a while.
In the meantime, please take care of 001.
Yes, sir.
Especially Ryotsu.
If 001 is broken, I'll ask you to compensate.
Why me?
If you break it, you're the only one left.
001 is the 30th year of the original government.
You developed it with one million and five billion.
That's right.
I'll handle it carefully.
I understand.
Please.
What are you going to do, senior?
If you touch it poorly and something happens, the director will tell you to be quiet.
Let it go.
001 is in the middle of the room, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
001, go to the corner of the room.
Roger that.
All right, you guys stand there for a while, please.
You can concentrate on it slowly and smoothly.
And everyone...
Everyone of you.
I'm your karşı!
I'm your karşı- consigo!
I'm your karşı-yase!
I'm...
Really...
Pretty...
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
Why are you staring at me?
I didn't do anything like that.
I just feel like that, Senpai.
I can't move at all.
I see.
Speaking of which, the police doll I saw on the road was also creepy.
Do you feel the same way about this?
Alright, 0015, look over there.
Which is over there?
Turn right and look at the window.
Roger that.
Alright, I'll calm down and get back to work.
I told you not to look!
I'm not looking.
Well, go patrol somewhere else!
What do you mean, somewhere else?
Think it over!
Don't do that, Ryo-chan.
It won't work unless you give a specific order.
You're so troublesome.
Then let's take a ride around old Mitokai-dou from Kan-nana.
Roger that.
What was that?
Where on earth is Kan-nana?
What?
Say you don't know!
If you don't know, tell me!
At least remember the map software!
Senior, there's a CD-ROM on the desk.
Let's install it.
Sure thing!
The Z-Unit should be on the back...
Found it!
It's 5 inches!
What is this?
It's a floppy disk.
What? Isn't a floppy disk smaller?
15 years ago, a floppy disk was like that.
It was the most advanced technology at the time, but now...
What about the CD-ROM drive?
It's not installed.
Then how do you remember maps?
Don't worry. I can remember everything I see.
That requires advanced technology, doesn't it?
I don't know if it's low-tech or high-tech.
It said the memory has passed.
It's amazing!
In 3 minutes and 10 notes!
It's finished up to 500 pages!
If you spend 5 billion, that's an obvious result!
All right, stand guard over there.
Roger that.
Finally I get to pay than.
I wonder if you can handle it alone.
Don't talk to me about it if you have to do it alone.
That guy's using 5 billion money!
But I'm still worried.
It seems to be okay.
Watch out!
The object is approaching. Calculate the damage caused by the collision.
We did it!
Are you okay?
The upper body is fine.
The rear is fine.
The left is fine.
The right is fine.
The entire circuit is fine.
It's so sturdy.
That's what makes it a tower.
Wait.
I think I can make a fortune.
Mr. Ryozuno!
Hey, Honda. What's up?
I came to see the robot officer.
He's not here. Is he patrolling?
That's because Ryo-chan...
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, he's here.
Curry rice.
What is this?
What's this?
What does this employee do?
This is 001.
What?
This isn't a police robot?
No.
This is too old to be a police officer.
It can't do complicated work.
I'm trying to make it work.
Until this morning, I worked at the subway construction site.
After that, I delivered tissues in front of the station.
Yesterday, I made a waitress do the job at the family restaurant.
But the customer was angry and ran away.
What?
I am very nice.
I just want to help the society.
I am a person who makes my own decisions.
But I'm sure your part-time job is all for Ryo-chan.
What?
I can't help it.
I have saved money for him to make his pay.
I didn't know that the robot has a pay.
Thank you very much.
It will be 650 yen.
Thank you for the meal.
Please take it from your part-time job.
Yes.
I've already finished eating this plate.
Please take it home.
Yes.
He's using a robot worth 5 billion yen for his own use.
Yes, I have it every time.
Hey, wait!
I'm sorry, but can you give me a massage?
Yes.
Can you give me a massage?
When I made you work at the sauna three days ago, you were pretty good.
What? That's not true.
0015, give me a little more strength.
Yes, I understand.
Oh, that's good.
More.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch! Stop it!
I won't forgive you!
Ouch!
R-Ryo!
It seems the opponent forgot about the metal.
It's a matter of time.
Okay, I'm done with the shoulders.
I'll ask for the legs next time.
Isn't it moving a little strange?
Yes.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ryo!
Ryo-san!
Mr. Ryo!
Idiot! Idiot!
Checking the same mistakes is not panicking at all.
Huff. Huff.
What?
customs.
Customs, your pay must be paid properly.
If you can't pay, You may be fired.
By the way, the other day, I was part-time at the debt collection.
Really? That's not a big deal.
You're so kind.
The customer will pay for it.
Oh, that's great!
If you can't pay, here.
What are you doing?
Ouch.
Customer.
It stopped.
I see. There was a switch over there.
It was almost done!
Senpai...
The End
This is completely overheating!
Ryo-chan will use the steamer.
I just let it work for four days without rest.
According to this manual,
"You must stop intense movement within an hour."
What?
I thought it was just a hard work.
It's different from the shockingly strong one and the continuous operation.
What are you going to do, Ryo-chan?
If the manager finds out, it'll be a disaster.
Okay.
This robot was designed 30 years ago.
I'll repair it and show you.
It's a vacuum.
And there's so much.
It's true that it was like this 30 years ago.
It'll be a disaster to get the parts before the repair.
It can't be helped.
0015 will be pulled onto the truck to save the child
and will be disqualified.
But even if we bump into the truck,
it's still safe.
Then, it's like being crushed by a monster to protect the peace of the Earth.
Who would believe such a story?
I don't know.
There are still a lot of unknown creatures in the world.
Senpai, let's think of another way.
Is that so?
Ryo-san, this is bad!
What's wrong?
I just got a call.
The leaders are heading this way to inspect 0015 with the chief.
What?
You're injured, but it's bad, isn't it, Ohara-kun?
After all, you're a ninja today.
It's no big deal.
For the chief and the chief officer.
Here, chief officer.
Thank you, Ohara-kun.
It's no big deal.
We've been waiting, chief officer.
Thank you.
What about Ryo-san?
Senpai is on patrol.
Oh, I see.
That's more convenient.
And 0015?
Yes, I'm writing a report inside.
Okay, call him.
Yes.
0015, the chief officer is calling you.
How's 0015 doing?
Well, it's...
It's doing a great job.
I see.
It's been 30 years since it started.
It's been rejected by 5 billion people.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm 0015.
Chief officer, this is 0015.
It's the first time I've seen it move.
What? It seems to have shrunk a little.
It's moving and it's stopped.
It's a different impression.
And it's been on a lot of work lately.
Maybe the electricity is out of power.
What?
That's no good.
0015 is 30 years old.
It's worth 5 billion.
Hey, Terai-kun.
Get ready to charge.
What?
Charge?
But that's...
What are you talking about?
Get ready to charge.
Yes, sir.
I'm ready.
Hey, you still have enough energy.
So you don't have to charge it yet.
It's a robot, but it's a very reluctant one.
Terai-kun, charge it a lot.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and do it.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Ryo, forgive me.
It seems to be charged and rampaging.
No, I'm sure he's happy.
That's right.
Terai-kun, then please increase the power and make him happy.
Yes, sir.
As expected, with just a 30-year-old boy and 5 billion of range.
There is nothing more dynamic than joy in charging.
I see, I see, I see.
Terai-kun, that's enough.
Are you okay, 0015?
You bastard!
I'm not okay.
I just had to go to the electric display in a little while.
Let's solve this problem.
What is this?
You can solve it in 10 seconds.
What is that?
It's a question for the Nobel Prize in Physics.
This is...
Can we solve this?
Of course.
We can't understand it.
But it takes too much time.
That's right.
It doesn't need to be charged.
I see.
Alright, Terai.
Charge it immediately.
Yes, sir.
No, no, no.
More strongly.
R-0015, are you alright?
R-0015?
I-I-I'm alright.
What is this?
What's going on?
Well, this is the first time
I've used an electric vehicle motor in the past.
The same program that I used for the first time.
R-0015 is the only belki.
R-0015 is also monochrome.
But what does it mean?
If it is monochrome,
R-0015 is monochrome,
which means it works in any Hugh 외.
R-0015 is primary energy.
R-0016 is primary energy.
R-007 is primary energy,
which is only used for power storage.
And R-0018 is primary energy.
Damn, this is going to burn.
Oh, as expected!
That's because the 30-year-renewal cost 5 billion.
It seems that the pace is getting slower.
Ohara-kun, what's wrong?
I think the electricity is running out again.
Oh, I see.
Ah!
It's over.
I see, it's juice.
Oh, thank you.
But it's a robot, but it's going to go on.
That's how successfully it's made to be close to humans.
What kind of test are you going to do next?
Next, we're going to do a test in the water, so I'm going to go to a river nearby.
Oh, I see. I'm looking forward to that.
Then it's not a joke.
If you do anything more than this, I'll kill you.
Even so, my throat is dry.
All right.
Ah! There's a UFO outside the window!
What?
Where?
Where? Where?
0015, where is the UFO?
Ohara-kun, I think I saw something I shouldn't have seen.
Yes, me too.
I can't see anything.
Oh, right. This time, to the right.
Where is it?
Good job. You did a great job.
What are you talking about? I'm 0015.
Your face is the opposite.
What about 0015?
I'm 0015.
You're saying it's not both.
That's right.
Yes.
What? Is the nearby temple a fire?
Are the firefighters still there?
It seems to be caught in a traffic jam on the way.
Please do something.
There is an important statue that has been passed down for more than 300 years.
It weighs 200 kilograms...
It's all right.
Please rest assured.
We have an amazing robot police for such a time.
Right, Chief?
Yes, yes, Ohara-kun.
Yes.
It's 0015's turn.
I was overworked today and my body is...
What? Oh, is that so?
Chief, 0015 is in the fire by himself.
He's going to jump into the fire.
Oh, is that so?
Let's go.
Is there something you don't like about him?
No, he's shy because of his shy personality.
I see.
Ryo, give up.
If you can save this Japanese-class statue, you may be able to see 0015 more.
A little more?
Yes, you may be able to save your life.
No way.
Ryo-chan.
It seems that 0015 has been found out.
Yes, but it's about my senior, so I think it will be somehow.
Ohara-kun, is 0015 all right?
It's all right.
That man is immortal.
It's been 30 years and it costs 5 billion yen.
Oh, I see.
This time, I'm also going to lose.
0015, I found you!
There are pluses, but you got minuses too.
And you're going to lose too.
0015.
I want torang my career.
Look, but 0015 is...
I want to use 0015 to return our country!
0015!
It's an alien station that uses artificial satellites.
You'll be allowed to stay there on 001.
Alien station?
Now, we're going out.
W-Wait a minute! I'm actually a human!
Hey!
Damn! I can't take this off!
He suddenly became hot...
He went into the water and cooled himself, so he can't take it off.
Hahaha!
As expected of a 30-year-old boy who has spent 500 million yen on a child's play,
his father is also a human.
Come on, 0015, hurry up!
This isn't a joke, really!
Come on, 0015, let's go!
Wait a minute! I'm a human!
B-B-Boo-chan!
T-this can't be...
This can't be!
Come on, 0015!
0015, you have to stay with me!
0015, I'm not your father!
0015, don't go!
0015, I'll take care of you.
0015, come here!
0015!
I love you with tears that kiss me
How much can people get
With such irreplaceable things in their lives?
You are me, I am you
I was filled with just that
Just laughing at you
I felt that I was healed from all the pain
Are you that great a violinist, Strahd Batlius?
Is the violin that amazing?
Next time, Stradivarius
See you!