Translated by 方 Hou.
I look at the sunset that floats in the river
When I kick the stone, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I'll go after I save up
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win
The cityscape that does not change even one yawn is strangely kind
From the fountain to the sea of the sea of the sea
The sunset falls to the sea of the sea
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again in the Katsushika Shiba
I noticed
I'm stupid
"Demon Throne Disappeared"
Don't come!
Yatsu!
Y pais! Be careful!
Senpai!
Don't come!
Whoever comes, I shall never come down!
I'm not getting off!
If you don't want to get off, you don't have to!
But at least tell me why.
Here, a set.
Tell me, Junpei. What happened?
Mom broke the promise.
Promise?
It's a movie. It's a pecomon.
If I don't go today, it'll be over.
I see. So that's why you're going to strike the chimney.
Mom's always like that.
She says something like, "I made it."
But she thinks it's okay to break the promise with me.
I did it on my own! I promised!
It's kind of nostalgic to see the city from the chimney.
What? Ryo, did you go to the chimney too?
Yeah. There was no tall building back then.
It was even bluer.
I climbed the Senju Ghost Chimney.
It's even taller than this.
Ghost Chimney?
Yeah. It's the largest chimney in Japan.
There were few buildings back then, so you could see the bottom of the city from anywhere.
The four big chimneys are just as big as you can see.
The number of chimneys depends on the size of the city.
There are three chimneys on the Sumida River, and two on the Senju Bridge.
So, it's a ghost chimney.
Yeah. That's why I often encoded the number of chimneys that I could see.
I wanted to meet them in one place.
I know I said it was just one.
What are you two doing?
Ah!
Hm?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm in trouble. What should I do?
Did you lose the chain?
What?
Yeah. Lend me a hand. I'll fix it.
Thanks.
This is how you do it.
Hm? Wow! It's a secret base.
Wow! That's amazing.
Yeah.
See? I did it.
You're so clever.
Hehe. This is my morning meal.
Oh.
Hm?
Then, Mr. Densuke.
Yeah.
Thanks. You really saved me.
See ya.
Thanks, you guys.
Let's go home.
All right.
See you.
Thanks, you too.
Hey, Kanchi.
Garko, are you there?
B-yeah, it's a surprise.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow!
There are three people who are the problem.
It's a trio of three people: Tonpei, Chinkichi, and Kankichi.
The other three will be here soon, so don't be nervous.
Yes, sir.
We did it! We did it!
We did it!
Huh?
Ah...
Hey, who's that?
Who's the bad guy who did that?
Kankichi! It's you again!
You idiot!
Where's the money?
Professor Kyoto.
Huh?
I'm fine.
Well, this guy is...
It's okay.
He's my student.
What?
Yesterday's...
Nice to meet you.
Hey, how are you?
We are in our third division, so long as miss Kuruma is here,
We are the R Shanghi, Saiki and Yoko.
Let me introduce ourselves!
Hello everyone!
I'm Yoko Saeki.
Thud!
Thank you for watching!
If you like this video, please subscribe to my channel!
See you in the next video!
Please subscribe to my channel!
What are you doing at this late night?
Hey, wait!
I don't know!
Then who broke the cup in the classroom?
Who broke the cup in the classroom?
It wasn't me!
Liar!
I saw you peeping into this classroom last night!
That's...
Is that so?
Yes!
I see, you're all doubting me.
Look into my eyes.
Tell me the truth.
It wasn't me!
You can't be fooled, Mr. Saeki.
This is the most problematic student!
It's not!
You all know that, right?
I won the cup because I was active in the school sports competition.
Why would I break it?
I was active in the school sports competition.
Damn!
Stop it!
Kankichi!
Why?
You idiots!
......
Damn it. Why is everyone like this?
How stupid.
You too, Sensei.
Kankichi-kun! Kankichi-kun!
I knew it was here.
What? Sensei, you doubted me, didn't you?
That's not true. Kankichi-kun fixed my bicycle chain, didn't he?
No, that's not true. I did the bucket water.
Kankichi-kun, how many chimney can you see from there?
One, of course.
That's right.
You can see one chimney.
But that chimney is...
Actually, there are four.
Depending on the angle of view, one can be seen, two can be seen, and three can be seen.
That's why it's called a ghost chimney.
I know.
That's right.
Hey, Kankichi-kun. Don't humans think so?
What?
Depending on the angle of view, one person can see many things.
There's a rampage, there's a thought.
But the nature of that person doesn't change, does it?
The nature?
I wonder if it's the real thing.
I think Kankichi-kun's kindness for fixing that chain is true.
So let's be brave and be proud.
I believe that Kankichi-kun didn't do it.
Yeah.
Is that true?
Kankichi-kun, the two of you broke the dodgeball after school yesterday.
I finally found the girl who saw it.
It's Naohito and Kazuya.
Thank you, Tompei, Chinkichi.
You're my best friends, after all.
Damn it, I'll beat Naohito and Kazuya.
No, Kankichi-kun.
What?
Don't cause violence.
Yes, teacher.
Teacher?
What's Kankichi-kun doing out there?
Well…
Good for you.
Kankichi's image
Episode Five: Kankichi's Parce
And now for the Final erle noche
Kankichi's Perction
I can't get out of the hospital easily.
He also seems to be talking about something.
And then, I came to the school in the morning and brushed the blackboard.
I also decorated the teacher's desk with flowers.
It's a big deal when I come to visit my family.
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Kinjiro, don't study here!
Oh, no!
Don't sleep there!
The teacher will come soon, so please do it properly!
Mom, the teacher doesn't have a class, so please give me a course.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Oh, he's here.
Welcome, teacher.
Welcome.
That's not a joke.
This is my mother.
And this is my little brother, Kinjiro.
And this is my father.
This is my father!
What?
You're here!
Teacher, let's go.
I'll ask again.
But the teacher suddenly came to say goodbye.
Huh?
Teacher, are you going to quit?
Teacher Kuruma, the teacher of the teacher's husband, has finished his home treatment and will return to school next week.
So he's going to say goodbye to everyone soon.
No way.
Damn it.
I'll ask Teacher Kuruma to take a bicycle and get him hospitalized again.
I'll go to school.
You don't have to say that even if you're joking.
Well ...
Even if you go back to university, you won't forget about Kankichi and the others.
These three weeks were valuable experiences for me.
I felt strongly that I couldn't be a better person.
Don't be so shy.
You don't look like Kankichi.
Oh, that's right!
Let's go somewhere on Sunday tomorrow!
I haven't done my homework yet when you fixed the bicycle chain.
Let's go to the movies, Kankichi.
Movie?
What kind of movie do you like?
Well, well, I like the movie "Chanbara".
Then let's go to the movie theater.
It's decided.
Time is 10:00 in the morning.
Really?
It's a promise.
Yeah, it's a promise.
Yeah!
I'm going to the movie theater with Teacher Yoko alone.
Movie theater with two people?
This is like a date.
Yeah!
Brother, please be quiet.
You idiot!
I can't be quiet.
Yeah!
Kankichi, go to bed now!
Teacher, you're late.
The first meeting will start soon.
What's wrong?
Please call me.
Yes, this is Yorozuya change room.
Oh, it's Teacher Yoko.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I promised to go to the movie theater with Kankichi at 10 a.m. today.
Why did you suddenly get sick?
Yes, I have to take care of it today.
Well, it's hard, isn't it?
I'll tell you right away.
Please. I'm really sorry for Kankichi-kun.
No, you don't have to worry about that.
Kenjiro, go to the Odeon-zama!
Yes!
Teacher's tip!
I'm sorry, Kankichi-kun.
But I couldn't go yesterday.
I promised you.
I hate you so much!
Kago Sakuya.
Don't think that time is infinite.
Life has limits.
In this short life,
you can't live with others.
If you keep listening to that,
I'll have to say goodbye to Yoko Saeki-sensei today.
It was a short 3 weeks, but thank you for your hard work.
Where's Kankichi?
Kankichi-kun?
He left right after class.
What a pain in the ass.
Kankichi-kun.
If that's the case,
I feel sorry for him.
I hate you.
I hate you!
Kankichi!
Huh?
Here!
Yoko-sensei said that you should give this to him!
Dr. Yoko!
I told you I was going to go!
You looked lonely, Kanchi.
Kanchi.
What are you doing, Kanchi?
Take off all the curtains!
We're not done yet!
You're not going to be late for the train, are you?
The train to Uenori is already set, so it'll be fine.
Okay, hurry!
Uenori
It's huge when you look at it up close.
It's so big!
What are we going to do, Kanchi?
Once a man decides, he'll do it!
Watch out! It'll be bad if you get caught!
I know!
What?
Oh, no!
Hey, don't come in!
I know, Tompei!
It's Kanchi!
Kanchi, leave this to me!
Go!
Yeah, I'm doing it!
Hey, wait!
Kid!
Yay, over here!
Hey, wait!
Wh- where do you think you're going?
Jump!
Uh-oh!
What's wrong with you, huh?
Why aren't you jumping, you piece of sh...
I know I should jump too!
Jump!
I'm tired of standing on the ground like this!
I'm gonna jump too!
I can't get off!
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
You're coming, Kanchi!
Jump!
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
Go, get over here, Kanchi!
That's a chimney!
What?
The chimney in Sumida River is visible from the train!
If it's a chimney, you can't see it because it's hidden in the shadows!
You idiot!
You should have said that earlier!
I did say it!
Damn it! The train is coming!
What should I do?
Alright!
If I can get on the wind, I'll be fine!
I did it! I got on it!
Kankichi!
It's trying to fly over there!
What?
It's dangerous, Kankichi!
Alright, let's go!
What?
Ouch!
But I did it!
I'll get on it quickly!
Alright, Kankichi!
Hang in there!
I'll send it to Yoko!
Mom, there's something on the chimney!
The chimney?
What?
It's heavy!
Thank you, Yoko Sensei!
And I'm sorry!
If only she were here...
Thank you, Kankichi.
I'll be a good teacher.
Goodbye, Kankichi.
Did you see it, Sensei?
Kankichi, you're the best!
Idiot!
You all were sent to the police!
Do you understand?
And then I got in trouble by the police,
and the school,
and the parents,
and I got in trouble for the rest of my life.
The only time I got on the chimney...
was back then.
That's it.
I'm going to go now.
Ryo-san.
Junpei!
Junpei, I'm coming with you!
Mom, it's dangerous. Leave this to Ryo-san.
But she's my daughter!
Mom!
It looks like she's here to help.
Ryo-san.
Don't worry.
You're not going to get mad.
She's your mom.
Okay.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'll get off soon.
Junpei!
Okay, Junpei.
Just follow me.
It's harder to get off than to get on.
Okay.
I'm going to get off.
Ryo-san, you're too big.
Junpei!
Now, jump into your mom's arms.
What?
She'll hug you gently.
Okay.
Mom!
Junpei!
What a moment of excitement.
Mom!
You stupid boy!
Why are you bothering people?
You always say that.
I'm sorry.
Mom!
I feel sorry for you.
You were about to say you were sorry!
I want to say to someone who's sorry,
Is there a child in the world?
It's little.
She doesn't know.
If everyone understands this,
Then, I'm going behind you.
-Alright then. -Alright then.
He was taken away
From the town, that huge and brave figure
I can't see it anymore
It's for us
I feel like one memory is going to break
I didn't feel like that
I couldn't be the hero
Why did I get in such a locker
With a naked Honda
I want to be bullied by children
I have to be chased by a rugby club member
Or a female wrestler
It's unreasonable
Next time, the scary box man
Thank you
Translated by 方 Hou.
♪ But it's more powerful than anything else
♪ If everyone comes together here
♪ It's like a dream, the last energy
♪ Looking at tomorrow, yesterday, the new world, drawing the universe
♪ Standing on the ground, the stars with a wavy face draw a circle
♪ Drawing a circle
♪ This is good, right?
♪ There's no reason to say