Fast and Furious
That eel looked delicious.
How can I tell.
The restaurant it's small, but cheap and really delicious.
Yeah.
Even so, Seppai knows a lot of Ueno restaurants, doesn't he?
Since I was a kid, I used to come to Ueno often.
Huh?
There's still some rice bowl left.
Huh? What is it?
When I was a little kid,
It was a place that makes Bentendo round.
What?
We did a bicycle race in Shinobazu.
However, it crashed and we all jumped into the Shinobazu pond.
It was hard to get out of the bike and the body of the horse.
In addition, it was cold in December.
We set a fire on the side of Bentendo and dried it.
Then there was a coal mine nearby.
Did you set a fire?
That's right.
The fire suddenly burned up and burned down to Bentendo.
I was desperate to save the pond water with my shoes and extinguished it.
If you made a mistake, Bentendo was gone.
That's right.
Your old stories are dynamic and talkative.
I came close.
Let's go to my house.
When you watch TV,
please make the room bright and look away.
Come to me, the poor guy.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
See you one day.
I will be able to do it somehow.
I'm a poor guy.
Don't worry about me.
Come to me, the poor guy.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
Akane, who is burning with a fire
I wonder what will happen to her
You know that, right?
If you know that, then shut up and follow me!
Akane's clamoring
Steve!
Mr. Kan!
You come back, again!
Shut up!
Why did you visit me all of a sudden?
Hello! Long time no see!
Oh, it's Nakagawa-san.
Ah!
Ah, stop it!
Hey, let go, Kankichi!
You!
Oh, Kankichi.
Oh, it's Nakagawa-san.
Hello.
I heard the car stop, so I went out and it was them.
Don't lie to me!
Why did you bring the sales of the store when you were going out?
Was that so?
I can't forget things soon.
I can't go to the store again.
You were going to lose to Pachinko again, weren't you?
Now, give it back!
Hey, you're not like that.
You said it well, Kankichi.
That's why you're a stupid son.
Yeah, I want to cry.
Idiot!
Idiot?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Kankichi, Nakagawa-san,
can you drink some tea?
No, I can't drink anything.
I don't have to worry about it.
Let's go in.
Oh, my God.
The profit has become a pair.
I often say that.
What's this prediction?
If you make such a big prediction,
you'll lose a lot of money.
A big prediction?
I'll kill you!
This idiot father is so annoying!
Hey, senpai!
I can't help it.
Nakagawa-san, hold this.
Yes.
I'll drink it.
Stop it!
That's it.
Just a little bit more.
That's not enough,
your parents are such a parent.
Yes.
You two're so old.
Don't talk like a child.
Nobody talks about it.
You know,
in such a house,
report an album
and..
It's all Kim's wife's.
Kim's wife.
I've been told that I want to see the pictures of you as a child, but I haven't found it for a long time.
You're a wound expert.
You say it well. I'm the one who got hurt.
Then, do you have a picture of your senior when you were a child?
Yeah.
This is when Kinjiro entered the national junior high school, I took it in a photo studio.
What?
Kinjiro is the main character, but he stands out.
He's been like this for a long time, Nakagawa.
You haven't changed at all.
You're saying something strange.
My father was drinking a lot at that time.
You have a big face.
That's right.
That's when I won the boy's baseball.
Did your father become a coach?
Well, at that time, I was a senior.
I won the game.
You say it well.
On the day of the final match, my team's coach collapsed due to high fever.
I had no choice but to do it in return for my father.
Is that so?
I'm sure he was drinking on the bench at that time, and the referee warned me.
This idiot father.
You don't have an idiot father for your parents.
What?
Are you going to do it again?
This idiot father.
You two are telling me to stop.
You're a fool.
Hey, hey.
Let's go home.
I envy you.
What?
What's wrong, Mr. Nakagawa?
I don't have a single picture I took with my father.
Not even one?
Yes.
I've only met my father about 10 times since he was born.
Nakagawa's father works 72 hours a day.
He's the busiest super businessman in the world.
The male and female CEOs of the iron wagon team can vaguely see a bright future.
It's like a child's dream.
What?
I haven't taken a day off for that.
Ask him.
Are you not tired?
You're yelping to me.
He said he wanted to give me something important.
That world's busiest father did it on purpose?
Yes.
Hmm, I wonder what that important thing is.
But now we can take a picture with my father.
Okay, I'll take it.
So where are you waiting for me?
That's a little far.
New York?
No, it's further away.
Then Brazil?
No, further.
Brazil is on the other side of Japan.
There are no other far countries.
It's not a country, it's a space.
What?
What did you say?
Hmm, a space?
Hey, only people from Tokyo know that place.
It's famous because there's a race track.
I don't know.
Where in space?
It's a space station.
What? A space station?
Is it a meeting place in front of the station?
So stop with the local stuff.
My father is building a space station to run space travel in 2003.
So he wants to meet at the bottom of the site.
In the past, it was manga and SF, but now it's reality.
That's right.
It's a space station for SF movies.
It's two years behind the 2001 space travel.
Oh, the joke of 2001 space travel in elementary school was a joke.
You're so quiet, Ryotsu.
So when are you going?
Tomorrow.
There's a launch base on the Naka-Gawa Space Development People's Island.
We're going to launch it with the friendship rocket there.
The Naka-Gawa Space Development People's Island
Since the airspace of the Naka-Gawa Space Development People's Island is the station,
we're going to dock the rocket and meet there.
Tomo!
Keiichi!
It's a meeting of big family.
It's going to cost us a lot of money.
I see...
Here's the phone.
What? The launch is cancelled?
What?
Yes, yes...
Wait a minute.
Reiko-san, excuse me, could you give me the world map?
Sure.
The north is...
The east is...
Here?
Oh, got it. Thank you very much.
What do you mean?
My dad said he had an emergency, so he's going to go to Earth with a capsule rocket.
So, the location written on that map is the landing point?
Yes, so we changed our plan to meet there.
That's a great change.
What is it?
I think it's a helicopter to pick you up.
Well then, Chief, please give me a ride from today.
Nakagawa, I'm going to take a two-shot with my dad.
Please.
Then I'll take it.
I'm also on a paid leave.
You're already used to it.
The rest of your pay will be deducted from your salary.
B-chan!
Senpai, hurry up!
Okay.
Kei-chan, I hope you can meet your dad safely.
Yeah.
It seems we made it in time.
The landing time is in 12 minutes and 18 seconds.
I didn't know it would rain from the sky.
I remembered.
When I was in elementary school, my dad and I once took a private jet.
We met a storm above Matterhorn.
Keiichi, don't make such a fuss.
Y-Yes, sir!
You can't trust your father, can you?
No, I don't.
You're a good boy, Keiichi.
You have something you want to give me in the 21st century.
What?
You'll get through the Thunder Lord!
Hold on tight!
Keiichi, hold on tight!
When we climbed the clouds, the storm didn't go away.
It was still peaceful.
Dad, what do you mean?
My father became silent and stopped talking again.
I suppose he must have said what his father wanted.
It doesn't matter.
It's fine, but Chichitoko is too dramatic.
Normally when Chichitoko talks like that,
it's either after the sunset or after the catch ball.
This is normal in my house.
Oh! Keiichi-sama! It's a capsule!
Oh, Nagagawa! You can finally take a two-shot photo with your dad!
Yes!
Ah! It's burnt black!
What?
It looks like it took too much time in the pool.
It's dangerous!
Mr. Toto!
There's a possibility that the inside is also heated.
Open it carefully!
Roger that!
It's opened!
It's not here! No one is on board!
What did you say?
Where did you escape from?
I don't know.
Oh!
Yes!
Huh?
You're going back to Earth by shuttle?
What did you say?
You're arriving at the Miami Space Center.
I got it!
Another change!
I'll call the helicopter immediately!
Oh, please do that!
What did you say?
About an hour ago,
I went home alone to pick up something I forgot.
What a busy father!
So, where is your home?
My home is in 72 places around the world, including New York and Tokyo.
72 places?
Anyway, where is the closest home?
Well, Florida?
Okay, let's go there for the time being!
What?
Do you know where your home is?
Just now, I was contacted that I was heading to your home in New York.
Okay, hey!
It's New York!
Yes!
There's an airport and a golf course in the middle of New York?
What's wrong with your father?
So, where is your father?
He said that it would be private from now on,
and he didn't tell the company, me, or the destination,
so he ended up going out.
Oh my!
It's been a while!
No clue again!
Senpai, it's okay now.
I'm going to give up.
You idiot!
What are you going to do with that photo?
If you give up now,
you can never take a two-shot with your father again!
Senpai...
That's right!
Okay!
Let's give him some money!
What?!
He's been an individual who has lived on a daily basis for a long time,
I'll have to catch you if I don't do it.
I may never see you again.
You're right.
If you find the person,
I'll give you $20 million in cash.
Please put a full-page advertisement on the newspaper.
$20 million?
I understand.
One dollar is 120 yen.
That's...
24 billion yen!
Again!
I'll find you!
I'll get all the cash!
Okay?
What?
You'll give me $20 million?
I'm in!
Send me the picture of President Nakagawa
through e-mail.
Roger that.
Nakagawa, you have your father's picture, right?
Yes, this is it.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Send me the picture of President Nakagawa
through e-mail.
I'll take this.
I understand.
Okay.
President Bakuryu is okay with this.
Nakagawa, you use your power
and find the whole of the United States
and the whole world!
Yes, sir!
Use all the land and sea
you can use to find him!
I'm Ryuden from President Bakuryu.
What?
I just secured a body in San Francisco.
All right!
You don't have to 이것.
The public will believe whatever you do
and as long as the public packed inside of Japan,
That's why...
The youths move on.
I want to carry this sword.
Why?
Because of you!
You can bring me the sword!
Well,
Dad!
I'm sorry I'm working!
This is the only way!
No!
It's not Dad!
What did you say?
You look like him, but you're a different person!
Look at the picture!
Even if you say that, I can only see your profile.
Ah!
It's me!
What? Did you find it?
Where is it?
It's the entertainment world.
I'll get closer to confirm it.
I'll take a picture and send it to you.
I can't see your face!
Make the picture more up!
Did you hear?
Give me an order right away!
There's no mistake!
Alright! It's the entertainment world!
I was preparing for it.
Make sure you shop through the internet!
Dad...
The color!
His face is completely different!
Wow, that's amazing.
Oh, Mentor...
I feel tired because I've been moving around,
so I can't go on.
ait's just the time, Mentor!
I found it again!
Me, too!
"Nagagawa"
Thank you for your hard work.
It costs 2.4 billion yen.
I need you to check it properly.
I've already arrested these 12 people.
Look at this, Nagagawa.
It's my father.
My father is full of them.
My father is...
Get a hold of yourself, Nagagawa.
Let's go to all the scene.
Get your fighter planes ready.
I'll go buy the plane tickets.
How is it? Is it real?
I... I... I see differently.
How is Switzerland?
The... the... the beach is totally different.
It's Egypt!
My chin is too much cracked.
How is Brazil?
It's... it's so... it's so...
There's no bath!
How about China?
My head...
I have no hair...
I can't take it anymore...
Hey! Don't sleep! 2.4 billion!
Don't you want to see your father in the middle of the night?
My father must have become a star...
Look, over there...
What are you talking about?
Don't give up!
2.4 billion will be a star if you don't find it!
Oh, father!
What? Where?
When I close my eyes,
I see my father behind my eyelids.
That's your mother!
My father is laughing...
Hold on!
Nakagawa!
Well, do you think I'm ready?
Ryotsu! Nakagawa!
I couldn't find it even when I searched the whole earth!
I didn't find any clue!
Kei-chan is also broken.
I gave up on my money.
I'll do the public investigation.
It's Kei-chan's phone!
It's an email from your father!
What?
I heard he's in Japan.
No way!
He's not in Japan!
I didn't think he'd be in this place!
There he is!
I really didn't want to see him.
He's Nakagawa Oki's father!
What?
Father!
Oh, Keiichi!
Keiichi!
Father!
Thank you, Nakagawa.
Thank you, Senpai.
Keiichi, you don't have time.
Yes.
I have something for you.
I was planning to give it to you last year,
but it's been a year.
Yes.
That's it!
A toy bottle!
It's a toy bottle
that you can get
by collecting five gold or silver octopus
in an octopus ball.
When Keiichi went to elementary school,
I asked him what he wanted in the future,
and he said he wanted this.
So I applied and got it.
I kept it for a long time,
and I finally got it today.
President, it's time.
Yes.
Well then,
let's meet again in a few years!
Goodbye, Keiichi!
You're such a busy father!
Kei-chan!
Hang in there!
I'm tired.
But it was really good
to take a picture with my father.
The S蓮
#1
I don't want to be like that
If I go down the wrong way
The moon will run away
Because now is not everything
Don't worry too much
Even if I lie and cheat a little
I'm helping someone sometimes
Baby, do you know me?
I'm heading to tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't be rotten
I'll do what I have to do
Cute breathing
It's hard to understand
I want to show it
It's better than seeing it again
Na na na na
Ah, I'm hungry
I can't wait to have breakfast
I want to eat
Dog, grandma, dog
OV champion
Are you all in my way?
Let me eat
Next time, Ryo's long day
Thank you
There's a wall over there
Oh, there's a wild wolf
Come to our town
Thank you