"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
"The
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The
One
Who
Loves
You"
"The One
Who Loves You More"
"The One Who Loves You More"
"The
One Who Loves You More"
"The One Who Loves You More"
"Not
I think you all know him, but let me explain to beginners who don't know him.
His real name is Neruo Higurashi.
He works in the same police station as us, Kameari Park.
He has superpowers such as awareness, drive and fire.
He solves unsolved cases one after another.
But he uses superpowers to use his body.
He consumes his body excessively.
That's why he sleeps 20, 50 hours more and more.
Finally, he wakes up only once every 4 years.
To be compared to the Olympics, people call him the Olympic man.
That's all.
What? Higurashi was walking?
But Higurashi must have been sleeping for 4 years.
He woke up in the year of the Atlanta Olympics.
The next one will be in 2000.
Isn't it?
Isn't it someone else's sky?
No, it's not.
I doubted for a moment, but there's no doubt about it.
He was wearing a business suit, but it was completely Higurashi.
Higurashi doesn't wear a suit.
And he was walking in Shinjuku.
But Higurashi gets really bad mood when he wakes up outside the Olympic city and goes crazy.
I see.
He woke up between Seoul Goring and Barcelona Goring.
He's more terrifying than the Daimajin.
He can easily blow up one or two buildings.
What?
So far, there's no damage to his supernatural powers, but it'll be bad if it happens.
Ryotsu, go and check Higurashi's room.
Yes.
Senpai, you just need to check whether he's sleeping or not, but you don't have to dress like this.
You don't know because you've never woken him up.
I know.
But Higurashi's room is more terrifying than the Amazon jungle.
When I went to wake him up two and a half years ago, it was really scary.
I think it was the deepest room.
Huh?
It's too beautiful.
No way.
He's still awake.
Oh, I can hear a song from inside.
What?
This is Kochikame's ending song.
No way.
The ending song he sang when he woke up was "Hofudiran's Smile", so he doesn't know the ending song now.
The key is not locked.
What?
Open the door.
We need to check the inside.
Yes.
What?
He's awake.
I knew it.
Hey, Higurashi.
What?
Huh?
Honda-senpai.
What?
Isn't it Hinata?
Do you know him?
He's Kouki's junior.
Hey, why are you living in this room?
No way.
Ryochi-san, I've been living here for 4 years.
Isn't the most farthest room Higurashi's room?
Higurashi?
Oh, I remember.
There's a guy named Higurashi in the next room.
What?
He was kidnapped?
Oh, I remember.
He was kidnapped last summer because he was expanding the side road.
I remember.
He was doing that construction.
He was sleeping because his senior was in the way of the construction.
And he pulled Higurashi out of the way.
I see.
I totally forgot.
Oh, Ryo-chan.
So, where did you move the Higurashi?
Well...
Oh, right.
I put it in the storage.
Huh?
There's no storage.
I think it's here.
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
Oh, grandma.
Where did you put the storage?
Oh, I forgot.
It's been so long since I opened the door, so I put it in the storage.
What?
Did something happen?
Higurashi was sleeping in there.
No way!
So, when did you put the storage out?
I think it was after the expansion of the road.
Last summer, huh?
Oh, no.
All right, let's go to the garbage disposal center on Yume Island.
You mean around the summer garbage last year?
That's about it, I guess.
No wonder.
Now, let's go home.
Hey, tenon.
Ryo-chan.
How can you take care of a pile of garbage like that?
I got it.
Let's make it our building department.
That seemed sincere.
Ow.
It's hard to find.
If the corpse is buried here, it's a complete crime.
Don't be so ungrateful!
We found a treasure chest!
That's it! No doubt about it!
There it is!
Tagumo, you're going to have to work harder.
I'll try again.
I'm sorry.
My heart is beating fast.
You've been here for over half a year, and you're still alive.
It's because I live here.
What are you doing? Get out of here!
Oh no! I'm in trouble!
That's me!
The one who brought me here,
I will not forgive anyone!
Oh no!
If they wake me up, I will be in a bad mood.
I will destroy everything!
Hey, stop it! Higurashi!
Reiko! Higurashi is as weak as a devil, so please try to calm her anger!
What? Me?
That's enough! Hurry up!
Geez.
Higurashi-san, please calm her anger.
Please calm her anger.
Please...
Okay, we did it.
Reiko, you did well.
Nakagawa, Honda, take them to the station.
Yes, sir!
I heard that someone is going to make a big scene at the garbage disposal site on Yume Island.
That's you, you idiot!
I love you!
She's asleep...
Whew. We have to get out for now.
To be continued
To Be Continued
Part 2
Next Episode
The End
Where's Higurashi?
He's somehow sleeping. He's a good sleeper.
Senpai, what are you going to do from now on?
Ryo doesn't have an empty room.
I can't just leave him here forever.
Higurashi has been sleeping in his room all this time.
Who was the person Ryo saw in Shinjuku?
I guess it was a mistake.
Hmm.
Okay, let's knock him out and see...
Hey, you idiot!
There's no one to wake him up even though you're being quiet!
That's right! What if he starts to go crazy again?
I see.
Then we have to leave him alone.
What?
Yes, this is the exit of the park.
Yes.
Huh? Three soba?
We don't have a soba restaurant.
I'm here to get the bowl.
Good work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Idiot, don't make a loud noise!
I'm sorry.
What does this mean?
I don't know.
Ryo-chan, please do something.
If Higurashi stays here, I can't work.
But still...
What?
Hey, you should not cause an accident like that!
What will you do if Higurashi wake up?
What?
I...
Phew, that was a good save.
Well, that didn't even make such a loud noise.
I'm a little relieved.
What?!
So you're the one who woke me up.
Even though the sound of the car accident didn't make any noise, why?!
Senpai!
H-Higurashi-san!
Reiko! Hurry and put Higurashi to sleep!
Higurashi-san, please put your anger to sleep!
Whoa!
Oh, it's all messed up!
Captain, you shouldn't put him to sleep!
What did you say?
Every time he wakes up, the whole town will be messed up!
In other words, you shouldn't put him to sleep!
But how?
I have a good idea.
Hey, Higurashi! Higurashi!
Huh?
You're waking me up again?
No, no, no! Calm down, Higurashi!
You're a bad sleeper!
I'm annoyed when you wake me up when I'm not sleeping.
What do you mean, you're not sleeping?
You've been sleeping for a year and a half.
Huh? I slept that long?
It's the 12th year of Heisei!
Japan is at a dead end because of the Shidoni Olympics!
Huh? Can you show me that newspaper?
Ugh, this is bad.
If I show you, you'll find out that I copied and cut and made a fake newspaper.
What are you doing?
Ugh, I was so bad at baseball!
I'm so sorry!
Ugh!
It's a little suspicious.
What? No, no, no!
Then what happened to Nostradamus' great prophecy?
Nothing happened.
Then what happened to Namie Amuro, who was a top idol four years ago?
She married a sub of TRF and has children.
Then what happened to Kenji Haga and Anna?
Ah, they finally broke up.
Eh?
Oh, I see.
It seems that she has been late in her time.
It's just a little while left.
Hey, how are you doing?
Ah, Chief, there's tea in the back.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, Higurashi, you woke up. It's been four years.
Ah, hello.
You all speak in a strange way.
No, it's not like that.
Nakagawa, can you turn on the radio for Higurashi?
Yes, please let me hear it.
Yes.
Ryotsu, I have something to tell you.
Yes, yes.
Well, I'll leave it to Nakagawa.
Yes.
Higurashi always goes to the Olympics when he wakes up.
That's right.
It's once every four years.
Hello, everyone in Japan.
We're broadcasting the final of the soccer game live from Sydney.
Ichikawa, cut the pass.
Just break the sideline and pass to Ono.
Ono, dribble!
One player missed in 'Taiwan'.
The Japanese soccer team went to the Olympics following Atlanta.
That's right. What's more, they were ahead of the final.
Such a killer pass!
Hanagizawa shoots.
In goes.
He's in the starting line-up, but he's not fast at all, huh?
I don't care about soccer anymore, I want to play Judo.
Huh?
Yes, sir.
Goal!
While watching the sunset, Yawara-chan is crying.
Please listen to this song!
Did Tamura win a gold medal?
It seems the match is over.
Are you playing women's volleyball? I love volleyball.
It's bad. I can't understand it clearly.
Chief, touch.
Even if you say that suddenly ...
Nakagawa-kun, switch quickly.
Chief, anything is fine. Hurry up!
The ace of women's volleyball, Kasai, this serve is shining.
I did it!
The Eastern witch, the demon's great victory ...
It's strange. This is a member of the Tokyo Olympics.
Wakagawa, break the radio.
Oh, my hand!
It's a pity. I can't hear anymore.
It's strange. I made a strange voice now.
Hey, Higurashi, you were playing the Olympics, right?
Now it's the 12th year of Heisei, right?
It's hard to believe.
I'll watch the Olympics on TV.
Hey, he!
It's no good! I can't, I can't watch TV!
Hello, I'm MHK.
I received the receiving fee for April 2011 ...
Heisei?
11 years?
Dangerous!
How dare you fool me!
Reiko, stop!
That's too dangerous. I can't get close.
Reiko!
Please do something about it with your power.
Please!
Thank you!
Oh!
Miss Higurashi, please calm down!
Ah!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh!
Ah!
Why do I always look awful?
If you say that you can't calm down just by Reiko,
I'll call Mars!
Maria!
Master Ryo!
Oh, Maria!
I'll definitely stop it for Master Ryo's sake!
Yeah! I asked for it!
Miss Higurashi, please calm down!
* maximize pressure*
Oh, I think you can pressure her with this!
Hmm?
Oh, it's the man!
Oh, no, no, I can't hold it off!
I'm not coming!
A mysterious super power has appeared.
Tokyo is in a big mess.
We have to stop them.
I need to go out.
Chief, there's a meeting.
Join us online in real time.
Yes, sir.
Use the helicopter on the roof.
A super power has appeared.
I don't know if I can handle Godzilla.
You're the one who can't handle him.
What is that helicopter?
Who are you?
You're Higurashi, right?
What's going on?
Nice to meet you. I'm Higurashi Neruo's twin brother, Okio.
What? You're Higurashi's brother? I haven't heard from you for a while.
I don't talk about private matters much.
By the way, I've seen you in Keizai City.
That famous corporate warrior!
You know him?
Yes.
He's an elite worker who's been running around the world for 40,000 hours for 4 years and has made millions of contracts.
He's a super corporate warrior who's been missing.
I see. So this is the man I saw in Shinjuku.
But he only comes here once a year.
I'm the only one who can stop him from going wild.
What? How?
Ryo-sama's here!
Hey, watch out!
Are you going to stop me in a year?
You hate me?
Yes, I do.
Ryo.
Hey-
Oh, you're like a child.
Are you the man I saw at the start?
No, I'm an elite worker.
Is that Ryo?
Yes.
So, do you even train in the fiber that spirit employed in that experience?
Yeah, I see.
About the other day, the answer was 20%...
Hey, don't talk!
Yes, I understand.
Then, as you see.
Ah! The barrier!
Yes, I'll ask you about that at 4 o'clock.
Yes, that's it.
He stopped in the air and was talking.
As expected of the company warrior.
After all, it's Okio.
I didn't expect him to come.
Okio! Go back to the company and do your job!
Yes!
You sleep!
It's a huge fight.
It's a terrible fight.
I think I made a big change.
It's a missile attack of the Self-Defense Force!
You're too naive.
Okio, don't get in the way!
You go to sleep quickly!
Air Max Cell Extension!
I did it!
It was a great fight.
Now he'll sleep again.
Yes.
Thanks to you, I woke up.
What? I'm still fine.
It seems that he has improved his power.
Brother, finish him off!
Hey, what's wrong?
What year is today? What month? What day?
He's been awake all the time, so he doesn't feel the day-to-day.
It's May 16, 2021.
I knew it.
He's been awake all the time, and it's been four years.
He's in a state of sleep.
What? Wait a minute!
Hey, wake up!
You're the only one who can stop the day-to-day rampage!
It's the opposite of sleeping once in four years.
It's not the time to say such a selfish thing.
Who woke me up?
Yeah!
I'm already so overwhelmed.
Nightmare
If it's you, I want to wake up
Even boring stories
Make my whole body hot
But I want to see my friends
I want to be loved
I feel like we're melting
To the point where everyone gets annoyed
I want to shoot you
For some reason, love is only cowardly
Don't hide everything
That makes you strong
Rather know what's better
I want us to reach
This far
Call me
Don't hide
I want to be loved