ZUKI Creator
When you watch TV
Light up the room and try to get away
It's after the rain like someone is calling
I walked back and forth
My mom pulled my hand
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked through the red and black tiles
I saw
Everyone was a child once
But
Everyone has forgotten
Politicians with a big face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
"Ton Demo Body Jack"
How is it, Nakagawa?
Do you want to go home?
I'm sorry to bother you, but today I'm going to have a little...
What?
I have a dinner appointment with Cameron Roberts.
I'm going to come to the movie I made just now.
Oh, You mean Hollywood's most popular actress?
Yes
I envy you
I'm very worried about her
I was at her home party last year
She is very kind
I see
I'm talking about Reiko
It's amazing
You two
You know each other with a world-renowned person
I'll tell everyone when I get home!
I met her at her home party last year.
She's a very kind person.
Is that so?
Then I'll take care of Reiko-san.
That's amazing!
I'm so happy that you two are friends with a world-famous person!
What?
Don't mess with me, bastard!
I'll meet the famous Hollywood actress,
and the father of a grilled chicken restaurant.
Don't say that, Ryo-san.
They're born rich.
Their efforts have nothing to do with it.
There's no such thing as unfairness in the world!
Well, well.
I'll change the head of the branch to me.
I'll go to the judge's meeting, the congressman's party,
and have a great dinner with famous people.
My life will be different from the people's.
I'll get sick of it!
The lead actress, Cameron Roberts.
So this woman is Cameron Roberts.
Body Jack.
Your body may belong to someone else.
Body Jack, huh?
I'd like to switch bodies with Nakagawa if I could.
I'll take care of my father.
Good night!
Ryo-san's brother, the 13th one!
Where did he climb from?
He couldn't get off.
Ryo-san, it's your turn.
Huh? What do you want me to do?
You can save him.
I'll do my best.
No matter what happens, I'll protect the cat's life.
Now, I have to make some sacrifices.
Sacrifices?
I'll sacrifice for Takaga's cat.
What do you mean?
Cats are more important than you!
That's right!
You guys are too much!
Calm down!
You're too much!
Captain Ryosu!
Yes, sir!
Go to the police station and get out of here!
Come on!
Yes, sir!
Don't overdo yourself!
Ouch!
Watch out!
Captain!
Takaga!
You can't move!
Someone get an ambulance!
Takaga!
An ambulance!
It'll be fine!
Yes, sir!
Why am I falling?
Huh?
But I'm here.
What nonsense are you saying, Ryozu?
Ryozu?
That's right. Don't say anything weird.
Look at this carefully.
My face is on Senpai's face.
What are you kidding?
I'm not kidding. I'm Nagagawa.
I got shocked when I bumped into Senpai and my body changed.
No way!
That's...
I can't believe it.
But when I saw his behavior...
What's going on?
Do I become Senpai?
Senpai, please be strong.
I just called an ambulance.
The helicopter is faster.
It's me, Keiichi.
My voice is weird?
This is not the time to say that.
I need an ambulance.
Senpai, please be strong.
Chief.
I'm coming with you.
I'm counting on you.
Doesn't he look like a real Nakagawa?
I feel like I've really changed.
Ryozu can't do this.
I can't believe it, but that's Nakagawa.
He's not sick.
His brain wave is normal.
He's not in any trouble.
I didn't even have to tell him that.
But why are you living in a shelter?
Think about it.
He's in my figure.
But he's inside Ryozu Kakuchi's body.
It's Senpai.
If he gets up and finds out that I got my body,
he'll turn against me.
And he'll do something awful.
I see.
Ryozu is the worst.
So, I'm sorry,
but I can only stay here for a while.
Please keep it a secret.
Okay.
What? The president's body has been replaced?
Yes. He's called the "Soul's Evasion Factor" in a professional sense.
There are many witnesses on site.
Besides, he knows a lot about the president's private life.
Then, President, what's the schedule for today?
Ah, today we'll be watching the Heperovsky Palace,
the agricultural lecture and the traditional Japanese culture.
After that, there'll be a dance party at the embassy.
Ah, excuse me.
How can you say such a thing about a schedule that only the president knows?
I'm sure the president knows.
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
If you believe me, it's all right.
Hehehe, we did it! We're finally in Nakagawa!
I'm glad I replaced the electronic notebook in Nakagawa.
But we ran into each other at the right time.
We can't miss this chance.
We can finally live a luxurious life!
After this...
You're going to do a report on the weekly Kamedasu, right?
Y-Yes.
Noriko-san, you're such a nice person.
No, you're in trouble.
I'm Keiichi!
Get out of here!
I'll go out!
He's saying that again.
I'm saying that again.
Ryozu Kankichi is such a guy.
Hey, why are you locking me up in such a place?
I can't believe this.
Without any clear proof,
I can't accept that you're the president of the company.
I see...
What do you think, everyone?
I can't believe this.
You're so mean!
OK, I understand.
What do you think?
The professionals on the road will judge you.
The professionals on the road?
There are such people?
Yes.
I'm impressed.
Good morning.
You're early, Ryo-chan.
I mean, you're Kei-chan, right?
I don't like it, Reiko-san.
Don't get me wrong.
Oh, that's Ryo-chan's seat.
What?
Where have I always been?
You're always doing research there.
Well, I...
Oh, that was like this.
Here, Kei-chan.
Coffee.
Coffee?
Isn't it Japanese tea?
Ryo-chan is the only one who drinks Japanese tea.
What?
Well, sometimes I think Japanese tea is good, but...
Good morning.
Oh, Ryo-chan.
Oh, no, it wasn't.
Nakagawa, is your body all right?
Yes, it's all right.
How about Ryo-chan?
It seems that he had a bad heart.
He was hospitalized in our hospital for a while.
Then, can I visit him once?
Oh, no, that's not necessary.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What's the matter?
President, I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
I'd like you to take a test to see if he's the real President.
Oh, all right.
I'm sorry.
Please don't ask me this.
I'm the one who needs everybody from the north and south to the south.
This time, you'll have to take a test.
Then, Eizaki Korosuke, the genius scientist, will give us its invention!
With this lie detector, we'll know if your body really has a soul.
Oh-oh...
If you get caught by this Masai, you will know for sure if it is real or fake.
Well then, please.
Hm? Gorilla-kun, are you ready?
Um, I am Keiichi Nakagawa.
Just a joke! I am Indonesian joke to release your heart.
Well then, let's start right now!
Let's start right now!
All questions are answered in less than 2 seconds!
Well then, the first question!
Hm?
What is your favorite snack?
Snack?
The answer is in less than 2 seconds!
What?
It's Monaca! Monaca!
You're so annoying.
Well then, the next question.
I wanted to make a bamboo stick with bamboo sticks, so I made it with bamboo sticks.
How is it?
Which one is easier, red-wrapped god, blue-wrapped god, or white-wrapped god?
What is that question?
You're out of 2 seconds.
Nyaa!
Red-wrapped god, red-wrapped god, blue-wrapped god, white-wrapped god, blue-wrapped god, red-wrapped god, white-wrapped god, white-wrapped god, white-wrapped god!
Hm?
This is a torture.
If you were a cat, where would you like to be?
Engawa!
Punch, perm, or claw? Which one is more manly?
Claw!
Which one do you like more, pro-wrestling or sumo?
Then, the last question.
Which one is more manly, a dog of Flanders or a dog of Flanders?
A dog of Flanders!
Time's up!
I have the answer.
This person is definitely Keiichi Nakagawa!
Why is that?
Many questions have their own answers.
The first question, for example.
What is your favorite fruit?
The answer is Monaka.
How do you learn this?
Monaka's inside.
And the answer is "Cat"
The side of the circle is the side of the middle
And the favorite one is K1
In other words K1
In other words, he confessed who he was unconsciously
The last answer is the answer of the last question
Flanders dog's pun is Flanders dog
This hypersense is unique to Nakagawa who has lived abroad for a long time
Therefore, the contents of the "looking gorilla" in front of me is definitely Nakagawa Keiichi
I'm impressed, professor
Now I can persuade the staff
Well, it's easy for me
I also thought it was Nakagawa
Me too
Right?
I'm saying Nakagawa Keiichi
He's persistent
I'll give up in the meantime
No, I'm glad I really found out about the president
It's a natural result
Thanks to the stupid professor
I was saved
On the contrary, it's like I got a real house
I want to avoid it
Because there are fivelio thorns in the middle
I have to come this far to get rid of it
I don't think I'll be able to do it
I'm sorry
I can't do it
The next episode
What did I do?
Why do I have to go through this?
It's finally quiet down.
Finally at ease.
Mr. Chairman...
What's up?
Here's a case that was Happening in Europe and America.
A case?
Yes.
I'm here to give the specific instructions as chairman of the Nakagawa Group...
Huh? Oh...
So it seems like this is the case...
Then keep going ahead and get to the bottom of it.
President! You must see the documents here!
Keep an eye on him.
President! What do you say to this case?
It's something we can discuss casually.
Shut up! If you want, let me be!
President!
Wh- what is it?
As you剛剛 said, this is the case.
The dollar and euro are in a big mess.
The world economy is in a mess like it was hit by a tsunami.
Is it something bad?
Of course!
It's a good opportunity, president.
I want to restore the messy life here to the previous form.
What is this?
You always call me in an hour.
Oh, I see.
From now on, I will do as scheduled.
I will do as scheduled.
At 10:00, a meeting in Ginza.
At 11:30, a computer-related inspection in Sendai.
At 1:00, the president of a company with 150 overseas companies will be in Kyoto.
Wait a minute, I want to go shopping.
Unfortunately, there is no time for a second.
Andri Noriette, a bearnaise sauce.
Andriou Yette, red wine flavor, anchovy.
The twilight of a scallop-like Marielle.
A lamb's brain miso.
I see.
I've had enough of your explanation.
Yes.
I want to eat the ramen of the common people once in a while.
That is not part of the schedule.
Please look at the documents carefully.
The market share will rise.
If I do such a thing, I will be in trouble.
I will be in trouble for a long time.
I want to do it.
I don't want to do it.
"It's not easy to do Nakagawa"
"Good morning. I'm Nakagawa"
"Please be careful"
"You're so rough"
"No, your body is too short to drive"
"Hey, that's Ryo's seat"
"No, I don't know why, but my body is too big for him"
"Oh, right, Ryo is coming to work today"
"What? Did he quit?"
"He?"
"No, he did"
"Yes"
"As Nakagawa said,
he's completely Ryo's"
"What's going on?"
"I stopped the second Kamehameha roll in 30 minutes"
"Are you Ryo?"
"What are you doing to your brother?"
"Sorry, sorry"
"Nakagawa, you've been so mean lately"
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry"
"I'll give you 100,000 yen for the deal"
"Nakagawa, please pay the 100,000 yen"
"Please don't give me money"
"No, I don't have any money"
"I'm not bringing the money"
"I'm sure you have a card"
"I'll lend you money for a few days"
"Hey, Ryo"
"Hey, Ryo?"
"He's there?"
"Please tell him if he's there"
"Damn it, we're only one step away"
"Huh?"
"You guys!"
What are you looking at?
You bastard!
You're so stubborn.
Hey, Ryo-ko! Tea!
Yes!
Today was a very important race.
It's totally me.
There are two of me.
Which means, where did Nakagawa go?
Hey, Ryo-tsu.
Yes?
You're not Ryo-tsu!
I always made Nakagawa look so bad.
I didn't know he was so mean.
You cleaned up Ryo's room, Ryo-tsu.
Yes. I finally woke up.
I threw away all the plums and figures I had collected.
What?
Hey, that's a valuable asset.
It has nothing to do with you.
Shut up!
I'm sorry!
At this time, you should get rid of the video.
That's right.
Wait! Don't give me your advice!
Why are you coming out?
I'm telling you, Ryo-san.
That's why I think it's better not to throw it away.
Hey, Senpai.
It's a waste if you throw it away.
I'm tired of erotic videos.
If you throw it away, give it to me.
What?
Kei-chan?
You're kidding, aren't you?
What should I do?
I should throw it away.
No, Senpai.
Absolutely no!
I'll buy it.
It's a million yen per volume.
No!
I'm a pervert!
Hey, hey.
Please.
I'm asking you to throw it away.
Please, don't do anything to me.
It's really not a big deal.
Please, take it all.
If you can't do it, don't throw it away.
You should have thrown it away.
I thought that it was strange.
So they are fooling me.
Hello everybody.
Nice party.
Professor Ezaki.
Now what?
The new invention of genius scientist,
This is the personality changer.
It's the same shape and shape, but only the personality is changed.
In other words, Gorilla and Nakagawa can be returned to their original form.
I see.
If we can really be replaced with Nakagawa, we can do whatever we want.
That's great, Senpai.
We might be able to return to our original form.
That's right.
You're back, Senpai.
I'm a little scared.
It's okay.
Nakagawa! No! No!
I'm so happy.
Now we can go back to our original form.
Please, Professor.
Okay. Okay. Karaoke. Switch.
Get out of my way, you idiot!
What's this?
Why am I dressed like this?
My body is there!
Oh, it's Nakagawa.
Now he can be released from my cage.
Ryo-chan! It's all your fault!
Senpai, what's wrong with me?
Why are you doing this to me?
You can't be fooled by such a thing!
Professor, can't we do something about this?
No! Don't tell me!
I'm not going to!
Ezaki.
Please take care of my Lone.
♪ Awaken, clock, kick, little finger, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ First, I draw my eyebrows, then I'll go to the station, dash, dash, dash ♪
♪ Every train, I sleep with my father's back ♪
♪ This week, I'm doing my best ♪
♪ The
♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ If the hot shower passes through ♪
♪ I can recover my energy with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ Monday ♪
♪ Monday, Monday, no problem ♪
What?
The hot shower passed through the first train!
No problem…
It's just a succeeded and that's all.
♪ It's a good thing the train hasn't passed through ♪
♪ The hot shower has passed through the first train! ♪
♪ It's a good thing the train hasn't passed through the first train! ♪
Thank you for watching!