When watching TV, look to the right of the TV.
When watching TV, look at the TV, and then look at the TV with the cover of your eyes, and then look away from it.
Those who have no money, come with me!
Come here!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
They'll get better eventually
You're a jobless guy, come to me
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds
They're burning
They'll get better eventually
I know, I know, I know
If you know, then come to me
I'm the 0-0-4th, a robot police officer who was made by the police chief's efforts
I was assigned to the police station before Kameari Park
But I don't know what to do
I'm just a doji
I'm a pain in the ass to the god Ryoichi-senpai
The name I was given seems to be useless
But the god did his best for me who was used as an obstacle
I managed to not get into trouble
Thank you, god
They're developing a new robot police officer
I'll do my best too
The robot police officer of the burning flames
Here you go
Thanks, Damedaro
No
I'm sorry. It's my job
No, it's normal for the robot to help humans
But it really helps
Damedaro is here
To sign-off the railings
Terai suddenly stopped working.
Please take care of Terai until he comes back.
Yes, I will.
It seems like Senpai is back.
Alright!
Who are you?
I'm Robot Officer Development 005.
Any complaints?
I don't have any complaints.
I heard that Robot Officer Development 004 is here.
You're 004, right?
Yes, I am. Nice to meet you.
Don't call me Robot!
But I'm your junior.
Don't you get it?
Senpai and junior are the rules of human society.
The world of robots is the opposite.
Look! This is my performance report.
What?
How is it?
It's better than you, right?
New robots have the latest technology.
It's excellent and great.
Remember it!
Y-Yes...
I see.
You have that kind of thinking, don't you?
What?
This bicycle looks like Senpai's.
I left it in front of the pachinko shop in front of the pachinko shop.
So I came here.
It's obviously a police item.
It's a police item, right?
What do you mean?
I didn't leave it here.
Where is my bicycle?
While I'm in the middle of pachinko,
what are you doing?
Damn it, I'll find it!
My bicycle!
God, welcome back.
Why is this bicycle here?
The development 005 has come.
The development 005?
Oh, it's me.
You're a robot officer again.
You!
The unqualified officer who was pachinkoing while working.
I was watching the shop.
Don't imitate me!
Are you motivated?
Robots are stronger if they have power.
Damn it!
Senpai, you can't be so violent.
I just took the punch.
You did it so well.
Think about the power of the robot.
Ultra Gear!
Damn it!
I missed it.
You're weaker than a human with just your tip of the tongue.
Yes, it's done.
All right, perfect.
Now I can't be a human anymore.
You're a hero.
You can't beat a human with just your tongue.
What do you want?!
There's both good and bad things to say.
What do you mean by just your tongue?
Delete it quickly!
Okay!
The bubble is all over my mouth.
Dumbass!
Are you going to make the exhaust a fire?
Well...
When the temperature rises, the wiring shortens,
and it may cause the fuel to be carbonized.
What?
Does that mean...
If you get angry, the fire will be on?
That's what it means.
What a ridiculous blood vessel robot.
What?
Who is a blood vessel robot?
A robot that burns with anger is a blood vessel fire.
It's obvious.
Okay.
Your name is Fire Robot Doikari Hono Onosuke.
Who is Hono Onosuke?
Don't give me that ridiculous name.
Ryo, don't make me angry.
Don't get angry, Hono Onosuke.
What?
Do you think you can be human?
What's that?
I'll go patrol.
You guys are so obsessed with robots.
You have good memory.
There's nothing I can do about that.
Damn it.
They're so annoying.
They're just good people.
There are robots that bite people like you.
So they'll get more angry.
But...
Robots are better than humans.
The speed of calculation of equations and trigonometric numbers doesn't even match with humans.
Humans can't even stand on their feet!
I don't think it's useful for a police officer's job.
For example!
There are plenty of other great things!
Ah! I got it! Please calm down!
Ah, Chief! Good morning!
Good morning!
O-Good morning...
Oh?
What's wrong, Chief?
What about development 0055?
Huh?
The development 0055 is here!
Yeah! Doikari Honounosuke, you say?
Doikari Honounosuke?
Ryo-chan gave it a name.
He's on patrol with Dametaro-kun right now.
I see.
Chief, don't let that blood-thirsty robot get you.
Y-You did something back there again?
Huh? Back there again?
Anything else you did?
No, that's just...
You did it, huh?
Actually, before I came here, I came into the walls of the principal's office and...
You got a job without getting paid!
Y-You're right!
A robot officer must get paid for something!
Huh? You got a job without getting paid for something!
Give us a day off and a payday!
Let's make a human-like union!
That's so reckless!
There's no such thing as a good example.
Then at least make a unit of independent robots!
It's a robot escape room!
I'm sorry for being mocked by humans!
I understand your feelings, but you don't have any achievements.
Then I'll make an achievement.
At that time, it's a robot escape room!
A terrible robot officer has come!
Yes.
That's what happened.
I see.
A robot escape room is a ridiculous idea.
Yes. Kameyari Park Pre-Escape Room.
What? An incident?
Give me 500cc of bleach.
Yes.
So, if you make an achievement, you can make a robot escape room.
I see.
Then you're with us.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Good.
It will be 65 yen.
What?
Yes.
As expected, the bleach is good!
It looks like an incident.
It's a chance to make an achievement!
Come with me!
It will be useless if you don't!
Yes...
Officer!
Quickly bring cars with him!
What an aggressive group!
We can't get close by this.
Captain, let's counterattack.
It's not good.
There's a gas factory.
Moreover, there are hostages in it.
I can't do anything about it.
Damn it.
This is the place.
Yes.
Tamedaro, Hanohonosuke.
Leave this to us.
The enemy has a gun.
No matter how much you're shot with a gun, it's okay.
Because it's a robot.
Are you an idiot?
What do you mean by idiot?
Even if you're okay, what if your hostage is shot?
This blood vessel robot.
You said it again.
You can't make fun of a robot for human habits.
Please calm down, Hanohonosuke.
Senior, don't make me angry.
You bastard.
Don't come over here.
It's noisy.
Did the cash arrive?
What?
Stop.
What's wrong with the hostage?
It's hot.
That eye is serious.
Run away.
Idiot.
Don't go over there.
It's going to explode.
Mr. Hanohonosuke.
There's a pond on the left.
Please go over there.
Don't come over here.
Go over there.
Mr. Hanohonosuke.
You die, Sir.
I got it.
Thank you for a hard-fought job.
That's to get lucky.
This time,
Thanks to the robot police, we were able to solve the case.
So, I'll give you this award.
Thanks!
The symptoms are good, but you can build a robot station, right?
Well...
Are you breaking your promise?
Oh! It's burning again!
You can't make me angry, boss!
Boss!
I... I got it!
I'll make a robot station!
Yay!
I'll be a big star from now on!
What's going on, boss?
Why is the robot station right next to my house?
There was no other suitable location.
There's no other way.
I'll go to the office, so don't skip it.
Damn it! It's not burning at all!
It's almost a centimeter away from the window.
Hey, Onosuke!
Yeah!
It's a great facility!
I'm not surprised!
Not for long, at any rate.
What's going on, Onosuke?
I finally got a job!
What?
I've finally got a job!
Ooh, I got a job!
You did?
Did they offer you something special?
No.
I was just sitting on my seat.
It's the second research lab!
What's wrong, Damedaro?
Huh? What's this?
Sorry, the fuel spilled and exploded.
This thing is the fuel?
Yes, it's the development 006.
To remove abandoned bicycles and illegal parking, we made a power robot.
I was expecting it, but it's this size after all.
Even so, it's huge. It's sticking out of my body.
Considering the strength and power, it's this size.
We're going to drive it ourselves from now on.
There's a driver's seat on the chest, so we can drive it together.
Sounds interesting. Let me drive it, too.
Sure.
Hey, stop!
Why are you coming?
Leave it to the police.
God, please turn the left steering wheel.
It will start moving.
This?
It's like a classic car.
Whoa! The ceiling is...
Wow! It's standing up!
It's easy to control.
Okay, let's go!
Whoa! It's a powerful movement!
What's it using for fuel?
Nitro.
Nitro?
Nitro is a little vibration that explodes.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Why would you use such a ugly thing?
Because it has the most power.
I'm not kidding. If the robot falls, it'll explode.
Shut up. You have to miss the control.
How can I guess your control?
What? The robot is better at controlling than humans.
You're good at this.
Hey, stop!
If you get burned, it'll explode!
Oh, I see.
I'll get off if I can get on such a dangerous thing.
What's wrong?
It won't open.
What?
God, where are you going?
That's the road!
You bastard. Are you making fun of me?
Hey, stop!
If you make a noise, it'll explode!
W-what are you doing, God?
My robot is going to explode!
How dare you!
I'm not doing anything!
Don't be stupid!
Don't come near me!
Hey, calm down!
Calm down!
The robot's exit is...
Hey, squid! It's on the road!
What?
I'm going to stop it!
You don't have to say anything!
Stop!
What are you doing? Stop it now!
I'm doing it too!
What's going on?
Is the robot moving on its own?
What?
Please give me a break.
Here, give me your license.
W-wait a minute!
That's...
W-what is that?
Hey, you! Stop!
Stop, you robot!
Stop!
I told you to stop!
Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
What are you doing, you bad guy?
You stupid! What are you doing?
Shut up! I was trying to stop it for the whole time!
You did it so well, Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
Reiko!
What's going on?
I don't know.
If I come back from the library, I'll be in trouble...
What could it be?
This is Tyrannosaurus.
It's the strongest dinosaur on Earth.
So it won't lose to anyone?
Of course!
Tyrannosaurus...
You're awake.
No! I can't control it!
I'll destroy it and stop it!
If you can, then do it already!
You were bragging that you're smarter than humans, you idiot!
What do you mean, idiot?
You idiot!
I'm not an idiot!
I'm a dinosaur!
It's burning!
It's a fire!
Help me!
What's up with this robot?
It's burning!
I'm saved!
You're lucky you got into the river.
What's wrong?
You look weird!
I see!
Calm down!
Be careful!
I want to deal with this robot asap!
Ah, did you see me?!
That's why humans are useless.
You're not to be blamed.
I'm sorry,
it's not good to be here with him.
What?
Senpai is?
He's abusing in the car, driving a massive robot!
Our car is damaged!
Ryo...
What about him?
Ohara-kun, what's going on?
I don't know.
Speaking of which, I heard that the president was very concerned about what happened last week.
What?
He said he would take revenge on you someday.
It's unforgivable to destroy the city with such a thing.
It's a big problem, president! A giant robot is coming towards us!
What?
Oh, no!
We have to go to the Katsushika office!
What? That's not good! Stop it!
We can't do that! We've been struggling for a long time!
Reiko, turn left!
It's a big problem! A giant robot is coming towards us!
We have to stop it as soon as possible!
But when did Ryotsu get the robot?
Oh, right!
He's with the robot!
I heard that the robot officer was on board.
I see! He made the robot officer do it!
Ryotsu's evil spirit and the robot officer's intelligence came together and the devil's invention...
Now!
No matter what you do, stop it here!
It's no good!
That's terrible! The chain is also torn and we're stuck!
Damn it! There's no way to stop this!
SS Team, we've arrived at our position.
If the robot gets within 30 meters, we may attack.
Yes, sir!
We have no choice but to destroy the robot if we come this far.
If everything goes well, the damage will be minimal.
That can't be...
Ryotsu!
How's this?
How's that?
Alright, that's good!
The fuel is cut!
You just have to walk another 10 meters to stop.
Alright, well done!
Now Sho's saved!
Shoot if you're only 10 meters away!
Stop it!
No, Taro!
Nitro is being used in that robot's fuel!
What?!
Hey, don't hurry!
We're about to stop!
Nitro is inside the robot!
Stop it!
You idiot!
Showa Katsushika was fully recovered,
but miraculously, no one was injured.
Except for me.
Ryo, I'm sorry.
I didn't think the robot was broken.
I'm really sorry.
Seriously,
this is all because I was with the robot!
What?!
Who's the robot?!
Hurry up, Sho!
I'm sick of being a robot officer!
Saya True
"The season of the new year has come!"
"Occult no flesh, the old auditory're on the rise!"
"Name!
"Name! - Kyokushinamiji-ulus..."
"Occult no flesh, the old auditory are on the rise!"
New Year!
Ah, summer has come again this year
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here
Big, small waves, small waves, a little bit of a thing
A big, small butt, a little bit of a thing
Ah, the scent of the southern wind
Ah, the big, small waves, big, big, big, big, big, big
Next time, we will go on a trip to Kameari Park Exhibition.
The theme of this trip is Tokyo.
First, we will visit the traditional Tokyo,
go on a cruise,
and visit the best outlet in Japan.
For dinner, we will enjoy a buffet.
Next time, we will go on a trip to the underground city of Ryosan.
Thank you for watching.
To our town!
Thank you!