"When you watch TV, light up your room and watch it from a distance."
"The Little Cat"
"Come to me, the one without money!"
"I'm not there, but I'm worried."
"Look at the blue sky and the white clouds."
"It will be all right somehow."
"The one without a job."
"Come to me, the one without money."
"I'm not there, but I'm worried."
"Look, the red clouds are burning."
"It will be all right somehow."
"You understand, don't you?"
"If you understand, then follow me!"
"Finding without a break!"
"Hmm..."
"How is it, Ryotsu?"
"This is terrible. I'm about to get my nails on the pedestal!!"
"Eh? W-Will you heal me, Ryotsu?"
It's an important ring I bought to celebrate my 30th wedding anniversary.
I believe the wedding anniversary is the day after tomorrow, right?
That's right. I was going to give it to my wife in secret and make her happy, but I accidentally dropped it and got caught in a fight.
Until the day after tomorrow, you have to repair it immediately.
If you ask the company, please prepare a repair fee of 100,000 yen.
Huh? Does it take that long?
This kind of technology is expensive, but I'll ask my acquaintance's workshop and let him do it for 30,000 yen.
30,000 yen? Oh, that's good. Your face is also useful sometimes.
Then I'll do it.
I asked you, Ryotsu. Whatever happens, please be in time for the day after tomorrow.
I know. Please trust me, Yobu-chan.
I can't trust you, but I'll ask Nakagawa.
I'll ask Ryotsu.
Please keep your promise to me.
I see.
Well, Ryotsu, I'll leave it to you.
Leave it to me.
You can't trust me?
That's right. I'm not asking the company.
I'll repair it myself and make a 30,000 yen profit.
Are you trying to trick me again?
It's okay. The director is happy that 100,000 yen is 30,000 yen.
I'm coming.
What's wrong?
Reiko is making a teddy bear in the back.
A teddy bear?
Good job!
Don't you mess with that, Ryo-chan.
But why is she making a stuffed bear?
She seems to be selling it at the charity bazaar at Katsushika-cho tomorrow.
Cool.
It's even cheaper at the charity bazaar than at the charity bazaar.
How many are you going to make?
I'm planning to make 200.
200?
Reiko-san's teddy bear is very popular.
It's always sold out quickly.
Teddy bears are
loved all over the world.
There are competitions
where you compete with your proud teddy bear every year.
Hmm...
What's that?
It's a bear from a friend in France.
It looks old.
It's worn out.
We'll buy it and make a new one.
Why would you do that?
In Europe,
when a baby is born,
they give a teddy bear as a present.
At first,
the teddy bear is bigger.
But they chase it
and share a lot of memories with the bear.
And when they get married,
they take it with them
and let the baby play with the bear.
I see.
you're going to take one teddy bear
with your children?
Isn't it cotton inside?
It's called a "pain-ya."
It's a fiber
that is wrapped in a plant called "kapok."
Hmm...
What is this?
It's a pellet.
It's to balance the weight.
You put it inside with the "pain-ya."
Oh, I see.
Hmm...
It's the same as the jewel in the manager's ring.
If you replace it,
you won't know, right?
The manager's eyes are like a hole.
Hey,
you're being noisy.
To be clear,
it's a nuisance.
It feels like there's a beast in a place
Hmm...
I'm sorry for the beast.
But you guys are not beautiful at all.
What did you say?
Let's go, Nakagawa.
Yes.
What?
Am I the only one in the way?
Of course.
Ryo-chan, if you help me,
you can stay.
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
I have more work to do.
See you.
Nakagawa, don't take me.
No, I don't want to.
Beep.
You're so annoying.
Thank you.
Please take care of it.
Yes.
Thank you, Saki-chan.
Oh, it's you, Aunt.
Thank you.
How many are left?
Ten left.
One more station.
You can sell it in an hour.
Thank you.
You guys are doing great.
Yes.
Mr. Hatsumura.
Ah, Mr. Saki-chan!
Is the ring okay?
Eh? Ring?
Oh, ring.
Don't tell me you forgot it.
Yes, I did.
I'll go to the jewelry store.
Will the repair be okay by tomorrow?
Well, the head of the club is worried.
Leave it to me.
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
No, nothing.
Ah, my cell phone battery is out.
Senior, what happened to your finger?
I don't know.
I thought I'd do it tonight,
but I didn't get it out of the box.
Where did it go?
Oh, once.
Senior, maybe when Reiko was making teddy bears yesterday...
I think there's a beast in a place full of beauties.
It's in that bucket.
Hurry up.
It's Reiko's teddy bear.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
Reiko, where is the teddy bear?
Oh, you want a teddy bear, too?
It's not that.
Where is it?
It's here.
Too bad.
One of the last ones just sold out.
You're late, Kusu.
What are you going to do, Senior Su?
There's a finger ring in there.
I don't know what it is,
but if you bought the teddy bear,
it's in the address of all of us.
Really?
Yes, I did it.
That's Reiko.
Hey, stop it, Ryo-chan.
What a fool.
There are 200 people in this computer.
What?
I'm trying to do my best.
It seems I'd do just fine.
No need to worry.
Yes, my name is Taipei.
Oh, when will you change?
- carpeting. - I don't know.
The shop will be jaki one month later,
but the company's going to be too tight.
Don't worry about it.
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
I got the shopping list!
There should be a ring in this teddy bear!
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
Yes?
It's from the police.
Yes... What is it?
Madam, you bought a teddy bear from the book bazaar.
Yes, what is it?
In fact, there is information that the drug is hidden in it.
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
What?
Senior, would you like to see it?
Yes, I'm on my way.
Are you sure? You can't say the truth by saying that.
Did you find it?
No, it's just a piece of junk.
Next! Hurry!
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
I cut the teddy bear!
We are the doctor of animals.
We will fix it right away.
Did you find it?
No, I didn't.
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
Yes?
It's from the police.
In fact, there is information that the drug is hidden in the teddy bear.
What?
But I bought this 15 years ago.
Is there another teddy bear?
Yes.
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
About 3000.
By the way, there is something that I bought somewhere in here.
*Teddy Bear is in the shopping list*
I think we should find such things from this inside.
Yes.
Well, it took us an hour.
Hurry!
Nakagawa!
Can you see me?
At my sense, it is suspicious here?
Yes.
Huh?
Hi, I'm Sayuri!
This is my favorite!
What do you want?
Nakagawa, hurry up and get that beer!
I can't stand this jari-jari head!
Nakagawa!
Yes?
Nakagawa, hurry up and get it!
I can't stand it.
How many have we got?
We've only got 7.
There are 193 left.
Anyway, let's hurry up and get it!
Oh, about that stuffed animal...
Well, come on up.
That stuffed animal was bought by your grandson, right?
Y-Yes...
I think he really liked it.
And what about that grandchild?
Oh, she just left with her son and her husband.
They're so lonely that they're going to die.
Where did she go?
By bullet train.
By bullet train?
To Atami.
Atami! Nakagawa!
Yes!
And then we'll take the ferry to Oshima.
Hey, you!
To Oshima!
Yes!
Do you have a photo of your grandchild?
I don't have any photo.
You're just looking for a photo, but you're making me wait for 30 minutes!
Oh, this is bad. I'm going to die!
Y-You...
Just go full power and get to the bullet train!
Yes!
We have to hurry up...
Let's hurry...
What is it?
This isn't a good time to waste our time...
A close shot of the bullet train...
Is that it?
That's right.
That guy seems to have gone too far.
Hey, wait a second!
I think he's too tired.
If you keep fighting like this, you'll fall asleep!
Just go full power.
The Gate
The gate is closing!
Get in!
To think Senpai would be so reckless!
More importantly, it's Teddy Bear!
Where is Teddy Bear?
Senpai, over there!
It's that ferry over there!
Damn it! I can't let them get away!
Senpai!
Hey, that ferry over there! Wait for me!
It's a true obsession.
It's not here! It's not here! It's not here!
W-what the heck!
There's nothing here.
Damn it! Next!
I can't get through.
We've got 199 points.
That means...
We've got one Teddy Bear left.
Minatoku Aoyama M. Christie
She's a foreign woman.
She's not the French friend Reiko was talking about.
I have a bad feeling about this.
A bad feeling about this?
Did she go to France?
Her first flight was at 4:00.
She'll be Nari!
Hurry up!
It's time for departure!
It's not getting there in time!
Let's see whether we make it or not!
How fast can we get to Moscow City!
Louis!
Captain!
We've received a message from Mars that the ship is being bombarded!
What?
Captain Kick!
We apologize for the inconvenience.
The ship is now in a state of emergency.
Please wait for a while while the customer is on the other side.
Are you sure you're going to do this?
It's a state of emergency.
If we don't find the ring, the captain won't be able to see it.
Everyone, please follow our instructions.
What do you mean by "explosive"?
Calm down.
There's a teddy bear in here.
There's a bomb in there...
What is this?
Well...
This is a special tour ticket for the Teddy Bear World Tour.
Why are you making it so complicated?
What should we do?
I know whose teddy bear it is.
Find the Frenchman Christy!
It's interesting.
Ah!
Who is it?
Reiko was repairing it at that time!
I'm saved!
Bring that teddy bear here!
Damn it!
Why did you understand it?
What?
Senpai!
If you move, you'll turn on the bomb switch!
I told you not to move!
If you turn on the switch, this bomb will explode in 10 seconds!
No way!
It can't be true!
If you're a real tumor, there's gonna be a bomb...
I will show you a real one!
Break off!
We have to do it or we'll be dead meat!
You worked hard on your flight.
But it doesn't matter to you!
Reito!
Ha!
What?
Let's get out of here!
They'll have to make it so easy!
Senpai!
This is bad!
I found the teddy bear for my purpose, but it's not even attached!
Ken-chan!
Nakagawa, what's going on?
Chief, Senpai is on that plane.
Ryo-chan is?
What does the culprit want?
What is he asking for?
That is...
I hate teddy bears!
So, gather all the teddy bears you have in the cargo room!
Throw them into the sea!
What the hell!
He's on that plane for that!
But why is he a teddy bear?
I don't know.
Ryo-chan will be the one to tell him.
But Senpai isn't on that plane.
He's on that plane!
My hands are numb...
Hurry up!
I'm going to throw away your teddy bears!
My teddy bears!
Don't be silly!
Why do you have to throw away my teddy bears?
I'll tell you then.
My name is Teddy Kumao!
So cute!
Shut up!
I don't want you to know how I feel!
Teddy bears, teddy bears!
I've been made a fool of since I was a kid!
If only teddy bears were not like this,
my life wouldn't have been like this!
It stinks!
That was my 4th birthday.
My relatives gathered and gave me a present.
It was all teddy bears!
They all gave me presents on my name!
Since then, I've failed in everything I do!
I can't marry, I can't go to college, I can't marry!
It's all Teddy bear's fault!
No, I was cursed by Teddy bears!
Even if I die, I can't get married!
You're crazy!
Shut up!
Captain!
Open the luggage room!
Hurry up!
Shut up!
I can't help it.
Now is the time to revenge!
Damn it!
Now I'm in trouble!
I'll get you!
This teddy bear is mine!
What's wrong?
It's here!
I've got it back!
The real one is here.
No, I was looking for here!
You shouldn't say that!
If you do anything strange, I'll activate the bomb switch!
Wait, calm down!
Ryotsu!
Don't make the culprit excited!
I won't let you die!
Ryo, hang in there!
Senpai!
Sh*t! I have to do something!
Take this!
Hurry up!
What's this?
What the hell?
Look at this!
The teddy bear with the bomb is...
The switch is...
Hey, wake up!
This is not the time to be in a hurry!
Sh*t!
I don't have time!
My ring is...
Thank goodness!
Huh?
This is not good!
Ryo!
Senpai!
Ryo! Ryo! Are you okay?
Look!
I'm safe!
Well done!
Well done, Ryo!
The ring...
Now, I have to find it in this sea!
Oh!
It's all right!
I'm glad, Captain!
You did a great job, Ryo!
I'm glad I found the ring, Nakagawa!
You did a great job!
Nakagawa Salveiji did his best to find the ring in that sea!
And, you earned a lot of money!
But, what I found in a day was a miracle.
A ring worth a million, huh...
You only become a leader because you don't know it.
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Turn to the side with a nice breath
Don't get crazy, there is something to do
With a cute, heartfelt breath
What is hard to understand
I want to show you
Better than the beginning
It's better than starting over
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
March 3rd is my birthday
However, my body is in trouble on this day
I thought I could have a day off today
But why am I running around the North country with a truck on my hand?
Next time, March 3rd, my birthday again
Thank you for watching!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!