Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the middle of the river ♪
♪ I took off my love stone and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was laughing at the captain of the taiko who was jogging ♪
♪ He said it was just a joke ♪
♪ I'm fine anywhere, I'm fine anywhere, I'm fine anywhere ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes is so gentle ♪
♪ The glass is crying, the rain is getting dark ♪
♪ The grilled chicken is running away ♪
♪ The beer is running away ♪
♪ The
♪
The Excavator
A Little Long Ago
The city of Kameari has changed a lot.
When I graduated from the police school and became a member of the police,
there was no public transportation yet.
There was a big cargo control room.
There were a few factories.
The population increased and the anti-corruption world was expanding.
There were five cinemas.
If I remember correctly, there was a tobacco shop on this corner.
Oh, I see. Yoko-chan's tobacco shop is gone too.
Yoko-chan?
Yes.
There was a tobacco shop here, and Yoko-chan was the sign girl.
I wonder how many years it's been.
Grandma!
Hey, grandma!
Oh, it's you, Lusca.
I guess I can't help it.
I'm sure it's always around here.
Thief!
I'm not a thief!
I'm a police officer!
I'm a thief!
You're a thief pretending to be a police officer!
No, I'm not!
I just came to buy tobacco!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
Grandma!
Grandma?
Let go of me, Yoko.
You're making that face, but you're a real police officer.
A real one?
I'm sorry, I was just...
I was sorry for trying to take the tobacco on my own.
But I was thrown away.
I get it now.
No one thinks you're a police officer.
I'm afraid that my head is in danger.
Mom, did Yoko ever tell you what happened to Yoko?
She just told me.
Oh, oh!
Mottl!
Sasaki!
Yoko!
You've been standing on the platform...
All of you didn't guess he had aBT, did you?
...to the platform?
Don't move!
That was good.
You two, get up.
I thought we would go to the Olympics.
But now, I'm just a woman in the mountains.
That's right.
Go, go, go!
Go!
Give me back my baby!
What's wrong, Terai?
When did you have a baby?
It's not my baby.
Hey, wait!
More importantly, Ryo-san,
A rare person is coming.
Hey!
A rare person?
Hey, it's a guest.
Guest?
To Ryo-chan?
Ryo-san.
Hey!
Long time no see.
It's Ryouko-chan.
It's been a while.
What? Ryouko-chan?
Yeah, yeah.
I was just passing by the tobacco shop and I heard a rumor.
It's completely changed.
What's wrong?
What?
Nothing.
I don't want to see the Kameari town for the first time in a long time.
You don't want to see the Kameari town for the first time in a long time.
I see.
Your husband was a reputable man in Kasumegaseki.
Are you doing well?
Yeah...
What?
Perhaps, what's that now…
Yeah.
He is a twin.
He is four,
but he's already playing tricks.
Is that so?
What's your name?
Koji on my name.
Together, they are called Koji Ken.
It's Koji on Kenji.
That's nice.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
Hey, Nagagawa, Reiko,
Let's talk about when you were in high school, Ryoko-chan.
No, Ryo-san.
Don't be shy, don't be shy.
Back then, the office had me, the manager, and the old man.
Ah, Totsuka was there too.
What? Is that true, Totsuka?
Yeah, it's true. I saw it with my own eyes.
That tobacco shop's Ryoko-chan fell in love with him.
Haha, it's spring.
Here he comes. It's him.
He's the senior of the literature club.
There's not much connection between the literature club and judo club.
Yeah, that's why he hasn't even spoken to them yet.
He's always just staring at them until they pass by.
It's hard to say.
Yeah, let's have a date somehow.
N-no, I just got here.
You're not even close to being a regular.
You're the gym guy, aren't you.
Don't you think the guilt that Raskolnikov has borne
will be applied to us high school students?
Y-yes.
What's going on?
I don't really get it.
Well, this is the first date.
That pretty girl is...
Kirimanjaro Yuki.
Eh?
Akkyu Shoden.
Oh.
I wonder why.
I feel a little sick.
That's about a different world.
W-what's wrong?
Ah...
That's...
A-a-a...
Is it an opportunity to tie her up or something?
Yes. Yes.
Ah-ah-ah!
Help, Mama!
Help, Mama, huh!
Is that where Mama is?
You're the one who's the one who's the one to blame, huh?
You're the one who's the one to blame, huh?
He-he-he-he-heh.
He-he-he-heh.
Well, Mama, you're going to have to go out with us.
Hey!
You're putting her in the wrong place!
I'm going to go get her!
Totsuka!
Leave it to me!
Ryo! Totsuka!
I'll be on your side, Yoko!
You did it, Mama! Now there's no more bad guys around!
I'm sure there are no more bad guys around!
Mother-Kon?
I don't know about that!
I now understand why only smart people can't do it.
That's true.
After that, the guy gave Yoko a massage,
and she kept chasing him around.
It's so frustrating.
If you're going to wait, then wait!
Don't write a prank on the handbook!
Give it back to me!
Geez, I won't listen no matter how much I say it.
Hey, Kenji! Koji!
Ha ha, it's no use scolding him.
He's so old now, he's always playing pranks.
Ah!
Geez!
Hey, Terai! Where's the key to the handbook?
That was also taken by the two of them.
What?
Oh, right.
You all went to the beach, didn't you?
On a trip to the Chounai Sea.
Yeah, to the Chiba Sea.
Then, you two,
make sure you don't get any bad bugs on your first-born granddaughter.
And take good care of her.
It's okay, I'm not worried.
I'm counting on you, Yoko.
We both have work to do.
Please.
Oh, yeah! Leave it to us!
We can't let any of us stay in our house!
I'm off.
"A
It seems like everyone's scared.
It's okay, it's okay.
We're trying not to let Yoko-chan get any bugs on her.
Since we're entrusted with this, we have a responsibility.
This is fun!
Right, Ryo-san?
I knew it. This is what you call the sea.
Ryo-tsu, the waves are coming this far!
That's enough!
Oh, it's a beauty contest.
Yoko-chan, you should try it.
Eh? I don't think...
It's okay.
If we cheer for her, she'll win!
Next up is the entry.
Entry No. 25, Yoko-chan from Katsushika prefecture!
Huh?
I've been waiting for you, Yoko-chan!
The tobacco shop princess!
Yeah!
Why aren't you wearing your bikini?
Take it off!
Hey, hey, take it off!
Show me your boobs!
Ryo-tsu, you're not going to do it?
Please don't take that cheap yaji.
Shut up!
I don't need a man!
I'm going to pull it out!
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Quiet!
Don't throw dirty yajis!
What?
Where did you come from?
I was in the B class in junior high school.
I'm in the C class.
You bastard.
I'll beat you up!
Hey, I won't give in!
I'm a sea net cleaner.
Ah, it always turns out like this.
Hey, don't get it wrong!
We're policemen!
Don't lie!
Where are policemen like you?
I'm not lying!
Don't say that!
I got it, I got it.
Listen to me!
If you're a officer!
You haven't changed at all since then.
You're right, you're like a senior.
Okay, I got it.
You took a long time.
Shut up, this wire is dangerous.
It can't be in my hand.
I'm sorry, I'm really not good at this.
You're right, you're like your mom, not your dad.
That's right.
I don't want you to look like me,
and I want you to look like me in many different ways.
Takashi-san, you should spend some more time with your child.
By the way,
I've been thinking about
what you're going to say about the new Tetsu-san.
Senpai and Totsuka-san are the only ones I talk about,
and Terae-san hasn't appeared at all.
That's true.
Hey, Ryo-chan, do you have anything to say about Terae-san and Yoko-san?
No, there's nothing like that.
You have that?
The most important episode about Terae-san?
No, Ryo-san, don't talk about that.
What, what, Ryo-chan?
I'd like to hear it.
What about Terae-san?
Actually,
if it's no good,
It's fine, it's just a matter of time.
I'm not going to talk about it.
Welcome.
Can I have a cigarette?
Just one.
Yes, the usual.
Thank you.
As expected of the super electromagnetic robot.
It's a powerful magnet.
Ryo-chan.
What about Terae?
If it's Terae,
I went to buy a cigarette.
A cigarette?
That's strange.
You don't smoke, do you?
I don't smoke, but I went to buy one.
It's the fifth time today.
Fifth time?
Oh, Terae.
It's about the documents I left here.
Oh.
Oh!
Terae.
Terae-san,
I am Terae-san.
I'm going to smoke a cigarette.
It was the first time.
Terae-san,
Terai-san,
did you come to the part-time job you wanted?
Wasn't it?
I was going to do it the last time.
I was about to do it the last time.
What's important is,
Kashimi's day off was an accident.
I realized that.
What happens?
What do you mean?
What's the point?
If you keep it up,
it's no good.
What do you mean?
and have a happy family life.
It's a quick thing to do.
Oh, right, Yoko-chan.
Do you remember the wedding?
Yes.
"Yoko's Wedding"
Oh, Yoko. What's up?
Grandma, I've been taking care of you since you were a little girl.
What's with the sudden greeting?
It's not good for your health to be greeted with such a stupid greeting.
That's right.
I wanted to do it once.
Something like a TV drama.
I'm sorry.
There were many people who wanted to get a man like you to be married.
A man like you is like a grandmother.
Your father and mother are quiet.
I was also told that I was gentle and good at smoking.
What?
No way.
I can't believe it.
What is this?
What is the daughter going to marry?
How do you hear that quiet mouth?
It's okay.
It's love and love with Takashi-san.
If you say that,
That's a big family.
The neighbors are different from the suburb.
It's a mountainous woman.
I see.
That's right.
I don't want to be a pain in the ass.
I'll stop getting married.
Say that again.
It's a lie.
I'm not lying.
I'll go to the wedding and do it well.
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Yeah.
I can't believe I can see Yoko's bridegroom figure.
There is nothing left in this world.
You.
Kiss with Princess
Grandma, you know where we are?
It's the princess hotel with the turtle.
I know.
I'll be going later.
We are both Doppler-ians, but we're different.
He's safe, and we're better than the others.
Y- you look so pretty.
Oh, well, my gums are actually quite puffy.
Here, it's done.
Hmm? That looks good.
Now then...
*crying*
Kouharu-san? Kouharu-san? Kouharu-san? Kouharu-san?
Yes, Sasaki speaking.
What did you say?
Is that true, father?
Yes. I got a call from the neighbor, Miyake-san.
Grandma...
I was so surprised. I was looking forward to seeing you as a bride.
Father...
Oh, you're here.
I'll make sure you don't steal my love.
Yoko-chan.
Ryo-san.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Grandma...
Grandma is at the hospital.
What?
I wanted to show her my wedding dress, but...
Let's go!
Huh?
Move, move, move, move!
Hey, move!
Here, take this.
Here you go.
Hurry up!
Ryo-san.
Don't be nervous! I'm going to show Grandma my wedding dress!
Okay.
Take this.
Having sixty boca...
Keep yourани ready.
Okay.
Ouch!
Ow!
Heave off!
Go away!
It's at your mercy!
Get out!
"Screw you!"
"You cannot touch me anymore, old man!"
"Old man!"
"Grandma!"
"M- you're late, but...
Grandma!
Grandma! Stay still!
Open your eyes! It's Yoko!
Yoko came to see me!
She came to see the costume!
Yoko, look at her!
Don't die, Grandma!
Shut up, man.
What do you mean, "don't die"?
It's meaningless.
Geez, can you die from the back of your head?
Can you die from the back of your head?
Huh? Back of my head?
What are you doing?
Is it your wedding?
Did Hanamiko run away?
No, no, no.
Don't worry.
I wanted to show this to you, Grandma.
So...
Yoko.
I'm going to take you to the wedding.
It's a beautiful bride.
Yoko, I know you very well.
You chose her.
She is the best bride in the world.
Do you understand?
You can't leave her no matter what.
Yes.
Go back! Hanamiko is waiting for you!
Yes! Ryo, please come again!
Yes!
Come on!
Did she fight with her husband?
Perhaps, what's the cause?
What's the reason?
No matter what it is.
Even if the city of the turtle changes, people's hearts do not change.
Those two should have returned to the feelings when they met.
Grandma is also happy because of the grass.
I'm still alive.
It's a joke. Grandma is still healthy.
Of course.
But the tobacco shop will retire.
Retire? It's not a joke.
What do you think will happen here?
I am the owner.
The first floor is a tobacco shop.
I will not die until my daughter-in-law gets married.
We were invited to an event to run the Orient Express in Japan.
But in the room where we ran,
Mrs. Christie was running.
The
The The
Kameari
There is Kameari
Ah, surely Kameari
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!