Translated by 方 Hou.
I look up at the sunset floating on the river.
When I kick the love stone, it flies to my shoes.
I wonder if I should go to the place I was saving money for.
I was laughed at for being a good girl.
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I only get a penalty.
The cityscape, which doesn't change even a single yawn, is strangely kind.
I wonder if I should go to the place I was saving money for. I wonder if I should go to the place I was saving money.
From the waterfront of the Tungani-boshi,
to the Taishakuten,
the sunset falls.
Tomorrow it's already over, isn't it?
I lost my happiness again because of the Katsushika-shiba.
I realized
I'm such an idiot.
The following is a true story.
The high-tech equipment police officer Bergman who raised and educated the mayor for 1 billion yen.
Hey, you.
Explain it to me.
Yes.
German police education is excellent,
and his ability to pass the 4-year training in the top class.
German police education is excellent, and his ability to pass the 4-year training in the top class.
One of these people's clothes has a stolen wallet.
Now, Bergman! Arrest the criminal!
Let's do it!
Brrrr...
Hahahaha!
Oh, he shook his head.
That means he's not the culprit.
Go on!
Hahahaha!
He's acting different again.
When the culprit does this...
Hahahaha!
What?
He's using the dog's body to give me cancer!
Hahahaha!
Even though Bergman is hurt,
he's trained to stop the culprit!
He's trained to stop the culprit!
Oh!
Let's take a look at the arrest
with the surveillance camera!
Oh!
Oh, this is great!
It looks like they're actually following him.
The faces of the three
and the results of the search
The evidence of the crime is recorded every day, and is a very useful evidence for the trial.
You can also use a microphone to send messages, and you can also record the voice of the scene.
He's fast!
The speed of the criminal is like a car!
He can jump over 5 meters of wall!
Damn! What a persistent dog!
Hey, watch out!
Watch out!
Bergman is fearless!
Amazing!
He's good at swimming.
Stop running away! It's a game!
Here it comes!
Ouch!
There it is!
Bergman's ultimate move
Moon Salt!
Ouch, that hurts!
Let go of me!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
As you can see, we've caught the culprit from the three of them.
It's impossible to escape from this Bergman.
Well, he's really a great dog.
He's spent 1 billion yen on this, isn't he?
I'm honored that I was chosen to train this dog.
I'd like to choose a partner for the Bergman of that training institution.
Please choose one.
I have a lot of great people in my town.
All of the results of the Katsushika office,
such as personality, blood type, star fortune, and love,
are all included in the computer.
The computer will choose the best partner for Bergman.
I see. That's logical.
Then, let's go.
Who would be a good partner for a dog like this?
I've decided.
The partner for Bergman is this person.
Ryozu Kankichi, the general manager.
What?
Why is Ryozu here?
Is this some kind of town?
Congratulations, Ryozu.
This is truly a great honor.
Well, well.
I hope you'll do your best.
The future of Japan is at stake in your founding.
Ah, ah.
I can't say anything with this.
Seriously.
Sigh.
The first dog of Japan and its partner,
the general manager of Ryozu.
Well then, I'll entrust Bergman to you for two weeks from today.
This is the Bergman's life schedule.
Huh? What is this?
He lives a more regular life than humans.
It seems like people will be disappointed to see this.
Listen to me, Ryozu.
You spent 1 billion yen on this, right?
This doesn't mean I won't come right back.
Okay, okay.
I understand.
It was just a dog and two dogs.
Hey, what's going on?
It's 4 P.M.
So it's time for Bergman to run.
Don't run away so early.
Ryozu can't get any better.
Really.
Hey, how long are you going to run?
-ハイリ
-ノ
-キヨーナヤツ
Huh?
Good morning.
It's 2:00 a.m.
The court order for the day before yesterday...
I've been running all day!
You're so fast, Ryo!
Congratulations, Senpai.
I've been running since early in the morning.
I'm so tired.
I can't even wake up.
I wash my face.
I brush my teeth.
What is this?
This is the monitor of Bergman's tracking camera.
It's a small version of the one you saw at the Katsushika library yesterday.
You can monitor videos within 2 km radius from Bergman's camera.
Reiko is filming.
That's amazing.
I'll play with this tracking camera for a while.
I'm just looking at the monitor.
Listen to me.
I'm so smart because I only studied in Germany and Japan.
I'm going to drink beer to the monitor.
I was thinking about you.
You can't be a freebie.
What?
Do you want to drink this beer?
Here.
Do you like beer?
All right.
Drink, drink.
What?
You want me to drink more?
Yes.
You often get stronger as a human being.
Your mouth is different too.
Maybe this guy,
can have you drunk to death.
Alright, here.
Alright, drink up.
Nice.
Good.
Go!
*Au! Au! Au! Au!*
I did it!
*Hee hee hee hee!*
I'll save it for later!
*Au!*
There's a dog!
Oh no! I found it!
*Au!*
Don't make a fuss!
Berlgman! Come back! Berlgman!
Eh?
Oh my-
What's wrong!?
Ah! No, I'm just that!
This time, we'll let you wait!
*Au!*
*Uu*
*Uu!*
*Au!*
It's not true!
It's a mess!
Wait, seriously!?
Ah, eeeeh!
*Au!*
*Ohh!*
I think I drank too much.
This is totally for two days.
I'm in trouble.
Seriously, this is ridiculous.
You're the worst.
Huh?
Ryotsu.
Ah, Chief! Good morning!
Ah, oh...
Huh? Is something wrong with Bergman?
It's ridiculous!
See, as you see, he's in a good mood.
Really?
Then let's get him to do the investigation.
Huh? What's the investigation?
The investigation?
There was someone who tried to use a dog to look for a woman.
Ridiculous.
He's so mean.
He wouldn't allow someone to use a dog.
Y-Yes, that's right.
He's the worst, isn't he, Bergman?
He said he wouldn't allow someone like that.
That's right.
This is the stolen item that the culprit left behind.
What?
Ridiculous. Ridiculous.
The culprit told Bergman to use the smell that was left in the hole
to find the culprit.
He's going to make the culprit smell the smell of the culprit.
Oh, I see!
Now, Bergman, this is the culprit's smell.
Hey, hey, you don't understand that easily.
Well, it's a house worth a billion dollars.
Okay, now, go, Bergman.
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
Huh?
What's wrong?
He's trying to make me laugh.
Now, Bergman, it's work. It's work.
What? What?
I see.
You've figured out the culprit's purpose.
Head, Ryotsu, the inspector.
We're going to investigate the culprit with Bergman.
Yeah, we're looking at the monitor right now.
Do it well.
Huh?
Ryotsu, don't get in the way of Bergman.
I... I'll do it.
Okay.
The last night's bath was a mess.
Bergman's been like this for two days.
How can we get him out?
Hey, Ryotsu!
What are you talking about?
Don't be serious!
He's not even talking much.
Huh?
Oh, no.
I think I saw him somewhere.
Who's this guy?
I found him!
This is the man!
The thief of the national order,
Kaido Heno 56!
What?
Really?
Ryotsu!
That man is the Kaido Heno 56 of the national order!
That's right!
Wait!
I forgot about Bergman.
Hey, wake up!
He's in my way.
Look!
Ryo is making a fuss.
He's much faster than yesterday.
And he's not looking.
Hey, Ryotsu!
What happened to Bergman?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
I'm fine.
That bastard!
Hey, jump, Bergman!
I can't do it.
Where am I?
What's that?
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah.
Hang in there, Bergman!
You're heavy as a sewing doll.
He's moving so much.
Yeah.
It's weird.
That damn staircase!
Yes!
All right.
Here I go!
Oh!
It's heavy!
Get out of the way!
He's running away!
Run!
You're under attack!
Here comes Bergman!
That was a great jump!
Alright! I did it!
You finally woke up!
Alright, Bergman! Arrest the culprit!
Arrest the culprit!
Hey! Don't get so agitated! Calm down!
Hey! You're being seduced by a female dog!
Get back here!
What's wrong, Ryosu? Is something wrong?
N-No, it's nothing.
Run away!
Wait, you bastard!
Damn it!
I have no choice but to do this in place of Bergman!
This is so hard!
What's wrong? You're too slow, Bergman!
Speed up!
Stop!
Let's do it again!
They're going down the stairs!
What's wrong, Bergman?
Hey! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's not you. It's Bergman.
He seems to be fine.
What happened to number 56?
Ow!
Ouch!
Wait, you bastard!
Bergman, cross this pipe!
What? A pipe?
Hurry up! The culprit is running away!
Yes, yes, I understand.
Go, Bergman!
What's wrong? What are you mumbling about?
Ouch!
Hurry up, Zenka! Hurry up!
He fell!
It's okay.
Bergman is good at swimming.
Ouch!
I hit my head on the river.
No! I'm being washed away by the river!
Bergman!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ryoji! Is Bergman okay?
He's fine!
I told you he's not you!
Where's the culprit?
I see.
Ouch!
You bastard!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I've been
Oh, no!
I did it! I got the bird!
Good. Well done, Bergman!
Thank you, sir!
You're not the one who's great!
Well done, Bergman!
Good, good, good.
Huh?
Huh? This dog...
Could it be...
Oh, I knew it!
Chief, this dog is Bergman!
What?
Then who just took the No. 56?
Chief, it's Ryo-chan!
What?
Ryo-chan is following the camera.
This is No. 56, the most famous dog in Japan.
Please take him to the Katushika Shrine.
Yes, sir!
Thank you!
Chief, this is Ryo-chan.
I just brought No. 56 to the pato car.
I see.
Well done.
By the way, Ryo-chan, I can't see your face.
No, no.
I'm here, chief.
Oh, where's Bergman?
Huh?
Oh, no.
He's trying to trick me.
Ryo-chan, you're gonna get caught.
Wait!
He's gonna have a good time.
That's why I'm gonna make him do it.
Huh?
All right, Ryo-chan.
You will continue patrolling the city with Bergman.
Yes, sir!
The women aren't aware of this yet.
Oh, no.
This is not a dog fight.
This is Ryo-chan's view.
What is this?
No, it's an edgy movie.
He's watching silently.
What a mean guy.
Oh, he's moving.
Yeah.
This is the time table of the movie.
What?
Oh, he's writing down the time for the movie.
What a guy.
Huh?
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
What are you doing in that outfit?
A fire!
Seriously.
Huh?
Where is it?
The switch!
What is this?
This is terrible.
The minister left his precious safe in there.
What should I do if it burns?
Huh?
Ryo-chan.
Bergman, I'm sure the fire will die out.
Call the guard to get the safe.
Eh?
Chief, that's so pitiful.
Don't say that yourself.
Chan, chan, chan, chan.
Bergman said no.
Go, or what.
Is Bergman a fake?
No, not at all.
I'll let you go now.
Damn it, you're such a bad boy.
Are you all right?
Are you not afraid?
Go.
He really got in.
Senior.
Ryotsu.
This is a very heavy and hot safe.
Do your best, Bergman.
He's a good one to play alone.
Bergman.
Hey, Bergman.
Did you come back here?
I was worried about you.
You suddenly disappeared from the inn.
All right, all right.
Oh, you were so worried.
Yeah, of course.
Bergman and I are one body.
I see.
So, Froyo.
Did you go with him?
No, I didn't.
I didn't go to the bathhouse.
What are you talking about, chief?
Takagawa.
Play this tape.
All right.
Oh, that's...
Wait a minute.
That's because Bergman sweated.
I feel like I went to the bathhouse.
What?
A dog!
I found it!
Senior.
You made Bergman drink beer, didn't you?
It's the same as Ryo-chan.
Well, well, well.
I don't like it.
It's a real trouble that it looks like my voice.
I'm scary!
I'm scared!
I'm a pervert.
I'm scary!
I'm scared!
I'm a pervert.
I have to admit that there are similar voices and forms.
You idiot!
No matter where you look, this is Ryosu!
You're the one!
Rumors say that I'm a woman who can't fall in love
But there are so many things I want to do
I am me
I want to run in the wild desert on my bike
I want to be free more than a bird
I wish I had wings
I want to be free more than that
I don't regret it
I'll stop being like that
I'll remain as female
Love is beautiful
The first battle
The third battle
The sixth battle
The eighth battle
The eleventh battle
The twelfth battle