When watching TV, brighten the room to let it look as bright as you can!
Come to my place, everyone who's short of money!
I'm not here, either, yet I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
You'll be able to do something somehow
If you don't have a job, come to my place
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's on fire
Ah, it's on fire
You'll be able to do something somehow
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
Don't make a fool out of yourself, 2-пис וandal
Don't make a fool out of yourself, 2-пис wyandal
Don't make a fool out of yourself, 2-pys wandal
Don't make a fool out of yourself, 2-pis wandal
I recommended you to the director, so please take care of him.
Understood.
And one more thing.
Can you ask a policeman who knows about the underground town to be a guide in the program?
That means you're going to be on TV?
Of course.
If you say that there was a underground town born in a police station in front of the park...
Just one person.
If there is a failure on the national net, it will be a nuisance to other officers.
It will be a nuisance to other officers.
Let's avoid it somehow.
However, the temple is from Hokkaido, Reiko is from Kobe, and Nakagawa is from America.
Ohara, if you know the underground town, you can go anywhere you want.
I see.
As expected of the director.
Are you going to write all this down in one night?
It's a sudden story.
I'm sorry, but it's for the sake of the Katsushika office and this town.
Don't do it.
But if you're going to guide the underground town, you're more responsible than me.
I know that.
What?
I don't know what to do.
I asked Ryotsu to take a big risk of image down.
I'm going to hire a serious and beautiful young policeman.
I've thought about it with the director.
I see.
What?
You're going to work in this station.
A great underground police officer.
That's right.
I'm not going to let you do it.
Anyway, the director is a direct officer.
So, please get on a big ship and complete the mission.
Does the senior know anything about this?
I don't know anything.
What?
I sold my first-hand and I made Ryotsu a minor from today.
I'm sure he'll be playing somewhere by now.
Today's main, Kamiori Steaks.
The start has been cut.
Each is on the other side in a stale state.
The battle is hard.
What will I do next!
Now, turn to the 4th corner and go straight!
What's happening here?
They're lining up in front of the Ararako branch!
They're lining up!
Oh my!
It's a flash!
What?
What's happening here?
It flashed!
What happened?
The tissue fell!
Hey!
This one fell too!
It looks like it's about to start.
Then, let's do the last one.
Yes.
What is this temple?
Daikyoji, also known as Shibamata Taishakuten.
What are its characteristics?
Well, its specialty is grass dumplings and hyakkaen.
Hyakkaen is Mukojima.
Eh?
Mukojima is Shobu-en.
Shobu-en is Horikiri.
I see.
Horikiri is Shobu-en, but it's Ohamajaya.
I haven't slept, so my head is getting confused.
Then, let's go to this one.
Aotomatsushi's second son, Taizo-kun.
Correct.
Then, who is this?
Hmm...
Kenichi-kun from Shibamata's
Senbei shop.
This is Midori-chan from Kanamachi Tenkatsu.
Kenichi-kun is this one.
Ah!
No!
If it's Paria or Milano,
I'm even familiar with the cafe's galson in the back street.
It's a one-night stand, so it's not impossible.
Well then, Nakagawa-san, please.
Ah!
Yes.
It's alright.
Be confident.
Well then, here we go.
5, 4, 3...
Te... Teyandei!
Bela-bomenei!
Hmm...
I can't really feel anything.
Ah...
Ah!
It's Ocha-i, isn't it?
Then, please continue.
Go... Go... Gochisora!
Date ni Ishita-machi no hashitsuzo otome nan ga shishichainei tten da!
Konjikisho!
Hmm...
S... Sorry.
I'm sorry.
According to the story I heard from the Chief of the Katsushika branch,
Nakagawa-san was born in Fukagawa,
and his father is a "Tobi-shokunin" who has been a "Tobi-shokunin" for 10 generations.
His mother is a former geisha of Yanagi Bridge, Haru Yakko.
His older brother is a "Hanabi-shokunin", and his younger brother is a "Rakugo-ka".
Oh!
Y... Yes!
I was really happy to hear that he was the perfect character for this program,
but he seems to be a very elite young man.
He's being ignored.
What should we do?
Hmm...
Actually...
The times have changed, I suppose.
Huh?
We'll have to make a little bit of a scene here, but that's fine, right?
Please help the two of them, too!
What?
Us, too?
All right! Let's go!
Next Hour
I think they're like "Tola-san".
Not "like". That's how they are.
All right, all right, I'm getting where we need to go!
Mr. Nakagawa's short pants and his short valiant look мер.
Then after half a year, we'll have Mr. Nakagawa come back with "bu-rari!"
Please welcome the two old friends warmly.
Well, that's just a great "Jun-sa" that I've never seen in half a year and I'd kill to regret it.
We're taking a walk around the town, so please walk around.
Please walk around.
We have no choice but to do as he said.
That's right.
There's a turtle there.
There must be a turtle.
Hey, worker, are you still an idiot?
Ryo-chan!
Hey, hey, there's a weekend job.
Huh? A TV station?
No, I'm not going to go. I'm going to the camera. Peace!
Okay, okay, I'm good.
I was wrong, Nakagawa-san.
Um, I'm over here.
Oh? Then who are you?
Huh?
I see.
I was about to believe the manager's nonsense of taking a few days off.
Ryo-chan, didn't you go to the police station?
Even though it's a big day,
why did you go to the police station?
It was a light-hearted fuss.
I was expecting a young man from America
to be on TV.
I had a bad dream.
Huh?
Senior.
Turn around.
Yes.
I told the manager that you were more suitable for the job.
I told you that you were suitable for the job.
You can't ask Ryo-san, who doesn't know what to do,
to do an important job.
What?
That's right.
If you are serious about your daily work,
I think the manager would have asked Ryo-chan to do it.
Don't treat people like a kid.
I can do it like a teacher.
Good.
Close.
Please do that line again with the name of the tongue.
Name of the tongue?
Stop it, tongue!
Don't treat people like a kid!
Like this.
Don't talk like that now.
Don't do that.
You are just like my father.
Hey, you.
You are making so much noise here.
I will teach you a lesson.
You are a good boy.
Okay.
Good.
I will wait for you.
I will ask you to be the guide.
You are a real man.
Leave it to me.
Oh.
You are like a tiger.
I think the manager likes you.
Ryo-san is back at the exit.
He is welcoming his colleague warmly.
Please say hi to him as usual.
It is hard to say hi as usual in this outfit.
Let's start.
You look a little thin.
Are you eating?
I am healthy.
You are full of hair and cat's dandruff.
Ryo-san is back.
Ah.
You were dumped by a beautiful woman.
No.
That's why I am in a good mood.
He is a real man.
What?
Cut.
Okay.
Great.
Now, Ryo-san who had a big fight with OI-chan,
will jump out of the building.
Who is OI-chan?
Ryo-san.
What are you doing here?
You have a day off until tomorrow.
You have been talking to me,
Even though you are a Katsushika-Hiroshi,
if you lead me to a low-ranging town,
there should be no one on my right.
This is the president's decision.
You have no right to say anything.
I will tell you.
I am OK.
Great.
Next,
Ryo-san who jumped out of the building,
will tell the old lady who appeared suddenly.
If I tell you,
the old lady will be...
Hey,
Don't forget to appear on TV on behalf of the Katsushika-Hiroshi.
It's a joke.
In that case,
you don't have to do anything.
I will be in all the shooting.
OK?
The president wants to be on TV.
What?
It's OK, chief.
Let's do it for the image of the Katsushika-Hiroshi.
Well,
which is Mr. Komine's house?
go straight and turn left.
OK.
Then,
I'll wear it and go to Edoben again.
What?
Go straight and turn left.
That's where you are.
Thank you very much.
This is a way of talking.
Really.
What?
Yes.
Next,
please tell us about the environment around this exhaust pipe.
Well,
this is the 6th line of the national highway,
which flows in front of this exhaust pipe.
From the place where you go to the Mito area,
which is familiar to you in the Mito Komen,
the name of the Mito Kaido has been given.
Although the real Mito Kaido is a narrow road in the back,
this 6th line is a new road.
In the past,
it was called the 13th road.
Why is it called the 13th road?
The road is just like the Mito Kaido.
The road width is just right.
13th.
This is a famous 13th-line road.
It's a strange story.
I hope you understand.
OK.
Thank you.
Don't you think that you really look like a police officer in the city of Shita?
Mr. Chief.
Oh,
I wonder.
I was also amazed at the place where you just shot Mr. Ryotsu.
Oh,
you were shooting?
Yes.
I was in a bad mood in the city of Shita.
Oh,
I see.
You're doing your best.
The feeling of loving the city of Shita is one in a million.
Yes,
it's okay for this.
That's good.
I feel like I'm making a mistake.
I can be on TV.
Well,
that's fine.
I'll let you off the earth.
bye.
Hey,
Let's go now.
Kuroyama.
Well,
you're right.
You'll do everything well.
Thank you.
That's fine.
You can go now.
Thank you for telling me no.
Thank you so much.
I truly appreciate it.
I'm sorry.
Kuroyama,
I respect you.
This is a show-off, Ryotsu-san.
He's carrying Mikoshi and is a man.
He's patrolling from Inase to Shibamata.
Shibamata!? How many kilometers do you think it's going to take?
It's 3 km by straight line.
Are you trying to kill me?
Boss, at least help me carry him.
I can't.
Gikkuri-koshi was not healed the other day.
Show me your spirit.
I can't.
Damn it. I'll show you my spirit.
O-ryaah!
Wa-shoi! Wa-shoi! Wa-shoi! Wa-shoi! Wa-shoi! Wa-shoi!
Here, here, here, here...
I'm so hungry I can't walk.
What's that?
What's wrong, Ryotsu-san?
Ah...
Let's make a scene where I ask the chief of the town to feed me eel.
What?
Oh, so you were born in the town, too, chief.
Well, um...
I was born anyway.
I'm living in Chiba now.
Okay.
Let's make a scene where we eat together.
Please take the sign of the restaurant.
Hehehehe.
Have you ordered anything?
What do you want to order?
Well, I'll have the eel bowl.
What?
The staff will treat you to a special eel bowl with liver soup?
Oh?
I see.
I'm the cheapest one.
So this is the spirit of the town.
Yes.
I can't afford the money I have to pay for the meal.
I see.
I'll have the extra sake and the cold beer.
Okay.
A special meal for 15 people.
Liver soup.
And cold beer.
Oh.
Ahahahaha.
It's always so lively here.
Thanks to you, I won't have to pay for the meal until the end of the month.
It's better than living alone.
I don't know why.
Huh?
What?
When I think back on what we've done so far,
I wonder if we can really make a PR program with that kind of scene.
Huh?
There's no way we can.
I thought it was strange from the beginning.
Oh, I see.
If we keep this up, we'll be laughed at all over the Internet, not just us.
Chief.
That's a problem.
I'm hoping that this show will be a PR program, too.
I can't even look at my parents and my ancestors.
Ah.
Oh.
It's Koto!
Get lost!
You idiot!
You're not going to get away with this.
Huh?
Chief.
Stop it!
Let him go!
Shut up!
Get lost!
It's Kota!
Ah!
Oh!
Chief!
Turn around behind him and stab him.
Roger that.
Ouch!
Let him go!
Shut up!
Get lost!
What's going on?
Damn it!
Any injuries?
No.
Get lost!
Stop!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Easy.
"Matsuo! Matsuo!"
"Wait!"
"What the hell is this guy doing at this critical moment?"
"Mucho!"
"We've been waiting for you, Mucho!"
"What's with that camera?"
"I just thought of a great idea!"
"A great idea?"
"I'm going to make a show with it!"
"Then the program's structure should be replaced!"
"Anyway, go after the culprit! I'm fine with it!"
"Roger!"
"Wait!"
"Don't you hear me say 'wait for me'?"
"What the hell are you doing?"
"Shut up! Stop right there!"
"You hear me?"
"Don't run away!"
"I'll kill you!"
"The 800-year-old Edo village's hidden " "G
yoyo Button's montsuki" "is
also a cherry blossom!"
"It's a young man called Hanakawa Sukeroku"
"or a young man called Ryotsu"
"from the Kameyari Park."
"Don't run away!"
"You're going to pay for it!"
"You're all going to pay for it!"
"What the hell?"
"You don't know what's going on, Sukeroku!"
"Give me back what you stole!"
"You're still resisting?"
"You little..."
"Oh?"
"Darn you!"
"You're full of yourself!"
"You've made a fool of me!"
"You turned me into a fool!"
"Ryotsu!"
"Don't come near me!"
"I know!"
"Let go! Let me go!"
"I won't let you get away!"
"What the hell?"
What's wrong, Ryosu?! I'm coming!
Let's go!
Hey, hold on!
Did you get it?
I'll use this!
Thank you for your hard work.
Here you go.
S-Sorry.
Mr. Ryosu, Mr. Ohara. I've been waiting for you for five times.
You understood, didn't you?
Look! This is the spirit of a police officer.
Yes, I finally understood.
I can make a wonderful show with this!
Thank you very much.
Ah, thank you very much for your help.
It seems I was able to keep my eyes on you.
This is good.
I'll have to excuse myself for this, again.
Shura Saito
Mr. Ryo, this is the place where we can put the secret of the secret.
Yes, Chief.
Here I go.
Close your eyes and we will wait for you!
Oh, thank you very much, I just want you to leave me alone.
I will record the scene in the latest DVD and tell my story to you.
I'll do it.
Ryo, congratulations.
The robbery was also arrested.
I thought what would happen when I went out with the chief.
That's good.
This is a champagne for celebration.
You don't have to be so careful.
One is 300,000 yen.
I'll sell it to the owner.
Ryo, the president is giving compliments.
I'm embarrassed.
This is the problem with the boss.
Thank you for your hard work.
You did well, Ryo.
It's all thanks to the chief.
Well.
The director also understood what happened at the end.
It's a perfect program for PR and image up of my office.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll show you the front row.
It's about to start.
A recover your spirit.
What's this?
It's not firewood.
This is a firewood.
This is the firewood.
It's your favorite firewood.
Let's do it.
The direction in which the firewood converges.
He's really here!
Laugh! Laugh! Laugh!
I'll send you a lot of "Shitamachi Jocho"
60 minutes!
80 minutes!
I'm sorry again
What is this?
That's...
Hey! Ryo-kun!
It's not my fault
The director doesn't understand!
It's an ounces please
Please, can't you too?
I'll send you a lot of "Shitamachi Jocho"
Ryo-kun?
I hear someone at the last minute
Someone's watching
Ryo-kun?
That's not it
And the blue lady above my eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
I can see you all
Let's go!
That's Kameari
Kameari for sure
Come on, everyone
To our town
Thank you!
You were listening to the story
of the worst man, Ryotsu Kankichi, right?
I see. Your face and way of talking are also vulgar.
Me?
I'm Ghiboshi Lemon, the younger sister of Matoi.
Next time on Super Kindergarten, Lemon!
Thanks for watching!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community