Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ in the head of a carpenter ♪
♪ and I was laughed at ♪
♪ for being a
♪
♪ a
What?
At this time,
the seat of the flower is not yet prepared.
What do you mean?
No matter what you say,
the flower is still far away.
You don't have to take a seat so early.
Too sweet!
Flower viewing is a big event in spring.
The place of the flower viewing is
a garbage dump,
near the toilet,
or the street of people.
The place of the flower viewing is a very noisy place.
If there is a strange shop near,
the participants will not be able to enjoy the flower viewing,
and the scars of the heart will remain for a lifetime.
It's too much.
It's not too much.
There are only a few special seats that can enjoy the flower viewing.
By the way, in the case of the upper park,
the area of the special seats of the flower viewing is one tennis court.
Is that all?
Yes.
That's why,
if you don't take a seat now,
what will happen?
I understand.
I'll leave this case to you, Ryo-tsu.
That's why.
I want you to take a seat immediately.
What about work?
Of course, you will be assigned.
I don't have time to play.
It's the same as night shift.
Don't answer.
This is an order.
I've done it when I was a student,
but it's enough the day before.
That's right.
That's too early.
Well,
I'll try if you say so.
Try?
There are three super special seats in the upper park,
which should be called special seats in the special seats.
If you can secure it by the afternoon of tomorrow,
I will accept your request.
That's true.
In return,
if you can't do it,
please follow my instructions.
Good!
One seat up.
The next one is here.
This is the last one.
Two seats up.
Three seats up.
With this,
we've secured all the three special seats
that Ryo-tsu had said.
It's easy.
Then,
we just have to wait and see until the afternoon of tomorrow.
You fool!
It's a mistake just to put on the seat and think you got the seat.
I'll tell you how strict you are
about making yourself comfortable in a far-away land.
I'm getting changed.
Huh?
Imaimai should be next, right?
But Imai-kun suddenly stopped coming to work.
I was asked to be his agent because I was his high school friend.
I see.
Then, I'll leave it to you.
Yes, please leave it to me.
I can't believe what the first person I met said.
Yes, your turn.
What is this?
Are you motivated?
What?
You bastard!
I've always hated your eyebrows!
The dark circles under your eyes are more disgusting!
Is this a fight?
I think so.
You bastard!
Broom!
I'm going to eat you up!
That woman is Gifted, Magic Girl!
Broom!
Did you abandon Moken?
How dare you!
I won't ask for an agent!
What are you doing in my place?
How dare you leave the market!
I'm sorry.
You're the best, Nano-chan.
I-I got hit.
Here too.
Kawashima!
What's wrong?
I-I got hit.
I got hit.
It's dirty.
The seats were spread out all the way up there.
You don't know.
When I came, there was nothing on the seats.
Don't be stupid!
You were blown up by the wind.
The wind wasn't blowing.
Now we have the right to hold all the iron ore.
Damn it. I got hit.
I don't know where to go.
The place is so hard.
You know how hard it is?
Yes.
When you want to take a seat, don't ever fall off.
There are a lot of people who are aiming for special seats right now.
Such as...
You!
Come out!
You've been looking for me!
Thank you, Mr. Ryozu.
I didn't know you had noticed.
What are you guys?
We are trying to secure the place where the fireworks are going to be held.
But it's not a cherry tree here.
What?
Are they the people of the American government?
It seems that they are the immediate relatives of Vice President.
Vice President is a great Japanese man, and he is also familiar with cherry blossoms.
He hopes to see the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
Full bloom cherry blossoms?
It's a legendary cherry blossom that almost nobody knows about.
It's a legendary cherry blossom.
It blooms much faster than other cherry blossoms.
After other cherry blossoms have fallen, it will continue to bloom for a while.
That's why it seems that it blooms all year round.
According to the research, it is said that it is located in the Okutama region.
However, Vice President's schedule for the next day is not yet clear.
Therefore, I want you to secure the special seat of the cherry blossom as long as you go to see the cherry blossoms.
Mr. Lee
What?
This is a request from the Japanese government.
The Japanese government?
That means that a price will be issued, right?
Of course.
Oh!
Please leave it to me.
Let's deepen the friendship between Japan and the United States through cherry blossoms.
Oh! Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Damn it.
It's fast if I use a helicopter.
I'll make a hole.
It is said that it will scatter the cherry blossoms on the bridge, so the helicopter should not be used.
Haa...
Well, it can be a little large.
We will continue to walk from here.
What!
Oh!
There is a store.
Excuse me.
Welcome!
Oh, I can ask you for a moment.
How long does it take to get to the place where the full moon cherry is?
Full moon cherry? What's that?
It's a legendary cherry, so maybe even locals don't know about it.
There's nothing on this.
Don't say anything bad. Just take it back.
Okay, okay.
Hey!
There's no way out!
There's no other way?
Yeah, it's only this way.
We have no choice but to take it back.
It can't be helped.
Senpai!
You can get money just by taking the cherry blossoms!
Can you take it back with this?
I guess I'll have to go with you.
The bridge is gone!
I'll go with you!
I guess we'll have to take it back.
Bulbul, the rope.
Okay.
Let's go!
I want to go home!
No matter how you look at it, this road has been closed for years!
I'm tired.
Did they really come here to investigate?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
No, they said they analyzed the satellite photos and determined the location.
That's right.
Damn it!
I can't move anymore.
I'm at my limit, too.
Go ahead, Ryotsu.
What's wrong? Do your best!
Full moon cherry is almost there!
Come on, go ahead!
It's full moon cherry!
So...
it's full moon cherry.
It's an elixir!
It's beautiful.
I've never seen such a beautiful cherry tree.
But I don't think there's anyone who would come all the way here,
but is there any point in taking the place?
Whether it's meaningful or not, if you take the place here, you'll get money.
Let's enjoy it until Vice President comes.
Here, here, here, here, here.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
That's it, that's it, that's it, that's it.
Idiot.
I'll go wash my face.
What the hell?
What's wrong, Ryozu?
You're so cold.
You guys, look around.
Around!
When did you come to this place?
What's going on?
Saku?
When did you come to this place?
You can't just come in here without permission.
I took the place here.
You're the old man who went to the graveyard at the foot of the hill.
You said you don't know the Ten Thousand-Year Cherry Blossom.
You're lying.
But we worked so hard and finally got here.
How?
I'm the only one who knows the way out.
Now, you're the one who blocked the road and dropped the bridge.
You can't let me see the flowers here.
Absolutely not.
Who are you?
The smell of romance in the cherry blossoms is good.
I love cherry blossoms and go fast.
I'm going to protect the Ten Thousand-Year Cherry Blossom.
Cherry Blossom?
Ten Thousand-Year Cherry Blossom?
You're going to protect the Ten Thousand-Year Cherry Blossom?
It's known that there are beautiful cherry blossoms in this land.
I want to see the flowers.
Then I can build a mountain of garbage.
I can build a toilet.
I can climb trees.
I can cut the branches.
Then, the Ten Thousand-Year Cherry Blossom is over.
No, it's not.
I've blocked all the roads here.
Here it is.
Cherry Blossom Fairy Tale.
You're kidding.
It was your fault that you sent us to a place like that.
We came here on a government order.
Right.
We have to let the Vice President of the United States see the flowers.
There might be a crack in the relationship between Japan and America!
After hearing that, I can't afford to hand over this place any more.
What did you say?
If the Vice President of the United States finds out that I had a nosebleed,
the nosebleed will be gone from the world!
Who's there?!
Take this! The Cherry Blossom Wind Jutsu!
You can't do this!
The hole will fall!
But you're the President of the Year-Rolling Cherry Blossom World!
Cherry blossoms are most beautiful when they fall!
Ponga!
Balbo!
Sagonji!
Damn it!
I'll take that place back even if I have to!
That's my place!
You're so scary!
This is the Cherry Blossom Wind Jutsu!
The Cherry Blossom Wind Jutsu is a strange form of love.
Hm?
Damn!
I'll never let that be!
I won't give up!
He fell asleep.
He's alone.
He can always escape.
Sakura!
He noticed!
He's here!
I'm here!
Damn it!
I'm not going to get angry!
The Sakura Wind Jutsu!
Balba!
Damn it!
The Sakura Electric Jutsu!
Idiot!
If it's a thick rubber glove, it won't turn on!
I'll make you pay for this!
What are you doing?
Senpai, look!
Kuma!
I was afraid something like this might happen, so I brought the bears of this mountain together.
Ouch!
This is the Sakura Wind Jutsu.
The Sakura Wind Jutsu
Are you a man, a menace?
Man, this old man is a man!
Damn!
Wait!
We're friends!
The Sakura Wind Jutsu
We have to make a move soon.
The front lots of him!
Chompy!
I'm a mirror beast!
Not yet...
Damn, I'm so tired!
Ryotsu, can you hear me, Ryotsu?
Yes, this is Ryotsu.
Vice-President's schedule is early. He'll be coming tomorrow.
I think he'll arrive by noon. He must have taken his place.
Of course! I'm waiting for Vice-President to arrive!
Well then...
Senpai...
In this case, there's only one way.
As you said, I'm on my way!
Let's go, Honda!
Alright!
Let's go, guys!
It's a sakura block!
Get out of my way!
Break it!
Damn you! You're no match for me!
What?
The sakura mechanism!
You're not my match!
Shit!
I may end up losing a fight!
Your Kanilworth is in trouble!
You're so annoying!
How dare you try to steal my position!
Sakura Block Jets!
Now!
Hey, hey!
Oh no! The special seat...!
Yes.
Yeah...
Hey! Nagagawa!
Let the helicopter go down and chase after the bears!
Huh? Don't be so reckless!
We're going to do it! For the sake of my money and the future of Japan!
If you guys can't do it, I'll do it!
Hohoho...
The full moon will be seen soon, Vice-President.
Yeah...
What's with that helicopter?
Please stop, Senior!
We did it!
Who's there?
And also what's with the
The cherry blossoms?
The cherry blossoms...!
Don't tell me, that's...
Vice-President...
Huh?
What're you doing, Senior?
You're not in a bad place to say that.
I'm just telling you that's my fault.
and you can only make up for the other person's anger.
That's right!
George Washington was the one who was like that!
What?
George Washington, the first president of the United States,
was honestly told that he cut the cherry tree in his youth,
and he was never scolded.
Of course, the vice president of the United States would know that!
If I confess honestly,
he'll have to forgive me!
I bet he'll have to forgive you!
Lyos!
Who are you?!
I'm sorry, Vice President!
I cut the cherry tree!
Forgive me, little boy!
Japan, I'm in charge!
I'm hungry!
This is for the good of the United States.
You may scatter.
N-no!
Please don't!
I hate flower viewing!
Subtitled by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
For that reason,
I walked only on the black road
we used to walk together as kids.
...As a politician with an arrogant and arrogant face,
♪ Let's go see that corner ♪
♪ We'll meet everyone, everyone ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, let's go to our town ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!
You think you can make a movie a big hit?
That's great!
If I help you, it'll be a success!
I'll make a movie that will earn 3 billion yen!
Huh? You're not even asking me to do a stunt?
Next time on Ryotsu! Movie Debut!
See you!
Please subscribe!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!