The End
When you watch TV
Keep your room light and keep your distance
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
I walked with a look back
I reached out to my mom
I felt
A strange feeling
So I tried walking on the red and black tiles
I tried walking on the red and black tiles
Everybody was once child
But, they all forget
The politician with a proud face
and the blue lady with blue eyes
Turn around
That corner
You will meet everyone
There is a wall
Kameari
Ah, Kitto Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Double Date in Hell
As expected from Borobo, what a great defense
Happy Birthday, Bobby
Happy Birthday
Congratulations, Bobby
Everyone came here for me?
Thank you, thank you so much
That was last year's birthday
What a ugly birthday
It's pretty grand
Yeah
This year's birthday is...
I wish I could spend it with pleasure like that
Shoro!
It's an explosion!
What's that?
Is it a bomb?
It's a communication capsule
It's for Borobo
There's no way to communicate like that
Your friends are all ugly
Oh, this is from Jody
What? From Jody?
So, what does it say?
Ah...
Um...
Hi, Bobby
Next week is your birthday
Take a break and go to Japan
Of course, I won't tell my dad
We'll spend a wonderful day together
Your Jody
It's an invitation to a date!
If it's just the two of us...
...we'll leave it to you
I thought you were asking for a date
There's no need
Yeah, I guess
I'm sorry
I'm just saying
But you should
How about you?
I'm not worried
I'll always be your friend
I see.
Have you ever spent your birthday with only her?
Sorry, I didn't mean to ask you.
You bastard.
You didn't have a girl until last year!
S-Someone! Someone save me!
What?
Barba!
Wait!
No one's coming to save you.
You're so stubborn.
Wait!
As expected of you, Bulba.
I didn't have a chance to come out.
Are you hurt?
Thanks.
Thanks for saving me.
Maria!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
You're in trouble!
This scene is too much!
Was it a movie?
Movie?
Why did Maria go to the movies?
No!
It wasn't me.
What?
M-Maria went to the movies with two...
That's Marilyn.
She's a big star in Hong Kong.
Her real name is Asatrin.
She's my twin sister.
Sister?
An actress?
Yes.
You defeated the best fighters in Hong Kong.
I love strong people.
Sister?
What's wrong with your chest?
Of course, it's real, unlike Maria.
See?
How bold!
A sister is always active.
Right?
This is...
I can't stand it!
What?
Hong Kong superstar Marilyn has declared a love with her actual lover?
Her partner is a public servant, aandidate.
He's Mr. Barbo.
How bold!
Now, I see...
This is a pocket video, Barbo.
How about marrying Marilyn instead?
Don't say that nonsense!
Oh, wait a minute.
What does this mean?
Hehehe.
Marrying Marilyn might be good.
No...
Watch out, Bulbon!
Bulbon, are you okay?
I just came out of the hole.
That's why I said watch out!
I was so wrong.
Jody again.
What's next?
This is...
Look, it's my birthday!
You thought about it.
You're so thoughtful.
You'll be a good wife.
I... I guess so.
I guess marriage with Jody is the best.
Dating in the pool of the fitness club is perfect for you two.
What? The pool?
Yes, it was written in Jody's letter.
That means...
Marry me.
I can't wait!
With this attitude, we still have a long way to go.
I guess so.
Someone's here.
Marilin!
Welcome back!
I've been waiting for you!
Let's go inside!
Wait!
Bobby, you're a good boy.
This is...
I'm sorry!
But...
This is...
Mar... Marilin...
W-What's that look?
Of course, I prepared it for Bobby.
Does it suit you?
It... It... It...
Stop it!
Bobby, are you okay?
Rin?
I knew you were here!
I saw the staff members looking for you.
You're making trouble for everyone.
What are you doing?
I get it, Ai.
Hey, Bobby. What's this calendar sign?
It's my birthday.
Really? Then let's spend the day together!
I-I understand.
I'm looking forward to it. Good night, Bobby.
Good night...
If I get in that mood on my birthday, I won't be able to get up.
I guess... something happened on my birthday...
What a sinful man I am!
I didn't know that I'd be playing with their hearts!
You just got into Marilyn's temper and forgot about your promise to Jody!
I'm glad you're okay with this.
I'm glad you're okay with this. I'm glad you're okay with this.
You were the same a year ago!
I happen to be at a workplace with no relationship with women...
I'm sure I've seen him being popular before.
I'll kill you, you bastard!
Mr. Nakagawa, can't you consult with a man who's popular with you?
I-I guess...
Jody and Marilyn, I don't want to see either of you crying.
I don't want to see either of you crying.
I think you'll get really mad before you cry, little sister.
Eh? I'll get mad?
No, little sister is strong.
You were good at fighting in the movies, too.
Of course I was.
Since I was a child, I've been training in all kinds of fighting games.
I'm afraid of you being mad, little sister.
You're as good as beating a cow with your bare hands.
What?
You're mad!
I see.
If you refuse to accept Marilyn's invitation, you'll have to follow the same fate as the cow.
Y-Yeah.
Marilyn can't stay in Japan until the filming starts.
Of course, I'll make her schedule more important.
But Jody's scared of you getting angry, too.
I heard you beat a bear with your bare hands.
A bear?
If you refuse to accept Jody's invitation, you'll have to follow the same fate as the cow.
A man with a lot of power is also a big trouble.
What should I do?
Tell me, Mr. Nakagawa!
You know that a man with a lot of power is Nakagawa, right?
I never dated such a great woman.
Is it okay for me to be a good-for-nothing?
Hmph!
Do something!
Well, I'll go with the same plan as you.
Choose a cow or a bear, whichever you like.
You're such a bad girl!
Wait.
This might be a good chance to make that man a good man.
Okay, I got it.
It's a request from a Volvo.
Leave it to me.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Thank you, Ryotsu!
I'll be grateful to you!
You can be happy now.
We should go now.
It will be hard to close the door if he shows up.
Then let's stay here, right?
Let's go!
Dibble, are you all right?
The Parking gamma will keep my business at loggerheads.
Okay, let's go!
What's up?
Now, now, this is what I'm talking about.
I'll have a look at your place.
It's not mine.
Well, I'll call the police now.
How many assistants are we looking for?
They have the costumes that can handle any situation.
Nakagawa is really something.
By the way, I've been wondering.
Why do you have a video camera?
I don't really know, but...
Senpai told me to film the scene of the date.
Double dates are like talking to someone else at the same time.
As you go by, you may not know what you were talking about.
You may not know what you were talking about.
Then you can watch the video.
I see.
But there's another way to use it.
You don't have any experience with double dates, but you're really into it.
Sorry about that!
Senpai, we're almost at the fitness club.
The hell of a double date is about to begin.
Hey, Johnny!
Bobby!
Johnny!
It's about to begin. Let's start filming.
Okay.
What's this?
This swimsuit is specially prepared for your birthday.
Does it suit you?
I-I-I-I can't stand it!
Bobby, are you okay?
I can't stand this tight feeling!
It's a little scary.
You know, Shinopuru is one of my seven mysteries in elementary school.
Same here. I can't believe I got to see real things.
Huh? Oh, it broke.
It's me.
Mr. Marilyn has just entered the shop.
I see. Please come quickly.
Yes, ma'am.
I hope this rest is going to calm you down.
Thank you, Jody.
Oh, how gentle of you.
Jody…
I hope you'll do the same thing after you get married.
I'm the happiest man in the world.
What's wrong, Bobby?
Bobby!
N-Nothing.
I'm going to take a break in the office.
Me too.
I-I'll be back soon, so please wait.
Wait for me.
If you don't wear a tie, you can't enter that store.
Understood.
Welcome.
You're Mr. Volvo Saigo, right?
That's right.
Bobby!
I prepared a special dress for today's date.
Does it suit you?
I-I can't stand it.
What's wrong, Bobby?
N-Nothing.
It's quiet here.
It's as if we're the only customers in this store.
I made a reservation for today.
I wanted to spend time with you alone.
I-I feel like my chest is...
It's a blood-stained ceiling.
It's a summer story.
Oh, it's me.
I'm in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Jody started looking for Mr. Volvo.
Well, eat up.
This looks delicious.
Here, Bobby.
Th-thank you.
She's so kind.
I wonder if she'll be like this even after we get married.
I'm the happiest man in the universe.
Bobby, what's wrong?
N-Nothing.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hurry up.
Jody's waiting.
It's about time.
Hey, the tape's about to come off.
What?
There should be a convenience store over there.
Go and buy it.
I'll take care of the car.
Okay.
There's a car that's been illegally parked in front of the fitness club.
Can you get it out of the way?
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, but I was a little distracted, and I got kicked out.
No, how do we get to the Chinese restaurant?
I guess we have to run.
What about the clothes?
It's a shop for wearing ties.
Lend them to Nagagawa.
Nagagawa, go with him.
Okay, I understand.
Let's go then.
All right.
What do I do?
You're a bully, so you need to learn.
You two go with the corvins.
But you must leave the tape on.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Sorry, but it's not suspicious.
Hey, sorry for making you wait.
Bobby, what happened to your costume?
I had some trouble in the toilet.
It's not a big deal.
Bobby, come on.
Oh, come on.
Hey, Jody.
You're in a hurry.
What are you doing?
Bobby disappeared on a date.
What?
Did he have a date with you?
Oh, no.
With you?
What do you mean?
I didn't ask.
What's with the tape?
This is...
You got it now, right?
Actually, it's from Volvo.
He and Jody were having a fight.
What did he say?
For him, women are just a game.
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you.
I got it.
Marilyn, I got a call.
Here it is.
You're...
Marilyn, I have something important to tell you.
These two have become slaves.
They were trying to take away your property.
You're a terrible villain.
I can't stand you.
I'll never forgive you.
Now you know Volvo's fate.
You're a woman's enemy.
Don't lie to me!
You're a loser who made fun of me.
What?
What was that?
Jody!
What?
I can't believe they came in here.
Jody, this is ridiculous.
Jody, you got away.
I'll never forgive you if you resort to despisancy!
Poor Bobby!
You were fooled by that pertaining woman, weren't you?
What?
Let's get out of here and start the birthday party!
Why would you do that!?
Hey, who do you think you are?
You're the one who's trying to drag Bobby into the path of evil!
I won't let that happen to Bobby!
No! Bobby belongs to me!
Don't touch him!
That's enough! Just go to hell!
I'm going to eat you!
Let go of me!
I said let go of me!
You're...
Now then, I have no choice but to defeat you!
Because you're a mystery!
You and I are in this together!
This is a big fight.
As expected from a bear and a cow.
You're a bear and a cow.
I'm not a bear.
I'm not a cow.
You're a bear.
What are you going to do?
The enemy is Boruto!
Hooray!
They're all so annoying.
Ouch!
Help me!
Why did this happen?
Bobby, where are you?
Bobby!
Ouch!
That's...
I'll take care of Bobby!
See you!
I didn't know they had such a thing.
You're the best actress in Hong Kong.
Damn!
I'll take Bobby back, even if I have to die!
I'll take care of Bobby!