Episode 1: The
The
Hey, I've been wondering about this for a while.
What is this stuffed animal hanging here?
Is it a raccoon?
Isn't it a Leather Panda?
Eh?
Doesn't it look like a raccoon?
What do you mean, "no"?
Isn't this Reiko's?
I always thought it was Reiko's.
No, it's not.
When I first came to this exit, it was already here.
Come to think of it, it looks like it's been here for a long time.
Oh...
Then what about you, Terai-san?
No, it's not.
I remember.
I've been here since I graduated.
Eh?
Then, could it be...
Chief Ohara's?
No way.
If that's the case, you're too mean.
Hmm...
Could it be that I've been living in this exit for a long time?
I'm the owner, after all.
No!
Ryo-chan, you're a...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha...
The End
When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away.
"Akane-gumo"
The last competition!
Alright, it's done!
You're really good at this, senpai.
Well, if I make a minicar, it'll be the best in Japan.
What's the best in Japan?
It took three days to make this, isn't it terrible, chief?
You idiot!
You've been working for three days, haven't you?
No, I mean...
Go clean up and go patrol!
Damn you, chief.
I'll punch you in the ear and make your back hurt.
Hey!
Pull!
I'll punch you in the ear!
Damn you!
What!? I have to pay a hundred million yen!?
To be precise, the cost of repairing the broken bike and truck,
as well as the damage to the goods,
is 9,999,980 yen in total!
What!?
Why do I have to pay for the bike that fell?
I'm a victim!
As a result of the investigation,
this mini car that you threw into the park
was the root cause of the accident!
No way!
Even if it's such a big accident,
he's a very lucky guy
to have not even a scratch.
Anyway, you have to pay with responsibility!
Nakagawa-chan, please!
I can't afford to pay a hundred million yen!
Let's make a wish together!
Just like this, give me a hundred million yen!
No matter how much you pay,
a hundred million yen is...
Nakagawa-chan, you have pocket money, right?
A hundred million yen is...
That's not true!
Ah, more importantly, Senpai,
there's a way to get a hundred million yen with your own money!
What!?
How can I get it?
This is it!
Huh?
A huge athletic field?
Nakagawa Group has put their all into it,
and made it into the Tokyo Bay's home,
and it's finally going to open next year!
To commemorate that,
they're going to hold a 100 million yen winning race!
And if we win, we can get 100 million yen?
Yes!
They've gathered all the participants from all over the country,
and there are over a million applications!
Out of them, 50 teams that have won will be participating,
but if you're Senpai, I'll let you participate by myself!
I see!
So what you should have is the support of the Nakagawa Group!
But we can't participate without the pair,
so we need to find someone with confidence in their physical strength.
Then please come out with us, Nakagawa!
I'm the organizer, so I can't!
I see, then...
What!?
You're going to join the pair!?
It's a hundred million yen prize money,
so it was worth it to spend the night and write a letter of application.
That's why.
I don't want to be a pair with you.
Don't take it the wrong way.
Damn it!
I thought it would be one of them if I joined the pair,
but whatever.
If I can go out with anyone,
I'll manage it!
Wh-Why do I have to participate in such a race?
Originally, the manager had broken my minicar that I made,
so it happened.
What?
Are you going to make something like that while you're working?
I'm sorry, sir.
But I can't pay a hundred million yen with my cheap salary.
It's enough just to join the pair.
I'll manage it later, sir.
I refuse!
There's not a single time I was happy to join the pair with you.
Pass the test.
I understand.
Then there's no other way.
Huh?
Are you sure, Ryo-tsutsu?
I'm going to attack the bank and take a hundred million yen.
I'll take the money.
The manager is the former boss of the gang,
but it can't be helped.
The chief will see the picture of me and the former boss of the gang tomorrow.
Then...
W-Wait, Ryo-tsu!
Don't be in a hurry!
I've already decided.
But, Ryo-tsu...
There's no other way to get a hundred million yen.
Think again!
Ryo-tsu is the one who gave up his chance.
Ryo-tsu, please stop.
Oh, is it the end of the poor subordinate who can't be blessed by his boss?
All right!
I'll come out!
I'll come out, Ryo-tsu!
Are you sure, Ryo-tsu?
I thought you would do it.
It's wonderful to be blessed by your boss.
Ryo-tsu, I'll get a hundred million yen for sure.
Let's do it!
Welcome to the Nagagawa Giant Athletic Field Open Memorial Race.
All the athletics held today are on the third stage.
Each field has a game prepared with ingenuity.
As expected of the pair who have passed the hundred million yen challenge.
The pair who are proud of their physical strength.
But, the one who will compete with us is...
Volvo and Komachi who throw away women if they are paid.
Captain!
You are already dead.
What?
I forgot the morning and night.
Ouch!
Mr. Hon-daro!
Why are you here?
I'm here to announce my world's strongest Honda-ra-ken to the world.
To build the division of South America with the prize.
What?
To do so, I made a postcard of 100,000 yen and made three teams participate.
The winner is ours!
Hmm... I hated the bad-ass subordinates.
Then, let's go to the first stage, the survival game field.
Let's go!
The survival game field.
What's this room?
In the dome, everything is made in giant.
This room has been made into a kitchen and living room for the survival game.
Giant athletics?
Is it about athletics in a huge thing?
Do you play with a gun in this room?
It seems to be so.
Then, please choose the air gun first.
What is this gun?
Are you going to make a fight with this gun?
This dome was made for athletics purposes.
It's not this big to be able to get physical strength.
Indeed, it takes a lot of physical strength to run with this.
Can you really shoot a bullet?
It's a special BB bullet.
There is paint inside the bullet,
so when it hits the body, the paint will be attached to the clothes.
So when the paint is on, it's out.
That's right.
If you can choose a gun, let's start the game.
Yes.
I'll announce the team.
Team A is from No. 1 to No. 25, and the host is the living room.
Team B is from No. 26 to No. 51, and the host is the dining kitchen.
Team A is from No. 26 to No. 51, and the host is the dining kitchen.
The team to be able to win the match loses.
There's Borbo with army experience.
He's pretty tough, isn't he?
Don't worry!
I and you are here.
This is the same team, so we're going to lose.
Then, spread to where I'm in charge!
Where's the survival game?
Boss, watch out!
Damn it!
I can't stand it when they shoot at us like that!
Morumome, is it a strategy that won't work because it's too heavy?
We have no choice but to go around and attack!
Wait, Ryotsu!
On top of the bookshelf!
That was close!
If we go out now, we're gonna be in trouble!
Ryotsu, there's a sniper on the left, so move!
I know! I'll crush him now!
That's heavy...
Boss, to the right!
Good, shoot!
Ryotsu, I've got one down!
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
I forgot to blow back this gun!
Tee hee!
Alright, second down!
My gun!
Looks like the enemy team has stopped moving!
We're gonna break through the central zone, so leave the rest to us!
Alright!
What's next?
Not a single shot!
You bastards!
We're breaking the rules!
Damn it!
I won't lose to a man.
It's better to have a team with Mr. Volvo and Mr. Sakonji.
But if I get a prize money, I think I'll win no matter what dirty trick you use.
That's true.
The match is about to begin.
I will definitely get 100 million yen.
That's enough!
It's spinning!
Break!
I did it!
Ryotsu, I'm tired. I can't move.
Chief, you can go and stop the bank at any time.
I-I can't do that.
Right?
Then...
If you beat them, you'll reach the empty ship.
Damn it! I can't stand there.
All right!
Oh, no! I'm in the bottom!
I'll make you pay for this!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Break!
Why did you use such a dirty trick?
But now's my chance!
Take this!
Damn it!
All right! Let's go!
What?
Let's go!
Alright! I got the empty ship!
What?
Oh, no! I hit the bullet!
What's wrong with you?
Are cockroaches as giant as you?
Yes.
It's a robot, but it has a proper input for fixing it.
Don't fly!
What's that?
Ryotsu, use this!
If it's a normal cockroach, I can beat it with this.
No, no.
It's a robot.
Ryotsu, I got it!
Team B wins!
I never thought we'd lose in the first battle.
I dreamt of buying a victory figure.
The second stage is a maze made of giant sushi.
Of course, sushi is a real thing that uses biotechnology.
Four groups who successfully passed the maze and quickly touched the center tower flag
enter the final field.
You guys know who made you stay here, don't you?
That has nothing to do with it.
Right. It's not a team battle from now on.
Team B!
You guys are so clueless.
One of them is a rice ball, but it's a real thing.
You use biotechnology to make something like this.
If you can overcome sushi, you'll be disqualified.
Get ready!
Go!
It's pretty complicated.
Damn, I don't get it at all.
Ryotsu, you've gone the wrong way again.
Chief! I can see the goal over there!
Go straight here?
Alright.
It's a hell with a castle on fire!
It's okay.
You're just eating it.
No, it's a great move.
I'm going with it.
Ryotsu!
You just have to climb over it!
To think that they think that they can eat sushi.
It's a real castle.
They're going to eat the whole thing.
They're already that close.
There are four levels.
Don't give up. You're too young.
Hurry up, you bastard!
I'm going to be the top!
Oh, my dear old man!
I won't let you!
Damn it!
I caught you!
Hey, let go!
I'm the top!
And the last one!
Damn it!
Get on, old man!
You go first, Mr. Kenshin!
The Hon-Dara sword is in first and second place!
Yay!
We're in third place!
We're in fourth place!
I can't do this. I can't make it.
I won't let anyone get the last chance!
Get out of my way!
Yay!
I'm in fourth place!
Be careful!
How can you be so cruel about this, when you have no one to listen to?
The final match starts now!
The four members will compete in a giant sports tournament!
The first match of the table tennis competition,
is going to be between the O-Hara pair and
the O-Seisho pair!
Please start the match!
Here I go!
Ready, steady, go!
All right!
I got it all!
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Hehe! The enemy's combination is too bad!
Komachi! I'll have to play in this match!
Yeah!
Alright! You've got a match point now!
Ryosu, it's the end of the match.
I can't play anymore.
But even if I lost, the bank robbery would...
I'm not kidding!
It's not a sudden attack! I know how to use it, so I'll show you!
Y-You're still giving up?
I'll definitely counterattack!
Strip!
Leave it to me!
I used a backspin!
When did you learn that technique?
Alright, counterattack!
Strip!
Alright, now it's sudden attack!
The one who gets one first wins!
What about the serve?
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors!
If this is the serve, I'll win for sure!
Naoko, be careful with the spin serve!
Okay.
You're not going to hit it that easily.
Kimutaku!
What?
Where?
Now!
Game set!
Ryotsu-Ohara pair wins!
How dirty!
The spin serve is a common thing in ping pong.
He's really dirty, even though he's an ally.
The final is a bowling match.
Now, please start with Team A.
Oh, there's a hole.
Okay.
Let's go!
William, let go of me.
.
He gets them easily on the strike.
I understand the approach.
I can do it!
I don't see any movement to the front, it's hard.
.
I'm not going to let you beat me!
Ryotsu! It's 9 points difference!
If you have more than a spare, you can win!
Hmph! I've never taken a spare before, but I can't!
Shut up! I'll finish you off with a strike!
Take this!
I'll finish you off with a strike!
It's a split! Even a professional can't take this!
I'm the winner!
I can give up 100 million yen by going all the way here, but...
If I end up like this...
Then you can't take a spare.
Is that it?
It's a match from here!
Here I go!
What the?!
What?!
A little more to the right!
I did it!
Looks like the last strategy was a waste.
I'll take the victory!
100 million yen!
I-I fell!
I did it!
I did it well, Ryotsu!
What a great year!
I lost.
I'm glad, Ryo-chan!
You won 100 million yen!
It was a wonderful match.
Thanks to you, my body is very stiff.
Okay, it's finished!
Eh?
B-Boss!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'll take this!
No, Boss!
No!
Give it back!
Let go!
I won't!
I'll take it!
What?
Wait!
I can't believe I've lost 100 million yen!
What's wrong with my body?
100 million yen!
I made it!
햇気!
country
Yes!
I walked through the crowd in black
Everyone was a child once, but they all forgot
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt on top of her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
I can see everyone, everyone
Let's go!
There's a turtle over there
There's surely a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Hey, hey, Ryotsu!
It's a festival, so don't be so excited!
Huh?
I caught a turtle once
You didn't wash your feet, did you?
What about the promise you made to me?
Next time on Matsuri Daiko
Thank you!
There's a turtle over there
There's surely a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!