"The End of the Rain"
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
After the rain, like someone calling
I walked while looking back
"Mom, please help me!"
I felt at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk only the black part of the Ake-dogai Tile
I tried to walk only the black part of the Ake-dogai Tile
No matter who, even if I was a child at one time
Everyone has forgotten
The politician with a cashier face
And the blue aunt over my eyes
Check that corner
And check that corner
Make everyone, everyone see you
♪ You'll fly together ♪
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ You will find the wall ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our city ♪
Thank you!
Nakagawa-kun was saved.
I didn't expect to see you in front of the head office.
It was a coincidence, chief.
Did you have a meeting with the head office?
Yes, the entire meeting of the taxi robbery that has been going on in the city recently.
There is a lot of damage in our ship.
Nakagawa, your cell phone is forbidden while driving.
Of course I know.
Chief, my car's phone is hands free.
Hands free?
Yes, this is Nakagawa.
It's me.
What is it, senpai?
Matt, wait a moment.
I heard a voice from the speaker.
I'm using Castelio's speaker.
The microphone is here at the steering wheel.
Sorry, sorry. I met a friend.
Are you on patrol?
Patrol? I'm not joking.
I'm not patrolling on a nice day like this.
I'm doing something.
What?
What's that weird voice?
Is someone by your side?
No, I was listening to the radio while driving.
I'll turn down the volume.
What? Radio?
By the way, Nakagawa, where do you think you are now?
Well...
The hint is this sound.
I can hear the sound of the waves and the engine.
Are you on a motorboat?
Oh, he's talking nicely, Nakagawa.
The hint is this.
It's where men who dream of a nuclear war are gathered.
Is it a field of battle?
No way.
Idiot.
There's no sound of the waves at the field of battle.
It's a court.
What?
I was thinking of taking back the loss of the field of battle on Sunday.
Sen...
Senpai.
You shouldn't talk too long.
Okay.
Go, go, Number 3.
Hey, idiot.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
Idiot.
Give me back my money.
You're quite a stubborn man.
What do you want?
Sen...
Senpai.
Your voice is too loud.
I was listening to you on the radio.
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
But I'm still hungry, Number 3.
Damn it.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Senpai?
What's the matter?
No, no, nothing.
Nakagawa, do you know where you are?
Isn't that the court?
I'm asking you where you are in the court.
You seemed to be in your room.
Idiot.
There's no phone in the bathroom!
Why do you ask so suddenly?
You got fired all of a sudden.
What happened?
But I remember the voice now.
It's me, Ohara.
B-boss?
Why are you there?
Wasn't there a meeting in the main office?
I'm going back to the headquarters.
Ryotsu, are you taking a rest today?
No, I'll go.
I'll go.
Did you hear everything I said so far?
I heard it well, Ryotsu.
Go back to the headquarters immediately.
If you arrive later than us,
I'll be in trouble.
No way!
Is there such a thing?
Nakagawa, where are you running now?
I'm near Aosu Station.
I'm on a bus right now, but I'm about to leave.
What? Aosu?
I'll cut it.
If it's a close distance, I can't lose to Ferrari.
But I don't have enough energy to go to the course.
What?
Thank you.
I'll take a taxi here.
Gassu, go to the Kameyari Park in front of the station.
Go to the Kameyari Park in front of the station.
I'm sorry.
I don't know much about this area.
I'll take another taxi if you're in a hurry.
I'll drive in the addressed area.
I'll drive in the same area.
Watch out!
Please protect the speed limit.
Shut up. I'm a police officer.
This bus will be operated as an emergency vehicle from now on.
Damn it.
Damn it! You're causing a traffic jam at a time like this!
This is a different road!
That road is U-turn forbidden, right?
That is V-turn, so it's fine.
Really?
Hello!
Can you please drive around the garden?
The people of the north are very friendly!
They will watch you a lot!
Hey! The train is late!
I don't think so...
Shut up! We're going down the stairs!
Hold on tight!
Stairs?
I can't breathe!
There's a corridor!
It's too narrow to pass!
There's no such thing as impossible in my dictionary!
Look to the side!
The wall is broken! The wall!
The people of the north are very friendly, so it's fine!
Even if the festival's shrine breaks the wall,
there's no one like this!
This is not a shrine!
This is ramparts!
This is a joy-seeker!
HARUTO!
Hey, what are you doing by the train?
He'll wear a mask!
That's a good idea!
I'm afraid the train won't let us pass-
I will!
I'm going to leave~!
Take the back road!
Hey, chief, what's going on?
Senpai, you're in time.
My neck is...
No, no, no.
I'm the type that always gives my best for work.
You ran from the court, but you still talk big.
I'm sorry!
Chief!
The president called.
What? From the president?
What?
Ryo-tsumo?
Oh, I see.
I'll go right away.
Chief, what's going on?
We have information that one of the taxi robbers is hiding in Katsushika.
Really?
We're going to set up a special investigation department.
You three come with me to the office.
Yes, sir!
Is this taxi real?
Yes.
We hired three taxi companies that usually cooperate with the police.
We want you to arrest the taxi robber using this car.
But why are you making this idiot do such an important task?
He's not an idiot, is he, chief?
In fact, he's a driver and a double-duty owner.
So we chose the right person to be the computer's owner.
It was Nakagawa, Reigo, and Ryo-tsumo.
I see.
So the computer has more eyes to see people.
Don't get carried away.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh.
I changed my clothes.
You two look great.
Thank you very much.
When the time comes,
this bulletproof glass will protect the driver.
Wow!
You two, I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Chief, where's my taxi going?
Oh, this way.
Your taxi is here.
Why is my taxi only with old-fashioned tubes?
It can't be helped.
Because I could only pay for this.
Boss, where is the button from the bullet glass?
It's not in your garden.
What?
What if it's targeted with a gun?
I don't think you'd die even if you were shot.
Well, then you'd better avoid it.
That's terrible.
It's a big discrimination against the middle class.
I'll be going.
What's wrong with Ryotsu?
He's about to come.
Get out of the way!
I'm going!
I hit it.
That's a putter.
Idiot!
Where are you looking?
Even if I say that, he'll jump out of the way.
What?
You're old.
You should know the trick.
There's no sudden stop.
Avoid it.
You're stupid.
S-sorry.
You're just saying?
Are you really all right?
Damn it.
The computer just picked it.
He'll get angry.
Damn.
I'll be in charge of the police station.
Please excuse me.
I'll take care of the police station.
Nakagawa, can you hear me?
Yes.
There's a possibility that the man with the ID is inside.
Roger that.
He might be moving in a taxi.
If the culprit gets on the taxi,
he'll be asked to go to the place where he was told to go.
Roger that.
Wait for him to contact his friends,
and make him a villain.
Okay?
Okay.
Please take me to Kameari Station.
You're mistaken for a real man.
Please. I'm in a hurry.
You can go back to the station in 10 minutes.
It'll take some time anyway.
Okay.
Thank goodness.
I'm saved.
I'll fly you.
We're here.
We are here in 3 minutes.
You saved me.
How much is this?
I forgot the meter.
I'll take it.
No problem.
Let's go.
What's this?
We're
It's good.
Go to Haneda.
I'll go to Haneda.
It's too far.
I'll ask for it. The flight time is...
I'll ask for it for 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
Alright, I got it!
You can get in fast if you start at the speed bump!
Hold on tight!
What's wrong?
A man with a mission has appeared.
What?
He's going somewhere.
Alright, Ryotsu's taxi is at the exit.
Huh?
R-Ryotsu's car is missing!
What?!
What happened to Ryotsu?
He got on a passenger and went somewhere.
What are you saying, you idiot?!
Oh no!
He got on another taxi!
The mission is a failure!
Ryotsu, answer me!
Ryotsu!
Damn it, the radio is dead.
Oh crap...
I'm so sorry, Ryotsu.
I'm sorry, Ryotsu.
How did you get here?
Is that you?
No, I'm the one who got hit by a car in the middle of the street.
Yo!
You are!
You'd better carry your luggage in your trunk.
Excuse me.
Should we go from Shibamata?
I'm from the Tora-san Museum, and I'm from Yagiri.
Are you two new to Tokyo?
Yes, I was wondering where to look.
If you look from the platform, it's close.
Ah, excuse me.
Senpai, where are you? The manager is in a hurry.
What? Nakagawa?
Sorry, but there's a customer.
I'll leave it to you guys.
What? No way!
Um, is Harajuku close?
Yes, it's close.
Then let's go from there.
I don't use my cell phone while driving. I'll cut it.
Oh.
Well, shall we go?
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Where did he run to?
He's a tenant, isn't he? That taxi.
In the first place, it's wrong to leave such an important task to Ryotsu.
Ah, thank you.
Move, move!
It's on the road of the Ryotsu taxi!
Can I force a traffic jam?
It's okay, it's okay.
The road is all mine.
Hey, the previous bus!
It's in the way, you bastards!
What kind of driver is the car passing by the bus?
Hmm?
Oh!
Ryotsu!
Hey, chief!
Oh, no!
I, I can't believe it.
Thank you very much.
Be careful of the strange men who hit you.
Yes, sir.
See you later.
It's been two hours, and you've earned 20,000 yen.
This is a good business.
All right, I've decided.
Still flowing spurts.
Hold on.
I've got a car you're interested in.
What do you need?
No problem.
I've got a taxi driver's license.
Do you have a taxi driver's license?
Stop pretending.
Sorry.
You've got a low-paying license, but
Ryo knows the back of the town!
He's probably an administrator.
You're right.
See you!
I'll pay you back after I finish the remodeling.
Do they happen to be lurking here?
It's the taxi thief after all.
It's the criminal.
He jumped into the cage from the bird.
Hey, please take me to Narita Airport.
Hey, customer.
Actually, the bad taxi traffic is popular these days.
I'm sorry, but can I ask you for a money for poop?
What?
Stop it.
I understand.
I can't help it.
How much is it?
I'll give you 20,000 yen.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'll give you 20,000 yen.
The one with the gun is the right one.
What's wrong?
That taxi has a bulletproof light.
Something might have happened.
Stop the car.
Yeah.
Huh? It's a stop sign.
Stop the car.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yeah.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please get off?
I'll take care of it.
I won't let you get away!
Hey, hurry up and catch him!
Yes sir!
Now, be quiet!
Now, come out!
You're in the way!
Senpai, that was a good job.
No matter what you say, I'll do it when I have to, Ryo-chan.
I'm glad I got to do the last five rounds.
Chief, thank you for your help for a long time.
What? The order?
Huh?
Hey, what do you mean?
I found out that the taxi driver was my shift worker.
See you later.
Hey, Ryo-chan!
Hey, don't wait! That taxi is a temporary one!
You idiot!
Ohara-kun, this is bad!
W-what's going on?
W-watch this!
What?
Huh?
We can't deliver the damage?
All the taxi drivers of Ryo-chan have been destroyed.
Besides, a number of reports of traffic violations have been sent in.
Damn Ryo-chan!
Nakagawa-kun, Reiko-kun, get Ryo-chan immediately.
Yes sir!
You can't be a local official in the foreign month!
I'll pay you all with this taxi!
I'll make you a taxi!
Oh no!
Stop the taxi in front!
I'm not kidding!
I'll kill you!
Damn it!
They're so stubborn!
Well?
I'm sure you paid for the remodeling.
Too bad!
What?
Don't let him get away!
Senpai!
Nakagawa!
Ryoji!
Stop the car!
Give up already!
You're a great driver!
You're good at driving!
No, not that.
Alright!
Please stop!
That won't do anything!
Kintaro!
Hahaha!
It's impossible for you guys to catch me, Akechi!
Reminds me of the 007 VONDO car!
Damn it!
Oh? But I'm sure it's...
Looks like you gave up.
There's no way!
Senpai, what happened?
Hehehe...
The car just went "dogaan" and I was thinking I should go back to normal work.
We've already paid for the ticket.
What?
You've worked hard all this time, Ryo-tsu.
Uh, Chief?
The taxi has received the request form of those who broke the fence, so pay it properly.
Huh?!
And that taxi is not a rental.
Pay it back to the taxi company.
Uh... Nooooooo...
Taxi...
♪ Mezanashi, tokei, kettobashi ♪
♪ Koyubi ga ai tatata ♪
♪ Toriazu mayuge wo kaita ra ♪
♪ Eki made dash, dash, dash ♪
♪ Mainensha, oyachi no senaka de hitomeru ♪
Oh...
I'm going to the gym and eat a lot of food.
I'm going to eat a lot of food.
To be continued
Do you like Kameari King?
I'm so happy to have you as my master
Be a great competitor and win lots of money
You will be a star at Nakayama K馬場
Next time "Run Kameari King"
See you
"The King of Kameari King"
♪ Kameari King ♪
Thank you!