Episode 1: The
Is it Nagasaki?
That's right.
You have something to do in the Nagasaki prefecture.
What?
To me?
Did you do something, Ryo?
Hmm?
When you say Nagasaki, it's Nagasaki Champon's Nagasaki, right?
That's right.
It was raining in Nagasaki today, Nagasaki.
Hmm, I don't remember.
You caught a thug who was aiming for only high-class cars last week, right?
Oh, by the way, is that guy related to Nagasaki?
He was arrested in Nagasaki.
It seems that he was dismantled and sold in Southeast Asia.
So I wanted your testimony of being arrested.
What?
It was like that.
I thought my senior was arrested.
Hey, why don't I have to be arrested?
Because Ryo-chan's rampant behavior is national.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, you can just make that kind of story a joke.
What's that?
It's obvious.
It's the flight fee and the hotel fee.
I don't want to be fooled anymore.
Idiot.
That's my own money.
Hey, that's not.
I'd like to say that, but I sent it from the other book.
Hmm.
It's a place to stay and a place to stay in Nagasaki, Tokyo.
What?
Aren't you going by plane?
The budget is small for the county and the city.
Just send it and I'll be grateful.
Hey, by the way, Nagasaki was a thousand years ahead, wasn't it?
Next to Iwate or something?
Hey, dad, one more drink.
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
What's wrong?
My body?
Money?
I don't have money.
What?
There is money here.
There is.
But this can't be used.
Do you understand, dad?
I don't understand.
Well, the money is okay.
Oh, Senpai, were you here?
Oh, my wallet is here.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry.
I'm going next.
What?
Please take care of this payment.
Thank you.
It's terrible, Senpai.
I haven't even had a sip, and you're paying me only money.
Hey, sorry, sorry.
I drank too much while waiting for you.
Here, drink.
Of course, I'll drink.
It's not my money.
Senpai, there's no money left.
I don't feel like drinking.
Me, too.
I drank it all.
Senpai, it's terrible.
It's terrible.
You were wrong, don't cry.
Wait.
If you search, I'll give you two 100-yen pot pieces.
I drank it all.
Oh, look at the problem.
Look, I have money.
Senpai.
Okay, I'll blame you now.
By the way, this money...
Senpai, let's go shopping.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it'll work out somehow.
Please do something about it.
Huh?
You used up all your travel expenses?
I'm so sorry.
Please, Nakagawa!
Give me back 50,000 yen!
I'll pay you back next month!
But...
No, Kassha.
Huh?
You used it yourself,
so you should be paying for it.
Reiko, don't say such nonsense!
How about you use it yourself
as much as you're responsible for it?
You bastard.
If I let you say it...
What?
Huh?
Well...
What are you doing here?
Chief!
I was discussing the economy of Japan.
Huh?
Chief.
I'd like to get a three-day leave.
Why?
I rarely get the chance to do so,
so I thought I'd go to Nagasaki
and spread my knowledge.
Oh, I see.
I don't mind that.
Well, then.
I'll pay you back soon.
What's that?
You must be very well prepared.
Well, whatever.
I'll just get a good salary for today.
Hehehe.
Senpai, are you going by bicycle?
I don't have money.
There's no other way.
Are you serious?
It's my man's will.
I have to do it.
All right.
See you.
Once you decide, you can't go back.
Oh, come on.
Huh?
It's already 12:00.
We've already arrived near Odawara.
Yotsuya!
I thought you rode a long distance
to Shinjuku,
but are you still in Tokyo 23-9?
Shit!
Tokyo Hirosugi!
I've finally arrived at Suginami.
Shibuya, I'm back.
This is going to take longer than I thought.
I have to make up a plan.
All right! Let's go with this one!
I did it!
Yahoo!
See? Even if you don't have money, you can do anything with your head!
What?
How much is the cost of a bicycle?
It's not just a thrill to ride a bicycle on the highway!
Oh no!
High-speed electric massage!
What are you doing?
I'm teaching the children what they shouldn't do.
Hmm.
By the way, do you know where Nagasaki is?
I don't know, but why don't you go to the sea for now?
I won't get lost if I go along the sea.
Oh, that's right. Thank you.
Oh, the sea. It's Enoshima.
Oh, I can't walk anymore. I'm going to fall.
I'm going to fall.
Yes, this is Honda.
Oh, Senpai. How can I help you?
I'm looking for a car.
Hello? What's wrong, Senpai?
Please hurry. It's Enoshima.
Enoshima? Did something happen?
It's no good.
Senpai, be strong!
I'm begging you. Please hurry.
Senpai! Senpai!
Hey, let's go now!
Senpai!
Oh, Honda.
After a short sleep, I'm tired.
I'm thirsty. I thought I could help you, so I brought you a juice.
That's all?
Are you going to Nagasaki?
Yes.
You can send me to Nagasaki ticket office.
It's such an honorable work.
You can just go to Nagasaki.
It doesn't matter how far it is.
Well, don't hesitate.
Let's go!
Oh? He can't go.
Oh...
Oh?
You didn't throw missed an empty can, did you?
You are a policeman, right?
No. I'm sorry. I was going to put it in properly.
It's not like a man to make excuses.
It's the worst thing to do if you don't protect your manners.
I told you I was going to put it in properly.
What's with that face?
If you're wearing a police uniform, you're probably scared.
Don't underestimate this truck lady, Haruyo.
If you have any complaints, wash your face and come back.
Don't yell at me. I'm not a trashy crow.
You're the one who looks like a gorilla who fell into the mud.
What? A gorilla wearing a police uniform?
That's so weird. Your belly is boiling tea.
You don't like it? Then boil it.
I'll boil it.
Whether it's tea or coffee, bring me a kettle.
It's a fight.
Hey, should we get drunk?
In return, treat me to tea.
Pick it up.
Pick up the cigarette you just threw away.
I can't hear you.
Just shut your mouth.
Don't mess with me.
You're so broad-minded.
Shut up!
Don't talk back to me.
Let go of my hand.
You're a strong lady.
I'm not. I'm scared.
I said let go of my hand!
What?
This guy!
Let go of me.
Don't fight with him!
You're messing with me.
Don't be a coward. The woman is your opponent.
You don't have to do anything unnecessary.
I see.
It's a pretty good game.
Are there no trash cans to throw them out?
Leave it to me. That's the job of the police.
It's a police job.
I see. I'll leave it to you.
Honda, the cars in the line are in the way of the passage.
Bring them to the roadside.
Yes!
Hey, Mr. Gorilla!
The empty can is in the trash can.
Who is Mr. Gorilla?
It was overwhelmed.
What a woman truck.
It's cold.
We came all the way to Hakone, but there is no hot spring.
Then, we should go to drink yesterday.
Don't say that.
The cold is so strong.
However, there are mountains everywhere.
I'm from Hakone.
Don't you get lost on the road?
We're going west.
I see Mt. Fuji on the right.
I have to see the map.
Shut up!
It's the sea.
It's a mess.
What?
What shall we do, senpai?
We can't do anything.
The next step is gasoline.
Let's ask the bus to give us the gasoline.
The gas in the bus is not gasoline.
It was a joke.
After all, I'm hungry.
Speaking of seaweed, it's eel.
Is it eel?
It's painful.
Eel! Eel! Eel!
I can't change my stomach.
What's wrong with your stomach?
My stomach?
Yes, your stomach!
My stomach!
Senpai!
I love my stomach too much!
My navel is moving to my back!
Senpai!
Ouch!
This is no good!
Honda!
Get me some water!
Senpai, get me some water!
Yes!
Senpai, I brought you some water!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Senpai, are you okay?
My stomach is moving to my back.
Let's go eat eel.
Huh?
Yes.
What?
Wow!
It looks so delicious!
Let's eat!
Yum!
Here you go.
But Senpai, you're a bad person.
You had money, didn't you?
Well, that's it for today.
Now, drink!
Eat!
Oh!
I ate!
He drank.
Next, we'll take a bath.
We'll have a hot spring.
We'll have a hot spring bath!
I'm the best!
Senpai?
Eat!
I drank.
I'm the best!
Now, you, greedy bastard!
The next step in a fine yoga bath is peeing.
Don't you hate
a man who can't hold it?
That's awful.
Hey!
What happened to you?
What?
I said I'm the worst!
I said I'm not good enough.
You can even reflect on yourself, you gorilla man.
You.
Look at this.
And this one.
Look. You're the one who made a mistake.
I did it.
Sometimes, you make such a mistake.
You're so short-tempered.
That's called being hasty.
When you take a bath, make sure you're sure if you're in the right position or not.
Make sure you're sure.
Ouch!
Oh no!
Please be careful.
It can't be helped. I'm a human being.
See you later.
Be careful.
He was a pretty nice guy.
Let's go.
What?
Don't be so nervous.
Nagasaki is still a long way to go.
Oh, by the way, where's my bike?
Senpai, could it be at the hotel?
Don't worry.
Just pay me back before it runs out.
What?
Did you buy my bike for the money I put in the nightclub?
That's terrible.
The bike...
The nightclub...
It can't be helped.
You were having fun, weren't you?
But my bike...
How can I make it work?
Are you going to Nagasaki?
Well, I guess...
Senpai, can you stop for a second?
Damn it.
I can't go hitchhiking in my uniform.
The sun went down just by walking on the boat.
I'm getting hungry.
Senpai, what are you going to do today?
What are you going to do?
Do you still have money?
Hey, Senpai, what are you doing?
Oh, shut up.
Leave it to me.
Leave it to me?
It's over there.
Let's go over there.
What?
Here it is.
I just remembered.
This is my relative's house.
Relative?
Senpai's?
Yes.
My father's cousin's third son-in-law.
His wife's cousin's cousin's house.
Oh.
Good evening, sir.
Is there anyone here?
Yes.
Who is it?
It's been a while, sir.
You?
You look fine.
How many years has it been?
This house hasn't changed at all.
Hey, Honda, come in.
Good evening.
This is my friend, Honda.
He said he wanted to see you, so he followed me.
Oh, right.
Is there an aunt?
She's in the back.
That's good.
What's the story about her?
"Aunt, I'm here to play in Tokyo."
Good evening.
My house is the same as ever.
It's the same as ever.
Good.
She's from Tokyo.
Your youngest brother.
He must be in Tokyo.
Then, my Hiroshi.
Yes, Hiroshi.
That's Hiroshi.
Who is Hiroshi?
Good.
He remembered me.
Oh, I see.
Hiroshi.
He's changed a lot.
I didn't know.
That's right.
That's what everyone says.
He's changed.
Is my cousin, Heisuke, doing well?
I'm fine.
Heisuke died.
Yeah.
He died in good health.
Did you get hungry?
I'm so hungry that I'm falling down.
Oh, my.
Let's have dinner.
You.
No, for Hiroshi.
I know.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry.
I think I made a request.
That's not true.
Well, the old lady is considerate and kind.
The old man is happy.
Well, that's a little...
He's a really funny person.
Hiroshi.
There are still many topics.
Let's drink at night tonight.
Yes.
Let's drink at night.
Today is the day of the festival of the old man.
You're welcome.
Then, I'll go to the festival.
I'll go.
That's all.
I see.
I'm really sorry.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry.
Well.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
That's all.
That's good.
I told you, I'm good at it.
Is there anything else?
Really? But...
It's okay. It's okay.
You can use the roof or the water, or anything.
Here's your tea.
Thank you very much.
So, are you going to Kyushu?
Yes. I have some business.
It's a mess here and there, but I'll be fine if you take care of it.
I'll come again, so I'll do it again then.
They're sleeping so well.
They're good people, but they're fooling me.
Well then, be careful.
Here's your lunch.
Oh, thank you.
It's still a long way to Kyushu.
Well, I've been taking care of you.
See you.
Come again when you get home, Hiroshi.
Okay.
See you.
Senpai, please go ahead!
Um...
What's wrong? Did you forget something?
No. Actually, Hiroshi is...
It was fun to say that we had a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Well then...
If you think about it, Hiroshi is still in junior high school.
That's right.
I see.
Thank you for your help.
Hmm...
Senpai!
Ha-ha-ha.
I guess you're having a good morning, Senpai!
What?
Now, let's get ready and go for a walk to Nagasaki!
Let's go!
Huh?
Senpai, I can't walk anymore.
Don't say such a bad word.
What's wrong with your energy?
Well, my legs got tired...
I can't walk a single step.
If you think you can walk, you can walk anywhere.
You're going to Nagasaki, right?
Come on!
But I'm not even in Nagoya yet.
Nagasaki is impossible.
Come on!
No!
I told you I'd go with you.
What are you doing there?
You're so lucky that you shared your bike with me.
But you saved me.
I'm lucky that I'm on my way to Nagasaki.
I'm so lucky.
You're so lucky that you're on your way to Nagasaki.
You can do it if you do.
How long do you think it takes?
I'll do it if you say so.
You can't, can you?
I can.
I'll do it even if I have to do it now.
No no no.
Zenbu- наверное なにするんですか?
Don't do it.
Shut up.
Let go of me.
N-n-ne-
Don't stop me, fool.
What is this?
What's this?
What? A cat?
Meow
Hey! Don't lick me like that!
Hahaha, it seems you like Senpai
What's your name?
Tamasaburo
Hey, stop it!
If you're a human, you're a scum, you know
Meow
But Senpai is just like you
I'm not kidding! I don't look like this!
I'm a woman who's more in love with men than women
You're a woman, Tamasaburo
What?
Hey, stop it!
He's not getting away at all
He won't be able to get off
I can't help it. I'll ride you to Nagasaki
I can't help it. I'll put you on
Hey! Don't lick my nose!
Hachoo!
Crap!
Hey, Goran, don't sleep on your knees!
Don't sleep in the car. It's heavy.
Hey, wake up, Tamasaburo!
Another run and you're in Nagasaki.
What's wrong? You've been quiet for a while.
Kanda?
Yeah. Four years ago.
Get out!
You're not a parent or a child.
You're just an outsider.
Yeah, I'm going out.
I can't stay with a stubborn old man like you.
You're so stubborn that even men can't run away from you.
You can't run away.
I ran away because you're a man and can't run away.
Then don't take advantage of my advice.
I don't like what you don't like!
Well, well, father and Haruyo, please calm down a little more.
You're so stubborn! I've already decided!
Once you've decided, the God of Heaven will not change your mind.
I'm a father, too!
Oh, Haruyo!
Don't you worry!
Oh!
Hmm...
"I'll be a father, too."
Did you choose your father's favorite husband as your husband?
It's obvious.
You're so naive.
I have to do everything my father wants me to do.
Why did you suddenly decide to go back to the village?
I was told that I had fallen.
And I had a job to come to.
So I thought I'd try to get a job.
For four years.
I worked hard.
And finally I bought this truck.
"I'll be a father, too."
Oh, you had a hard time.
Well, yeah.
Now, it's time for the Gravaen.
Oh!
"I'll be a father, too."
Sorry, Tamasaburo.
I'll be back soon.
So please wait quietly in this situation.
Then, how are you feeling?
I don't think I'm doing that well.
I can't get up very well.
What if I just fall asleep?
I'm worried about my mother.
Ah!
Is today a festival?
Yeah.
A festival of reflection.
"Fantasy festival"
"The festival of reflection"
The boss is also in the fishing team, but he used to be the captain.
He drank too much alcohol.
He can't go to the festival, so he's not doing well.
If you show your face, you might get better.
I know.
Then don't be upset here.
If you know, it's unnecessary care.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
To your father's place.
Wait a minute.
I haven't decided yet.
You idiot.
That's why you came back to Nagasaki.
Or is it better to be a priest?
I'm your father.
I'm like your father.
If you don't do as you want, you won't feel better.
If you don't like it, I'll take you with me even if it is tied up.
Ryo.
My truck.
It's a truck thief.
Stop.
You can't take it.
-Sanakaburo! -Sanakaburo!
Sanakaburo!
Senpai!
I won't let you do that!
Excuse me.
I'm a cop, but I'm tracking down the truck.
Lend me that motorcycle.
Yes.
I won't let you get away!
Now, get on it!
Huh?
Y-Yes!
Let's go!
Oh, no!
Sir! Are you all right?!
Help!
Tamasaburo!
Go!
I wonder if this is going to be okay!
Hey, you cop! Stop the car!
Stop the car!
Yeah!
Hey!
Tamasaburo!
You bastard!
- -Darn you, stupid cat!
ARGHHH!
U-Ugh!
Tamasaburo!
Where? Where are you?
Haruyo!
I'm counting on you!
Senpai!
Tamasaburo!
Sorry, I must have scared you!
I'm glad you're safe!
Tori!
Senpai!
Tamasaburo!
That was a great blow.
I'm so happy.
Ryo?
Hmm?
Thank you.
Huh?
So that's all right...
"Dad, I'm going to the grocery store."
"Oh."
"Huh?"
"Nyaa."
"Oh, Tamasaburo."
"Sorry."
"Oh."
"Hello."
"Um, what is it?"
"Oh, nothing."
"Hey, what are you doing? Hurry up!"
"Ah."
"H-Haruyo!"
"Dad, Dad!"
"Haruyo, Haruyo has come back!"
"What?"
"He's at the entrance now."
"Are you waiting for him?"
"What?"
"He's moved. Let him go home."
"No way."
"Dad."
"W-What are you doing? I'm not feeling well. Please go home."
"I didn't come back because I wanted to. I just happened to be here."
"I'll go home."
"Wait!"
"Who are you?"
"Hehehe."
"Well, you've heard me out."
"Ryo-san."
"That's a big deal. You have nothing to do with it."
"But you know, this is the end of our relationship. I'm engaged to your daughter."
"W-What?"
"Ryo-san."
"Say it again!"
"Yeah."
"So we're engaged to each other. Love, love. Yeah!"
"Haruyo, is that true?"
"It's true. Right, Haruyo?"
"Don't touch my daughter so easily!"
"Oh, you're not a red-haired stranger?"
"Huh?"
"If you're moved, you're not a parent or a child, right?"
"Kuh."
"If you're against it, you should be moved first."
"You're making a big deal out of it."
"Umm, let's just make a few excuses."
"Well, then. We'll live happily together."
"It's a nuisance to have such a stubborn father."
"No!"
"I won't forgive you!"
"What do you mean by that?"
"We can get married on our own will."
"No, no, no, no!"
"Haruyo is my daughter!"
"It's too late now."
"Then, shall we go?"
"Wait!"
"I can't let my daughter be a coward like you!"
"Then, who do you want?"
"If your daughter is a man who can handle your glasses,
you don't mind if she doesn't?"
"I just want my daughter to be happy."
"You're moved?"
"Umm..."
"If you really want your daughter to be happy,
you should let her do what she wants."
"You're just obsessed with your pride and will."
"You don't understand how my parents feel!"
"You stubborn old man!"
"You can't say anything!"
"You're a man with a long eyebrow!"
"You're a fossil from the late ages!"
"You're a human in the hands of a man!"
"You're a man in the hands of a man!"
"You're a pumpkin!"
"Dad..."
"Dad!"
"D-Dad!"
Father...
That's good.
Eh?
Wait, Ryo-san!
Thank you.
Thank you, Ryo-san!
Hey, stop it!
The play is over!
Play?
That's what I'm saying, so don't worry.
I knew it.
Haruyo is a noodle eater.
She's a noodle eater.
But...
If you're a person like Ryo-san,
would it be okay to go to a wedding?
Huh?
Don't joke around!
I'm glad, father.
You got on the ship you've been wanting to get on.
Yeah.
It's all thanks to Haruyo.
I'm going to stop going back to Tokyo.
Huh?
I'm going to get a ship ticket and live here.
I-I see.
Hey, Ryo-san!
I want to ski on your dad, too!
I just got on the ship!
We'll have lots of fun today!
Hi!
Dad!
There's a sukiyaki that your dad likes on the ship.
Is that so?
You're a good-for-nothing.
Eh?
...
If you're a person like Yose, can I go to see you?
Ah, um, what...
Huh?
Ah, ah, ah, what?
Why is Dolphin Dekka here?
Ah, it's a dolphin.
What's wrong?
Ah, no, nothing. Let's pretend I didn't see it.
Ryo, what did you say just now?
Ah, um, um...
What?
Ah, ah, ah, amazing.
Why is Dolphin Dekka here?
What's wrong?
No, nothing. Let's pretend I didn't see it.
Ah, um...
What?
Huh?
Why is Dolphin Dekka here?
What's wrong?
No, let's pretend I didn't see it.
Do you have something to talk about?
No, um, I'm about to...
Um...
Tamasaburou!
Meow.
Ah!
Meow!
Ken!
H-Haruyo!
What?
When did you get back?
Today.
I...
I went to Haruyo's house right after I got back from the port.
But Haruyo was no longer there.
Ken...
Are you going on a foreign ship? When are you coming back?
I can't tell you.
Haruyo!
You idiot! Why didn't you say you'd wait for me?
I was an idiot. I've been regretting it ever since.
Ken...
Um...
If you're fine, would you stay by my side? Forever?
Are you sure? Haruyo.
Yeah...
Oh, yeah, there's someone I want to introduce.
Ryo...
What?
I didn't say I wanted you to know...
Now, you're gonna tell me what?
But you have to stay by my side.
Oh.
What?
You didn't want to come, either?
So, I'm here...
Huh?
What are you doing?
Oh, a rat.
Hey, Tamasaburo! Come back here!
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
The annual fireworks show is about to begin.
Please look forward to it.
Senpai, where did you go?
Mr. Honda.
Oh, Haruyo. Do you know Senpai?
We were looking for him, too.
Oh, right. I'll introduce him.
Mr. Ken Yasukura.
Hello.
We're getting married.
What?
Oh, you know that he's gone, don't you?
Hey, Tamasaburo!
I did it.
Here we go.
What's this?
Hey, Tamasaburo!
If you keep waiting, I'll...
All right, let's get started.
Let's fight!
All right!
Oh, wow!
I'm sure Senpai's watching this fireworks show somewhere.
Mr. Nagasaki, the kid is dangerous.
Let's freaked out.
Yoroshiku!
You're sc緒 befoe!
You're now on the attack team of the police.
And now I'm a member of the police?
I won, I won.
It's my fault.
Do it!
I'll get you.
He must be playing with the fog tail.
When he comes back, I'll take a lot of it.
Ah!
Yes, this is Kameyari Park Exhibition.
Uchya!
Gyotsuka!
Idiot! Where are you now?
I'm in Hakodate right now.
Hakodate?
Why are you in a place like that,
That was Hakodate where I was hit by fireworks in Nagasaki
and got caught in an airplane and got off.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, please send the money to the chief.
I don't know anyone like you anymore.
Just be a crab in Hokkaido.
Chief! Chief!
No way!
How can I get home from here?
I'll ask them.
What?
Somehow I don't want to be an idiot with luxury cars.
If I break the road at the corner turn, the moon will run away.
"This is not all."
I still haven't seen it.
Don't worry
Even if you lie and cheat
You're sometimes helping someone
Baby, do you know me?
I'm heading for tomorrow
With a nice breath
Don't get sick
I'll do what I have to do
With a cute breath
What's hard to understand
Is the war I want to show you
I hope it's better than seeing you again