When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away!
A man without money, come to my place!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds!
It'll be okay!
A man without a job, come to my place!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the red clouds burning!
It'll be okay!
Do you understand?
If you do, follow me quietly!
Follow me!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
I don't care.
I'm here!
That's it!
Don't go.
I don't want to serve you.
I don't like being here.
I can't believe I can drink so much beer while reading the text.
You have to link everything in this world.
You can't eat rice crackers and fart while watching TV, can you?
It was stupid to talk to Kankichi about lemon.
Lemon was stupid.
What? Lemon and Kyoto?
Yes. Lemon is going to the restaurant of his son's depression who is cooking in Kyoto.
But the restaurant staff is busy this time and they don't have time.
So I have a problem.
Lemon is doing well but he is a kindergarten student.
Can you take him to the restaurant?
Yes. I can rest anytime.
Lemon's brother's depression is trained in a first-class restaurant.
If I take Lemon to the restaurant, I can cook delicious food.
I will arrive at Nagoya station in 5 minutes.
I dropped my ticket.
Where should I go?
Here you are.
This is it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Nagoya.
Then I'll go next.
Nagoya. Nagoya.
The stop time is 3 minutes.
Be careful of your feet.
Thank you, young lady.
I'm in the train.
I wonder where the train goes.
Ah.
Wait a minute.
The train.
Please tell me.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
I want to take the train to the station.
I got it.
This way, please.
Thank you for your work.
Be careful.
Ah.
complaint
who was it?
did you fell asleep?
there was no lemon
do you go to the toilet?
ah, it's a topic
yes, hello?
What? We're at the station!
Did you get off?
You're at the Nagoya station's platform!
I got it! Don't move!
Wait!
Damn it!
Alright!
I feel like someone just passed by...
Hey, come on!
The train will soon arrive at Line 15.
I'm coming back from Kyoto...
It'll take an hour.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Kankichi!
Sorry to leave you alone.
Yeah, but you were fast.
After I got your call, I got off the Shinkansen right away.
Thanks to you, I'm back.
I'm sorry, Kankichi.
It's alright.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
What does that have to do with you?
Huh?
I'm talking about the kid who was at home, who was asking for help.
He's my relative!
He doesn't look like him at all.
I guess I'll ask him at the office.
Damn it! I'm a police officer!
You're a great liar!
I'm a police officer!
Don't tell a lie.
Come back!
No, no, no!
It's true!
I'll find out if I contact the chief of the Katsushika office.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure of it.
I'm a relative of Ryo.
Thank you for the trouble.
It seems he was mistaken for a kidnapper.
It can't be helped if it's Ryo and Lemon.
Kyoto! Kyoto!
Hurry up!
No, I just got a call.
If he's still like this, will he get caught again?
Could be.
I didn't think he was a cop.
I've been for your help!
No, thanks.
Don't worry.
See ya.
Bye-bye!
I'm not sure I can make it.
Kanchi is not good at dressing,
and his clothes are not good.
That's why he gets it wrong.
Leave it alone!
I wonder if it's around here.
Kanchi, it's that shop.
Is this really the place?
It looks like a very high-class shop.
I've been here with my grandma last year, so I'm sure.
Let's go, Kanchi.
Giboshi Yuutsu?
Isn't that about Yun-san?
Oh, that's right.
I'll go and call him now.
Don't wait inside.
Lemon!
Yuutsu!
You came here well.
I'm getting heavier.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
He looks like Matoe.
He's a good-looking man.
Could it be that you,
who was in his grandma's email,
are Ryotsu Bakakichi?
No, I'm Kanchi!
I knew it.
He has a bold name.
Damn you, Geppardo.
You really are a cute little sister.
You look exactly like Yun-san.
How old are you?
I'm five years old.
We're brothers, too.
You're not his brother?
No.
I'm his relative from Asakusa.
That's right.
You look totally different.
Leave me alone, you idiot!
Cheers!
The sake I drink on my trip is delicious.
Kyoto's sake is delicious.
It's really delicious.
As expected of Matoe's older brother.
He's manly and has a good sense of humor.
No, no.
Matoe is really a woman.
What?
He wasn't that manly as he liked when he was a child.
His mother was a master of Japanese dance,
so Matoe had been learning to dance for a long time.
When he was in kindergarten,
Matoe had very big eyes and was a cute girl.
Hmm, that's hard to imagine.
Maybe he played baseball as a kid?
That's my influence.
Ah?
When I wanted to have a brother,
I wanted to be a sportsman, so I taught him baseball.
So you're good at baseball?
I was getting better and better because I was smart.
Thanks to that, he quit baseball and started playing softball.
If I didn't teach him baseball, my sister would be a woman.
What's wrong with you?
What a poor sister.
She's crying when she drinks.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried about you.
I knew it.
Don't cry.
The big guy is not a good guy.
The customers are watching.
It's okay.
I'll stop right away.
I feel better after crying.
What were we talking about?
What's wrong?
Lemon, you're a different character.
You are depressed and bright.
Get used to it.
Why are you so weird?
You are a fool.
I was a fool.
You think I'm a fool.
I thought you were a fool with a face I thought you were a fool but I was wrong.
I'm a fool.
I have a mistake.
I'm afraid to tell you why I have to endure this.
I don't want to know about anything.
Thank you very much.
H will
I have a mild good stock
Sweet and bitter of the strong vegetables in this season
It is really good with the harmony with the paste
I feel a little nervous about the taste of the lemon
I'm sure you'll like it.
Yuu-tsu, you've mastered the taste of the restaurant.
Really?
As much as you can say a hundred years,
Gepard said he was a master of taste.
I got the sweet and sour sauce.
Be happy, Yuu-tsu.
Yes!
But there are less customers at our restaurant these days.
I think the customers are tired of this taste.
You're overthinking, Yuu-tsu.
Now the world is not a cake.
Every restaurant is the same.
That's right.
No, I'm a true chef because I make food that customers come to me no matter what.
There's a problem with the food I make.
You're really a person who changes.
Have more confidence in your own skills.
Yuu-tsu is serious.
Yuu-san, don't think about that.
That's right, my sister came to me.
Today is a holiday, so go somewhere to change your mood.
That's right.
That's good.
Lemon likes historical drama, so let's go to the historical drama village of Kyoto.
Let's go.
Lemon loves historical drama.
It's good to be able to meet your favorite mito and gomou.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Hurry up.
Wow, amazing.
That's good.
There is a corner of the big special.
Let's go.
Oh, how nostalgic.
Is this the 32nd year of Hōei this year?
Did you watch Kankichi?
I've been watching it since the beginning.
When did you watch Lemon?
From here.
A year ago.
If you think about it, I'm still a 5-year-old Enji.
But I've been watching the reboot, so I know the first and second generation of Komou-sama.
What?
I see.
Do you want to buy something?
I'll buy a picture of Komou-sama.
Kankichi.
Yes?
Which do you prefer, the
over-sized model or a large quarter of a model?
I put a Nagamikai for you.
Yes.
Ah, I want to buy another one.
Thank you.
I want to buy an illustration.
Do you?
It's a《Kungaku Hà?》
I guess I'm verdi.
I'm estimating it.
What?
I wonder if I can buy it.
Really?
I asked for it.
There are many rare ones,
and
It's true.
Wow! It's the same as the TV!
So this is the Edo period.
It's the best period drama open set in Japan.
Edo is gone.
It's here, isn't it?
No, it's not.
The people who appear on TV live here, right?
No, they don't.
But there's a house for the Zenigata Heiji.
Yeah. I built this for the shooting.
Why can you read kanji?
I learned it on TV.
Grandma has a video.
See? I know other characters.
Then write "lemon."
Well...
I wonder if it was like this.
Which country's character is it?
It's good. I'll write it one day.
Really?
First, remember your name.
One, two, two, four.
I did it!
I can't do it.
It's okay.
I'll write it.
Don't move.
I'll transfer it.
Cheese.
Good job.
You can take a walk in the Edo period drama village.
Oh, really?
Let's go to Lemon Princess.
It's not a bad place.
Tooyama Kinshiro.
Oh, cute!
Please take a picture with me.
Please.
Oh, okay.
Okay, pose.
I feel like I'm Mickey.
What?
What's wrong?
Who called an ambulance?
Hey, what's up?
A cooking person cut his hand while shooting.
I'm sorry.
I can't shoot now.
Then maybe he's good.
Eh, really?
Hey!
What ?
I can't be an actor.
Cooking is the type of thing.
I know it's a good thing.
You've done a good job.
Really?
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, I'm the real Heikichi Ajihawa.
Heikichi Ajihawa?
I'm Ajihawa, Ajihawa, the Ajihawa of Ajihei Torimonocho.
I'm sorry, but I'm looking forward to working with you.
Y-Yes.
Yuu-tsu, Ajihei has asked for this much.
If you don't help him, he'll kill you.
I-I understand.
Ready, start!
Cut!
You're the best!
Th-Thank you.
Next, we'll have Ajihei eat the Kamo-nape in the studio.
Please!
Ready, start!
Lord Ajihawa, it's done. Please eat.
Oh, I see.
Chuta, the Kamo-nape here is excellent.
Now, eat.
Yes, sir.
It's delicious!
I'm sure it is.
Amazing.
Ajihei is really happy to have eaten Yuu-tsu's cooking.
Kankichi, Yuu-tsu is really amazing.
Cut!
Perfect!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I ate it.
That was really delicious Kamo-nape, Mr. Ghiboshi.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I can't be more impressed.
Ajihei is a very good cook.
He praised me for that.
He told me to be more happy.
Y-Yes.
Yuu-tsu is the happiest person in Japan.
I can be more confident in my cooking skills.
Y-Yes.
Wow!
I've gained confidence.
I want to go back to the restaurant and cook more.
Kankichi, I'm sorry but I'll leave it to you.
Hey, you're still wearing the costume.
Oh, he left.
He's really a strong guy.
I got an autograph from Ajihei.
But I'll keep it as a treasure for the rest of my life.
You really like historical dramas.
What do you like?
Oh, I'm shooting another one.
Let's go, Kankichi.
Okay.
What's wrong, Kankichi?
Oh!
They're here!
Why are you running away?
Oh, no!
I'm going to leave Lemon alone again.
I'm going to borrow this.
I'm going in!
Oh, no!
I don't know!
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no!
Why don't you leave?
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
The filming of "Koumon-sama is going to America" is going smoothly.
Oh, are you Koumon Mito, chief?
Yeah, I'm doing the site report.
Senpai, you're also in Kyoto, right?
I'm sure you're playing around.
In other words, here, ah!
Kankichi! Koumon-sama is in danger!
I got it! Hold on tight!
pai! - Even Lemon
-chan! - Why is Ryozu on TV? - - - - K
ankichi
is here,
so it's okay. Thank you, Princess. You
're good at this,
you idiot!
Kankichi, send them to the
He's gone!
See, it's actually great.
Well, I'm totally paralyzed.
I can't lip-sync.
- It's all your fault! - - foi who?
- You can't lip-sync. It's all your fault! - You can't lip-sync. It's all your fault!
There was an unexpected thing during the filming.
It's a great happening!
Are you from Kyoto Prefecture?
No, I'm from Sakura.
I'm from Naku-Komodabaru.
I'm from Katsushika, and I'm from Ryo-tsu.
You're naked!
You even have a tattoo!
And you're the boss and I are the president!
What's with the tattoo?
You drew it earlier.
Our president and our chief.
You're looking so stupid!
Chief Ohara is a boss who can't help but get angry.
This is the limit!
Let me stop it!
That was a bad cut.
By the way, when is this report going to air?
It's live.
What?
Live?
Yes.
Boss, the president's head is steaming!
He just stood up!
Ryo-tsu, wait!
He ran out of nowhere!
That was just a joke!
I'm busy, so I'll take this!
Let's go, Raymond!
Wait!
Kankichi!
The head is steaming!
Raymond's happy!
Great!
Let's go home now!
Before the president comes!
Let me talk to him more!
I'm going to make you pay this time!
I'm not giving up!
Revenue
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
I don't want to be someone who fights for looks
If I go on a crooked road, the moon will run away
Because it's not everything now
Don't worry too much
Even if I lie and cheat a little
I'm helping someone sometimes
Baby, do you know me?
I have a nice breath heading for tomorrow
Don't get sick of it, I'll do what I have to do
A cute breath
What's hard to understand
I want to show you that
I'll show you
It's better than seeing you again
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!