『GaruGaru』
中川に浮かぶ夕日をめがけて 中川に浮かぶ夕日をめがけて
砲石を蹴ったら靴まで飛んで 砲石を蹴ったら靴まで飛んで
From the top of the mountain, to the top of the mountain, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this, won't it?
If you win or lose, you lose happiness again
I realized, because I'm such an idiot
Because I'm such an idiot
There's no bicycle. That means…
Lucky! You're on patrol with Ryo!
Nao, you're so happy!
Let's finish it while the idiot is gone.
Cheers!
We're from the Katsushika branch, Aoshin.
Oh, you're early.
Is Aoshin the one you put up on the library's corridor?
That's right!
We deliver at your request.
It's a newspaper that's very popular among the police officers of the Katsushika branch.
Oh, I've seen it before.
And today?
We're here to interview Reiko Akimoto!
We're going to show her uniform on the paper.
Reiko, please.
Okay. I'll go change in the back, so wait a minute.
Excuse me, come on.
As I thought, it's bad, Senpai.
Don't make a noise, fool.
I wonder when you got this poster.
It's a rather unnatural poster.
It's just my imagination.
There you go.
I-it's terrible, Sen-Senpai.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Ouch...
Ryo!
Hey, Reiko! What are you doing here?
That's my line!
"I hate to take a woman's chance!"
Don't say that!
I was just in the classroom with Honda,
and you came in and tried to take off your clothes!
That's a painful excuse.
What?
Reiko, what's wrong?
I heard a strange noise.
I'll open it.
Here you go.
Ah! Ryo Kamakichi!
Hi!
What's wrong?
What happened?
I saw you!
What?
I said I was wrong!
I thought you were listening to the interview.
You're a pervert!
It's a misunderstanding! It's really a misunderstanding!
Then what's that camera?
No, it's just...
What's this?
What's that?
It's...
A prank sexy photo?
The prize is 200,000 yen!
I see. So this is the highlight!
If you get angry, I'll stop it.
You don't have to say it.
I'll help you.
I don't have to say it!
Hey!
What?
What a bad guy!
He's such an idiot.
He's a pervert!
He's got a bad temper.
What should I do?
I can't believe it.
I don't have to.
He's going to take it.
Excuse me!
Can I drink some water?
Here it is!
Take it!
Thank you!
She attacked me!
She caught me!
Huh?
I'm not a pervert!
Wh-what?
Are you serious?
Come to think of it,
If you knew I'd be here,
I wouldn't have thought of it.
Are you mad?
No, I'm just...
I was just practicing to save the land in the next year's year-end party.
What? Is that so?
Ryotsu 13: Practicing to Save the Land in the Next Year's Year-end Party
If you can't do anything about it, I'll let you play a little.
Really?
Yes, cheese!
I'm counting on you.
Let's go.
This is good.
That idiot!
What's with him?
You bastard!
Why do I have to practice to save the land?
It looked like you were having fun, but...
I won't forgive them! I'll avenge them!
But if you don't do anything, it'll turn into a newspaper story again.
I have a good idea.
What?
I'll let them taste the humiliation I suffered yesterday.
Wait, you idiots!
I'll make you pay for making Ryotsu 13 angry!
What's with that good idea?
Do you have more than you can eat?
Oh, it's been a while, Mr. Ryo.
You're still not motivated.
You're working on a sports newspaper?
You're just like me.
Can you leave your own newspaper out to the world?
I'm fine.
There's no one who reads our newspapers anyway.
I...
You're the editor of the official newspaper,
the Katsushika Newspaper Club.
And he's stronger than the editor in charge, Ken.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you're not only a newspaper of the blue signal,
I've never seen another.
I just posted it on the corner of the hallway,
and I told him to do it.
I don't want to bother you.
Let me go.
I have a suggestion.
What?
Let me take over the position of editor-in-chief.
Don't say that.
I refuse.
I think I won a lot of money in the first place.
I won a lot of money in the first place.
I don't know who made me do this.
I have come to this realization.
Actually, thanks to Mr. Ryo.
To tell you the truth,
You are confused and fragrant at the same time.
Do you know that I am still working here?
Go out.
Please leave.
Sangarin
Alright, now I know his trick.
You know the drill.
You said you know...
What are you going to do with the editor at the newspaper?
Hamurabi Houten.
He has eyes on eyes, teeth on teeth and privacy on privacy!
We'll go through Komachi and Naoko's faults, and recreate it in this newspaper!
Bring it on!
Go, Keel!
Huh?
Ahahahaha!
Wh-Why?!
You're at the place where your boss can't see you and you're working so hard!
You always go to the gym, but why are you going out today?
You should be reading sports newspapers in the coffee shop or going to the pachinko bar.
You should be doing some things everyday.
I think you're the only one who does that every day.
This won't be in the article!
Shatter change!
-You did it! -You did it!
You did it!
Senpai, what are we supposed to do with the pictures?
This is what we need.
"Sai kuwa ryu ryu shiage wo gorou jirou"
And the editor-in-chief, leave it to Ryo-tsu Kankichi, you know?
"Sai kuwa ryu shiage wo gorou jirou"
Are you sure you're okay with this?
It's amazing!
I-I love it!
"Sai kuwa ryu shiage wo gorou jirou"
It's you again, Senpai!
-The money's on me! -The money's on me!
I have a new magazine, so please line up!
Line up! Line up!
-This is way too popular. -Line up! Line up!
This is great! This is really great!
These two are wonderful!
I see. I can only see them as little girls, but they're really naughty.
Hey, you're a little ahead!
"Sai kuwa ryu shiage wo gorou jirou"
You're so good!
Hey, Komachi and Naoko, what's up?
Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
So you were behind all this, huh?
What's with this newspaper?
I'm just reporting facts as they are.
But this photo is not a copy.
I'm sure it was a fake.
Yeah, it was.
And thanks to this newspaper, you guys became popular.
People should be grateful for that.
You shouldn't complain.
Popular?
"How long will this newspaper last?"
Did you realize how powerful the newspaper is?
They really bought me with that paper, huh?
"How long will this newspaper last?"
It has to be a police record.
How can a woman be remembered like this?
"How long will this newspaper last?"
Can you at least read the whole story?
What are you looking at, Major?
What's this?
Major!
I picked it up.
I happened to pick it up when I was in the hallway.
Anyway, you don't need two locomotives in one police station.
But I have to listen to the other side.
You're right. You don't need two locomotives in one station.
Ryo.
Senior...
So you recognized it yourself.
Good. Now the "Katsushika Newspaper" is out of service.
No, the "Katsushika Newspaper" will continue to do so.
What are you talking about?
You recognized it because you didn't need it.
It's your newspaper that we don't need!
What did you say?
Major, it's a stupid newspaper that doesn't have a blue light.
It should be out of service right now.
You don't need to copy and paste the "Chosei Weekly" news.
That's not true.
The "Katsushika Newspaper" is out of service.
You don't need to copy and paste the "Chosei Weekly" news.
That's right!
Even if you say that, what should I do?
Well, let's have a game.
A game?
Let's see who is more suitable for the "Katsushika Newspaper" and "Katsushika Newspaper"
Let's have a game.
Sounds fun.
What's the game?
Each time the latest news of two newspapers is published,
the "Katsushika Newspaper" will vote on the most popular one.
The one who wins will be the most popular one.
The one who loses will be the most popular one.
Of course, the person who loses is the loser.
The important thing about the newspaper is to catch the reader's heart.
If you don't have confidence, stop reading the newspaper.
Who said you didn't have confidence?
I'm just hoping for it.
I'll take that game.
You did it.
I don't know.
I'll crush your rotten newspaper.
Watch me.
That is my line.
You'd better be prepared.
The loser makes theuru.
The winner is Thaturu.
With the help of the people helped by Katsushika Newspaper
by the people helped by Katsushika Newspaper
By the people helped by Katsushika Newspaper
The Lose
Yoramaru Mori
Is it ok for me to lose this game?
It's ok.
You can't beat Aoshin-go
If you destroy the Blue Ring, I won't be able to say anything bad about you.
I don't think that's personal right now.
What?
No, no, no.
Last time, it was very popular, but until now, the Blue Ring has been more popular and more famous.
Even if it's popular, it's just between the rich and the poor.
In the Katsushika Shogunate, there are more men than the rich and the poor.
If you grasp the feelings of men, you will definitely win.
That might be true, but...
Leave it to me. I'll make a man's newspaper.
A man's newspaper?
Senpai, what is a man's newspaper?
What is necessary for a man's newspaper. It's the Oiroke of 1 and 2.
I like it!
Today is the women's kendo practice day.
Why do they have to practice kendo?
That's right.
If I don't do it, I'll be a pauper.
Let's go!
Kichi!
It hurts...
I'm tired...
Everyone! Kichi Ryotsukan is peeping!
Be careful! He's taking terrible pictures!
Sen...Senpai...
No! No! No!
No, it's not a bad photo. I'm just here to do some research.
Here, here.
Liar!
You're just taking pictures of Komachi and the others!
Come on, let's go. We're practicing outside.
Yes!
No, that's it. This is it.
Hey, hey, hey, wait!
Ryo-sama.
Huh?
Maria!
Ryo-sama! Long time no see!
What? You were practicing with Fukie too?
That's right!
Even though I know you're a man, your kendo figure is sexy.
Hey, Maria.
This is useful.
Maria, I'm actually here to do some research on women's kendo, but the others are not cooperative.
How about you cooperate?
Yes, I'm happy for you, Ryo-sama!
Stand over there.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Okay, okay.
It's not very interesting.
Please sit down for a moment.
Like this?
Hmm, it's not quite right.
It's easier to break your legs.
Put your left hand on your head.
It's better to turn your head a little.
Okay, perfect!
Awesome!
Now you're really trying to make an appearance, aren't you?
You're not Aikido!
Come on, let's start!
I couldn't stand them!
We're tired, so we're going to go do our best!
What about me?
Can I join you for a while?
50 yen, right?
Yeah, that'll do.
I think we got a new idea.
Okay, let's get this over with.
Senpai, what's next?
The second stage of the Sports Beauty is the Basket Beauty.
-Let's go! -Let's go!
Here they come.
Just as I expected.
Guys, the defense against the Ryotsu is on!
Get ready, Maria.
This is the war between the Fukuoka and the Ryotsu Kankichi.
Don't try to stop us like you did the other day.
Okay.
What's wrong, Senpai?
I think they're locked.
Hey, it's a material of my own!
-I'll give it to you! -Hey!
-Hey! -I'll give it to you!
-I'll give it to you! -I'll give it to you!
That's Naoko Komachi's voice.
This is dirty!
It's the office's duty to cooperate with the locomotive.
You don't have to go over here to make a newspaper.
You can go over here.
Veniac!
Not yet!
It's open.
Hey, you!
You!
Tsk!
Take a photo!
Spin around?
You're an expert.
Tsk!
Yaaah!
Sheesh!
This week, a special episode of Sports Beauty is impossible.
Impossible.
How do you fill in the blank?
How about reviving the corner of the boss and boss' party?
Who reads such a thing?
Okay, let's predict the top news of this week.
Then, let's start my serial manga.
Oh, no!
You're not supposed to do that!
You're copying me!
We're not stealing!
We're getting permission from the boss!
That's not good, Timo!
Number 3.
"Kaname Sotomawari"
Number 2.
Number 10.
"Harahoro"
You're not getting what you expected.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Wait!
I'll hit you next time!
You're not getting it!
Oh, no!
You're to blame!
Well, it's a backwater now.
It's time to...
Don't you ever read any of this!
What do we do, human?
At this rate, Katsushika Newspaper House will be empty!
What I'm supposed to do...
Don't be mad.
I'll take back my word.
Backward?
With this plan, any magazine or newspaper can be re-run.
And these will help fuel more popularity of the couple.
It's a way to recover your popularity.
No way...
You're so silly.
Reiko is especially popular among male police officers.
According to Maria, Reiko will be staying at the women's room today.
She will be taking pictures of the scenes in Ryo's bath.
Is she really going to do that, senpai?
It's too much to put the "Nudo" book on the locomotive.
Reiko is a clerk at the Katsushika library.
It is the duty of the locomotive to announce the clerk without hiding the crime.
Is that so?
Huh? That's...
Start the operation!
It's a little hard to take pictures of this.
Don't worry.
This CCD camera can be taken out of anywhere.
The camera will be taken out.
The pictures that are taken out can be seen on this monitor.
You can print them on a high-quality printer.
Ready?
Here.
Here it is.
We're number one, aren't we?
Here we go.
This is...
Hurry up, Reiko! Hurry up!
I'm coming!
Okay, I'll take a picture with the WAP.
Damn it!
I got it!
You were out of soap, weren't you?
It wasn't you!
I wasn't you!
Reiko!
No, no, no, Reiko!
Just a little more...
Be quiet!
Senpai...
Let's stop this.
This is definitely not good.
What?
Wait a minute!
Stop it!
Hey, isn't it noisy outside?
By the way...
What's that?
Camera?
Ah!
Ryo! Kankichi!
Oh no!
Ryo!
I won't let you!
This is...
That's...
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow!
Come on!
Why?
I won't stop!
Hey, come on!
Why are you doing this to me?
Aren't you shorts!
I died here many years ago...
You can't just admit it like that.
Don't let me get away with this, you idiot!
Senpai, I was also punished for the crime.
What do I do with my bike loan?
I was chased out of the house by my wife.
What am I going to do?
Even if I tell you that...
I don't care!
Please, editor-in-chief, do something!
Editor-in-chief, please!
Hey, you!
I finally got the bonus after I found the
Koshi-tora sweat.
I'm told to return the debt, but I can't return it without saying, "Yes, is that so?"
If you can get it back, do it and look up!
You idiot!
Next time, bonus Soda Line 2!
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I want to return the debt, but I won't.
I don't care!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry!
Oh my god!
A changing lady's dream
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait for me
The future of the panorama
The dazzlingness that comes with a dive
You know that, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me