What to Do in a Night Chair
Take a look at the room with the TV and stand away!
♪ Come to me if you're not rich!
♪ I'm not too rich but I'm always worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be alright
Come to me if you're jobless
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red moon is burning
The red moon is burning
I'm sure they'll be alright
Come to me if you're jobless
Oh, it's quite a famous hotel.
The octopus dishes are very delicious.
Yes, that's the final destination.
Wait a minute.
Normally, Tanji decides where to go on a first-person trip.
Why do you decide without consulting me?
I don't know where to take you if you decide.
Previously, I used my travel expenses and was deceived by the tourist tour.
I was taken to a mountain that I didn't know why.
If you leave it to Ryo, it won't be a good thing.
Then, what should I do?
If you have a destination, there is nothing to do.
There are many things to do.
Handling of transportation, confirmation of departure, printing on the same day.
And the travel expenses.
That's me and the director.
I'll give you the money.
Don't use it up.
Yes, yes, I understand.
Then I'll go to the library.
Thank you for your hard work.
Octopus dishes, huh?
I'm looking forward to it.
I've eaten once, but the octopus dishes there are excellent.
It's just octopus.
Ryo, why don't you write something on the envelope so that you don't use it up?
Yes, yes.
Octopus...
Bobi, are you going on a trip?
Yeah.
All the staff, including Atami.
It's a waste to come to Japan.
It's just a stupid method of going to eat octopus.
Originally, I decided to go to Kanji, so I had no choice but to collect the expenses.
To be honest, how is this kind of travel?
Everyone...
Senpai, you drank too much~
Shut up!
Why did you even bother coming all the way to Atami Kunari to eat octopus?
That's impossible!
Eh? Octopus-H compassion!
This hurts...!
Ryo, you sure are rough.
Yeah. Apparently, he didn't like his woven path that he decided on by himself.
Ryo, let's just drink tonight!
We can hang out 'til morning~
What to do~!
I see!
Alright, I'll take it!
Yay!
I don't give a shit about octopus!
Ryo-san, Ryo-san!
I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Do you have money?
Money?
Let me see...
Uh...
Oh, this is a lot!
What? Octopus?
What do you mean octopus?
Oh, oh!
It's the prize money from last month's octopus-frying tournament!
Now, Sakonji, Barba, and I will drink it up!
Oh, that's fast...
Bring me a big bottle of sake!
Hey, Ryo-san...
I have a lot of money!
Thank you very much!
The morning sun is so bright!
It's a cool morning!
You really drank until the morning, didn't you?
Ryutsu, what's wrong with your emotions?
No, I was lucky enough to have the prize money from the octopus-frying tournament.
What?
I think you drank it on the night of the octopus-frying tournament, didn't you?
That's right. I drank it with Ryutsu's prize money.
It's not enough, so we all took out a little.
Then, what about this money?
Ryo-chan, write something in your envelope so you don't use it up.
Hey, hey, octopus...
Oh, it's the cost of the accommodation trip!
What? Did you spend the money for the trip?
What are you going to do, Ryutsu?
Huh?
It's finally time, Ohara-kun.
It's finally time, Chacha.
Oh, this kind of dish comes out.
They say you only use freshly caught octopus.
I'm looking forward to it!
But why are they gathering on the dock?
Are they going by boat?
I don't know.
I can't see the boat for that matter, but...
It's about time to depart, isn't it?
This is...
A submarine?
Look at that.
The "Katsushikasho Goikko-sama"?
No way...
Oh, everyone!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Ryutsu, what's going on here?
Are you really going to go with that?
Of course.
The main part of this trip is octopus.
So I've prepared a submarine to let everyone taste the feeling of octopus.
How about it?
It's a good idea, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Jody.
I'm sorry for asking you to do this.
Oh, no!
If you can travel with Bobby, I'll gladly cooperate with you!
I'll be glad to.
All right, everyone's on board!
Yeah.
Then, let's go!
Now, everyone!
Do it fast!
Even if you say so...
It's too quiet to go home and calm down.
I don't think you can see the outside.
Oh, that's right.
Click!
This is a video of a submarine camera.
It's a simple sight.
I'm just excited just looking at it.
Ryutsu, I have a simple question.
How much does it cost to rent a submarine like this?
That's right!
I have a karaoke ready!
Let's have a karaoke tournament!
Hey, Eriho-tsu!
Well, let me sing first.
Bad guys have a big robot punch.
Throw it to the end of the world.
No, no!
Bad guys have a big robot punch.
Throw it to the end of the world.
All this time, it's gone.
What?!
Bang! Bang! Ba-bang!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
I've done it along with you.
This is a big robot punch.
5 minutes later
Here we are.
An Atami!
But it's far from the beach.
It's just a few miles away, so it can't be any closer.
How do we get to the hotel?
Don't worry.
This way.
7. Shaking aやん
Are we going on rubber boats?
Yes.
11. Fire
Now everyone.
Let's make a fire!
Turns out...
coming on a而已n trip and getting burned off a boat
is as bad as Normandy landing.
All of them have bad ideas!
12. Hotel
This is a wonderful hotel!
This is wonderful.
Wow, it's beautiful.
It's wonderful.
Ryotsu, please guide us to the room.
I'm tired of the boat ride just now.
Ryotsu.
I'm ready.
I see.
Let's go to the hotel.
This is the hotel.
This is luxurious.
It's wonderful.
It's a long walk.
Ryo, are you still here?
It's almost there.
Are we going out?
We're going to stay at the inn.
Inn.
Here we are.
It's a wonderful hotel.
The main building behind us.
It's a different building from the inn.
That's why I said it was a different building.
Hey.
You're telling me to stay here?
I also complained to the hotel, but they didn't accept me at all.
What do you mean, Ryo?
In fact, in recent years, there have been many cases of group guests causing trouble to other customers by making a fuss in the hotel.
I see.
To avoid such a situation,
From this year, all group guests will be in the hotel.
Then you can stay here.
Huh?
No way.
I can't believe you're such a liar.
It's quiet.
What's this?
A dirty room.
After coming here to eat octopus, I didn't expect to stay in an octopus room.
What a terrible room.
Ryotsu, you must be having a proper meal.
We're here to enjoy octopus cooking.
Of course. I'm cooking right now.
Cooking?
No, cooking.
I'm cooking right now.
The top chefs at the hotel.
You're not going to catch any?
I have to get enough octopus by the time of the dinner.
Chief, we're here in Atami, so let's go to the hot spring before the dinner.
That sounds good. Let's go together.
Ryotsu, there's a bath, right?
Of course.
The bath is here.
What's this?
The customers of the other side are going to be here.
As I said earlier, the group customers are causing trouble.
What's that?
It's not a joke. We're paying for the hotel.
Why do we have to go to such a place?
This is the hotel's policy.
I don't agree with that policy.
We should be serious about this.
Isn't that right, Chief?
Yes.
That's gross.
Let's go to the front.
That's right, that's right.
The bath is the only thing that can be used in the main hall.
I was told so.
Let me show you the way.
There are so many people here.
If we're fair, we can hide in the bath.
Now, everyone, here we are.
Please come in.
It's a public bath.
This is a wind dragon.
What?
Mr. Ryo, that is a woman.
It's not a ghost marriage.
From time to time, the outlet is split into men and women,
and the hot spring is on the inside.
Sir, what should we do?
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
You've seen this place the last time.
It's the king, so just stay calm.
Hey!
Hello, hello.
I'm coming in, miss.
What?
You're Mr. Hondara!
What? It's been a long time.
What are you doing here?
I've been staying at a hondara camp for a week.
What? Camp?
Camp?
Hey, Ryotsu!
Can we go there, too?
No.
If they find out that we're staying here,
they'll find out that we're in a different camp.
What? You're in a different camp, too?
Come here!
Stop!
What is he doing?
Let go!
H-Hey!
What are you doing?
You're all warmed up, right?
Get out of the bath!
What do you mean, "Get out"?
I'm just worried about you moving around.
That's no point!
Hondara Kenpo, Tsubanomai!
You're so annoying!
I won't forgive you!
Hondara Kenpo, Umihippai!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You bastard!
Umihipparegaishiii!
Hey, Ryotsu!
What's up, Chief?
See what you're doing?
Hey, golly!
Huh?
Hondara Kenpo.
Shut up!
Stop! Let me go!
What?
Who is that?
You're embarrassing me.
No!
Akichi, you're here.
You came to see the bath, as promised.
No! It's an accident!
No! No! No!
You're here to see the president?
No, that's a misunderstanding.
Everyone!
What's all this fuss about?
No, that's...
Where are the guests?
Excuse me, we're staying at a different hotel.
Different hotel?
There's no such thing at our hotel.
What?
Ohara-kun...
You're a good guy.
Idiot!
I can't believe you used all your travel expenses on a bar.
Fortunately, the hotel is empty.
We're staying there.
We're going to have special octopus dishes prepared.
But we'll deduct your next salary.
What?
No way!
It's self-interest.
You can reflect on it.
Darn it!
Phew...
I'm sorry, everyone.
You don't have to worry about Jody-san.
They're the only bad guys.
Jody-san.
He brought us all the way here.
Why don't you all go to the hotel and have lunch?
Oh, wonderful!
Here you are, sir.
Oh, sorry.
Now, let's enjoy our hotel's special octopus dishes.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Finally, we can have our special octopus dishes!
I guess everyone is eating delicious octopus dishes.
Octopus?
I can eat it in Tokyo.
But it's the best octopus dish.
I just wanted to try it since it's so small.
Anyway, the octopus...
I'm hungry.
Yeah, me too.
All of this is because of the octopus.
You idiot octopus!
Kanjiki-chan!
Senpai!
You don't have to kick me so hard.
Don't be silly.
I didn't kick you so hard.
What's going on?
It seems to sink.
An accident?
I don't know.
The monitor is not working properly.
This is it!
First, we will make fresh octopus!
It's so grotesque!
This is an octopus!
What?
A huge octopus is attached to this ship!
It's a gap!
It's because you say octopus's bad words!
Octopus can't understand words!
It's delicious!
This is more than I expected, Ohara!
Next, we will make octopus marinade!
It looks so delicious!
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
It's so healthy!
It's so delicious!
We can eat octopus!
We ate octopus!
Shut up! Don't cry!
Now we have to move the ship!
Can you do it?
I will control it!
Then who will do it?
You!
Come here!
No, no, no!
It's impossible!
I've never moved a submarine!
What?
It's got a handle!
It's similar!
It's always like that!
It's not easy to control a submarine!
I'll cut it into pieces!
You did it!
Let's go!
Good luck, Honda!
We are going to eat octopus!
Octopus is sooups!
I'll give you octopus tempura!
It's so crispy and delicious!
It's as if it has bones.
Whoa!
It's looking at water!
Don't eat!
You crazy octopus!
Go away!
I'll give you octopus grilled dish!
It smells so good!
It's delicious!
I'm so happy!
Ah! Good taste!
We're almost there!
We got them all!
Let's go!
Lastly, let's have an octopus dessert.
Oh, it's rare to see a dessert.
Ryotsu!
Ah, hello everyone. I'm Enmo Takenawa.
What the hell is going on?
You!
You're the one who made us not eat octopus!
Hey, wait a minute!
Ryo?
I can't forgive you.
What's wrong with you?
You're so annoying.
There's a deep reason for this.
I was attacked by a giant octopus.
If you're lying, you should tell me a better lie.
You're right, Deba!
Ah!
Octopus!
That's enough!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Please come in!
Welcome! Welcome! Please come in!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
What's that?
My recommendation is...
Be careful of the fried chicken!
Huh? Is that a gag?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
I can't understand.
Are you serious?
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Masai!
What the hell?
I just kicked him a little.
He ran away!
The exit is closed!
Do I have to prepare the temporary exit until I rebuild it?
It's not easy to find such a convenient place.
Next time, "Meso! Here is the temporary exit!"
Thank you for watching!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Oh, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
See you again!