S Schneider's
Oh, the summer is here again this year
It's here! It's here! It's here!
Oh, the mayor of Okinawan is waiting
♪ I'm a little bit of a big booger ♪
♪ I'm a little bit of a booger ♪
♪ Ah, this year too, summer has come ♪
♪ I'm a little bit of a big booger ♪
♪ Ah, I'm a little bit of a big booger ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ A scent of the south breeze ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I'm a little bit of a big booger ♪
Ryoichi
Episode 1: The Big Bang!
The Big Bang! The Big Bang!
...What was that?
What's this?
A meeting?
Huh?
Are you quitting, Senpai?
I don't want to, Chief.
Please call it a "restaurant request".
A restaurant request...
What a fool!
What?
A big adult can't even write a kanji!
So you're taking a vacation?
Are you going to a wedding?
No way.
I-I've written down the reason in detail.
Reason?
Huh?
"Ryotsu Kankichi is watching the Tameari fireworks show?"
I haven't seen any fireworks show since I was a kid,
so I don't know what kind of work you're doing!
I don't know what you're doing, either!
I don't know what you're doing!
Of course!
I'm a policeman!
You think you're a policeman,
so you can take a vacation at a fireworks show!?
Fireworks shows are amazing every year.
I want to borrow a cat's hand as a guard.
Huh?
What do you mean, "I don't have money"?
Don't worry.
If you do that, you'll be fired!
You're kidding!
I'm not kidding!
The chief's head of stone is using his brain every day.
It would be great to ride him and watch the fireworks show.
Damn it!
There's no way I can get a good vacation!
Hey, Ryo!
Huh?
Hey!
What!?
No!
My money is all over the place!
I was just about to return it!
I won't pay for anything I don't have!
Huh?
Is it that unfair?
Yeah.
I have to pay for Ryo-san's money.
Then I can have a good vacation.
This is a step forward.
There's no food here.
But the shop is located near Kagono.
If we don't have any food, why are you riding a horse?
Let's go!
I'm late.
What!
What is going on?
If we don't when we get to Higashiyama, we have to come back.
But the shop's open again.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
This is resistance.
I'm with you.
I gotta go.
I'll be on the watch.
Good.
I'm off, then.
Theに音 is noisy. It is much easier.
Nothing to be afraid of.
I'm doing it, Katsushika Balloon Club!
Hey, Ryo.
Komaki, you're nervous.
Yeah, I'm in debt.
Where's the old guy?
He's in the warehouse.
If you don't mind, lend him to me.
I have a friend who's interested in him.
Yeah, we're very happy to have more friends.
I don't mind.
It's hot.
Does it mean I should go down by this?
You'll use propane gas for fuel, for reference.
So we're making ramen in here.
How do you like it?
Actually, I heard you liked this one.
I said I want to go down on the ship.
Please!
Really?
I see. Then let's try to drive it ourselves.
It's getting bigger!
Remember the procedure.
What?
We'll drive it when it's time.
Don't ask that bald guy.
I heard you're going to do a business with Nekikyuu.
Do you think he'll be happy to cooperate?
Besides, the Nekikyuu don't allow night flight in Japan.
What if he finds out about it?
People with beards are scared of getting angry.
- Maybe you'll get bitten to death! - What?
Ryosan, get in the car.
- Alright! - Let's calm down.
Don't be so rude!
What?
As expected of a professional.
What a great technique.
The basic movement of the heat ball can be adjusted with this burner.
You can go up to a pretty high level, but...
It's okay to fly so high.
You can even go up to the height of a high-rise building.
What?
When it's quickly melted, you can also remove the heat.
Um, remove the heat...
Oh, you're so enthusiastic.
Because I have a business to do.
Business?
No, I mean...
I wanted to be a professional in the heat ball,
so I wrote a book about it in my elementary school.
I wanted to do a business to fly in the sky.
What?
Ah, yes.
That's reliable.
I'll get it done.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
We're running out of time.
It's a pain in the ass to go to the convenience store.
Oh?
What's that?
What?
It says ramen.
No way.
It also says my phone number.
I'll try calling it.
Yes, this is Kikyu Ramen.
Are you coming?
What?
Um, can I have two ramen, please?
Yes, two ramen, please.
Which one would you like?
This is Yamada from Room 3011 of Room 8.
30 times, right?
I'll take it.
Wait a minute.
I ordered it properly.
But how can I deliver it?
It's coming.
I'm scared.
Welcome!
It's Mr. Yamada.
Y-Yes.
Here you are.
You're fast.
I'm in Kikyu.
It's a ramen shop.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's 1,000 yen.
Hey, this is Kikyu Ramen.
Yes, hello.
Three ramen.
Beat 40235.
All right.
It's that room.
Kikyu Ramen
Yes, okay.
Let's go.
Oh, here it is.
Hey, I bought the ramen.
Hello.
Jarshu Ramen.
70 cents.
Five miso ramen, please.
I understand.
Oh, I'm so busy.
Kikyu, there's a patrol car.
Someone called the police.
What should we do?
Formation launch against the emergency!
Formation, launch!
That balloon...
Where is it?
It's dark and I can't see anything.
It's called the Dark Night Crows.
That's why I painted the balloon black.
Only the bad guys are good at this.
If I get caught at the first light of dawn,
I'll be in big trouble!
I didn't think it would be this bad.
I didn't think I'd be in big trouble.
If I make money like this,
I'll be rich, and I'll be rich.
You're in a good mood.
But is it okay for a policeman to work part-time?
I'm a policeman.
I have a duty to help the people in trouble.
If there are people who are hungry at night,
it's the way to help people.
A suspicious balloon is seen near the high-rise apartment in the city.
It's a big possibility that it will appear tonight.
Strengthen the night patrol and work for discovery.
Are you listening?
But I don't think I'm going out tonight.
How do you know that?
That's the person who...
It's a policeman's pipe.
Did you have a policeman's pipe?
What?
Then what?
What do you want to write, chief?
A thousand yen for a bite.
Idiot!
Do you think it's okay for a holy policeman to gamble?
Chief, what about this?
If Ryo-chan gets the clue to the suspicious balloon,
he'll make the fireworks festival day a holiday.
I see. That's good.
What do you think, Ryotsu?
Is it good?
Huh?
That's right.
I don't get it...
I've decided already.
What's wrong with my cell phone?
I'll give it back to him.
Well then, let's take our summer trip to the tenütz.
Oh, it's a bit later today.
You wanted to leave me, didn't you?
a busy guy.
Why don't you have any face?
She's a bad dude.
I know!
Then what? Can you see it with your own eyes?
Well, just take a look.
A bird?
Why? It's a bird.
It's so dark, but it's very clear.
It's a starlight scope used by the U.S. military.
If you take a look, you can find a black, suspicious balloon right away.
That's bad.
Oh, no. I've got something amazing.
Senpai, why don't we find a balloon and make a gift together?
I'll give you the gift.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Oh, Ryo-san.
I always make money for you, so I thought I'd give you a late-night meal.
Idiot!
What if you get suspicious by wandering around this place?
Oh, it's a ramen shop.
I'm glad.
I was just hungry.
Oh, I've never had ramen at a restaurant before, so I want to try it.
It smells delicious.
Is this how a ramen shop is built?
Huh?
Yeah, that's Nakagawa's son-in-law.
He's a policeman by hobby.
He makes ramen.
I don't eat ramen very often.
It's not like you're doing it as a hobby.
Come to think of it, a suspicious balloon is selling ramen, right?
Huh?
The phone is ringing.
Oh, hello.
Hello, balloon ramen.
No, it's just a ramen shop.
Huh? Just a ramen shop?
It's a balloon ramen shop, right?
What time will you come around here tonight?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Today is my day off.
Oh, yes.
Please come again.
Isn't your day off a business trip?
Oh, no.
I was thinking about going early tonight.
Right, Ryo?
Don't ask me.
I don't know anything.
That's right.
Oh, my.
Cut.
Air sock.
Third turn.
Oh, it's Ryo.
I'll open it now.
What's that luggage?
You'll get a good profit if you just eat ramen.
The theory of what's good to sell is developed in various ways based on the needs of the times.
Yeah.
Right?
What's that?
and the Combin-i that flies in the sky!
Everyone, we're sorry to keep you waiting.
Combin-i Kikyu Ramen is here!
Combin-i Kikyu Ramen!
Hello, sir!
Three chashu noodles, please.
Can I have a rice ball, please?
Sure!
Here you go!
The limited edition of Idol Hell 3rd edition set!
I really wanted this!
Hey, you want an egg?
Here you go!
Oh, you have everything you need!
Chocolate, please!
I'll have oolong tea and yakisoba!
Thank you!
I'll have a cup of coffee, too!
And a drink, please!
Here you go!
Melon, strawberry and condensed milk.
Which one would you like?
Oh, that was a great help!
Oh, by the way,
can I have two or three of these?
Sure!
You're in a hurry!
What a big profit!
Oh, look!
It's that balloon!
It's here!
All right, let's get going!
This is Nampo!
We just discovered a suspicious balloon!
Where is it?
Okay.
Kei, please prepare the Starlight Scope.
Roger that!
Haha, that was a big profit!
Hello?
Ah, sorry.
It's sold out today.
Here you go!
Ah, it's Ryo-san's mini-bat!
What?
That must be Komachi and Naoko?
All right!
A first match for the formation against a mini-bat!
Oh!
You've erased Ryo!
It's okay.
You can see it through the moonlight.
Oh, look!
It's a balloon!
Hehe, that's right.
This is a secret strategy.
The Kasumika-Kumoka strategy.
You really know how to work well, don't you?
I can't see the moon.
Just follow the smoke!
Follow the smoke!
But I can't see the road.
Damn it!
Where is this going?
I can't see anything!
Ah!
I'm going crazy!
I thought I was going to die.
You bastard!
The earth is facing this way.
I can't see it at all.
That telescope is okay in the dark, right?
It should be fine up to a few kilometers away.
But now I'm going to die.
K, look at this lens!
What's wrong?
Ah!
This is a black operating instrument.
Who did this?
If you ask me who did this,
Hahaha!
I don't think we can be caught that easily!
I'm sorry, Ryo.
I was able to help you until the day of the fire.
You can pay the debt in a few days, right?
I'm counting on you!
Where is it?
Yes, this is the convenience store machine ramen.
I want you to give me your number.
My voice is...
As I thought, Ryo-chan.
Today is already the end. Good night.
Why is Reiko's phone number?
There's no doubt.
Because the strange machine is always at Ryo-chan's absence.
If this happens...
The police officer got a cold?
She's a nice woman.
I think it's time to open the store.
I'm in a hurry.
It's okay.
I have to clean up this pile of stock.
Let's make a lot of money at the end.
If it goes well, you'll be able to hold a store.
How can I make so much money?
Use the fireworks competition.
Fireworks competition?
But Ryo-san, can you take a day off?
My relatives are unfortunate.
I can take a day off if you say that.
I have many older relatives.
Chief, actually...
I know. I know.
It's about the vacation, right?
What?
Well...
I've heard the report.
You were on the day of the fire.
You're looking for a strange machine until the second day.
Oh, I see.
I'm impressed with you.
I'll take a special vacation for tomorrow's fireworks competition.
Please continue to investigate.
Yes, sir.
What?
You don't look very happy.
It's not half!
Hurry up and give it to me.
I can't afford to waste it.
I'll take the discount.
Please, no.
It's not half.
I don't have half.
I'm sorry.
You're my hierophant.
I'm not going to let Reiko get in the way of business!
Ryo-san, it's finally time to decorate the finale!
Yeah!
The last delicious ramen at the convenience store!
I'm going to make it as lively as fireworks!
Everyone, thank you for waiting!
The convenience store that you've all been waiting for, Kikyu Ramen, has arrived!
Drinking beer while watching the fireworks of Ido-cho is a true Japanese delight!
The last one!
Everyone in the high-rise apartment building who is the first class of fireworks!
Beer, snacks, and shaved ice!
All of these are convenient stores that are happy to sell to you!
Yes, everyone, let's go together!
Let's go!
Hey, give me some beer!
Give me some shaved ice!
Okay, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
I knew it!
I was beaten up!
Ryo-san, if you keep this up, you'll lose everything!
This is a great profit!
What's wrong?
Oh, the burner's out of order.
It's old, after all.
Stop!
Kei-chan, where's Kikyu?
I think he's on the way.
There's no mistake.
As I thought, you were good.
You bastard!
I'm going to get you!
What?
What is this?
Looks like he's involved in a fireball explosion and is doing a dutch roll.
He's a freak.
Ryo-chan...
Is it over?
No, there's a 15-ball left at the end.
A 15-ball?
It's only 300 meters in diameter, so if he gets caught...
Caught?
You've been involved in a natural disaster!
That's a terrible end to a foolish man.
What?
Money has flown in from the fireworks!
A fireplace.
Uh, I don't want any money.
Eh, oh well.
I'm sorry. I was able to see the fireworks near the storehouse.
I'll give them to everyone as a souvenir.
Gege!
I won 5.5 billion yen with a foreign currency!
I'll return the money, buy a plastic model, eat eel, and eat a steamer!
I can't use all of it!
Next time, we'll do a one-shot promotion!
See you then!
♪ Let's smile anytime ♩
♪ Even if you wake up in the morning ♩
♪ Smile cutely ♩
♪ You can go out with a face that's nothing ♩
♪ Hey, smile ♩
♪ You're not bad ♩
♪ You've been like this all along, yeah ♩
♪ Let's smile anytime ♩
♪ Her sly charm is not good ♩
♪ You should smile now ♩
♪ As long as you're not a child ♩
"I'm sorry, I can't help it. I'm sorry. I'm sorry."