Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the passing seasons ♩
♪ The brightest and greatest harem ♩
♪ Crossing the new era ♩
♪ The hero is diving to the city on his own ♩
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♩
♪ Rather than just wearing the trendy clothes ♩
♪ I'll be 100 times more honest ♩
♪ Let it rip ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Let's run ♩
♪ Dreams can't always stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow, too ♩
♪ Let me run ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Even if it's a little dark ♩
♪ It doesn't hurt to spit it out ♩
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♩
♪ And raise it high ♩
♪ You're all the same ♩
They're new to the battle!
Wasn't that weird?
No, that's weird!
Okay! It's done!
Thank you for your hard work on your New Year's interview!
After that, we're gonna refurbish everything on the stage!
Thank you for your hard work.
Ryo, you've been working all day long since the dawn of the new year.
Of course.
Unlike Nakagawa and Reiko, I'm working hard on the construction site.
I'm burning with a hot mission to protect the safety of the people even during the New Year.
What's so funny?
Dad, just kidding.
What?
I know. You took too many summer vacations last year, and you're having your New Year's Eve party.
You knew that, didn't you?
Well, let's go home.
Ryo, what are you going to do from now on?
I'm going to have a cold drink and go to bed.
There's no New Year's Eve party at the chief's house this year.
That's strange.
I met the temple lord at the first temple day yesterday.
He said he would go to the chief's house for a annual worship with a new dress.
What a mistake!
The chief said he would go on a family trip without his parents and children.
New Year's Eve party?
Yes, the annual New Year's Eve party at the chief's house.
When is the New Year's Eve party next year?
Next year is the end of the year.
I was looking forward to eating Osechi at the chief's house during the New Year.
Ryo, you're exaggerating.
Well, don't be so disappointed.
It's been a long time since we went on a hot spring trip with our parents and children.
You care about your family more than your friends, don't you?
Don't say that.
I'm old, and I can't travel without my parents and children.
Well, that's what it is.
Everyone, the New Year's Eve party is next year.
Yes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Now that I think about it, I feel like everyone was very uncomfortable.
I wonder if they were just thinking about me.
All right.
Is this the house of the chief's house?
I'm Ryo-tsu.
Congratulations.
By the way, the chief has an errand to do.
What?
You did it, Captain.
You made me a fool.
Damn it!
If you do that, I'll eat any and everything you want!
I won't forgive you!
Ryo, are you in a trance?
This is a bloodbath.
Happy New Year!
You're here.
I'm counting on you this year too.
Hiromi, you're so cute.
Reiko, you look great in this.
Thank you.
Huh?
Hasn't Senpai come yet?
You know, Papa...
Hiromi, I don't want to think about him since New Year's.
Anyway, Nakagawa,
get in the car.
Did you park the car in front of the house?
Yes.
It's a small place, but get in.
What?
Captain, why are you closing the window in the daytime?
It's a spell of demon payment.
Demon payment?
Ouch!
Senpai, please forgive me.
I'm going to the first wedding with my sister.
You can always go to the first wedding,
but this is the only New Year's party for you.
Don't talk nonsense.
Aren't you upset?
You're not invited to the first wedding.
Of course.
I'm part of the White Squad.
I'm not a dispatcher.
Don't say silly things.
You're my best friend.
Just take me to my boss' house.
Ouch!
Senpai!
Huh?
Hmm?
Hehe!
Hehehe.
You're a tough guy in the beginning of the New Year.
I got it.
Get on the car!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Oh, sorry.
Oops.
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
The engine sound is Honda's CBX, right?
Maybe you're here, too.
What?
You're already coming to me?
You're good at listening to the devil's voice.
Listen!
No matter what happens, don't speak up or show up.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Damn it!
You're a tough guy.
I guess I went on a family trip after all.
That can't be true!
Look at that.
Huh?
What's that?
You're using a cheap hand to cover it with a sheet.
Hey!
Oh!
It's a Ferrari F50!
It's different from the one you always ride.
It's definitely Nakagawa's Ferrari.
Really?
Maybe it's the neighbor's car.
Look around you!
Where do people live?
Look at the license plate, too.
Hmm?
It's a boy's license plate.
Nakagawa, you know,
even though he lives in Tokyo,
he's dressed up and using all his cars as boy's license plates.
Yeah.
All right!
Shhh!
Ohana?
I'm a past delivery.
A delivery, please.
Ohana, come out, please.
You're so obvious.
I'm not sure what to say.
Damn it.
He's just trying to get rid of me.
The curtains are closed.
He's on a family trip.
Oh!
The enemy is in there.
What?
Look at this.
Isn't this just an electric meter?
Look at the meter.
If you're a homeless,
your phone and refrigerator should only be working.
The meter won't work like this.
I see.
Everyone,
how about some sukiyaki?
Sounds good.
I'm just tired of cooking.
I'll help you.
Chief!
I know you're in there!
He's so persistent.
Hurry up and put us in!
Dad, I'm sorry.
Just put us in.
No!
You may not know this,
but he's making the house messy on New Year's Day.
If I do this,
he'll make my bonsai useless.
he'll make the tatami weaker.
If I scold him,
he'll have my face stained with ink.
And then he'll make the whole room black.
I won't let that man enter the house again.
I don't want to see him.
He's making me a scarecrow.
I don't know what to do.
You're surrounded!
Give up and come out!
I don't care.
He doesn't seem to react at all.
Damn it!
If you're going to do that,
I'll use my strong hand.
Your strong hand?
It's quiet now.
It seems you've given up.
No.
When I'm full,
you'll have a bad habit.
So don't worry.
Is it power outage?
There's no way I'm going to build electricity on New Year's Day.
The gas in the kitchen has stopped suddenly.
What?
They're all doing the same thing.
Senior,
let's stop here.
Shut up!
If this happens,
I'll eat your food.
Geez.
What a stubborn guy.
It's fine if you reverse the water corridor and the sewer corridor
to panic,
but smash the door and get out as quickly as possible.
Wait, senior.
Senior,
that's no good.
The chainsaw is...
It's all right.
Don't worry.
What?
You only have to break the minimum.
I don't feel at ease at all.
I can't go.
Let's go!
Ryo!
Chief, please don't open it suddenly.
Life is shortening.
I'm the one who's shortening my life.
Senpai, what are you doing here with a chainsaw?
What are you doing here with a chainsaw?
The door...
No, I mean...
I was asked to clean the bathroom.
Liar!
I've never asked you to do that.
I don't like it.
I forget it when I get older.
Right, Honda?
Yes.
No, no, no!
Chief, didn't you go on a hot spring trip?
Huh?
That's...
Well...
I couldn't get a ticket because of a travel agency.
So I'm staying at home.
Then why are you staying at Nakagawa?
Well...
I was suddenly bored, so I called Nakagawa and Reiko.
Of course, I contacted you and Nico-Nico Ryo.
Unfortunately, I'm on leave.
Of course!
I've been on the escape route for a long time.
Is that so?
I was just being careful.
Well, it was a coincidence.
It's a coincidence.
Let's go somewhere, Honda.
Chief, of course, I don't mind.
Oh, yeah.
I'm glad you came to Chiba to clean the bathroom.
Then, let's start cooking!
Oh, before that...
Thank you for waiting.
Hmm.
It's a good thing you came to clean the bathroom.
I brought it so that you wouldn't be in trouble if something like this happened.
Honda, it's a little rude to look like that.
Well, it's okay.
It's the chief's house.
Ryo, remember what to do.
Mr. Ryo, Mr. Honda.
Happy New Year.
Come on, sit down there.
Hello.
No, congratulations to all the group members.
Congratulations.
You're a good-looking man.
You look good in a Japanese dress.
Why are you talking about that?
If you're wearing such a nice kimono and coming to the New Year's party,
I'd like you to say something to me.
Honda, I'm happy to have a really good colleague.
You're happy to have a good colleague, right?
Senpai.
Ryo, stop being so annoying.
What did you say?
Well, it's New Year's Eve, so let's have fun.
I'm tired of New Year's dishes, so I'm going to make sukiyaki.
What do you think?
What kind of punishment are you doing?
You're eating Osechi food for New Year's Day.
This is the Japanese custom, right?
Chief.
But...
There's no such thing as Osechi food in the field.
I'm trying to make my husband rest during the New Year's holiday.
I'm putting in a lot of things that I feel like, and I'm not doing any New Year's work.
It's a Japanese old-fashioned wisdom to eat it.
But it's not something Ryo would do, is it?
Even if it's about Osechi, it's clear.
"Homumaki" is "yorokobu".
"Kuromame" is "mame ni hataraku".
"Ebi" is "engimono".
It all has a proper meaning.
What do you think of making it a sukiyaki from the New Year's Day?
New Year's Day in Japan is definitely Osechi!
It seems that the Osechi is ready, so it's better to serve it.
It seems so.
Mom, there's still some Osechi left, right?
Give me that.
Yes, sir.
Yay!
Here's Osechi!
We're going to make sukiyaki here, so you can eat Osechi there.
What?
Unsurprising!
Don't make it here!
Well, I just needed the Osechi to come down.
Here it comes!
All right, I'll serve it.
Thank you!
What?
...
I didn't notice any of your friends here...
That's because I had it all.
The rest is over there.
Oh!
Kuro-mame , Kobu-maki , Kamaboko . . .
The Osechi's comrade-in-arms, right?
The best three are still left.
The main character's non-existent hotpot dish is not good.
Looks delicious!
All right, it's been a long time.
Uh, uh, uh, chief!
Let's eat.
Itadakimasu!
Um, chief!
Huh? What?
If you don't mind, can I help you with your sukiyaki?
I've made your favorite hotpot dish.
I'll leave the sukiyaki to you until you finish eating.
All right.
I'll eat the hotpot, right?
Of course.
Good.
I was wondering how to get rid of the remaining hotpot.
It's perfect for cleaning up the mess.
Ryo-chan's stomach is as strong as a caterpillar.
That's right.
I'll introduce you to the one who's a little hurt.
More importantly,
I'm going to eat the hotpot.
Before you finish eating,
you should eat the meat.
Yes, yes.
I can finally eat sukiyaki.
Itadakimasu.
There's only one piece of meat!
Damn it!
What?
It's too bad.
I was faster.
No, I was faster.
Honda, aren't you?
Honda, I'm telling you.
No, no, no.
It's the same.
It's better to avoid meat when you're older.
It's for your health.
You're the one who ate the hotpot so much.
Don't do that!
You bastard.
Even if you get used to the meat, it won't work.
I'll see what you can do.
You two aren't children!
Oh, right.
What if the winner eats.
Winner?
How about a victory with a kalta, like a shogatsu?
Sounds interesting.
Sounds good.
There was a police kalta.
Police kalta?
I did it with my sister yesterday.
If you walk the police, you'll be in trouble.
Well,
"A moment of caution, and a lifetime of injury."
It sounds good, doesn't it?
Kalta like that is not interesting.
What do you think?
Let's do it with my kalta.
Did you bring kalta?
Yes.
I made it when I was on a holiday.
You're on a holiday?
Are you going to do a kalta game?
Are you not going to do it?
I'll do it.
I'll definitely win and you won't eat meat.
No, I'll be the last one to eat meat.
You're not going to do it.
I'll eat meat.
So, I'll go now.
Ah....
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to read it?
I can't read it.
Mr. Nakagawa, you go ahead.
I don't care who it is.
Read it now.
I understand.
"One day, I will eat a big pie from Reiko."
What did you say?
Oh, uh, no, I...
Yes!
Chief, you should write it down first.
What are you doing?
Idiot.
Next.
The name is definitely Ryotsu Kankichi.
What?
Take this!
I like this one the most.
It's just made by a senpai, but it's a mess.
You're so grumpy.
Chief Ohara, you're so grumpy.
What are you doing?
Yes!
It was right in front of you, but it was a shame.
My home, the temple of the Lone Hell.
Not yet.
There it is!
You're so naive, Chief.
You're a master of Karta.
You're not my enemy.
This Karta is a lie!
I made it myself, so you're definitely more advantageous!
You're going to make a mess because you lost?
No, it's not like that.
The handwriting is dirty and hard to read.
Only you know. It's unfair.
Chief, where are you going with the drawing?
I'm making it fair.
I'm going to make it messy.
What?
Are you going to make a mess all over the house?
It's fair to make a mess.
Okay, that's good.
We'll find Nakagawa to read it here.
When he finds it, he'll bring it and ask Nakagawa to check it.
Sounds interesting.
Okay, let's start.
Yes...
Nakagawa, the one who likes to do it.
The one who likes to do it.
What?
Stop!
All right!
I found it!
Damn it!
Kankichi Ryoz, the best in Kameari.
Honda, more insolent than Tora.
You did it, Ryo!
Pachinko, a big fever!
You're better at raising wages than increasing blood pressure, Chief!
Oh, my...
Ryo has 20 cards, and the leader has 19.
The remaining cards are two.
I can't believe I lost to Jyotsu.
I remember.
There's a toilet.
It's a school on the second floor.
Don't eat only the lunch box.
It's the toilet!
Damn it!
You!
Now I win!
Now I'm in.
You're using dirty tricks.
I'll give you the last card.
I'll reverse it.
This year.
You're so cowardly.
This time I win!
What?
It won't open.
You're so naive.
I put a lock on the book.
Damn it!
I lost.
You're so singular.
What?
There's no lock.
That's strange.
Does that mean the leader can't go in?
Alright!
Sorry.
You're so slow.
You went outside.
Huh?
Nothing.
What's that noise?
What's going on?
Damn it!
My book!
Chief, you're a bit late.
I won.
Well, Chief, you did a great job in the end of the year.
I did.
Well, next year's New Year's Day...
Next year's New Year's Day...
I won't let you win!
This is what happened this year.
Watch it again this year.
Here in Katsushikaku, Kameyari Park, Exit 1.
Your father's sick?
I'm sure he's just a little sick.
It's nothing serious.
He'll get better after a few days of sleep.
Unfortunately, I'm so moved.
I can't let him go through the housework.
Next time, "The Most Irresponsible Parent and Child in Japan."
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to the channel.
Even if it rains, tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye, let's wash our hands
I say goodbye to the unpleasant things
Oh yeah, let's live as we like
Let's live, there's something good
Outside the door, the sun is calling