One- stirringι
When you're watching TV
Make sure to lighten your room's lighting and try to stay away
It's the end of the rain
I walked looking back at the black place
I was walking
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk only the black place
I tried to walk only the black place
I was a child but everyone forgot
Politicians with a big face
And a blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
I can see everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What happened?
Special exhibition
Monalisa's big explosion!
I was beaten!
It's Kami-kaze Gout Dark!
It's here!
It's a girl's manga!
It's here again
Kami-kaze Gout Dark
This is the fifth one this month
Leave it alone!
It has nothing to do with us
He's only aiming for art
Senpai, Ryo
Idiot!
Chief, are you here?
That's a lie!
Ah!
As usual, we're playing with this!
It doesn't matter if it's a theft!
It doesn't matter!
It's a light joke!
Well, we're playing with this until today
Eh?
In order to solve this case
Specialists from the main office will be sent
We will all join the command
Eh?
There was this pattern before
It's always that pattern where perverts come out
I'm sure something strange will come again
Maybe, maybe, maybe that specialist is a special detective!
Well, well
I knew it
Hmm
The person who came from that detective didn't seem like a decent person
This time, it's okay
There was me, but I was in a very ordinary outfit
And my behavior was also decent
What kind of person are you?
I didn't hear your name, but you were probably called Profiling Deca
Profiling Deca?
What is that Profiling Deca?
Answer me
Huh?
Profiling is a method of extracting the criminal image from a small clue and dividing the criminal
For example, this tank
It looks like a normal plastic model
But in fact, it's actually a little reinforcement material
This shows that it was made of plastic before Gunpla
Therefore, the age is from the late 30s
to the late 40s
The finishing of each part is also very delicate and polite
But in fact, this kind of work is more suitable for a thick and rugged finger
And it has a slightly manly smell
Moreover, this is not in the bath for three days
That means the possibility of a single man is strong
Judging from the above information
This will start!
It must be yours!
Amazing!
I got it!
How about this?
This is Profiling!
Then you are!
Profiling Deca Aso!
Good, it's pretty good!
No, I can't be relieved
That's right, how many times have we met with painful eyes in this pattern?
I have a lot of work to do
Then let's start the investigation meeting immediately
The culprit has never been seen before
But there are several clues
First, five illustrations left at the crime scene
It's written in a political ink in Kento city
And this part is used in the screen tone "S-401"
Screen tone?
Screen tone is something like a sticker used by a manga artist
Exactly
In other words, the culprit can be assumed that he is a manga artist
So the culprit is a manga artist?
It's naive!
It is not a manga artist because he is a manga artist
What?
From what I saw, the culprit is a woman who wants to become a girl manga artist
Why can you say that?
This card
It smells like cosmetics
There is no man who paints and writes manga
And this name
This is clearly a girl manga
Now the culprit can know more about girl manga
Furthermore
If you're a professional, you can't draw other people's manga
Really?
Probably
OK, let's focus on the girl manga artist
All of you, go out
Yes
Wait a minute
What?
Do you have something to talk about?
Do you think the profiling is complete?
But now
The real profiling will start from now
Jyuteemu Jyuteemu Lali Poppi
Become a girl manga artist
What is this?
Have you ever heard the voice of a star?
The voice that whispers from beyond the night sky
It may be a message from him to you
It began after all
The voice that whispers from beyond the night sky
The profiling is complete
Aso, Ruri
Now, she has transformed into a beautiful girl
I'm a girl manga artist's daughter
Call me Ruri Rin
What?
What do you mean a girl manga artist's daughter?
A girl with beautiful face
I didn't expect I'd become such a pervert
How cruel
You should not say I'm bad
It's not such a problem
But it's okay
I'm sure he'll understand
The real face hidden under my glasses
No
You should say it's cuter to take off your glasses
Can I say that?
Yes, you can
I don't know what a girl manga is.
I guess we all have to transform.
What?
Jyuteemu Jyuteemu Lali Poppi
Let's be girls of the girl manga world together.
What is this?
Why are we dressed like this?
Because we have to understand the feelings of the criminal to do profiling.
Can you understand it with this?
The criminal's hobby this time is girl manga.
That's why we have to immerse ourselves in the world of girl manga.
What's wrong with Nakagawa and Reiko? They haven't transformed.
They are still in the world of girl manga.
I see.
Don't you understand?
Don't you think it's embarrassing to be dressed like this?
Right, chief?
But why do you look like a ballerina?
Because in girl manga,
the ballerina is the standard.
I see.
Is that so?
Mizusawa Megumi's writing like that, you know.
Well, I will teaching you a lot of world of girl manga from now on.
It's important that we create a mood for girl manga.
Let's build up this silly atmosphere with the theme of girl manga I made.
Then, let the music begin.
Music
Lululala Lulala
One step to the beat of spring
I will grow wings and fly away
No matter how hard it is
No matter how much tears I'm about to shed
I won't lose
Because I have that person
Lulululu Fight! Lululul
Fight! Lulululu
Everyone's voice is calling
Lululala That kind of smile
Is the best energy
See? It's like you're doing a girl manga, right?
Yes, it is.
No, it's not a girl manga this time!
Let's move on to the next step.
Yes.
No, it's definitely not.
That's right, Masumi.
One step to the beat of spring
I will grow wings and fly away
I can't believe I'm going out in this outfit.
Now, the next step is...
Everyone will be able to experience the world of girl manga.
How?
Don't worry.
In times like this, it's magic.
Chute M Chute M Lali Popping
Become the perfect home for the main character of a girl manga to live in.
What is he doing?
Somehow, I get the impression that...
he is in love with this girl.
Oh, it's done.
I knew it. I found the right way.
Don't mind the details.
But I think it's better to buy a house that is more luxurious than the main character of a girl manga.
Then I will buy a house that is my own.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Don't attack me!
Yes, everyone knows nothing about this.
Most of the readers are ordinary girls.
I'm just a normal girl.
If you make the main character rich,
you can't have a reader's sympathy.
I see.
Next is the main character's room.
Chutemu Chutemu Lali Poppin
Become the main character's room of a girl manga.
This is going to take a long time.
Me too.
I'll go with you.
Hey!
You're cheating, Reiko!
You ran away from me!
Calm down, senpai!
I'm surprised you made it this far.
I'm ready.
I'll show you the world of girl manga.
This way!
I knew for a long time that the prince on the white horse was gone.
But I believed that someday we would meet again.
No!
Why didn't you wake me up?
I woke you up many times.
I'll warm up the milk right away.
I don't need it anymore.
I'll go.
What a good idea.
I hope you can be a little more like a girl.
Ouch!
Are you all right?
What?
That was the meeting with that girl.
What a girl's manga scene!
Isn't it great?
What are you going to do with the bread I eat?
Don't worry about it.
I'm a girl manga.
I've been concerned about it since a while ago.
I feel that the shape of the car is strange.
Don't look at it!
I'm not good at making girl manga.
But, but...
What is this flower?
Where does it come from?
You don't get it, right?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Then we should make a world without bread and cars.
Once upon a time, there was a princess Jaja-uma.
Princess! Princess! Where did you go? Princess!
Princess!
You still haven't found her?
Yes.
You're in trouble for being a princess.
Oh, that!
Princess! I'm in trouble!
Please come back, princess!
Don't worry, uncle. I want to see how you live.
Are you alright?
You're a bad boy! Don't touch me!
You're a good princess.
Actually, I'm a young lord from the neighboring country.
How romantic! This is how you should act in your own time!
Hey, isn't this a little strange?
Normally, there are many ponds around the castle.
Besides, there's no use in being around the castle.
If you're around the castle, you'll be suspicious.
Don't worry about that. It's a girl's manga.
How long has this been around?
How many years has this been around?
If you don't know that, you won't be able to set up your clothes or background.
Shut up!
Then, let's go back to the original point and...
...be a ballet dancer!
Then, I'll announce the next character.
Asou Rurika, the heroine.
Yes.
As expected. As expected of Rurika.
The heroine.
The leading role.
The connection eyebrow.
That's right.
You.
What?
What's your response?
What's going on?
It's a mistake.
I don't believe it.
Coach, I can't do it.
It's only been a month since I started ballet.
Is that all you have to say?
Huh?
Well...
The practice starts in 10 minutes.
Don't be late.
I... I...
I'm sorry.
Hurry up, hurry up.
If you're late, congratulations to the coach.
Ouch!
The nails by the toe shoes.
Who did this?
Mr. Otoha.
I'm sure it's Mr. Otoha's doing.
I'm thinking that I have taken away the role of the opponent of Ms. Rurika.
Oh, what should I do?
Mr. Coach, please help me!
-Please come here! -That's great!
This is the essence of girl manga!
Hey, who is this Otoha-san?
The villain of the girl manga has always been Otoha-san.
Let's move on!
-You're still going to do it? -Enough!
What are you saying? The culprit hasn't been caught yet!
The culprit?
Kamikaze robber, Dark!
Oh...
He hasn't forgotten about the incident.
I guess he hasn't forgotten about the incident.
We can't stop researching girl manga until we arrest the culprit.
But if we keep this up, when will we be able to...
That's right! The camp!
-The camp? -The camp?
Let's study girl manga in the camp!
What? Ryo-sama is in a camp?
That's right. It was a week ago.
So, when is he coming back?
I haven't been able to contact him.
Huh?
What?
♪ Lu-la-la, lu-la-la ♪
♪ One step towards the summer ♪
♪ I'll jump into the world and become a doll ♪
♪ No matter how sad things may be ♪
♪ My heart is about to break ♪
♪ I won't let you down ♪
♪ Because everyone is here ♪
♪ La-la-la-la ♪
♪ Fight! Lu-li-lin ♪
♪ Your voice is smooth ♪
♪ Your bright smile is the greatest policy ♪
♪ Your voice is the biggest policy ♪
Ah, I have a dizziness...
He-Reiko?
You're back, Maria!
Ryo-sama?
Yes! I'll bring tea!
Hey, Reiko!
What happened between us and Luz?
Even Chief Ohara...
Huh?
Anything strange about me?
Oh, no...
What was this?!
Ouch!
It's because of the camp.
She's become a perfect woman.
Maybe she's more than me.
How about you, Kei? What's wrong?
Did you call me?
It's said that a person's dream is fleeting.
A person's dream is truly fleeting.
Kouchi!
It's okay. Until the day when the fire of life burns out,
I will continue to chase my dream.
Kouchi!
Even Kei...
Let's all make Kouchi's dream come true!
Yes!
Our dream is...
To catch Kamikaze Gout Dark, who is touching the world!
It seems that you haven't forgotten about your job.
As a result of thorough profiling,
I've come to understand what the culprit is thinking.
Everyone, let's transform!
Yes!
Jyutem! Jyutem! Narikopin!
Become Kamikaze Gout Dark!
What are you doing?
I'm changing.
Kamikaze Gout Dark has arrived!
Lord Ryo, what is that outfit?
Kamikaze Gout Dark is definitely dressed like this.
I guessed it from the results of the profiling.
Yes!
It can't be helped if you only know the outfit.
But you know what the culprit is aiming for next.
Yes!
Really?
It's amazing!
Because...
It's written on this sumikko.
The author often does it in shoujo manga, right?
Yes!
Then, let's go, everyone!
We'll catch him tonight!
Yes!
Everyone, fight!
Everyone, do your best.
I'll always be watching over you.
Nakakawa, are you okay?
Don't let him catch you, Maria.
It's just a play.
A play.
I see.
Even the bones of the bones are painted in shoujo manga.
Oh, no!
I'll go after the ace!
That's enough!
Thieves who stir up the world...
We won't forgive you!
We're arresting you today!
Oh, no!
He's a man, just like us!
Hey, didn't you say the culprit was a woman?
I've made a few mistakes, too.
It's a big mistake!
What?
It's not that bad.
You're always like that.
That's not true!
Anyway, an arrest of the culprit is ahead.
Look!
He's running away!
It's him!
Let me go!
Hey!
I managed to arrest him with your help.
It's brewing time for tea!
Yes!
Okay!
I'll be watching you forever.
I made some mint tea today.
Wow, it smells good.
It's hot.
Well, the important thing is the store.
Since then, it seems that everyone has stopped coming back from the world of girl manga.
What are you doing?
Well, this kind of thing often happens at this time of year.
Everyone, go back to your original place.
No, no, even if you say that,
Goodbye!
Wait! Do something!
It will be all right!
I'll be watching you forever.
Goodbye!
When the hot shower turns blue
Everyday is No Problem
I'm in the pillow, I'm feeling better
I love myself like this
Everyday is No Problem
My heart is beating on Monday
Monday, Monday, No Problem
Hey, Ryotsu!
Ah, what was it again?
I've only been remembering it until now, but...
Ah...
Oh, that's right!
Next time, when you've forgotten the Waza-Wive,
let's do it again!
There's a wall over there
I'm sure it's worth it
Everyone, let's go to our town
Thank you!