Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset in the middle of the river ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was joking with the captain of the boat ♪
♪ He laughed at me saying I was just a child ♪
♪ I can't help but laugh even when I'm in a good mood somewhere ♪
♪ The cityscape is the same as the bad mood ♪
♪ It's kinder than the night ♪
♪ The sun is setting because the crows are crying ♪
♪ There are many grilled chickens ♪
♪ In the building ♪
♪ I hear the sound of the crows' crows ♪
♪ The sound of the crows' crows ♪
♪ From the waterway of the Tongari city to Taishaku Station ♪
♪ The sunset is falling ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be different and it'll end too ♪
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ Because I was just a stupid fool ♪
What is this!?
Where am I!?
Have you noticed?
"Promo-Ya Ozaki"?
And the one at the store...
No way!
I don't have money!
I promised to give you a bonus for the first time!
And you're suddenly copying me!
Stop copying me!
No, I'm not talking about the bonus today.
I want you to lend me your power somehow.
My power?
Come to Kameari Shopping Street!
You want to borrow my power?
What do you mean!?
Look at this.
What?
This is...
The sales of Kameari Shopping Street in the last few months.
Hmm, this is a surprisingly good right-hand drive in Mt. Fuji again.
What are you talking about?
I'm busy with my life.
I know the cause.
This is it.
It's a large shopping mall built in the next town.
Most of my customers have taken it.
Thanks to that, Kameari Shopping Street has been completely empty...
It's daytime...
But the customers and passers-by don't come.
But it can't be helped.
It's cheaper there, and there are cinemas and bowling courses, so it's natural for customers to choose that place.
I know...
I know, but we can't back down here.
Please, Ryo-san, lend us your power!
Ryo-san!
Please bring the customers back to Kameari Shopping Street!
No, no, no, no, no!
Hey, that's our own business effort.
We're just trying to get things done!
We sold a lot of things.
We sold flyers...
We sold Ad Balloons...
But it didn't work at all.
If we don't do anything, the shopping mall will be destroyed!
So what does that have to do with me?
If it's business, it's Ryo-san.
You've succeeded many times with your power, guts, and ideas.
I want you to lend me your power, guts, and ideas at Kameari Shopping Street!
Please, Ryo-san!
I have no choice but to rely on you to win that shopping mall!
Please help us!
Even if you say that, I have a job too.
I see.
That's too bad.
I thought I'd be able to repay you for the sales.
Repay?
What?
I thought I'd be able to repay you for the sales.
Bonus?
Ryo-san!
Why didn't you tell me that sooner?
I'll leave everything to you!
The secret to success in business.
First, you have to do research on the enemy.
You have to look at the price and the service contents,
and you have to think about the service that goes up.
Otherwise, the customer will not be able to call you back.
I see.
Well said.
You're a great person.
Look at this radish.
All of them are much cheaper than those in the shopping mall.
Not only that.
Look at the arrangement of those products.
We have many customers here!
That's how they call in customers
that sell new products.
The same goes for the home appliances. This video is half the price of the shopping mall.
If you're going to sell at that price, you're selling at a fairly low price.
That's not all.
Welcome! Welcome!
By keeping the same business partner by your side, you're making them compete with each other.
I see. Even though they're in the same shopping mall, they're rivals.
They're rivals?
They're 20% cheaper than any other shopping mall.
They're stronger than I thought.
Don't worry. I'll take care of everything.
Welcome!
This is one way to attract customers!
I see.
Good morning!
What?
The question is how to attract customers.
Did you learn something new by eating something weird?
You idiot! I'm a genius!
Oh, right, Nakagawa. I need to talk to you.
I see.
General! The time has finally come!
The customers are coming from that disgusting shopping mall.
To get back their customers, the time has finally come!
I've been thinking of various ways to do it.
If I do as I say, I'll recover my business, and I'll make a big comeback!
So, I decided to start with the development of this shopping mall.
Look at this!
What?
It's a shopping mall.
Shopping mall?
Huh?
Ryo-san, this is the wrong location.
The next shop is a fish shop.
We're next to the Sangen!
No, you're not wrong.
From today, everyone will be moved to the place written here.
What?
What do you mean, Ryo-san?
Listen, sales can vary greatly depending on the location of the store.
What?
So, I decided to move the shop from a high-selling store to a place that stands out.
What does that mean?
Even though we're both friends of the same shopping mall, we're rivals in business.
If we're just friends, we can't do it for the sake of the shopping mall!
No way!
Shut up!
The people who are great are saying it, but without reform and growth, this is a decisive event!
What is this?
I wonder if it's okay to do this.
If this happens, we won't have time to move, right?
If you're frustrated, the sales will increase!
Work hard for the business!
Senior!
We've finished moving the shop!
Okay!
Then, let's continue with the second reform plan!
R-Ryo-san, what is this?
Can't you tell?
It's an old TV, video, and air conditioner.
That's not it.
I'm asking why you brought me here.
Of course I know.
From now on, you're going to make new sales using what you have here.
What?
If you choose the materials from here, it won't cost you anything, so the ultimate cost is down.
For example, TV-type rice cooker, cooler-type rice cooker, washing machine-type rice cooker.
You can't buy these anywhere.
Will they sell?
Anyway, make and make original electronic products!
That's ridiculous.
I'm sorry.
Ryo-san, let's go home!
We can't do this anymore!
Idiot!
If you don't catch fish here, you won't sell anymore!
B-But...
Stop talking gibberish and fish!
See!
This is the new costume for Kameari Shopping street.
Wow!
From now on, you'll wear this to attract customers.
Men will definitely be in line!
Are we going to wear it?
Welcome!
Idiot! Who told you to wear it?
It's for the girls at the part-time job!
It's almost done.
Are you sure it's going to work?
It's fine. Believe me.
Once it's done, we'll be able to go around the shopping mall.
What the hell is this?
What happened? Why aren't any customers coming?
What happened?
T-Tenjo, this is bad!
What's wrong?
Look at this! The Kameari Shopping Mall is in a terrible state!
What?
I can't believe it! It's so intense!
Welcome!
It's cheap! It's cheap!
All 5,000 yen each!
This is the original, with a refrigerator!
It's a set with a DVD with an electronic range!
It's a great deal!
Ma'am, this is amazing!
The Kameari Shopping Mall with ear cleaning!
We have a washing machine that can wash plates!
We have the cheapest store!
Welcome!
The traditional sweets are delicious!
The legendary taiga!
Welcome!
Idiot! It's impossible!
It's cheaper than ours!
For unlearning
What are you talking about?
Yes, I didn't say it!
I hope I can remember it well!
Welcome!
The Kameari Shopping Mall!
Great!
The Kameari Shopping Mall with ear cleaning!
Welcome!
This is the Kameari Shopping Mall!
I'll look further and more EAT!
How did the shopping street that was in danger get so busy?
I want to get to know the secret of that.
Then, let's ask Mr. Ryo-tsu Kankichi who planned this renewal.
Mr. Ryo-tsu, what was the secret of success?
Well, it's a company secret, so I can't answer it.
This time I will tell you a special secret.
That is...
1. A bright smile for people.
2. A good business effort.
3. A response to everyone's hope.
4. A really cheap item.
5. Always by your side.
You too, let's go to the Kameyari Shopping Street!
Um, this...
He is the candidate for our Kameyari Shopping Street.
He is fighting day and night to protect the peace of the earth and develop the shopping street.
I see. So he is the popular local hero.
Exactly.
He is doing different attractions every day so we can't get bored.
Shopping street that make us want to come again and again.
This is my ideal shopping street!
I understand.
With Mr. Ryo-tsu's bold and wonderful idea, Kameyari Shopping Street is reborn.
That's right.
Everyone watching TV,
Kameyari Shopping Street is waiting for you.
Pramoya Ozaki, your shop's sales are back.
What's going on?
Well, I was a little sick last week...
No need to say.
Pramoya is moving to the next to the public toilet.
W-wait!
This week will be full of sales.
Please give me a little more time...
Wooooaah!
Wagashiya and Sakane are on sale, so they'll be next to the public toilet.
Futonya is in good condition.
Hana and Kamputsuya are moving to the end of street one by one.
Mr. Ryo, this is too much.
That's right, the things we sell are different.
Idiot!
You are the one who make a plan!
If you want to survive, use your head a little bit more.
Okay?
I understand.
You're so cocky.
You're so generous.
What are you doing?
What's the answer?
Yes, sir!
Now we have a lot of money and a lot of bonuses.
No!
It's terrible!
What? What's wrong?
Come on!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I don't know.
Why did he suddenly disappear?
Mr. Ryo, I know.
The shopping mall people are...
What?
Well, well, thanks to your daily support,
we're holding a Super-Fukubi-ki.
You can get a 1,000 yen discount
and get a car that you like from Genki-Washizukami.
Genki-Washizukami?
A car that you like?
What are you going to do, Ryo-san?
We have a customer who came back,
but he was taken away again.
You're right.
Mr. Ryo is usually careless.
That's right.
He was in a good mood
because the customer came back.
What?
Is it my fault?
Anyway,
we have to think about
how to make a bonus
or how to make a bonus.
As soon as you guys got in a pinch,
you suddenly gave me a hand.
I got it.
I'll definitely get the customer back!
I'll get the customer back!
What should I do?
Should I run away?
No, I can't.
If I run away here,
the guy will throw me out.
However,
I don't have any other choice.
I can't prepare
a luxurious product
to compete with the same Fukubi-ki.
In general,
there is no such thing as a normal Fukubi-ki.
Hmm?
This is it!
What's up, Mr. Ryo?
You called everyone.
You guys
want to rebuild this shopping street, right?
Yes.
Well,
you want to make it a shopping street
that has a lot of customers
and makes a lot of money, right?
That's right, but...
Are you prepared
to do anything for that?
What are you talking about?
That's obvious.
All right,
don't forget that word.
This is the next strategy.
What's that?
It's the same as that.
You're so naive.
There's no way
I'm going to make a Fukubi-ki
that can be found anywhere.
What do you mean?
In other words,
this is what I mean.
What?
This is the one.
Isn't it enough?
You see this?
With this lottery machine,
the Raspberry Ghost Game is complete.
Our customers will return immediately.
But...
With only this...
Right...
After all,
we should decide about the winning item.
You've left me no choice.
I'll let you win
that luxurious prize
that won't let you get lost over there.
Listen closely.
Massage, massage, massage.
Hey!
It ain't a joke.
Who would do such a thing!
You said you'd do anything for it.
I told you so!
You'll keep your promise!
Don't worry! We'll win!
Again!
Hi, Mezamashii Investigation Team!
Today we're at Kameari Shopping Street, where a huge lottery is held.
We're at Kameari Shopping Street, where a huge lottery is held.
Now, I'd like to talk to the general producer, Mr. Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
Mr. Ryo-tsu, you've come up with an amazing idea!
Of course! It's my job to think for the customers!
I see. But I've heard that you just increased the lottery.
Don't worry! A huge lottery is important, no matter what you say!
I've prepared a special prize for you!
And that prize is...
This!
In this lottery, the shopkeeper will receive a ball,
and when the ball comes out, they'll give you all the products of the shop!
I didn't know you had such a big plan!
You're a real man, Mr. Ryo-tsu!
I'll do it when I'm playing the game, Mr. Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
I can't hear you.
Now, let's get started!
The shopkeeper, please enter the lottery machine!
Stop!
I told you to remember!
Now, the Kameari Shopping Street Super Lottery Competition will begin!
Here's the first customer!
Thank you very much!
Please pull the lever!
Okay!
Oh, what a shame!
I'll give you a pocket tissue and a discount ticket!
Okay, next customer, please come to the lever!
Congratulations!
Please take the sashimi!
We still have a lot of products!
Oh, no! The light!
Are you okay?
No! The ramen shop this time!
Don't fall! Do your best!
Damn it! Why do I have to do this?
You have to do this!
Oh, I can't believe I'm going to be like Mr. Ryo-san!
That's right! I'll survive after all!
Yes!
Here's the package and discount!
What? You said you'll get all the products at the shop, but you're not coming at all!
I'm sorry!
I'm afraid they won't come out soon.
What are you thinking?
If no one is coming out, it's like a scam.
Alright, if you're going to do it, I have an idea!
Now is the time for the reverse turn!
Turn to the other side!
Whoa! It's a reverse turn!
Don't fall! Be careful!
Next is the high speed turn!
Turn at full speed!
Stop!
Damn you, Ryo!
You can't beat me!
I'll help you.
Come on.
Come on!
If you're going out alone, you have to trust the customers!
I won't let you get out!
What's wrong?
This doesn't belong here!
I lost half my time!
Enough!
Next is the reverse turn!
Turn!
Mentally weak!
Don't waste your energy!
I don't want to do it again!
That's right.
Wh... What?
Agh! Run!
Please take a look. The super large generator has collapsed and the Kameari shopping street has become a city of ruins.
That's...
Ryo-san!
What are you doing? Aren't you crazy?
Originally, Ryo-san was thinking strange things.
That's right! That's right! I should have done it normally from the beginning.
What? Is it all my fault? These ignorant people!
Shut up! Securit!
You were doing well until the middle, right?
It doesn't make sense until the middle!
I'll double the money you've earned so far!
I don't like it!
After the rain, like someone is calling me
I walked while looking back
I reached out to my mother
I felt a strange feeling at that time
That's why I tried to walk on the black side of the Akedogai's rail
Everyone was a child at one time
But everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
Let's go!
There's a Kameari over there
There must be a Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Let's go!
There's a Kameari over there
There must be a Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
What? You're going to leave me with a new store?
Good! I'll do it!
I'll go to the Kameari!
You're so old!
Let's go to my town!
If you don't come, I'll leave!
I'll do it!
Let's go!
Everyone, come to my town!
Let's go, children!
Let's go!
Everyone, come to my town!
Everyone, come to our town!
Let's go!
Thank you!