When you watch TV
Make the room a little brighter and try to leave
"The End of the Rain"
Just like someone calling
I walked looking back
"Please give me your hand"
I felt that strange feeling at that time
So, I'll give you a rope
Just a black one
Just walk
with me
I saw it
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There's a wall over there
Come on, everyone
To our town
Thank you!
"The End of the Rain"
Three letters.
Spring break!
Amazing!
What are you doing?
It's a finger print.
I write on my back and hit it.
Oh, you're really good at it!
Huh?
Let me try it.
Can you write in kanji?
Yes, I can write it well.
Stand sideways, left and right.
Got it?
Two letters.
Well, it's a little difficult.
It's a character called "Yu-tsu"
Don't write such a number of letters!
Even if I write it in front of you,
I don't think you can read it.
I see.
Hey, Koran!
Then, Reiko will try it this time.
I'll give it a try.
What? Me?
Nagagawa, tell me the most difficult kanji in the world.
Well, how about a rose or a lemon?
Well, Reiko is good at kanji.
Say, "Baby, how are you?"
I don't think she'll understand.
It's decided.
I'll write it, Reiko.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What?
Oh!
Don't tickle me anymore!
I'm not tickling you.
I heard that you don't like hands.
That's right.
I got it.
Then I'll write it quickly.
Quickly?
Ah!
Hahaha!
You tickled me!
Stop it, Ryo!
Stop it!
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
After all, Ryo will give it a try.
Don't write kanji.
If you get it right, you'll get 100 yen.
Okay, Reiko?
It's 100 yen.
Hmm...
Well...
"Ba"
Next is "ga"
"Baga"
"Baga"?
It's your line.
Ah!
Boss!
"Baga" is written on it!
That's how you should self-awe.
Damn you, Boss.
"Panic the mobile phone!"
Here.
It's a mobile phone, Boss.
It's not mine.
This is not my Chacomero.
It's not mine either.
This isn't it. This isn't it.
This isn't it.
This isn't it either.
How many do you have?
So this is it?
Even in a place like that?
Whose cell phone is ringing?
You guys can live without that.
Hello?
I see. I'll just buy some sauce for the yakiniku.
Then...
You too?
No, I was asked to buy some stuff on my way home.
I was asked to buy some stuff on my way home.
Look at this.
Even a general public's cell phone is a must.
I'm glad you're here.
I feel like I've become an important person.
People all over Japan are in a provide cell phones.
But still, you think its a bad thing because you don't have any?
You are an Fortnite?
What do you say?
I hate the...
The manner of those people who don't care about your cell phones!
I thought you didn't ever treat your cell phones as an excuse!
If you don't like it, you can have cell phones without your cell phones forever only.
Oh, that's fine.
I don't mind if I don't have those.
I don't mind if there's nothing else.
You said it, chief.
Don't forget that word.
You don't have to say it.
They're fighting again.
It's like a fight between two children.
The chief gave me a cell phone?
I told you I don't need a cell phone.
I said I don't need a cell phone.
What's wrong with you?
I brought it because you're a good golfer.
I said I don't need it.
With this, Daisuke can always hear his grandpa's voice.
It's pathetic.
It's just a day.
But it's not a bad thing.
That's right.
I looked into it.
I heard that you had a problem with your cell phone.
There were many stories.
One of them is that a man who was injured when he went out for a walk at the age of three called for help.
Another one is that a man who was trapped in a sauna box at home was called to the police and was saved.
What?
Did that happen?
Yes.
It's ringing.
What should I do?
Well...
You don't know how to use it, so don't have a cell phone.
I just forgot.
Well...
Press here, chief.
Here?
Yes.
This is Ohara.
Here you go.
It's not a police radio.
Shut up!
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Of course you can.
Oh, Daisuke.
What?
Yes.
It's from your granddaughter, Daisuke.
I can tell by looking at your face.
I see.
See you.
Oh, I forgot to bring a toy.
Oh, right.
Can you tell me your phone number?
If you register with a short-term registration, you can connect with one button, right?
Yes.
My number is...
Mine is...
Um...
090...
Well, I'll go to the library.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Have a good trip.
Bye-bye.
He finally went away.
Well...
Ryo, what is this?
I was asked by Sakonji to make it for me at 20,000 yen.
I can't make it at the place you are.
Oh, I see.
It's such a delicate task, you know.
It's mine.
Hello?
It's me.
It's me, too.
Chief!
What?
He just left!
I forgot.
Ryo, tell him that I'm not here,
and don't play with him,
or make a mess!
I-I didn't do that!
Do it seriously!
See you later.
I was surprised.
I didn't have to call from nearby.
Oh, right.
Huh?
This time, it's my turn.
Yes!
Ah, Chief!
Reiko.
Did you get the water for the planter before the launch?
Yes, I got it this morning.
I see.
Then that's good.
Thanks, Jia.
What did you say?
Did you get the water for the planter?
Huh?
This time, it's mine.
Yes, I'm Nakagawa.
I forgot to tell you.
I'm leaving at 4 o'clock.
I'll call you later.
See you later.
He said he'd be back by 4 o'clock.
He keeps calling me for all sorts of things.
He's like a chimpanzee who just learned how to play the trumpet.
Again?
Hello?
You idiot!
I just said what I had to say!
Don't make such a loud noise!
You don't have to watch,
just bite it and you'll know.
Got it?
Do it seriously, Ryo!
Hey!
Huh?
What?
Ryo?
Are you...
What, Ryo?
Ryo, aren't you leaving?
What?
What's with you?
Well, what do you want?
I...
I want my hat.
What?
I just...
I want my hat, and...
I want my hat!
The End
Thanks to you, I've been able to learn a lot.
Ah, then, please take care of Hideo-kun.
Dear,
even though you have a phone,
you don't have to spend money on your cell phone, do you?
N-No, it's a useful thing, so I just...
The phone is much more expensive than the phone bill.
Please don't lose it or lose it.
It's said that you can be used by a stranger and be charged a surprising amount.
I know.
I'm not that kind of person.
Well, then, I'll go check on him.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Ah, finally I'm out.
Well then, let's continue what happened yesterday.
Oh, the manager has forgotten about me.
I'm the one who's being scolded every day.
Look.
Ah, it's Bagryu! It's me!
Where are you now?
What?
I'm practicing in the North Pacific.
Ah, no, it's nothing special.
I thought I'd make a long phone call.
Oh, by the way,
Mr. Hondara said he was going to Australia for training.
Hehehe.
Oh, Mr. Hondara!
What are you doing now?
What?
Training the one who has the guts?
Ah, no, it's nothing special.
Ah, Professor Tondemo!
What country are you in now?
Eh?
Are you heading to the North Pole in a dog's tail?
No, it's nothing special.
Hello, this is Ryo speaking.
Oh, no, no.
It's nothing special.
What a strange person.
Ah, so he's in Australia.
I never heard of it.
Where are you from?
From Canada.
I just spoke with him,
he doesn't understand the meaning of the word "you".
No one understands it in his heart.
Hum .
Ah, who's there?
What?
Who?
No one.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, it's Ryo.
If you say ban, it's ban.
Watch carefully.
Yes, yes.
Now, let's finish it before the chief comes.
The eyes of a blacksmith are life.
Ryo-tsu.
Yes?
Where's the cell phone?
It's on the desk over there.
There? Where?
Where? On the desk of the chief.
Huh?
It's not there.
That's strange. I'm sure it's on this desk.
Ryo-tsu.
What are you doing while working?
I was looking for it.
Well, that's...
It's not that.
Where did you get my cell phone?
Huh?
That's my mistake.
It wasn't here from the start.
It was on the phone earlier.
Don't lie to me.
I was so busy making it that someone took it out.
You didn't notice, did you?
Listen, Ryo-tsu.
Find my cell phone somehow.
I'll pay for what you spent in the meantime.
Huh?
No way!
What?
This is no joke.
Just who on earth brought it out?
Huh?
Hmm...
"Wife's Theater: The Red Crescent of Love"
Yes, yes.
Yes, this is Ohara.
Oh, no, Chief.
What?
You said you're going to say goodbye to your wife, didn't you?
Hey, who are you?
Hello?
I'm the head of the club.
Ohara-kun?
Hello?
Get married.
Huh?
I've liked you since the first time we met.
I love you.
I-I see.
Even if you suddenly say that, I have a wife and a cat.
That's not a problem.
What a man.
Oh, no, no.
We're both men.
If you don't marry me, I'll die.
What?
I can't live without you.
You are my everything.
Ohara-kun, you can't be too hasty.
I'll break it up.
I-It's my phone.
Huh?
My phone.
Can't you understand?
Come out right now!
Yes, sir?
Hello?
We're very happy to have you.
What's going on?
What the hell is this?
Hmm, Kasue!
Hey, can you hear me?
I don't know who you are, but I want you to return my phone!
Ah, damn it! It's cut off!
Yes, this is the station before the park.
Oh, it's you.
What?
What the hell is going on?
Who was that woman earlier?
You're about the same age as your own daughter!
What are you talking about? I can't remember anything!
Yes, this is the station before the park.
Ah, it's the director.
Hey, you!
Hello, this is Ohara.
What did you say?
You can't be early.
I'm glad you're fine, but...
Yes!
I'm sorry!
Please wait a moment.
Director, this is Hiromi.
What?
Oh, excuse me.
What's wrong, Hiromi?
What? I'm moving to Alaska?
I have a phone call.
It's a prank!
I'm not saying I don't like you.
I'm just wondering why you're getting married.
Married?
Hello, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no!
This is a different story.
I'm going to be friends with you from now on.
No, no, I mean, director!
Director!
Are you getting married with the director?
No, no, no, no!
What?
Akki!
Listen, Ryo-tsu.
No matter what you do, no matter what happens,
you have to get my phone back.
If you fail, you're fired!
I'm fired!
What should I do if I fail?
Damn it.
Oh, it's the director again.
Huh?
It's the phone that's gone.
Hello?
What's going on?
Here it is again.
Number 70, Akki!
Start!
Jyan-jyan-baribari!
Everyone, get ready!
Let's go!
Next, number 18...
This is the pachinko hall in front of the station.
Congratulations!
Is the director's phone in front of the station?
No, it's not.
Who's calling me on my phone?
It's very funny.
They're so funny.
What?
Seriously, why?
Ah!
Everyone is mad!
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Give me back my phone!
If you can hear me, just reply!
Say something!
Ishiaki-imo.
This season, this time, over there!
Hey!
Did anyone with a cell phone pass through here?
Cell phone?
No, no one passed through.
That's not possible!
Someone passed through!
I'll call the police if you lie!
This sound...
It's the sound of the third road construction!
Wait! Don't move!
Damn, it cut off!
It should be around here.
Hey, I can't find you!
If this happens, I'll call you from here!
If you hide, you should be able to hear the call!
Hey! Where did you hide?
Come out quietly!
Give it back!
My bag!
Thief!
What?
Where is the thief?
Hey!
You!
Police!
Are you going to let me go?
I'll kill you!
Thank you very much.
You're a nice guy, Marisa.
It's amazing.
No, I'm just kidding.
Because of the usual patrolling, or rather, because the manager's cell phone was stolen...
Hey!
Yaa!
Ah!
Hey, wait up!
I can't help it.
Come and take me to the police station!
I'm begging you, Marisa!
Oh...
Wait up!
Stop!
I'm going to get you!
Damn you!
So annoying!
You're not getting away!
Hey!
Give me back my phone!
You made me work so hard...
I managed to get it back.
That dog...
He ate everything!
Well, anyway, I got the chief's phone back.
Yes!
Oh, Senpai!
Ryochi, huh?
Where are you?
Did you get my phone back?
Senpai, where are you now?
Eh?
Behind the escape room?
There are so many things that have disappeared from the escape room.
Oh, my phone!
My shoe, too.
The chief's favorite, the bath.
It was all the dog's doing.
But I managed to solve it safely thanks to my contribution.
What is this?
The police's secret?
Ryochi, show me the police's secret.
It's not a "hah" !
Just show me.
Yes, it's over here.
Ryochi!
You idiot!
Here it is!
Come to think of it, I haven't found it since about a month ago.
I couldn't find it.
You're a police officer.
You're not keeping your important notebook.
What are you doing?
But the dog is the bad guy.
That's why you're playing with this toy.
But...
But not.
You don't have to pay this month.
No way!
Wake up clock
Kick it
My little finger hurts
D-d-d-dash
When I draw my eyebrows
I'll dash to the station
D-d-dash
The main train
I'm sleeping on my dad's back
This week too
I'm doing my best
Even though I can't do anything
It's almost 5 o'clock.
10 o'clock
I love myself like this
No problem every day
My heart is beating
Monday
Monday Monday
Go Go Go
Chief!
I'm Ryo Tsukaguchi
I'll be your tour conductor this time
Hot springs, food, and beauty
I will definitely deliver a journey that you will be satisfied with
Next time, "Tabimakase Onsen Tour"
Thank you for watching