bazuko
When you watch TV
light up your room and make sure you don't get so far
it's as if someone is calling
after the rain
After the rain, I walked while looking back
I was drawn to the gacha
At that time, I felt a strange feeling
So I walked only in the black part of the Akedo Gai Tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgot
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
Everyone can meet everyone
Ah, there it is
There is a wall
Ah, there is a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Circus Symphony
It's a nice day, senior
Autumn with high sky and good night
That's right
Tomorrow's race will be 2-3
But it was 6-7 just now
My wild instincts were fluttering
6-7 is not a good horse
Hmm, you're pretty good, senior
Oh?
What is it?
It's a circus
Circus?
Yup, I used to come here often when I was young
It looks interesting, let's go
There's another Higashiyama
Hey, hold on
I'm so dizzy just thinking about it.
Who's there? What are you doing?
Come here.
Senpai, wait!
Ouch!
Be careful, Honda.
Sorry.
Ahaan.
Why are you making such a weird noise?
You're so rude.
Because Senpai...
Ahaan.
What did I do?
Look closely.
What? Senpai, what happened?
That means...
It's a snake!
It's just a snake.
This is a snake-shaped ball.
This is no time to joke.
I'm going to eat you!
No!
Ouch!
Come on, now.
I'm saved.
I'm short of life.
Huh?
Could it be...
Honda-kun?
Huh?
Well, yeah, but...
You know Honda?
It's me.
I was with him in junior high school.
Ryuhei Iwabuchi.
What?
Now that you mention it...
You remembered me.
Long time no see.
Boss!
A weird guy was wandering around in the tent.
Well, don't worry about it.
He's my friend.
Oh, really?
I thought he was a member of the Haraguro Company.
Excuse me.
Huh?
I'm sure your father was the leader.
My father died last year.
So I'm the one who took over this circus.
Oh, and Tachibana-shi didn't come to my room.
Since I was in elementary school, I've been doing well in gymnastics.
People in the girls' community all say "Kya! Kya!"
But I'm always jealous of them.
I've been on stage since I was five.
But I always went on trips when there was a school business.
I didn't go to school that much, so I didn't have many friends.
Hmm...
By the way, I was just wondering...
How's the Haraguro Company?
Huh?
Uh...
Haraguro Company?
It's a non-popular back-end financial company.
As expected of a policeman.
I'll apologize for lying to you, but...
The business is very tough here.
There's a debt from the Haraguro Company.
A debt?
Hmm...
Unlike when we were kids,
I don't think kids these days can even think of circuses.
It depends on whether the company will do well next time.
Huh?
If we fail,
this circus will be gone.
No way!
This circus will be my third one.
There are people who have been working since I was an old man.
I want to do something for them.
But I can't get more customers.
But...
But?
No, it's nothing.
Mr. Ryuhei?
Oh, sorry.
Customer?
It's okay, Sae-chan.
This is my classmate from junior high school.
Mr. Honda and his senior, Mr. Ryotsu.
Oh, hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sae Shirayuri,
Oh, nice to meet you.
Would you like to see some practice?
I'll show you a new technique that I'll show you at the next workshop.
Oh, I really want to see it.
Right, senior?
Yeah.
Is it really okay to start from such a high place?
Shut up and watch it.
Oh, I'll show you.
Let's do it, Sae-chan.
Okay.
It's over!
Oh, my God.
Amazing!
You're good.
You can't do it if your two people don't do it perfectly.
That's right.
It's amazing.
Why can't you get any customers even though it's so amazing?
There's not enough publicity.
I know that, but the cost is quite...
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Okay, Honda.
All the Kameari members are gathering.
I'll save this circus.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Iwabuchi Circus is starting to operate.
We're waiting for you.
Wait!
If you don't come, you won't be able to get in.
From 2 p.m. today, at the special venue of Minamisenju Kasenjiki,
there will be an exciting opening.
Please come and see.
Okay.
The customers are gathering.
It's very effective.
They are coming.
It's been a long time since I've been in such a big place.
Brother, it's more successful than I thought.
If you keep this up, the president will make fun of you.
I'll disturb you because I don't care.
Ladies and gentlemen ramen.
Please enjoy the circus!
Welcome to Iwabuchi Big Circus.
It's showtime!
Please enjoy the circus.
It's gone.
Huh?
Yes.
Iwabuchi Big Circus
"Ryo's
""
"It's a success, Ryo-chan."
"I can't believe you're letting me do the advertising."
"I hope things go well in the town of Senju."
"I'm glad to hear that."
"It's okay if you can take this."
"What?"
"What? What?"
"I don't have to worry about it. Nothing's wrong."
"Thank God."
"I just worried."
"I know."
"No matter how good this ad is, the main character's kids will never have customers!"
"Ryo-chan, leave the rest to Mr. Sae."
"Yeah, I will."
"Take your time to rest."
"Okay."
"See you!"
Are you okay, Ryuhei?
Thank you, Sae-chan.
You're welcome.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Those two seem to love each other.
If they don't, they won't be able to act so lively.
I'm jealous.
You're a great actor.
You don't need to worry about this.
Thank you, Senpai.
Ryo-chan does good things sometimes.
Everyone, thank you for today.
Hello.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll leave it to you, Ryo-san.
Leave it to me.
I hope we can pay back the debt for those people.
If that old man says that the circus will be gone,
I'll be shocked.
Ryo-chan, you're talking too much.
You're so noisy.
Okay, next.
Next.
Ryo-chan!
Yes.
I'm at the arena.
Okay.
What?
Senpai, something bad has happened.
The two snake-like snakes of the circus
are entangled in Shibamata's Tora-san Castle.
What?
Ryo-chan, the circus bears are running around Nikkou Kaido.
What's wrong?
The circus's master, the circus monkeys, has attacked the Kanabashi Line!
What's going on here?
Who did this?
What are we going to do?
Even if we have a customer, this is...
We can't open the circus at this rate.
What should we do, Mr. Ryuhei?
Mr. Ryuhei!
I've been talking about it...
Are you going to say you refuse?
Yes, I'm sorry.
The world's best Boroshoi circus is trying to scout you in a desperate situation.
Think again.
If you join Boroshoi Circus, you can compete with the famous people from all over the world.
It's a chance to become the world's best Ryuhei.
I beg your pardon.
I don't think so.
The Iwabuchi Circus that my father left for me is more important than the Boroshoi Circus in the world.
Please understand.
Yes.
Mr. Shibuchinski says this.
"I'm in Japan by the end of this week, so if you change your mind, come visit me anytime."
He says he has the appropriate contract money.
Thank you very much.
If I have that contract money...
I won't be able to participate in this circus.
Mr. Shibuchinski should be in Japan tonight.
Mr. Ryuhei!
Boss!
Anyway, we have to split up the animals that escaped and catch them.
That's the only way.
Ryuhei is right.
We don't have time to waste.
Mr. Ryotsu!
Let's go, everyone!
Yes!
Okay, let's go!
Ryuhei!
Mr. Ryuhei!
You want some?
"I don't know what you're talking about. Your priorities are only human."
"You think you're so great, aren't you? You're an ordinary person!"
I can't let Lucas go on like this.
Senpai!
Be careful!
Leave it to me!
I'll catch the monkey from here!
Fish on!
It's fun!
I'm so excited!
It's a waste if they turn into bears!
I'm not saying anything stupid!
I'm going to do it!
Come down here, Pochi!
Help!
Stop!
If you don't listen to me, I'll make you a thief!
Last night, a monster escaped from the Iwaguchi Circus,
which was on the way to Minami-senju.
The footage you are seeing is a terrible story.
The animal escaped from the Iwaguchi Circus,
and it became a mess.
Perhaps the customers are not going to come back anymore.
It went well, Aniki.
The president will praise me.
Damn it! Who the hell did this?
This is the badge of Haraguro Industry.
Haraguro Industry?
He got away, Aniki!
We have to run!
Ryo, over there!
Don't let him get away!
He's gonna get away!
Damn it!
There!
Ready...
Set...
Let's go, Ryo!
Fire!
I'm counting on you, Ryo!
Ryo, hang in there!
They got rid of them easily.
I heard they were hired by Haraguro Industries.
But even if we catch the culprit,
if we cause such a scene,
we can't get anything back.
That's too bad.
Look, Senpai!
Here! Here!
This is the circus where the animals escaped!
I've never seen such a ghastly circus.
Senpai!
It's a great show!
The animals' performance was a great advertisement!
You did it, Saori!
I don't care.
No, I mean...
Now, we're gonna be busy!
Oh, no!
Ryuhei-san's not here!
What?
I'm so jealous!
We've got so many guests,
but we can't show them
the main stage of Ryuhei and Sae!
What should we do, Senpai?
Sae-chan, don't you know
where Ryuhei-san went?
I don't know.
I'm not ready to go there.
You'd better stop thinking about the guests.
There are so many guests
coming to see our circus.
We need to finish this.
Huh?
But...
But...?
Oh, that's nothing.
That's right!
Ryuhei will be here!
Until then, we'll connect the site with him!
Yes! Yes!
"Aizawa Land"
Thanks, new captain.
No one can win the circus.
That's right, Ryuuhei.
Way to go!
You're being too mean, Ryuuhei.
Sorry.
She's not here yet.
Are you sure you're okay, Senpai?
Shut up and wait, Ryuhei will be here.
Oh no! Kei from Ippon Zuna...
What happened?
What's wrong?
Sorry, I can't stand up.
I'm in such a bad situation.
What should we do?
There's no other team for Ippon Zuna.
Okay, I'll do it.
What?
Dotsan!
Are you okay, Ryo?
Don't worry.
I learned this when I was a kid.
That's good.
Now you're the best Ryuhei in the world.
This is harder than I thought.
Are you okay, Ryo?
It's a real fight, isn't it?
Ryo!
What are you doing, Ryuhei?
I'll do it with my Ryo.
Ryo!
Ryo...
Ryuhei!
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
The Circus Flower-shaped Air Blanket Show is finally starting!
Mr. Ryuhei!
I'm sorry. I thought you'd come.
Sorry for being late.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm sorry.
Please make sure this story never happened.
Mr. Iwabuchi!
As I thought,
Ms. Sae is the best partner for the Circus Flower-shaped Air Blanket Show!
It's beautiful and elegant.
It's like two people playing classical music together.
Circuses are like a great symphony where each person's power is played together.
Circus symphony?
That's exactly right.
Yes!
No matter how hard it is, we can't help but hesitate.
Sae is here, everyone is here,
the guests are here,
and we're here.
This is my happiness.
Dad, please watch this.
I will make this circus the best circus in the world with everyone.
Sae says,
"As I thought"
These kids sure are really cute.
This is my Christmas gift.
This is my gift?
This is it.
I love you all.
I love you?
♪ I'm having a good time, but I'm feeling gloomy and gloomy ♪
♪ I'm still frustrated about the work that I've been doing ♪
♪ I'm frustrated, so I'll get over it quickly ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ When the hot shower is blue ♪
♪ I'm recovering well in the sleeping pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating, it's a Monday ♪
♪ No problem, no problem, no problem ♪
Fly in the sky and deliver tacos?
I see. This way, it doesn't take much time and you get a lot of work.
What's this black thing?
Why are you disturbing us?
Next time on Fly in the Sky, Delivery of Tacos
It's not a "sudako," it's "tacos"!
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a wall ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!