"I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to make it to the next level."
When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away.
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'm not sure if I'm going to make it to the next level.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Come to me, you poor thing!
Look at the red clouds burning.
I'm not sure if I'm going to make it to the next level.
You get it, don't you?
If you do, then be quiet and follow me.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
To be continued
Where are we, Ophiuchus?
Huh?
Did Ryo-chan buy another phone?
Pe-he-he.
Ta-dah!
This one's got some videos on it.
Did Ryo-chan buy another phone?
Did you buy it?
I was filming earlier.
It's the latest model that can send video emails.
You can also shop with mine.
When you press the barcode reader,
the purchase loan will be automatically withdrawn from the account.
It becomes a credit card.
That's amazing.
Mine is the new model scheduled to be released this summer.
Since the screen is big, you can read newspaper articles like this.
You can also watch TV.
That's great.
I can only call my phone.
What?
You had a cell phone?
Yes.
I got it when I went to a nearby shopping street four years ago.
I don't use it often.
This is a very old model even four years ago.
You can't send emails.
I see.
But the watch function is on.
I don't have a cell phone that doesn't display time.
I've never heard of it.
I see.
Lately, the mobile phone has become popular,
so people don't use watches anymore.
Why don't you just paint the screen and just call?
No, stop it, Ryo-san.
It's a phone.
Me too.
Hello, everyone.
It's an electric pole.
If you want a mobile phone,
please leave it to my super electron.
If you want a mobile phone, leave it to my super electron.
This is a telephone.
It's amazing.
But why are we talking about mobile phones?
What?
I've heard everything you've said.
We just need to go inside.
You just want to show off your cell phone to everyone, don't you?
It's true that mobile phones have evolved rapidly.
But there's a flaw in it.
What kind of flaw?
For example,
the small-sized lightweight that was often used in mobile phone commercials.
But if the small-sized lightweight is too advanced,
the buttons become too small and it's hard to call.
When you put the speaker on your ear,
the microphone is too far away,
so your voice gets louder.
Hello?
Let's go again.
What are you talking about?
It's too light, so you don't notice even if you drop it.
It's true that it's still lost.
That's why you buy a cell phone so often.
This is what was developed there.
What's that?
It's an old black phone.
This is also a great cell phone.
It's a dial type, so you can turn it around without a mistake.
The size is the same as a home phone.
Hello? It's me.
You can talk calmly and openly.
If you put it in a special holster,
it has a cord, so there's no need to worry about losing it.
What do you think?
I'll make it half price now.
What?
Even if you say that suddenly ...
Hey Spark,
did you come to the cell phone business on purpose?
No, I'm running a test run of a new car.
This car has a automatic control function that is linked to the car navigation.
What?
Automatic control function?
Tell me the destination of the car navigation.
Well, then,
Nico Nico Ryo.
I have set the destination.
When you leave, put your hands on the steering wheel.
It's a safety measure.
If you hold the steering wheel tightly,
automatic control will be removed.
When you leave,
put your hands on the steering wheel.
What?
What is it?
It will return soon.
Hey, it's easy, easy.
Just put your hands on it,
you can run without permission.
Oh, it's a red light.
It's okay.
It automatically detects red traffic lights
and the brakes start to brake.
Wow!
Is it right to keep the distance?
There is an impact-bearing sensor.
Is the route changing?
There is an Between-енти 것처럼 break-off across the road.
The route has been changed.
I see, that's what is it.
The function is connected to the traditional car navigation.
Until now,
it took a long time to send traffic information.
In order to do this,
can be reflected in the sky.
It's Saconji!
Hey, Saconji!
Ryotsu, what's wrong with this car?
It's testing the new automatic-powered vehicle.
According to the traffic law,
this place will stop for 5 minutes.
Wow!
This is a new product that I'm proud of!
This car navigation voice...
It's just like Saori...
What?
Is that so?
We have arrived at the destination.
Then let's go back to the exit.
Huh?
Oh, Honda.
It's me. What's wrong, Honda?
I'm around Tamagawa right now.
I found a toy that looks a little interesting.
Really?
Yeah.
It looks like Ryotsu's husband wants it.
It looks like he's sleeping on the ground.
I got it. I'm on my way.
Where is it?
Well, the road is a little rough,
so it's hard to find the place.
In that case,
put your phone in the cell phone holder there.
Take out information from the other side's notebook
and set the destination.
Honda, what is the name and location of the shop?
Takamatsu, a toy shop.
It's near Tamagawa Bridge.
It's a shopping mall.
Let's go there.
Okay, we're out.
Set a route.
Can I borrow this car for a while?
We're going on a business trip to the US on an evening flight.
We might have to contact Narita before then.
I'll contact the company.
We have enough time.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
*Burps*
Oh, I forgot to bring lunch.
I'll eat somewhere else.
I'll use the car navigation system at times like this.
Please stop by the fast food shop on the drive-thru.
Is this place okay?
Yeah.
I've changed my route.
Double cheeseburger set, with hot coffee.
How about you?
No, I'm fine.
I'll drive, so you can eat in the passenger seat.
Ah, I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to stand in the passenger seat.
Press this switch.
You can change the mode with one touch.
It's like a transformation robot.
Sometimes you feel sleepy while driving.
That's why.
It's useful when you're tired.
By the way, if you let go of the handle...
Please hold the handle.
If you can't hold it for 5 seconds, please stop.
Oh, well.
It automatically stops at this state.
Please resume driving.
Good.
Right.
Did you get the helmet it was wearing?
It's fine
Good room.
It's like a lot of things here.
Did you get the helmet it was wearing?
It's fine
It didn't feel good.
Good room.
TRANSMISSION
Even if you don't whatever it is, I consider you are a little similar to a human.
It's even better.
Good
Sedans
He's stupid, it was a car 57 00:04:21,470 -- 00:04:25,050 Who would ignore the traffic light?
Hey, this car ignored the traffic light,
I can't be hurt when you're little stupid
This car automatically stops when the red light is on
But it was red, you've seen it, haven't you?
Humans have their own way of looking at things.
Hey! This isn't a road!
I-I-I'm sure the carnavi decided that this is the shortcut.
What an idiot!
See? It went back to the normal road.
Yeah!
Why is it running in the middle of nowhere?
I'm sure there's a traffic jam somewhere.
Furano? I heard that somewhere.
This isn't a northern country!
It's running in Hokkaido!
That's our new car!
It's going all the way to Hokkaido!
Don't be so serious!
The carnavi is broken!
See? It's in Tokyo!
To be continued
What a car!
Hey!
I-I'm saved!
We're going to have a big accident!
Get rid of the automatic control!
Actually, I've been doing it for a while...
I can't get rid of it!
What did you say?
Oh, right!
I can stop automatically if I let go!
Oh, I see!
I did it!
I can stop!
I can't stop!
Hey! Stop!
I can stop!
What's wrong with you?
I told you to stop!
He's going!
What's wrong with you?
Is it our new car?
What're you gonna do to me?
It's my line!
I was very generous because of that car!
Seriously...
If this goes on, I'll have to contact Honda and get them to pick me up.
Hm?
Oh no! My phone is connected to a car navigation system!
Hey, give me back your phone!
Wait a minute! I have to get it picked up too!
My phone broke!
Don't make that loud noise!
What was that?
It was the email message!
No! I can't read it at all!
Calm down, Spark!
Maybe this guy just broke the LCD!
He might be able to call!
I-I see!
I'll call the telephone function...
No! It's not showing!
Calm down!
It's broken, so it can't be displayed!
The voice input is...
That's right!
It's broken!
The company!
Hm?
The voice input is broken too, it seems.
Haha! What's going on?
You can just press the phone number!
I don't remember that.
Damn it! You're not reliable!
Give it to me!
There's got to be someone at the station!
What was the number again?
You don't remember either!
I remember it from a long time ago!
What do you mean, "I remember it from a long time ago"?
"Yoroshiku" or "Ii-kuni" or something like that...
I can use my phone's name after it's been popularized!
No! I can't remember!
Don't you remember anything?
Like your house number?
I'm not bragging, but I don't remember anything!
Damn it! Someone tell me!
Oh, right! There's a number guide!
I see! You know...
How many numbers do you have?
I think it started with one, so it's three digits.
One, one...
Wasn't it nine?
Okay! One, one, nine!
Yes, this is the fire station.
What?
S-sorry! I've made a mistake!
119 is the fire station!
I-I see!
Um...
The number guide is...
Wasn't it 110?
That's the police's number 110!
It's your number!
I-I see.
Um...
The number...
That's right!
Your phone has a "re-dial" function!
I see! Re-dial!
I called the company when I put you on the phone earlier!
Yes, this is the fire station.
I'm in a emergency!
I-I'm sorry!
I just called the fire station!
If I had known earlier!
What should I have done?
Calm down!
We have to go in order!
Yes, this is the number guide.
Yay!
I see! 104!
I'm calling Tokyo's Super Electronics!
I've received your call.
Please wait a moment.
What is it?
It's a note paper.
Do you have anything to write on it?
Huh?
My cell phone has been replaced by a note book lately.
Do you have one too?
I have one too!
I used to use the memo function of my cell phone.
I left it to you.
I'll read out the number.
Ah! Wait a minute!
I have to find the note quickly!
I see!
Um...
Wait a minute.
What?
Super Electronics Co., Ltd.
Wait a minute!
Unstable!
Run!
This time it's broken perfectly.
Wow!
What?
Yeah!
Damn it!
Where's the last call?
It's because the number has been reduced recently.
Come to think of it.
Maybe we could use the phone's phone number function and call anyone, and get them to contact the company.
Don't say that after it's broken!
We can do that when it's broken next time!
I'm sorry for that!
There it is!
Look! I put the phone number here!
Yay! Now we can call the company!
That's good!
What is it?
10 yen.
You just bought a new phone yesterday, so there's no waste of 1 yen.
Don't you have any money?
Unfortunately, everything I buy is a card.
I don't have any cash!
Then what about your telephone?
I have a phone, but I don't have any telephone!
Then how do you call?
You don't know?
Oh, no!
I've made it to the phone number.
And if you think about it,
even if you can't get in touch with the company,
you won't get a ticket to the company if you don't know where you are!
Don't worry!
I have a GPS built into my phone, and I can...
That phone is broken, so you're in trouble!
So, we're lost in the middle of Tokyo!
What should we do?
Calm down, Spark!
Can we calm down in this situation?
We're going to sign a contract with Ooguchi for our next business trip!
What are we going to do?
If we mess up, we'll lose tens of billions!
Ah, by the way,
the email you just sent might have been some kind of important matter!
I'm curious about it!
Hey!
Stop it!
Come on!
I'm going to the company!
That's right!
If you take a step to one side of the wall like this,
you will get to the destination.
*clock 끝*
...?
We passed here before.
It's the same place we went before.
No way! Why did I get back here?
I think maybe it's because you lacked the way to get out the mail.
Haaaaa!
Oh, yeah! It's the Hokuto Shichisei!
Find "Hokkyoku" and you'll know which way you're coming from!
Let's go to the North Star!
There's no way you can see the constellation in the daytime!
That's right! The wristwatch!
The wristwatch's single axis is facing the sun!
The direction of the single axis and the direction of the dial at 12 o'clock should be exactly in the middle!
Now, the wristwatch!
Unfortunately, I can't carry a wristwatch.
My cell phone has a watch on it.
So, in the end, you can reach there.
Ah!
Why is it broken?
My cell phone!
Hey, calm down.
Spark!
Excuse me.
Yes?
If you're on the phone, I'd like to borrow it.
Ah, it's me.
I'm Spark, the president.
Please come to the address I'm going to tell you.
Well, it's been about 30 years since I borrowed a phone.
I used to hear that a lot.
That's right.
There used to be a lot of houses without phones.
I got a call.
I'll be right there.
Really?
Here you go.
Ah, no, I'm...
Don't hesitate.
It's a good deed.
Yes, I'll take it.
Mmm.
Is this what it used to be like?
A long time ago, there were many houses like this.
That's a big difference from your house.
Thank you for the extra benefits.
Do your grandparents have cell phones?
No way!
But when I wanted to call outside...
Well, that's part of it.
It's a no-brainer.
T-That's...
If you have to, just ask someone.
You too, right?
If you get lost, ask someone.
We can all help each other.
Maybe we were made to dance by the tools because we had so many useful tools.
Made to dance by the tools...
You've done a great job.
I didn't do anything big.
When you're in trouble, you're both great.
Honda, I'm sorry, but can you lend me 10 yen?
No problem.
I borrowed your phone.
When you're in trouble, it's polite to do this.
Here.
Okay, okay, I got it. I'll be waiting.
Who was it from, senpai?
It was Super Electronics' Electrical Spark.
He's coming here soon.
It seems that the contract in the US went well too.
It's all thanks to that old couple.
It was the one who lent me the phone.
So, what's your business?
Yeah, he said he developed a new product.
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
You're here. What kind of product did you develop this time?
The word that you're being made to dance to a tool is ringing in my heart.
So instead of being made to dance to a tool,
I thought about a dancing tool!
How is it? Isn't it amazing?
You don't know anything!
What kind of dancing tool is it?
You idiot, take a break!
You're wasting the love of a person!
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Ryo's why, why, why!
Ryo's eyebrows look like black hair. Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
He wears sandals but he can run really fast. Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Ryo's always doing arm wrestling. Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
He's always being so flirty, yet he adores everyone. Why, why, why, why, why, why?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Even though it doesn't really matter,
the title of this anime is so long.
Katsushika, Kamen Rinko, Emae Hatsutsujo
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Why? Why? Why?
Chief! What are you hiding?
Chief! You can't cheat!
Chief! I don't have any eyes!
This is not a trap!
Chief! You don't think that you can live for free by doing that, do you?
Next time: Chief Ohara gets addicted to games!
Please watch!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!