"Soccer Club N drifting loves Jura-San"
"When you watch TV, please make your room bright, and look away from him."
"Come to my place if you don't have money!"
"I'm not with you, but I'm worried."
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, the one without a job
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the fire is burning
The red cloud
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you understand, come to me quietly
Follow me!
Shackle Panic
We move our lungs up and down to breathe.
However,
When this diaphragm starts to contract on a flat surface,
The rhythm of breathing is disturbed,
The vocal cords in the throat are open,
The air is suddenly exhaled,
Inhale with recoil,
This is Shackle Panic
What are you saying?
I don't know
Damn it!
Let's rewrite it again!
Yes!
Stop breathing and drink water.
If you drink water, you will stop shackling, Ryo-chan.
If you drink water, how many times do you drink?
How many times do you drink in the morning?
Is that so?
I'm sure someone is talking about Ryo-san's rumors.
That's a snort.
Eh?
Ah, I see.
What do you mean, "Shackle"?
Shiyu-kun,
If you move it to the temple, the shackles will stop.
Eh?
It's not a snore, so the shackles won't stop, Ryo-san.
If you stay quiet, you'll stop before you know it.
Quiet?
Then write this report instead of me.
Eh? What kind of logic is that?
I'll take a break until the shackles stop.
Write it yourself, Ryo-chan.
Anyway, I can't work until the shackles stop.
I'm going to take a break.
Oh, my.
Great! I asked you.
I understand. I'll write it.
I'm just thinking about skipping work.
I did it.
Here comes another one of us.
You little.
That's all for the news this afternoon.
Damn it.
I can't understand why the screen changed when I saw the shackles.
I see.
I don't need a remote control.
Even so, I hope it stops.
I can't believe it.
What?
What is it, Reiko?
Are the shackles stopped?
What?
Oh, I see.
Oh, no.
Sorry about that.
It's me, Ryo.
What? The old man?
How was it? Did the shakuri stop?
Good morning!
Did the shakuri stop, Senpai?
Don't say that, Nakagawa!
I was surprised, too.
Ryo, you shouldn't be skipping work to excuse the shakuri.
Don't make fun of the shakuri.
They say that if the shakuri lasts long, it's dangerous to live.
It's possible.
That's too much.
That's right, Senpai.
I've heard this when I was a kid.
If the shakuri doesn't stop, it'll die.
That's a lie.
When the shakuri starts to appear, it takes three hours.
It's more like a physical burn than you think.
It's also like a breath.
That's a pain.
It's okay, Ryo.
What else can you do to stop the shakuri?
I know how to stop the breath and drink water.
And how to scare people.
I think there's something else, too.
You should ask the wisdom bag at a time like this.
I'll go call the third-floor old lady.
It's okay now that I'm here.
What are you going to do?
Water!
Yes!
Here you go.
Okay.
What are you doing?
A chopsticks.
Yes.
Here you go.
Water!
Stop it!
Go!
What are you doing?
Open your mouth.
Yes.
Take this.
Drink from the mouth of the chopsticks.
Stop it.
Yes.
It's delicious.
How was it?
How was it, Ryo-chan?
That's good.
Ryo-san, that's great.
That's wonderful.
Yes.
This is the best for Shakkuri.
See you, Ryo.
Good, good, good.
Thank you, Grandma.
You're welcome, Osamatsu-sama.
Well, I'll be going now.
Yeah.
Ryo, you did well.
Hey, Ryo!
That's ridiculous.
All of my grandchildren stopped at this way.
No, no, no, no.
That's not fair.
Huh!
Mr. Tamai.
Who are you?
Mr. Tamai, who is visiting Hattori-san's house.
Those two are not close.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to stop Shakkuri.
I asked you to do this.
You don't even listen to what I say at home.
You're always like this.
Don't fight.
You two, go home!
Um,
We'll be going now.
How do you stop Tamai-san's Shakkuri?
Lower your head a little more.
Ouch!
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
I did it on purpose!
It's against the law!
Please calm down.
What do you mean, it's against the law?
Don't say that!
Ryo-chan,
I think your Shakkuri stopped.
Huh?
Speaking of which,
this time,
I really...
Ah!
That was close!
It didn't stop!
Damn it!
It's no use after all!
Huh?
If you're a Shakkuri,
you have to look up and drink water at once.
Who are you?
That's it!
Hey!
Raise your chin!
There's a rugby match
on the ground nearby.
Really?
But rugby is played by the big guys, right?
Yes.
There are other people on the ground.
Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
See?
It's true.
I drank all of it!
Oh, yeah!
Ah!
I can't drink water!
I'm a surprised person!
Rugby has nothing to do with it!
Senior,
I think your Shakkuri stopped.
Did it stop?
Yeah!
If only your Shakkuri stopped,
I would be grateful.
Yeah!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Ryo,
you should try this!
Huh?
I can't drink even a drop of water!
Not water!
I remembered
when in my wife's countryside,
I had to drink
to make Shakkuri stop!
A pot of persimmon?
Try it with Damemoto!
Huh?
What is Damemoto?
Anyway,
Just drink it, thinking it was a trick.
I can't help it. It's just a little.
It's bad.
How is it?
It's good.
Is it bad?
Why can't I stop my shakuri?
I guess you can't be bad at shakuri.
My children stopped it.
Ryo, are you there?
You can't stop your shakuri?
Shakuri is tofu after shakuri.
This is the best shakuri.
Sit down.
Do you know how to make tofu?
Tofu?
How to make tofu?
You have to answer or not to make tofu.
Tofu is also a soy.
What are you doing?
Stopped.
Stopped?
Really?
I just answered soy.
Amazing.
It's brilliant.
I don't know why.
There is a store. I'm going home.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
But Ryo was there.
Ryo?
I can't believe it.
I never stopped doing shakuri before.
I didn't see you fighting on this totally.
Do you know how to stop your shakuri, either?
Of course.
Ryo?
Shakuri is also good with eggplants.
Eggplants?
Eggplant?
Yes, you just think of an eggplant in your head.
Just think of it?
It's even more creative.
It's an eggplant, Ryo-chan.
There are many things with eggplants.
Grilled eggplants, mapo eggplants...
You can imagine a normal eggplant, right?
Yes, it's in your head.
You can imagine it, but my shakuri won't stop.
Ryo-san, concentrate on your feelings and think of an eggplant.
Eggplant...
Eggplant, eggplant, eggplant...
I don't know.
When I think about it again, I can't think of anything else but eggplants.
When I think of eggplants, I think of peppers, tomatoes, onions, and lotus roots.
Eggplant...
Ryo-san, calm down.
Look, it's a blue and purple eggplant.
I'll go buy some eggplants.
It's faster to draw than to draw.
Eggplant...
I think this is an eggplant, Ryo-chan.
It's a plum eggplant.
A normal eggplant looks like this.
Like this.
Eggplant looks like this.
No, it's not.
Like this.
Eggplant looks like this.
What's wrong with eggplants?
Eggplant, eggplant, eggplant, eggplant...
Ryo-chan, you remembered the eggplants.
That's good, Ryo-san.
Thank you, everyone.
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
What?
That's right.
Good job.
I've heard the saying, "If you don't stop twitching as a child, you die."
Twitching?
I'm going to die!
Kankichi!
Huh?
Kankichi, you stole the money from the shop, didn't you?
M-Mama!
I said you stole my money!
What's wrong with you?
I'm a police officer now!
I've stolen a few drinks,
but I don't want to get in trouble with the police.
I don't want to get into trouble with the police.
You stole the drinks?
I thought you stole the drinks.
Was that your doing?
Well, that's...
What are you doing here?
Look, mom.
This is a workplace.
I want to be called a sex slave.
It's amazing.
Did you always get scolded like that when you were a child?
I'm in trouble.
I'm embarrassed.
Thank you very much, mom.
I can't stand it.
I'm in trouble for doing something like that.
What?
I was told to come to Reiko to stop your mischief.
What do you mean, Reiko?
When I traveled to Mongolia a long time ago,
I remembered that my mother was asking me if I was a thief to stop the mischief of children.
What kind of parent are you?
You're saying that?
I'm a mother of two children.
What?
I was a little mischievous, but I thought that I would be released from the mischief.
That's amazing.
It's the Mongolian way of stopping the mischief.
You're such a noisy child.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Then I'll go home.
I'll send you to your house.
Oh, that's fine.
Kankichi, don't bother everyone with mischief.
I know.
I'm fine now.
I don't have to do anything.
That's right, you are.
What's wrong with you?
My mischief is getting faster than before.
Push hard, Kankichi!
Your mischief is not as tough as it seems.
Why don't you try a little more overseas?
I've heard a lot about Reiko's Mongolian side.
I've been listening to it a lot.
But where should I look for it?
I have an idea!
Alright! Please get off here.
Where is it?
It's a Japanese school run by Nakagawa Group, Senpai.
Japanese? School?
I asked students from all over the country to help me.
It's global, Ryo-san.
Hello.
He's a student from Vietnam.
My mother asks a lot of questions at home.
The kids will stop.
Let's give it a try. Please.
I'm Kankichi's mother.
It's all in Japanese.
What kind of questions do you ask?
Anything is fine.
Anything is OK.
Please ask a lot of questions.
You're weak. What's your favorite food?
My favorite food?
It's not my first date.
I don't know what to ask.
I'm a father, but I don't know my son's favorite food.
It's yakiniku.
What's your favorite animal?
Animal?
You're so stupid.
You have to answer seriously, Kankichi.
I like and hate animals.
There are many kinds of animals.
What?
I've thought about it.
What's your favorite animal?
Dog.
More questions.
What's your favorite type?
Type?
What?
It's your type.
My type?
I'm beautiful.
I'm good-looking.
I'm good at cooking.
And...
I mean, I'm still a child.
You eat meat like a child.
No, I don't like meat.
And you are a child.
You eat meat like a child.
You eat meat in front of your mom.
You eat meat and go crazy.
A child is good-looking.
And a child is good-looking.
The last question, please.
Do you hear it?
Who says something bad?
A child is a good-looking.
She has a sudden appearance.
I do not want to hear about it.
I'm going to the gym.
Did you stay?
I'm not a baby.
What's next?
I'm going to the Mexican red thing.
I'm going to the baby shack.
I'm not a baby.
I'm going to the lab.
He's going to the lab.
There's a lab.
But it won't stop.
In America,
when you're shivering,
you breathe in your hair.
I know this.
You can't do that.
In France,
you breathe in your hair.
I got it.
I'm going to the US.
What about Italy?
I'm going to the hair shop.
You can't do that.
Where are you going?
I don't care.
to you
I'm going to the hair shop.
I don't care.
everything I do
It's me again.
Miss Litz.
You're trying to win the war,
Stop it, Maria!
We can't do anything, can we, Ryotsu?
Just give me a little bit of your feelings.
You stink of water, don't you? Say anything you want, senpai.
I've done my best. Now, I just need to rest here.
Don't die, Ryousama!
If you die, Maria, you can't live!
I don't want to either!
I won't let you die! I won't let you die!
I won't let you die!
Just be patient for a little bit.
Ryousama, do your best!
Don't lose to Shackley!
That's not what I'm talking about! That's not what I'm talking about!
Shackley, you bastard! DTG!
This kind of technique isn't in judo!
Ryousama!
Senpai!
How is it? Has Shackley stopped?
Eh... Eh... Eh... Eh... Eh... Eh... Eh...
Oh no!
Ryousama!
Next up is engineering attack!
Let's go, Ryousuna!
I'll defeat Shackley for sure!
I don't care. Just let me sleep in peace.
Fly away. Fly away. Shackley, take me!
Eh...
Uwa... Help!
Hey!
*Slow motion*
Man, My bike is...
Chiruencia. You did it wrong.
I thought you were going to die
How do you expect me to come to this neighborhood
and go back to the past?
What?
All right, I'll somehow get to Ryo.
Wait, that reminds me...
Yay! The shakuri stopped at last!
Ryotsu! It's all right now!
Bulba!
I'll get rid of that shakuri from my body!
Ryo! I'll stop the shakuri for sure!
No, you don't have to stop it!
It's already stopped!
Ryo!
Ryotsu! Don't lose to the shakuri!
That's why I don't need the shakuri anymore!
Damn it! It's a trap!
Oh, it ran away! Follow me, Sakonji!
No, I don't...
Damn it! Why do I have to face this when the shakuri stopped?
It's a trap!
I lost!
Are you all right?
Not yet!
Ryo!
What is this?
I'll get rid of them all!
Kankichi!
The shakuri's sister, Sato Mitsugaki,
made a mistake, didn't she?
It's f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f.
"I'm not sure if I can be a good guy."
"I'm not so sure."
"Baby, do you know me?"
いるくいいのはそう見せたいセンユ Yeah
見掛け倒しよりいいでしょう
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na