Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking up at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle ♪
♪ I picked up a pebble ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ on the head of a motorcycle ♪
♪ and was laughed at ♪
♪ for being a good boy ♪
♪ Even if I try to ♪
♪ I can't help but get mad ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes ♪
♪ is kinder than the evil ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ and the birds are singing ♪
♪ Are there any wild birds ♪
♪ in the wild? ♪
♪ From the water tower ♪
♪ of the Tungari Falls ♪
♪ to the Taishakuten ♪
♪ the sunset falls ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be the same ♪
♪ as it ends ♪
♪ But we'll be happy again ♪
♪ even if it's just a year ♪
♪ I've realized that ♪
♪ I'm an idiot ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪
We're leaving! Hurry up!
Please be careful!
Nakagawa-kun's company is amazing.
Running a real Orient Express...
I can't believe it.
It's a dream to travel around Japan with this.
Yes.
We're working hard as Nakagawa Group to let people experience the real Orient Express while staying in Japan.
We worked hard on this project.
You were invited to the special train before the opening.
It's a great thing.
Nakagawa and his colleagues really helped out.
After this, please go to your individual rooms.
The room is...
Room 1 for me, Room 2 for Reiko,
Room 3 for Chief Ohara,
Room 4 for Senpai,
Room 5 for Terai.
What other men are invited to our room?
Room 6 is for my relative,
Madam Christy.
Room 7 is for the president of Seikyuden Railway,
Room 8 is for veteran actress,
Miyuki Takamura.
Room 9 is for me,
Room 10 is for the princess of the forest,
Kurofutsu Osho.
And the person who was supposed to be the vice president of Yokomizo Seishi,
is in Room 10.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'd like to see your driver's license.
Huh?
That's strange.
What's wrong, Chief?
Well...
You lost your driver's license?
I lost mine, too.
No way.
It's strange.
I should have brought it with me.
Please be strong, Chief.
You seem to be very generous to me every day.
What's the point of being a role model for a chief like you?
Calm down and think about it from the beginning.
What?
From your personality,
you should have made sure that you had a proper invitation when you left the house.
Oh, that's right.
And when you were on the train at the station,
you folded it and put it in the parking lot, didn't you?
That's right.
I didn't have it.
But you were worried that you might drop it in the parking lot,
so you put it in your hat.
That's right.
I put it in my hat.
I didn't have it.
But you worried that your hat might be blown away by the wind,
so you put it in your socks.
That's right.
I found it!
That's good, Chief.
Ryo, you're amazing.
You're like a great detective.
It's not that bad.
Well, I'm not as good as you.
The situation here is different.
How is it, Nakagawa?
Does it suit you?
It's perfect, Senior.
You're a great detective.
I'll go check it out.
Huh?
A suspicious light.
What is it?
It's the hand of the head.
That's something to be passionate about.
Excuse me.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Huh?
Something is falling.
Ah!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Gotcha!
No, no, you're not.
Hey.
It's me.
Oh, you're it.
What's up, kid?
Let's go.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Yum, yum, yum.
Ah, it's so good.
Ryo-chan, you should eat more calmly.
Even the world's best chefs are shaking their arms.
Please try to enjoy it.
That's why I'm enjoying it. Like this.
Rero, Rero, Rero.
Huh?
Is it off?
I can't see anything in the dark.
What's wrong?
It's broken.
My bag...
Ah, I don't have any meat.
Huh? Huh?
Ryo-san, you took my meat!
What are you talking about?
I don't have any!
My diamond ring...
You can't see it?
Yes.
I'm sure I put it in this bag, but it's nowhere to be found.
Hey, everyone.
Let's split up and find the train.
Yes.
I don't have any.
Me neither.
If you don't have any, then...
That's an important item that the deceased master gave me for the first time.
If that's not there, then...
I don't have any.
Huh?
Ryo-san, give it to me.
This diamond ring...
Ryo-san that you gave me...
sampling for what I want?
No, it wasn't a diamond ring.
No, it isn't.
Ryo-san, help us with this?
To put it simply, that diamond ring was found in the car.
"I don't want to talk to you anymore!"
"Please leave this case to the great detective, Sherlock Ryozu."
"I will find the culprit, no matter what."
"Sherlock Ryozu?"
"Yes, Watson."
"Watson."
"Wait, what are you talking about?"
"I don't remember being told to be so generous."
"I'm sorry to say this, but we are police officers."
"Please help us."
"I'm glad you said that."
"Right, everyone?"
"Yes."
"Thank you for your cooperation."
"Ryozu, stop being so judgmental!"
"You are quite the boss, aren't you?"
"What?"
"Who do you think found the driver's license that you lost?"
"Who was it?"
"Well..."
"Please leave this case to the great detective, Sherlock Ryozu."
"I can't help it. I'll leave it to you for a while."
"The crime took place within ten seconds of the power outage."
"The culprit stole a diamond from the bag of Lady Christie's wife."
"At that time, he dropped the bag on the floor in a hurry."
"Therefore, the police officer who was not there at the time of the power outage,"
"and the waitress, Miss Terry, and the driver, Mr. Akagawa Kyotaro, may be exempted."
"Of course, the victim, Lady Christie, too."
"And we, the police officers, will be the four guests."
"So I thought about it."
"And I found a person who had a great motive in this."
"That is..."
"You!"
"Mr. Elari!"
"Are you stupid? Why did I..."
"The Nakagawa Railway and Seikyū Railway, which you are the president of,"
"were rival companies."
"If the media finds out that the diamond was lost on this train,"
"the reputation of Nakagawa Railway will be in a mess."
"No! Definitely not!"
"If you doubt it so much, then take a look!"
"All right, Watson!"
"Me?"
"You can find out."
"Excuse me."
"Go ahead."
"But Ryo, I understand your motive, but that's not all."
"There is evidence that it won't work."
"Evidence?"
"I heard it with my own ears."
"Just now, Mr. Elari was..."
"Damn it! I can't beat him!"
"You're right."
"It's not anywhere, Ryo."
"What? That can't be!"
"Did you find it, Elari?"
"Yes."
"That's strange. You said you were going to destroy it."
"That's because I told you about this bean!"
"A bean?"
"You idiot!"
"I told you to stop, Detective Hidori!"
"You're going to do this because you're going to find the culprit with your own method!"
"Wait!"
"Please wait a moment, Mr. President."
"This time, it was just a little bit too sweet."
"Next time, I will definitely find the culprit."
"I want you to give me another chance!"
"Ugh..."
"The crime took place in the middle of the night, when the lights were off."
"Then, why did the culprit steal the diamond in the middle of the night, when there was nothing to see?"
"No, the culprit saw everything."
"Because the culprit is you!"
"The Black Shirt Man!"
"Please investigate."
"Mr. Watson."
"Yes."
"Excuse me."
"I'm sorry."
"So, Ryo-chan, how did you find the diamond in the middle of the night?"
"I saw it with my own eyes."
"The Black Shirt Man was polishing his head with passion just now."
"So?"
"He changed the light of his head to the light of the time when it was off."
"Wow, you're so stupid that I can't even talk about it!"
"It's nowhere to be found."
"You big idiot!"
"You're making a big mistake again!"
"I'm sorry."
"Wait!"
"You were just a little too naive this time."
"Please give me another chance."
"The guests on this train are all rich people."
"But why did the diamond get stolen?"
"The culprit is you!"
"Mr. Takamura Miyuki!"
"Please investigate."
"Please wait."
"Ryoko."
"What? Me?"
"Please investigate."
"I'm sorry."
"By the way, Ryo-chan, why is the culprit Mr. Miyuki?"
"I don't know why, but..."
"There's no one who's interested in diamonds as a man."
"Diamonds are women."
"How about the evidence?"
"There's nothing."
"There's nothing, Ryo-chan."
"You big idiot!"
"This is the third time!"
"Wait!"
"You were just a little too naive this time."
"But next time..."
"Shut up!"
"You're not going to be fooled again!"
"It's fine!"
"I'm going to find the culprit this time!"
"This crime was really clever."
"Therefore, the culprit is highly likely to be a professional who has been trained."
"In other words, the culprit is..."
"You!"
" verify the advisor on your interview."
"You're not even close to the Mr. Yokomizo,"
" flipped to a man."
"and surprisingly suspicious."
"You're like a man who says the chaos when he's painting."
"Then why didn't you tell me at first?"
"It's too suspicious to do, so I didn't tell you."
"You're the most suspicious."
"Due to a difficult time I was in the middle of it."
What's that thing that's all over the passageway?
Isn't that the tool to steal the jewel?
What's so funny?
That's the seven-tool of the detective.
The detective?
I'm Detective Edogawa Poirot!
Edogawa Poirot?
Episode 9: The
It seems that it's my, Detective Poirot's turn.
In fact, I was secretly looking for a request from President Yoko Mizu to investigate a case that might have happened in this train.
And as expected, the incident happened.
But don't worry. I will solve this difficult case and give it to you.
Thank you very much, Detective.
I was looking at the situation for a while because it was interesting, but it seems that there is no way to solve it.
What is this?
First of all, let's remember exactly when the incident happened.
Do you have a mirror?
I have one.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Please be quiet.
Then, why did you come to the station?
Why? Why did you do this?
I see.
At that time, I was stuck in the back of the train.
Oh, no. Then I will be turned into a thief.
I have to do something.
Everyone, do you remember?
At that time, there was no one who did anything strange.
I'm sorry.
What? There was nothing in particular.
Then, there was no one who did anything strange.
I see. There was no one who did anything strange.
But the diamond was gone.
Excuse me.
How did you steal the diamond from this bag?
Damn it. It was just a little while ago.
How did the culprit find this bag with the diamond in the dark?
And how did you steal the diamond from inside?
This is very important.
Damn it. I was put in such a place.
In such a place...
Ah, you're the suspect...
Well...
Don't bother me. I'm going to keep looking...
Hmm...
Ah, I see...
*Sigh*
Question 1
What is the motive?
Question 2
*Sigh*
Question 3
Where does the diamond hide?
*Sigh*
What kind of possibilities can be imagined by the enemy?
If you think about it, you can come to a conclusion.
It's hard, it's hard, it's hard.
So, the most characteristic of this incident is...
Thank you for waiting.
Is it you?
Are you still reasoning?
what?
Do you know what?
It came to my mind.
This is the case of the famous detective, Sherlock Ryochi.
What?
Without motivation, there is no culprit.
So where did the diamond disappear?
No, it doesn't disappear anywhere.
In other words, it doesn't jump out of the bag.
What an idiot.
No, no, it was not in the bag.
Watson.
Yes.
Look it up.
Oh, it was there.
No way.
It was certainly just now.
I'm sure he was lost somewhere.
Now, this is it.
This is fake.
What?
This is?
How do you know?
On my ring, on the back side,
There is a picture of love from the master.
But there is no message in this ring.
What do you mean?
What's the matter, Detective Mei?
That's the end of it.
Huh?
You.
Wait.
By the way, you're the only one who hasn't checked your body.
I'm a detective.
Because you're a detective, you cannot say that you're not the culprit.
And what did the detective Nanatsu-dogu do on the road with that thing?
That's...
Watson, check the electrical circuit.
Got it. I'm going too.
Nakagawa, call the president of Yokomizu Seishi.
Yes, I'm calling right now.
Hello? This is Nakagawa Keiichi.
There it is! Ryo-san, the timer!
The telegram was made by a man.
Yes, the president doesn't know Edogawa Poirot.
The monster's skin has finally peeled off.
Edogawa Poirot, you're the culprit!
Who are you?
Kaito 1035.
Kaito 1035?
You don't know him?
He's making a scene in the world right now.
He's a gemstone.
He's a gemstone thief.
I'm sure he gave you the ring.
Give me back the diamond!
You're a liar, detective.
I was going to save time for the next station, but I had to be caught.
Farewell.
Wait!
You can't escape now!
Now, give me the diamond!
What a pain in the ass!
What are you talking about?
If you can get it, try it!
What?
What is this?!
You chauffeur, no good!
What are you talking about?
I told you to stop!
Go to hell!
He was after me!
I helped you!
You caught him!
What? What? There is no case that can't be solved if it's Sherlock Ryo.
That's amazing, Ryo.
To arrest a criminal with a murderous intent.
It's a great achievement, Ryo.
No, no, it's not a big deal.
This guy stole the invitation from the president's house in Yokomizo City and pretended to be a representative and got on this train.
And he used a timer to turn off the electricity and took the bag of Lady Christie's white shirt.
But how did he look in the dark?
His glasses contained a infrared scope.
And he switched the diamond with a fake one.
But Lady Christie, who felt the presence of a person, turned away.
The bag fell to the floor and a fake diamond fell from the inside and got on the monk's body.
I stole it, so it got in between my teeth.
Thanks to that, I had a hard time so much that I put the diamond in the bag.
Ryo-kun!
What?
You got caught between my teeth?
That's right.
So you borrowed the mirror from me, right?
And you pretended to be on the phone and tried to get back secretly.
Oh, I saw a shadow outside the window.
That was a senior.
Ryo-san was the one who ate my meat after all.
Hey, no, that's...
Ryo-san!
Everyone is sharp!
What's wrong, Bujo?
The father of Daishike's grandchild is injured.
So he wants me to take him to the sports competition instead.
Leave it to me, Bujo.
I won't lose to this kind of bad guy if I use my body.
Next time, "Run! Student Sports Club!"
See you later!
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ Oh, there must be a wall ♪
♪ Come on, let's all come to our town ♪
♪ Oh, there must be a wall over there ♪