The End
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
I walked with a look back
At the end of the rain
I held your hand
I felt
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk
On the black tile outside the arcade
Who is it?
Once I was a child
But everyone forgets
A politician with a big face
And a blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around
That corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall
I know that there is a wall
It's a vastiiit
There is a place
I can see
Over there
There is a wall
And behind me
There are several values
There are manyي
And there is no down
And I can see
There are two environment
Genki High School is heading toward Matsudo with a red Ferrari.
Damn it! He's so stubborn!
Chidan, it's my turn!
I'm going to lose!
Yes!
Big brother, there's still one left!
What?
I'm going to beat him.
But I'm also a man called Akagi Yama's red water student.
Can you catch up with me?
I won't let you chase me to a place like this!
What on earth is this place?
I think it's in between Chiba and Ibaraki.
What?
It's gone!
Ouch...
It's over!
It's the last one!
Damn it! It's the gas!
I'm going to run away, Chidan!
Wake up!
No, no, no!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
No, I can't!
I can't get inside!
I can't!
They're running away!
Pull forward!
Yes, sir!
It's a trap!
Trust me!
What?
What's wrong with him?
Did he pull the trigger?
No, he didn't hit me.
Are you all right?
Please be strong.
Where's the criminal?
I don't think he's gone far yet.
But where on earth is this place?
I'm sure he knows.
It looks like the uniform of the former Japanese army.
I think he played survival games.
He used a model gun with a old-fashioned gun like this.
Get up!
I'll shoot you when you wake up!
Like this.
It's a real gun!
Give me back my gun!
It's dangerous.
Guns are the soul of the police officer.
Police officer?
Don't be surprised!
You two, come out slowly.
Who are you talking to?
I don't know.
No matter how much you hide, you can't.
I can see it.
Your body looks like a balloon.
It's an airbag.
Is that so?
Don't come out!
Airbag!
You don't even know the airbag?
It's dangerous to get close to the police.
They are the most evil people who committed a terrible crime.
What's that?
What crime did you commit?
Speed violation.
Idiot.
This is how it is.
What's this?
You used a strange technique.
By the way, you look at it with one eye.
Who are you?
I'm the chief of the Ryotsu-Kakichi police station in the Katsushika prefecture.
Chief of the police station?
I'm sorry for not knowing that.
I'm the chief of the Imogashira police station.
Imogashira?
Actually, we were in this car.
What?
Even though you are the chief of the police station, you can't commit a crime.
We were chasing the criminal.
Chasing the criminal?
That's right.
We chased the criminal who stole 50 million yen in cash and came from Tokyo.
50 million yen?
You suddenly jumped out of the car and ran away.
This car looks like a patrol car.
What's this car?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry for dying.
Idiot, stop it.
Let me go.
I have something to ask you.
I can't let you die here.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so harsh.
I'm an officer.
Tell me what to do from now on.
If you catch the criminal, you can be punished.
You can be punished.
Please help us.
Yes.
First of all, tell me where this is.
Is it Chiba Prefecture?
Or Ibaraki Prefecture?
No, this is Doinaka Prefecture.
Doinaka Prefecture?
I don't know.
I got in touch with the Japanese government last week.
Now I'm applying to be on the Japanese map.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
So you were in the situation of Shouichi Yokoi?
Is this Japan?
Even if you say Yokoi or Onoda,
your children wouldn't understand me.
Even if you tell me?
I would like to ask this question.
What year is this year?
This year is Showa 75.
Showa ended over ten years ago.
This year is Heisei 12.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, by the way, we were following the culprit.
I'll put the contact information in the book.
No, it looks like it's broken.
Huh? Where's the cell phone?
Outside the prefecture.
It's not impossible in a place like this.
Oh, is there a phone somewhere?
I think it's somewhere in the village.
Okay, guide me.
This week is the traffic control week.
How many people have you been looking for?
There are no criminals in the last 50 years.
It's a tricky case.
Dog? No, it's not.
It's a wolf.
It's a wolf that was supposed to be extinct.
If you get close, you'll hit it.
There's a wolf herd around here.
What a place.
That's a land.
There's a military base nearby.
There's so much.
If the director of the environmental department sees it, he'll cry and be happy.
No way, is this a mountain cat with a mouth?
It's just a stray cat.
Oh, I see.
I saw it.
You saw it, right?
That's Doinaka Prefecture, Doinaka Village.
Wow.
Grandma.
Marry me.
Over here, please.
Thank you for coming.
Do you know anyone?
People from Tokyo.
Tokyo?
That's quite a long-winded phone call.
I suspected it.
I was thinking, but I can't believe it's this far...
Here's the telephone exchange certificate.
Exchange certificate? Isn't it a direct connection?
What? Direct connection?
No way, senpai.
I've seen it. It seems that the level of civilization has stopped 20 years ago.
I see.
Excuse me, which way do you want to connect?
I'll take a long distance to Tokyo.
Tokyo?
I'm sorry, but I can't make long distance calls right now.
What? That's not helpful at all.
No, it's not.
I can't run the electricity line to the house in the village.
I want to call Tokyo.
They're negotiating with the power plant to get a telephone line.
NTT, right?
That's right.
I can't understand foreign language.
What should we do, senpai?
It's dangerous to return to that mountain road.
Then, we should stay at our house tonight.
There are many mountains.
We don't need to hold back.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
The old cucumber tasted like this.
What are you talking about?
The old cucumber is the old cucumber.
I see.
It's good that it's from the past.
What?
I've been wondering about it for a while.
What is it?
It's a side dish I bought at the convenience store.
I'll make it for myself.
This is a side dish of a person from Tokyo.
Please give me some hot water.
I'll make it so that you can eat it.
Please.
Here you are.
This is Chinese soba.
It's very convenient.
Do people in Tokyo eat this every day?
It's not every day.
I eat it almost every day.
What's this?
Coke.
This is a drink that I bought after the war.
Try it.
It's a black liquid.
It exploded in my mouth.
It's a drink like that.
What is it?
Next.
This is a Tokyo soba.
It's the first time I've seen people from other villages.
It's not fake.
It's the first time I've seen people from Tokyo.
It's the first time I've seen people from other villages.
Is it true that Tokyo is bright and bright all night long?
Is it true that everyone speaks English?
Is it true that everyone is dressed like this?
No way.
Only a small number of girls in Tokyo do this.
This is how Tokyo is misunderstood.
I see.
It's interesting, so let's take a picture.
Oh.
There was a disposable camera.
A photo?
Then I'll take it.
Cheese.
What's wrong?
If you take a picture, your soul will be pulled out.
There's nothing stupid.
I don't want to die yet.
Brother...
Good morning.
Mr. Secretary, I'm ready.
What?
I'm preparing for a ceremony.
For a ceremony?
Is it going to be fireworks?
What is this tank squad?
It's a local Keira car.
Is it a patrol car?
It's using the tanks from the war.
It's a warm welcome.
I feel good.
Thank you.
I salute the commander of Ryotsu Kankichi.
I have brought another person.
Good work, commander.
There are a lot of soldiers.
I'm sure they are better than the chief.
Maybe they are more experienced.
Welcome to the countryside.
I'm Wadasu.
I'm the chief of the countryside.
I'm Yonesuke Omaeda.
Chief?
Why are you a chief?
I've been a police officer for 58 years.
I'm not lucky enough to have a chance to serve.
Anyway, the incident that happened in this year is only a 30-year-old thievery.
A thievery?
That was an incident handled by the former chief.
The former chief was killed.
It was a case that was handled by the former chief.
The activities of the previous generation.
I still remember now.
I feel hot in my eyes.
The previous generation was the chief at that time,
but since then, the incident has not happened,
so everyone is still in the same rank.
Really?
Then what is that medal for?
This is the medal for the 10th year of the metal.
The 15th year of the metal.
The 20th year of the metal.
And this is the rank of the summer festival.
The prime minister of the sports competition.
And you are the 25th year of the metal.
And you participate in the national体育 competition.
But that's enough.
What's this?
A flock of birds.
I don't know.
Let's get out of this mountain and fly somewhere.
I don't care if it's a car or a lucky charm.
Let's steal the car.
Stop!
It's a strange machine.
Idiot! It's a vehicle!
I have no choice but to do this.
Stop!
I'm dying!
Dragon Blade!
It's easier than I thought.
But why is this car for villagers?
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, let's get out of here.
What?
Two men with guns stole a car?
They were farming in the field.
It's been 30 years since the incident.
They must have stolen the cash we got.
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Mr. Colonel, I'll give you five orders.
Okay.
All cars, go!
You, Colonel.
What's the suspect's expected route?
Yes, sir.
It's a road that leads to the next farm.
Okay.
All cars, wait there!
Damn it.
Where the hell is this place?
I can't find the map.
Brother, there's a car ahead!
Idiot!
You're gonna get kicked out.
We're driving here.
I see.
What's the problem?
Okay, here we are.
Damn it, this road is...
Mr. Colonel!
You did it.
It's a counterattack.
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
What's with those tanks?
They might have got lost in the Self-Defense Force's training ground.
No! They're after us!
They're shooting! They're shooting!
I did it! It's a motorcycle!
It's scary!
Damn it! The culprit stole the motorcycle!
That's the only tank in the village.
It's the
Damn it.
I can't catch up with a tank that has slow legs.
Don't worry.
There is an Air Police Division in the village.
An Air Police Division?
Yeah!
Hiyenni, Hayabusa, Hayate,
Raiden, Shidenkai, and Zero-sen.
Those are all planes during the war.
Yeah, if the maniacs see us, they will be furious.
Mr. Colonel, which one are you going to take?
I'm going to take the Zero-sen.
Where did he go?
Mr. Colonel!
It's the direction of the left-hand center!
What?
Is that it?
All right, let's start the attack!
Yes, sir!
It's a panic!
Be prepared!
The 될er of the zone!
What? It's the Zero-sen, isn't it?
Why is it the Zero-sen?
How stupid of him to think I'm the 0-sen!
Anyway, get out of here!
What did you do to me?
Wow!
Hahaha!
I thought you'd run away, so I sent the police to the water.
There's such a battleship!
What a place!
I saw it!
The lightning!
I don't like this life anymore.
It's hot.
Hey, give up. It's still too early.
You're giving me gas from a broken car?
As expected of you, brother!
If I get on this, I won't be afraid!
You still haven't found the culprit?
Yes! I still haven't found him!
The police are here!
The culprit is near the police station!
He's found the car!
He's running at an unbelievable speed!
It's the Ferrari that he was riding at first!
It's going to be 300 kilometers.
If we keep going, he'll run away.
I have no choice.
We have to get that out.
Is there still something?
This is the train law of the Toinakasho Railway Police Force!
That's ridiculous!
Now, Chief Inspector, your orders.
Don't care about it!
I'll fire it!
Roger that!
Train law, ready!
Toinakasho Railway Police Force No. 07, set off!
Distance 22.25 km!
Wind from the north-east island! Wind power 2!
The target speed is...
.2!
Wind power 2!
Wind power 1!
The target speed is...
Fire, 10 second!
Fire!
If you cross the mountain, you'll have to leave this stupid village;
Farewell!
Yay! It's a masterpiece!
I can't take it anymore.
Please, just catch me normally.
Yay!
A masterpiece!
Banzai!
The culprit has become pitiful.
That's true.
Huh? I can't believe it.
There's such a police station.
We don't want to believe it either.
But Kei-chan never lies.
The culprit is saying the same thing.
It's like a strange story for the four of us.
Ryotsu.
Did you write something about the countryside?
Yes.
I don't say it's impossible to believe.
The countryside's potato head.
There's a wire in it.
What?
From the potato head?
This is Ryotsu from the Katsushika office.
Mr. Chief.
What's wrong with the potato head?
It's a terrible crime again.
What?
It's a terrible crime.
It's a thievery.
The culprit is heading toward Tokyo, beyond the prefecture.
We are also following him with our full strength.
Please cooperate.
With your full strength?
No way.
Stop!
Mr. Chief.
But I'm very serious.
What are you talking about?
That's how things are.
We are under threat.
Major Step.
He's gathering us here.
No offense.
We're innocent.
I know?
♪ I kick it and my little finger hurts ♪
♪ I draw my eyebrows and ♪
♪ I dash to the station ♪
♪ On the main train, I sleep on my dad's back ♪
♪ This week too, I'm doing my best ♪
♪ I'm doing my best to make a good sound ♪
♪ But my body is so hot ♪
♪ I'm still feeling irritated ♪
♪ I want to help clear up the anger ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ If you walk through the hot shower ♪
♪ I can heal myself by the sleeping pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
Every day is No Problem
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
Monday
Monday Monday Good morning
Huh?
Are Honda's childhood friends playing circus?
I used to come to see them when I was a kid
What? The debtor is about to get a circus?
Leave it to me
I will do something about it
Next time, Circus Symphony
Thank you
There is a turtle there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you