Subtitles by fignyafsyakaya
I look at the sunset floating in the river
I kick the pebble and it flies to the shoes
I wonder if it's a good idea to save money
He laughed at me as it was
Even if I try to cheer up, I can't do anything
The cityscape that doesn't change even a single wail
It's surprisingly gentle
I look at the sunset floating in the river
I kick the pebble and it flies to the shoes
The sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness because of the Katsushika Shiba
I realized
How stupid I am
Mo "Nakagawa "No Father
Shina
No father
Kato
án
Потому
Because
Yeah, because everyone's putting their lives on the line for the railway model.
That guy used too much money on the railway model and got away from his wife.
And the guy next to him just made a 1/2 scale SL,
and he's in trouble with the location, so he bought a new house.
But that stupid leader is Ryo-sama, right?
Yeah, I'm the stupidest...
Hey, what are you making me say?
I'm not stupid.
SL is great, after all.
Hey, Ryo-san!
What are you doing?
Let's go to the station.
Hurry up!
Why are there so many people?
There's no way. This is the last time SL will run here.
Yeah, this railway will be a waste of money.
It's a pity that there aren't many railways that can run SL.
Here it comes!
Ryo-chan!
Huh?
Ryo-chan! Ryo-chan!
Ryo-chan! Come here!
Come here!
Hey, Nori-chan!
I got a place for Ryo-chan.
Sorry, Nori-chan.
Of course, this is for my darling.
D-Darling?
Ryo-sama, you're so mean to me!
Don't get me wrong.
Nori-chan is a man with the same P as you.
Huh?
Ryo-chan, who is this special person?
Is it me?
Then it's fine, but this is the one.
Oh, I see.
We're a good match.
What's your name?
I'm Asato Ai.
Please call me Maria.
Maria-chan?
I'm Nori-chan.
Nice to meet you.
I'll be back later.
Nori-chan, I'll take a picture of you.
Hey, guys!
Get ready.
Excuse me.
Ryo-chan, help me when the shooting is over.
Yeah, leave it to me.
This is the last scene from the shoot.
The shooting is over.
It's time to go to the market.
The famous Okama bento of Oge is this one!
Welcome, welcome!
Okama bento?
Thank you very much!
Here you are, thank you!
Thank you so much!
Thank you, everyone!
"Oka-ma Bento"
Nori-chan's Okama Bento is still very popular.
You really sold out all of them.
In the end, we were too lazy to eat them.
What are you talking about?
We left some for you.
Oh, as expected of Nori-chan!
Let's eat!
It's delicious!
Right?
This Nori-chan's Okama Bento is the best in Japan.
It's the best in Japan.
Thank you, Ryo-chan.
But this is the last thing I can ask you to eat.
I'm getting old, so I'm going to quit.
What?
You want to see me come here every year, right?
You want to eat this Nori-chan's bento!
You're going to quit that?
I want to keep going.
But it can't be helped if it goes to waste.
I can't help it if it goes to waste.
Nori-chan.
I have an idea!
I won't let you go to waste!
What?
Leave it to me as if you were on a big boat!
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-sama, are you sure you want to do that?
Don't worry.
I have a walking cash box called Nagagawa.
Well, if it's you, Ryo-sama.
But I've been a little jealous of Nori-chan.
Hey, hey, don't misunderstand!
I just want to keep the taste of that bento and good memories with Nori-chan.
Memories?
That's a story from decades ago.
When I was in elementary school, I had a fight with my father and left the house.
I left home, but the money arrived immediately.
I got hungry and went to the other side of the road at the bench at the station.
Oh, I see.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry right now.
If you don't mind, I'll take your meal.
Eh...
But I don't have money.
I don't need money.
Really?
Thank you!
Nori-chan...
She didn't even tell me about my escape.
She just smiled at me.
And he gave me a ticket to the train on the way back.
I still remember the taste of the lunch and Nori-chan's kindness.
Well, Nori-chan has grown up a lot.
That's a very good story, Barrio-sama.
Please let me continue my work at the station.
Yeah!
What? Stop the police!
Actually, I was invited to participate in a big project
that was the result of the good fortune of Nakagawa Group.
A big project? What is it?
It's a very good plan to build a road that will be able to cross the Pacific Ocean
and the Pacific Ocean by 2033.
It's 35 years ago!
Barrio-sama, what if Nakagawa-san of Peiuri is gone, and Nori-chan...
Hey!
It's not that!
You're the police officer!
You're serious!
You should refuse!
Of course I refused!
But my father won't forgive me!
You!
You're the police officer because you like being a police officer!
You can quit as soon as your father orders you to!
Sen...Senpai...
I'm sad.
I thought Nakagawa was born to be a police officer.
Senpai, don't say that about me!
He's done one more thing.
He's called Ryo-chan Kei-chan, who was born before the park.
If he hadn't done it, he would have wanted to be a milst buttock!
Isn't this a 'manzai ?'
Is it okay you just leave Nakagawa?
I-I don't think so...
Then why not stop?
Nakagawa, how about a talk with him?
Do you think you can do that?
Fine, I'll try!
Sen...Senpai!
Huh?
Never saw Nakagawa's father though.
I've never seen it.
I've never seen it either.
Me neither.
Actually, I've only seen it about three times since I was born,
and I don't remember its face very well.
What?
What did you say?
What kind of father is he?
He's a super businessman.
He only sleeps for five minutes every three days.
He's still the boss of the company,
so he can work 72 hours a day.
Don't you have any family photos?
I do, but...
This is the only photo of my father.
Is your father Nessie from Nesco?
His name is Ryoichiro Nakagawa,
but I can't contact him.
He's been around the world.
Just contact the company.
I don't think it's possible.
Don't you want to continue being a policeman?
I-I understand.
I'll contact him.
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa.
I'd like to meet the president.
Huh?
I have to make a reservation for a meeting?
I don't think it's possible.
Hello.
It's November 31st, 2011.
It's available from 11:00 to 3:00 p.m.
What?
Don't let him fool around.
Give it to me.
Hey,
your son is Ae.
Yeah.
Damn it.
I'm fired.
Nakagawa,
I'm going to meet him in person.
Wait, Senpai.
This is my father's schedule.
He's really sick.
He's not in the same place as Go-Fun.
Luckily,
I've been in Japan for the first time in 10 years.
I have 8 hours and 25 minutes left.
Are you coming here 11 years from now?
Yes.
You're like a
Parisian.
You're a father like Suisei.
I see him!
Huh?
That's him!
Oh!
What a pervert!
Why are there so many helicopters?
I have no objection.
Huh?
Take this!
Sir, we have 30 seconds left until we get there.
Please give this document a copy.
All right.
I'll do it for 15 seconds.
Put it in here.
What?
Where did it go?
Oh!
Take this!
Thank you very much.
Sir, please copy this document.
I have no objection.
I have no time.
I'm sorry.
You have 15 seconds left until you get a drink.
Which one would you like?
I'm a bit sleepy.
Then I'll have a Super Ultra Super Drink.
Here you are.
Hmm?
Ahh!
Here, here, here it is!
It's here!
I see.
Hey, it's only 5 seconds.
The deal is closed.
I'm leaving.
President Nakagawa!
I'm sorry for being late.
There was an accident in Stockholm.
No excuses.
Let's make sure this story never happened.
Yeah.
You only have one business chance.
No way!
President, one more chance!
I thought he was down, but he's already down.
I'm impressed.
You're impressed?
Was it my father who just got on?
Maybe.
I don't remember it clearly.
President Adam has just arrived.
I see.
I'll be there in 3 minutes.
Come on! Come on!
Welcome back.
Thank you.
President Adam is waiting for you in the room on the 35th floor.
I see.
We've arrived on time.
This is President Nakagawa.
Oh, Mr. Nakagawa!
I think I explained about the contract in advance.
I don't have time, so I'd like to ask you a quick answer.
Pe-la-pe-la-pe-la-pe-la-pe-la-pe-la.
Pe-la-pe-la-pe-la-pe-la-pe-la.
It's an honor to meet you, Mr. Nakagawa.
Please take this opportunity to...
I've never heard of this!
Yes or no? Which one?
I-I don't know...
Okay.
It's according to the plan. Wonderful.
I'll sign the contract.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yes.
The helicopter is here to pick you up.
Oh, my God!
Let's go!
Get to the next scene immediately!
Yes, sir!
Thank you for your hard work.
Hm, I'm a little tired.
I'll sleep for a minute.
I'll wake you up, no matter what.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
We're finally here.
No escort right now.
Put the helicopter on the side.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Mr. Nakagawa!
Can you hear me?
Hm?
We've got five seconds left.
I told you not to wake me up.
I'm sorry.
The helicopter was approaching without warning.
Hey, Mr. Nakagawa! Can you hear me?
Damn it!
The Tegane is here to see you!
Nakagawa, you talk too!
Brother!
Please pass the test.
What a guy!
If he's like this, I'll help him!
Hey, put the helicopter on top of it!
Yes, sir!
That's it!
I've got it!
Just wait!
What?
I'm busy!
No!
Damn it!
I'll get you!
He jumped!
That's ridiculous.
All right!
Take all the parts back!
Hey!
You caught me!
Hey, I'm sorry for making you wait.
Listen to me!
Then I'll give you 10 seconds.
Okay! Don't put your son Keiichi in the project!
Cancel it right now!
The answer is no.
10 seconds have passed.
Farewell!
Remember that!
Get out of here!
Sir, I've been waiting for you.
Damn it! You've prepared a car!
Hey! Wait!
Damn it!
Wait!
Who are you? Why are you so busy?
Ryo?
What? Is that Nori-chan? What's wrong?
I thought about it.
I thought I shouldn't bother Ryo anymore.
So I decided to give up on my life and go back to Hokkaido.
What? Where are you now?
At the airport.
Idiot!
If Nori-chan goes back, I'll quit being a policeman.
I'll risk my life and never let you go to the ruins!
Cancel the plane and wait!
Okay?
Ryo...
Uh!
Hey!
I'll rent a bicycle.
Get out of here!
Sir!
I've received a call from the Brazilian ambassador.
As planned.
Guest Okada
How do you like it?
I see. I see.
I'll be there in 198 hours.
You!
I'm catching up!
Hey, I'm calling the police!
I'm the police!
You have to listen to me!
Okay, I'll give you 15 seconds.
Okay!
Your son didn't join the project!
Take Nakagawa out of the project!
The answer is no.
The project is already in motion!
Wait!
Nakagawa's helicopter!
Are you good?
Hey, you can't run away anymore!
Dad!
The police are here!
Listen to me!
It's nothing.
It's a signal for the lunch time.
It will take 5 minutes.
Listen to me.
Don't be surprised!
I didn't think that the president would have lunch here.
The fastest is the best.
When you come to Japan, be sure to stand by.
You can use your cell phone.
Why do you need a wireless phone?
I don't want to be caught.
I'll change the frequency every time and contact you.
By the way, I'm Keiichi.
I'm...
Excuse me.
Hey, are you running away?
I'm not very sensitive.
What?
A hotline from New York?
Here's the white rock.
It's like a telecommunication service.
My father has hated people for a long time.
He was always on his own.
So that's why you're sick.
Are you living an ordinary life?
Keiichi.
Yes.
The project of the Pacific Border Road has been postponed.
It will start in 2098, a hundred years from now.
It's been decided just now.
Really?
I'm glad!
I thought that you would quit the police!
Thank you, senpai!
Keiichi.
Yes?
Yes!
Eh?
We've met for the first time in 20 years, and you've grown up so well.
Dad!
You suddenly became like your father.
Huh?
Excuse me, it's time for a drink.
Hey!
Ha!
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
Here it comes!
Hmm, I think I can work 72 hours.
I'm sorry for causing a big fuss this time, Keiichi.
I want to see you and your mother slowly this time.
Actually, I meet my mother every year secretly.
Eh? Really?
Listen, this is a secret to everyone.
Ah, yes, I understand.
Even so, I'm happy to have a senior who works hard for you.
Yes!
From now on,
I'll be in your care, Mr. Ryotsu.
Yes, thank you!
It's time.
Huh?
Well then, goodbye!
Next time is 2009!
Until then, take care!
Dad, take care too!
Good luck!
I see, you didn't quit.
I'm glad, Kei-chan.
This is also thanks to my seniors.
No, I'm...
By the way, Nakagawa, I have something I want to ask you.
If there's anything I can do, please say anything.
Really?
Yes!
Congratulations!
Kei-chan, you did it!
Good, Nakagawa!
Thank you so much, Ryotsu-chan.
Thank you very much!
I told you to leave it to me!
Nice to meet you, I'm Nakagawa.
Thank you for coming.
Please continue to support the Okama Bento of the famous mountain pass.
Yes, thank you very much!
The first race of Nakagawa Bento is coming!
Well, welcome!
Welcome!
How about Okama Bento of the famous mountain pass?
Yes, I bought it!
Thank you very much!
Yes, please!
Next, please!
Welcome!
I look forward to working with you.
I thought something would happen because of you, but I didn't expect to be bought by a railroad company.
You are like a senior.
You are proud of yourself, aren't you?
You are doing your best for your friends and the station.
But is it okay?
You bought the Akaji Railway for 3 billion yen a year.
I have never bought it if I can be a senior.
Next, please!
Nakagawa!
Yes, sir!
Why are you looking at me?
Help me!
Yes, sir!
Next, please!
You again, Professor Ezaki!
You bought the Chanson, Cafe au lait, and Citroen?
When did you buy them in France?
So, I'm done with your invention!
Don't deceive me!
Listen to me!
Next time, "The Delusional New Invention"!
Thank you for watching!
Next time "The Delusional New Invention"!
Next time "The Delusional New Invention"
♪ Like a dream, the last energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, yesterday, and the new universe ♩
♪ When you stand on the ground, the stars will turn ♩
♪ It's a fairy tale ♩
♪ Isn't this good? ♩
♪ There's no excuse! ♩
♪ It's a fairy tale ♩