"The End of the Rain"
When you watch TV
Make sure to lighten up your room
And try to keep your distance
It's like someone's calling
After the rain has stopped
You look back and walk
I'll hold your hand
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk
On the black tile outside the arcade
Everyone was a child once
But
Everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle there
There must be a turtle
There's something green
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Bonus Battle
Bonus Battle 4
Bonus Battle Four
Every one here is with us
No, the fish shop is still...
Sorry for being late.
Did your wife run away again?
That girl...
If she fails to pay the debt this year,
she'll be in trouble!
She left her kid behind!
This is bad.
Let's do something about it this year.
Now, the 27th episode.
The
What are you listening to, senpai?
It's just a joke.
If Chief Ohara finds out, he'll scold us.
Shh!
The people in the shopping district are talking about my bonus.
I was so sorry last year.
No way, senpai.
Are you crazy?
Don't say anything bad about it.
When I went to the plum shop to get the defective product,
I found a plastic bottle I made in the middle of the play.
It contained a small-sized plastic bottle.
This is called "unfeasibility".
You must have done it on purpose.
That's right.
I think it's Ryo-chan's fault for not paying the debt.
Why don't you just give it back to him?
I didn't say I wouldn't give it back to anyone.
But I've already decided what to buy with this year's bonus.
The world's first double-speed robot robot.
Robotta-kun.
Oh, it's the one that's been a hot topic on TV.
It's a limited edition, so the competition rate was extremely high.
But I managed to get a purchase ticket.
All I have to do is deposit the money.
By the way, Sakonji has applied for a super limited edition Saori version.
He deposited the money with his salary the other day, so it should arrive soon.
What are you going to do with that?
It's bound to be a luggage soon.
Shut up!
The robot will come into the house without waiting for 21 years.
Don't you think it's great?
It doesn't have to be Ryo-chan's house.
You don't know what a man's romance is.
Debt is more important than romance.
So, what's the plan this time?
It's an important part.
Before that, I have something to tell everyone.
What's wrong with you? You look so serious.
Did something happen?
At the end of this bonus battle, I'm retiring.
What?
What's wrong, senpai?
What do you mean by retiring, Mr. Plum?
Retiring?
I'm thinking of moving to the countryside by building this shop.
Are you serious?
I'm not old enough to retire yet.
Why?
Actually, my shop has been in red since recently.
What?
Recently, I've been pushed by the game, so I can't sell my Promo.
Oh, today?
Originally, I started this shop because I love Promo.
I didn't feel like buying a business.
So I thought it would be better.
Hey, you're giving up too soon.
Where's your usual patience?
That's right.
Who can compete with Ryo-san except for Mr. Plum?
It's the same for every shop.
Let's work hard.
I've been trying to make my wife run away many times, but I'm still working hard.
It's decided.
Mr. Plum.
That's all I have to say.
Let's resume the strategy meeting.
He's going to disappear.
What?
Don't you think it's better to let Ryo know about this?
Y-Yes.
Ryo-san is not a demon.
If he hears that Mr. Plum is retiring, he might give you a flower.
I see.
Stop it.
But...
At the end, I want to compete with Ryo.
No hands.
I'm retiring.
I'm just talking about this.
I don't want to be disrespected by Ryo-san.
Mr. Plum.
You are a man.
I didn't know Mr. Plum would retire.
Senior.
I have to give you a flower this time.
Don't be silly.
He said he doesn't want to be disrespected.
Mr. Plum, this is the last time.
You can buy the robot anytime.
It's a limited sale.
I don't know if I can buy it.
Senior.
It's my bonus.
I'll buy it no matter what.
Oh.
Ryo-san, I got the bonus.
Who gave it to you?
I'll get the bonus this year.
I'm tired of hearing that.
This year.
...
Here it comes!
Oh!
You got it!
The Toshin Dai 2nd Hoku Robot!
Yeah, it seems it's being shipped in the order of the number of tickets.
Ryotsu, you should hurry up and get it ready.
I know.
Hurry up and do something!
You'll be surprised.
Saori!
Saori?
What is it, Tatsuo?
Ah! Saori!
You just replied.
I didn't reply.
This was a dream of the Doki-Memo fans.
I should have been called by my real name, Saori.
You're a robot.
No! I'm the real Saori!
You're totally wrong.
Hey, I don't think you're just a robot that replies.
No, I'm not.
Watch me.
Hey, Saori.
Tea.
I understand, Tatsuo.
Huh?
Here you go.
Thank you, Saori!
Oh, your moves are surprisingly smooth.
Hey, let me try something else.
Then, Saori, one more cup of tea.
I understand, Tatsuo.
Here you go.
Thank you, Saori!
It's the same as before.
Let me try something else.
Then, Saori, two more cups of tea.
Okay, I got it.
Here you go, Tatsuo.
Wow!
Thank you, Saori!
Hey, I can't believe it's only this.
No, I just got it today.
There are still a lot of things I have to do.
Saori, clean up the room!
Hey, Saori, clean up the room!
What? I don't understand.
Saori, I don't understand.
Then, Saori, rub your shoulders.
What? I don't understand.
I don't understand.
Hmm?...
Saori, wash your face!
Saori, rub your fals aqui!
Saori, brush your teeth!
Eh? I don't understand, Saori.
Eh? I don't understand.
This isn't like you can't do anything!
You talk a lot...
Oh yeah, please stop!
I'm going crazy.
This isn't like only tea dolls.
They've always existed...
Like you know anything.
Look at this one.
It's the same manual.
Look at it.
It's just a matter of programming one of the actions.
What do you mean? Do I have to read it like that?
Then shall we cancel it?
Cancel?
If we cancel it, we'll have a bonus.
No, no, what are you going to do with your kindness here, Ryo Tsukakichi?
W-What's wrong?
I'm not going to cancel it!
I'm going to buy it for sure!
I-I understand!
The next day
Ryo-san, are you there? We have a visitor.
Y-Yeah.
Huh? You guys!
Actually, I've been stopped by Plamorya-san.
I thought I'd put you in Ryo-san's ear.
Actually, after the bonus delivery battle this time...
What's going on?
I'm busy! I don't have time to be your opponent!
Hey, Ryo-san, listen to me!
What's wrong?
Hey, Plamorya-san is...
I said I'm busy! Go home!
I can't help it. I think we should withdraw for today.
That's right.
Sorry about that.
You're non-covert, so today we're taking care of business!
I'm busy tomorrow, so I'll leave it to you the day after tomorrow.
Got it.
Then look, I'll make sure you're on time tomorrow, okay?
I'm on it.
Excuse me.
Good job today.
Ehh...
Err...
Well...
Let's see...
Ryo-san!
There was no one who could understand what I was talking about.
What's wrong? The shelves are all messed up.
Well, I was just about to sort them out.
I see.
Ah. I found it.
This is it.
What is this?
This is the one you wanted.
Isn't this a figure for promotion?
I'm a mania, so I would give you 100,000 yen for it.
I'm a mania. I told you I would never let you go. Why?
Even if you leave it, it will become your luggage.
You should give it to the person you want, right?
You won't get any money. Don't worry.
It's a plum.
However, you will have to pay the bonus for the past time.
I know.
Don't worry.
We will give it to this mania.
That's nice.
Isn't it a plum?
But it's the Mania.
What is the Mania?
I just told you, it's a good idea to leave it here.
You are mistaken.
If you bring along many plums here,
This is Nico Nico Ryo.
I'm ready to deploy.
It's finally time, Mr. Plamo.
When this match is over...
Grandma.
Please let me concentrate on this match today.
Please.
Mr. Plamo, you're a man.
We'll send you to the camp.
According to the information from the reliable source, Mr. Ryo's bonus payment date has been revealed today.
Since last year, Mr. Ryo's bonus has been transferred to the bank.
But, based on his personality, he will withdraw from the full-time course immediately.
Don't let that happen. Take all this.
This year, we will win this bonus battle no matter what.
I pray for your consideration.
That's all.
I'll catch Mr. Ryo no matter what it takes.
This is the plan.
This is the last year for Mr. Plamo.
This year alone is for the sake of Plamo.
Excuse me.
Show me your face.
What is it?
It's a different person.
I see.
Wait a minute!
Show me what's in your bag.
This?
W-What's this?
It was on TV.
It's a two-speed walking robot.
This is it?
Okay.
I'll take it.
They're so stupid.
They don't even realize I'm here.
See you.
Ryo.
You didn't do anything strange to Saori, did you?
I don't think so.
I'm sorry.
If you're going to do such a thing, go to the bank right away.
Saori.
Take it.
This is my report!
Saori is coming.
Yes, sir.
I thought you would come to the bank only after 1 am because of Mr. Ryo.
Nico Nico, are you still here?
I'm still here.
Did someone come out?
A big man was helping me last year.
Maybe he was in the action market.
He was helping me last year.
Sakonji?
Yeah.
Soso, do you have any luggage?
Oh, I checked the contents, but it was a robot from Toshin Dai.
A robot from Toshin Dai?
Get into Niconico right away!
Get into Ryo's room!
I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Ryo may have escaped.
How is it?
It seems like he's here, but...
What?
Shut up! I'm sleepy!
See? That's ridiculous.
Ryo! Ryo! Ryo!
Hey, Mr. Pramoya!
Shut up! I'm sleepy!
Even if you fool other people, I won't be fooled!
P-Pramoya!
Shut up! I'm sleepy!
I knew it.
I'll contact the people in front of the bank immediately.
Ryo is coming!
Oh, what?
Don't let him escape!
This is the last fight!
I'll catch him!
What are you doing?
Kaori!
Now, get involved, Ryo!
He's not here!
What?
I-I can't believe it!
I see.
He's not that far away yet.
Go find him.
It seems Ryo has escaped.
Let's go, too.
Ryo!
Okay!
You changed the bank account!
Did you withdraw all the money?
Yes!
I have it in my pocket!
Huh?
P-Pramoya!
What are you doing here?
I found this in Ryo's room.
That's how I found it.
Damn it! I'll catch you!
You fool!
You think you can escape?
It's Snow Mobile!
I've prepared something like this.
Get ready!
Damn it!
You can't use your usual power with this snow.
You're going to regret it!
Damn it!
Get him!
Wait!
Why are you coming here?
Don't tell me!
My bonus!
Pramoya!
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, it's Ryo.
He's broken his leg.
I can't keep chasing him.
Pramoya!
I can't beat Ryo.
I'm sorry.
Pramoya, you...
But I don't regret it.
I can fight with such a powerful opponent.
It's the pride of my life.
Thank you, Ryo.
Pramoya!
Ouch!
What's wrong, Ryo?
He's broken his whole body in shock.
I have to find him now.
Or, maybe I can just take him to the hospital.
But Ryo.
Damn it!
There should be my bonus over there, if I looked.
Too bad!
I have to back to the hospital.
I should have told you.
I feel sorry!
If you need a doctor,
you should go to the field.
There's no doctor in our village.
It's tapi...
Sorry, Saori.
Saori...
I can't believe you're in my eyes...
Come back to me, Saori!
I got it, Da-chan.
Sa-Saori!
Huh? Hey!
Where are you going?
Saori!
Whoa! That's...
We did it! We caught Ryo-san!
It's Flamaya-san's year-end victory!
You're a man after all!
I'm going to make money!
You!
You're lying about moving to the countryside!
I didn't say anything like that to Ryo-san.
Huh? But the store...
We were just preparing for the remodeling.
These days, games are more popular than plastic models.
Why did you think I was retiring?
Did you steal it?
Huh?
Well, you noticed that I was being stolen and acted.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it!
The others will come too!
No, they won't know.
The allies are the first to attack the enemies.
Then, about the retirement...
It's all a lie...
Oh, I know!
The old man's father and grandfather were doing a shop there.
That's a real edukkko!
Huh?
Then there's no way he's in the countryside!
You tricked me!
Shut up!
It's worse if you get tricked!
Now, you'll get a bonus this year!
Oh my!
You think you can get away with that?
I won't!
Just because I never hurt a guy can't mean I won't do anything.
Don't you ever say something like that again!
You think this game is bored and obnoxious?
You said that Basudan was a whole human being!
Who said that Basudan was a whole human being?
You're late!
The next day
Where did it go?
Saori!
Here you go, Dacchan.
Over there!
Stop the machine now!
What are you doing?
No!
What's wrong?
My bonus was turned into chips!
Sakonji, it's your fault!
Saori!
Why did you do that?
You're too upset to get angry.
That's right.
Then, can we get angry?
You tricked us, Plum!
Please, stop.
I had to take the bonus.
It was Ryo's fault.
You're the one who lied!
I don't care.
Ryo!
I'll win next year for sure!
Stop it!
You should retire!
Stop it right now!
I'm sorry.
What happened?
The cars and people around us are frozen close.
Time stops, almost.
Hey, what's up with you guys?!
You can't just call us aliens, right?
Next time, we'll see how time stops in Japan.
Bus stop!
Don't forget to subscribe!
:
Supa Deca сб Terra