Episode Four "Ten defense"
♪N-, n-, when you watch TV♪
♪Make the room bright and separate yourself♪
♪At tip-top speed, like somebody calling♪
I walked while looking back at the rainy afternoon
I was drawn to the gacha
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked the Akegogai tile only in black
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
The politician with a great face and the blue aunt above his eyes
Look around that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall there
Everyone come to our town
Thank you
This is a story of an autumn when my senior saw heaven and hell
The story began from the autumn art exhibition hosted by the Katsushika Book
It's pretty good
Ohara
The art exhibition we started to interact with the locals has finally been recognized.
It's really a wonderful work.
It's like a professional work.
We are honored to be called by the president who is deep in art.
Right, Ohara?
Yes.
This is a work of Jun Nakagawa, the director of our publishing house.
He has been learning painting since he was a child.
I see.
This is a work of my agent, Reiko Akimoto.
This is a wonderful water painting.
It's a real-life work.
This is a work of my agent, Terai.
Ohara, are you going to introduce all the works in the book?
I'm sorry.
Everyone worked hard during their work, so it's hot.
No, no. I'm satisfied.
Is this a work of your agent, too?
This is a water painting.
Ohara, he must have been very happy with it.
Yes, he should have.
What did he do?
He must have put this in the wrong place.
Ohara.
I'll clean it up right away.
Get out of my way.
What?
No, it's not that like in my old world.
OK, this is it.
Good.
Hey, Ryotsu.
What are you doing here?
You're mean, director.
I will help you.
That is because...
Where do you want this, kun?
OK.
This.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm going to exhibit my works.
My works this time are amazing.
First, paintings, then sculptures, a number of crafts.
And the ship made by Matchbow, the eye of the year.
From now on, please call me Davinci of Katsushika.
Oh, this is...
Don't touch my art so easily, old man.
Old man?
Excuse me, I need some tea.
Please come here.
Ohara, do something.
Wait, wait!
Ryotsu, please don't disturb me today.
What do you mean?
I'm just cooperating with the art store.
Listen, calm down and look around.
I know you're in the hall.
Your works are floating around, but you're destroying the harmony of the space.
That's art, boss.
Art always destroys the atmosphere of the space and destroys the values of the spirit.
But your works...
Last year, you made a figure of a blonde woman on a plastic model tank.
Last year, you made a cosplay of a special hero.
And this year, you made a battleship Yamato made by Matchbow.
This is art.
It's not related to the story, is it?
No, it's not.
This is Musashi, not Yamato.
They're almost the same size, but the number of three-layer guns is different.
Is he that detailed?
What do you mean, "detailed"?
I warned you because I said something wrong.
People like you say that a battle machine is a zero-sense gun.
But the five-style guns and Hayate are similar, but they're different.
Stop using too many 'about' words.
Since I'm a police officer, please use correct Japanese.
This is so cool!
Really cool!
I want one!
Look, boss.
Don't you see the heart of my work?
I think those works are real art.
Ryo-tsu, stop.
Art is what Nakagawa-kun and Reiko-kun draw.
Compared to this, your drawings are just a piece of drawing.
A piece of drawing?
Then I'll ask you, director.
What kind of art is the one that Nakagawa and Reiko draw?
But, both Nakagawa-kun and Reiko-kun have been studying painting since they were kids.
They have been to many art museums around the world and have been taught.
Your drawing is different than yours!
Is it art if you have been taught to draw by money?
Do you say that there are no artists in poor houses?
I didn't mean that.
Then what do you mean?
Where is the basis that Nakagawa and Reiko's drawings are art and mine are drawing?
That is...
You two have been in the art world for a long time.
That's right.
It seems that Nakagawa-kun and Reiko-kun's drawings are recognized as art by the world.
That's the basis.
You are more interested in entertainment than art.
What happened to Ms. Debbie?
What happened to the Kano sisters?
Don't underestimate entertainment.
Can you do a bad job in art?
Will art have a jigsaw battle?
What?
You...
I'm sorry.
Can you do a bad job in entertainment?
You...
Let go.
You're a bastard.
Boss!
I can't stand it anymore!
You're so boring!
You two have a corner to support.
Let go of me!
What?
Oh...
Uwaaaahhh... It feels like a classic.
Your work has a strong personality, so it would be better if this was the one.
Perhaps others would pity it if you only treated it specially...
That's good, Senpai.
I'm sorry, President.
Unlike someone else, you're a key to our conversation...
What's with that mean tone?
Ohara! Cut it out!
Ah... I'm sorry.
Hehehehe
I'm so sleepy because I finished it in the middle of the night.
Ohara-kun
Bangkok is not a surprise, so there is no battle ship for the city.
As expected of the chief, a wonderful strategy to defeat the enemy.
You can't do it properly with that guy.
Ohara-kun
I was surprised.
Eeeeee
Nyaaro
Senpai, what should I do?
Do you know, Naman?
Even if you tell me that ...
What did Ryo-chan do in the middle of the night?
It seems that Senpai's works were put in a cage so that no one could see them.
Finally, this year the chief gave a speech.
What is that?
I did it myself.
Actually, Ryo-san's work is a little ...
It's a work to be exhibited at an art exhibition.
I think it's okay if you enjoy it as a personal hobby.
Eeeeee
Even you guys are all insulting me.
I'll tell you, Ryo-chan.
Art is not such a sweet thing.
No way.
Among the artists who are said to be great masters, some people have not been recognized at all.
Eeeeee
So I'm the same.
If no one tries to recognize me, and if I bury my talent, I will be a great loss to the Japanese art world.
It's too much.
Then, why don't you go to an art exhibition?
That's right.
Then everyone will recognize your talent, right?
Yes.
I see.
Then, I will enter a famous art exhibition.
Wait, chief.
I will definitely show you guys a flower.
My painting will definitely be selected.
I'm very confident.
I wonder if it was bad to make him feel that way.
No matter how you think about it, that painting will not be selected.
Considering that it was a easy choice.
Eeeeee
This year, there are so many works to apply.
That's true.
This is the painting of Akatsuka Gahaku's grandson?
Yes.
100% entry rate.
It is the highlight of this exhibition.
The exhibition will start soon.
Ah, yes.
Then, please take the works from the entrance to the venue in order.
I understand.
I have to make a mistake, so I will transfer the works of Rakusen to another room.
That's right.
Tsu, Tsu, Tsu.
O-Oh no, I'm in danger.
My feet are dangerous.
Ah!
This is the work of Akatsuka Gahaku's grandson!
That's Rakusen's place, isn't it?
It was a dangerous place to put Rakusen.
Oh my.
Huh?
There are seven paintings in the new signature work.
It's a bad painting.
What is that?
Forget such things.
Really?
No. 52.
A work by Yoshihiro Miyagawa in Shibuya.
It's a masterpiece this year.
It's really terrible.
I heard that this year there will be a painting of Akatsuka Gahaku's grandchild.
Is that so?
I haven't got a gold medal in a few years.
I'm afraid I won't get it.
This is not good.
I'll have some water. I'll drink some medicine.
No. 53.
This is a masterpiece of Akatsuka Gahaku's grandchild.
What?
It's truly a great talent, Sarah Brett.
How do you like it, everyone?
Yes.
Certainly.
I feel the unique character in this work.
I feel a strong touch and a strong structure.
Is it okay to say that everyone is the same?
Hey.
It's a gold medal.
Excuse me.
I heard that you got a gold medal for the first time in five years.
Is that so?
That's right.
A wonderful work was born.
Excuse me.
Would you like to have a piece of the work?
Yes.
This is the gold medal.
What?
That painting is different.
Yes.
It seems that the name plate has been replaced.
What about the real one?
The one you were talking about?
What's wrong with this one?
What about the painting of your great-grandson?
It seems that the painting is thought to be an abduction.
It seems that it has been thrown away.
What do you mean?
It seems that it was not painted as a 'picture of the audience'.
Please draw here, too.
If this happens, I have no choice but to push the painting through.
Gahaku's painting does not reach the audience.
Oh, no.
So, who is the illustrator of that painting?
It's Mr. Ryozo Kankichi, the director of the Gahaku.
The first entry for the first time.
He's a new police officer,
so he's been picked up by mass media.
It's been a hot topic that a new painter is coming out.
He really is a man of the times.
Tonight, we have a super hot topic.
Mr. Ryozu Kankichi will be on the show.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Ryozu Kankichi, the hot topic right now.
Why?
Why is this painting so popular?
When I think about it, it looks like a strong line of personality.
Yeah.
When I think about it, there are many artists who are like Ryo.
Hello, everyone.
Ryozu!
What's that costume?
Is it a uniform?
What's that uniform?
Oh, there's a very good art store there.
It's my work, which is recognized for its artistic quality.
Isn't it Mr. Ohara, the director who said that it was a graffiti?
What do you think of that theory?
Thanks to that, the graffiti has a value of 5 million yen.
5 million yen?
No matter what, the world has recognized that I'm a genius.
Because there are such achievements.
I'm a treasure of the art world now.
You're being hurt.
Because you're wearing a bag.
I don't want to turn it around.
You're more suited to the art world.
The director is calling.
Oh, Ryozu!
Congratulations!
You are the pride of my Katoshika-shu.
Actually, I saw your work at the Katoshika-shu art store.
I thought, "What if this is it?"
Why did you surround my work so that no one would see it?
I don't care if the person who won the gold medal is small.
Director!
By the way, Ryozu.
I have a consultation with you.
Consultation?
Actually, the director of the department says he wants to buy the first work of your gold medal entry.
What's the matter?
The director of the department?
I understand.
I'll accept it.
Really?
Oh, good.
Now my face stands out.
That's good.
But there is one condition.
No, no.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You have to stick your cheeks closer.
Like this?
Ryozu.
Are you really going to hide our appearance?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
He's an artist of the gold medal.
We, the ordinary people, have no choice but to follow the truth.
But...
I understand.
This is in the way.
I don't like it.
Ryozu.
You don't like it?
Then I'll stop drawing.
Ohara, you have to be patient.
Be patient.
I don't like it.
I'll do as you wish.
I see.
Then,
I'll pose like this.
What?
Ryozu.
Ohara.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Ryozu.
You two are getting better.
Next is...
Ryozu.
Don't move like that.
Then,
it would have been better not to be a model.
That's what art is.
Ohara.
Anyway,
let's forget about him soon.
You're right.
Yes.
Yes, this is Ryotsu, the prize winner of the gold medal at the art exhibition.
Yes, I'd like you to draw a picture for me.
And the budget is...
Wait a minute.
Yes, this is Ryotsu, the prize winner of the gold medal.
Since the park, the price is...
The power of the gold medal is amazing.
You're a good at ordering, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
Is Mr. Ryotsu here?
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations on the gold medal at the art exhibition.
I'm a painter.
My name is Rodoriges Ito.
Nice to meet you.
So what do you want from me?
Actually, I'd like you to help me.
I'm in time.
Don't say such a thing.
Please help me.
Let me go.
I'm saying no.
If you weren't here, you could have made a million with the prize draw last time.
What?
Did you sell it?
No, not yet.
That's good.
It's a problem for amateurs.
In that case, first make a lithograph based on the picture.
Lithograph?
It's a stone print.
If you use this, you can copy and paste many pictures.
You can buy it for 10000yen per piece.
It's limited to 500 pieces.
If you sell 500 pieces, you can get 500,000 yen in no time.
You can also get the original.
It's limited to 500 pieces.
Even if you sell 50,000 pieces, you can't get it.
What do you think?
Do you want to work with me?
I think I can work with you.
You finally understand.
You can open a store.
You can work more than two times.
It's like calling your friend.
He's getting popular.
If he opens a store, it will be a big success.
Related products sold very well.
He also developed new games.
He drew 500 meters in the Expo.
He is very popular.
He is a charismatic artist.
He is good at drawing.
He is a role model for many media.
The guest commentator today is Mr.Ryotsu Kankichi.
Hello.
There's another senior commentator.
He is a member of Bunkajin.
And..
Well, don't worry.
At the same time,
the public and the media are also side of her.
Even though now,
you don't know when
you'll hit her
with your palm.
From now on,
try drawing for her.
And,
now I wanna test your art in the overseas.
I want to try it.
Overseas?
We will have exhibitions all over the world and return as the world's artists and artists.
So please look forward to it.
Sensei, please think about it.
Your work is a domestic work, so it's very difficult to go overseas.
Sensei.
Let go.
I don't want to.
Please think about it.
Shut up.
I don't want to.
Sensei.
If I have the ability, I will definitely apply overseas.
I don't want to.
No.
Let's look for the next newcomer.
Yes, it's me, Ito.
What?
The elementary school student has entered the department store?
That's amazing.
And his senior opened a private store in New York, Paris, and so on.
However, this became a lifesaver.
This marketingavas aeres for overseasvl.
Everyone has been
attacked and run over by the mass media.
Ryo Kankichi's painting is easy to draw or not.
He made news to the news in Japan.
And all the Japanese world came to see him.
That's why it became not that great.
That de facto position as a painter has collapsed.
Sensei was hit hard.
Since failing to open a private store overseas, his reputation is falling.
It's terrible.
This is terrible. It's like a one-shot match.
Well, I expected it.
I was doing it in the morning news.
The people who bought Ryo's painting
They said they pushed the department store and Garou to complain.
I was praised a little, and I was a tengu, so I was punished.
But I feel a little poor.
Where are you now?
Come on, come on, come on.
This is a work of Ryo Tsugahaku, who won the gold medal at the art store.
This is a department store on the corner.
A sister who got white clothes and black clothes and red clothes.
Please give it to me.
50,000 or 100,000 is a waste.
Don't clap when you're in the party.
Wake up, watch your watch, get off, go to the store.
When the door opens, open your fingers.
First of all, if you draw your eyebrows,
To the station, DASH DASH DASH
My train, my father's back,
One sleep
This week as well,
Go-Kuro, Go-muri, Go-mo-to
I'm making a racket with one hand,
But Kyudon, Takumori, Tsuyu, Dakute
As well as the remaining
It's annoying, annoying, and refreshing to solve.
Every day is no problem
If the hot shower goes through
A peaceful pillow to recover your energy.
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
Every day is a No problem
My heart is beating
On Monday
Monday Monday Go Go World
Senpai, this is bad!
My sister Eve is having a fever and she fell down!
So I'm going to talk about the ring I gave her when she was a kid!
Senpai, please look for it too!
I should have buried it somewhere!
Next time on Honda Family Family 2: Eve's Treasure
Please check it out!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!