When you're on TV
Make the room look brighter
And take a look away
A night coming up on the inside
I wonder if you're going to the gym that you used to go to
She laughed at me saying I was just a kid
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can't do it
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn is strangely gentle
From the tapestry of a cap, the sun sets to the taishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
I heard that the happiness of Katsushika and Shiba is also lost
Hey, the seats are broken!
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, thank you.
Hey, mister! Be careful!
Oh, sorry.
Noooo!
Don't touch my butt!
Not me! How can I touch you in this state?
Oh, I see.
I see.
I'm going to the station.
Ouch!
Oh, no!
Why are the trains so crowded?
What?
What's going on?
I want to take a train too.
Huh? The manager is buying a car?
Today and the day after, the train is full.
Every day, the train is full for more than two hours.
Oh, Amalia.
Reiko is on a paid vacation, so she's in trouble.
Thank you.
That's why you have to build a house in the countryside.
But I said I didn't have enough money to pay for a house.
Right now, you're late for such a thing.
Anyw-
The manager, there's a few cars I've only driven a few times.
Do you want it? I'll give it to you.
What? Really?
No, poor you, Kei.
I bought the same color car two times by mistake.
And what's the abilities of that car?
It's a yellow Porsche.
Yellow Porsche!
"Porsche"
I'd pay you 10 million if I were you.
10 million?
I can't afford such a high-end car.
Why not?
I'd be happy to buy it.
You idiot!
You're being moralized by the civil servant.
Even if you're a subordinate,
you can't afford such a high-end car.
That's a waste.
So, how much do you plan to buy?
About 500,000 yen.
Then you can't even buy a new car.
I can buy a used car.
Your subordinates, Nakagawa and Reiko,
are driving Ferraris and Porsches.
But the chief is driving a used car.
I don't want to hear
that you're driving a new car!
It doesn't matter to me.
Wait.
Is this a chance to make money?
You'll get one.
I understand.
I'll help you choose a used car.
What?
You're kidding!
If I bring you with me,
I can't even make a deal.
But, chief,
there's no one who can beat you.
But...
When you choose a house,
or when you travel abroad,
you've achieved a lot.
You're right.
I'm sure you'll give me a good deal.
Leave it to me.
"Your new car is here."
"I'll buy it for you."
"You can't even buy a used car."
I remember a bad face.
I'll be fine today.
Oh.
"Hi."
"Oh, you're a traveler."
"You're selling a used car now?"
"Don't say something so mean."
"This is a honest and honest shop."
"I can't trust you, but I'll take a look."
"That's too bad.
I'm on a day off today."
"Don't lie to me!"
"I'm not on a day off."
"What am I doing?"
"I'm on a day off."
"This car is worth 500,000 yen."
"How is it?"
"It's shiny."
"It's really beautiful."
"It's like a new car."
"There's a way to paint it all."
"Giku!"
"How do you like it?"
"I thought it would be a luxury car."
"It's only 6,000 km away."
"That's right. It's almost new."
"The 1993 model?"
"It's strange that a car that was 5 years old was 6,000 km away."
"Giku!"
"You're right, I can't do it."
"I want to see the engine, so please turn on the bonnet."
"Okay."
"What's wrong with this engine?"
"It doesn't seem to have a very long range."
"Hey! It's only 2 laps per meter!"
"That's ridiculous. It's only 1 lap per meter!"
"It's ridiculous. It's only 1 lap per meter!"
"Oh no!"
"That means it runs 106,000 km, right?"
"This man is such a cheat."
"Friends in Gocho!"
"This used car center is..."
"Please wait!"
"I'm a pro!"
"I'll show you my super eyes!"
"Super eyes?"
This is the price for the two years of full equipment.
I've been looking for such a cheap car all over Japan.
Even the engine...
Indeed, the engine seems to be working properly.
It's not bad, but it's 698,000 yen.
I understand.
I'm a customer of the first round of the conference,
so I will do my best to serve you.
What? Really?
How about it, Ryotsu?
The bumper is new, but the number plate is dented.
This is an accident car.
It's not a joke.
If you buy a new car, you will get more than 2 million yen.
This is an accident car, but it may have pulled many people.
Never do such a thing.
What are you doing?
I'm calling out the spirits that have settled in this car.
Ah!
Three people.
The chassis was just damaged by the car.
It's an accident car.
I got it.
You're cheating again.
I'll deal with you with a fraud.
Please forgive me.
Oh!
What?
It's a Wagen Beetle.
It's nostalgic.
I don't know the price, but how much is this?
Oh, it's not for sale in my car.
Oh, is that so?
When I was young, I admired this car.
You have a good car.
Thank you.
The chief likes it so much.
I'll sell it to you.
He said it was a defective product.
Everyone in the town hall,
this car is an accident car.
It's a defective product.
Please stop.
Then, will you sell it to me?
I understand.
But that car costs more than 500,000 yen to restore.
If it's not about 1 million yen...
Everyone in the town hall.
I understand.
I'll pay you back with 500,000 yen.
I see.
Ryotsu, what have you been doing?
Please be happy, chief.
He says he will sell it to me.
What?
Really?
But it was my car.
What?
There are so many cars.
We are negotiating the price.
Please wait a little longer.
I see.
Thank you.
I introduced you to the customer.
Of course, you will be introduced.
I'm not kidding.
I already lost 500,000 yen.
Please.
I understand.
Please don't be an accident.
Thank you.
I'll be back tomorrow.
I'll buy you the best car.
Good luck to the car dealer.
Ok, I was there.
kendya
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, but it's not a fire truck, so it's a little bit red.
I gave you a million dollars, but don't complain.
Oh, isn't that the chief?
Really?
Chief!
Oh.
What's wrong with this red car?
No, I just bought it.
It's unique in shape, and it's red, and it's kind of fashionable.
I see.
I thought so, too.
You two should drive together next time.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, then.
Yes, be careful.
Well, isn't red pretty good?
What kind of personality is the chief?
No, no.
The Beetle of the Wagen is pretty cool.
Isn't it?
The engine is in good shape, and it can be driven for another ten years.
The chief is the type to be taken care of, so it's all right.
Chief!
The chief wants to talk to you.
Oh.
I'll be right there.
Next time, I'm going to drive the car in Nakagawa and Nikko.
That sounds good.
You're really good at it.
Oh, what are you doing?
Huh?
Ryo-san, get the ball!
All right! Leave it to me!
Oh, senpai!
Ryo-chan, you're the best!
Thank you, Ryo-san!
As expected of you, senpai.
You're different from when you rode a bicycle!
Sen... Senpai! Are you all right?
Ouch...
Oh!
Huh?
Ryo-chan!
Sen... Senpai!
You're in trouble!
Oh, really?
Actually...
If the chief sees this, he'll turn into a demon!
What... What should I do?
Here I go!
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-chan has run out of
Where did he go?
Listen, Ryo-chan.
What's that come about?
That's something I don't want to hear.
Ryo-chan...
You go over there and talk to Senpai.
Yes...
Ryo-chan...
Alright, this should be enough.
Now we just need to paint the plastic.
It's not enough at all.
Look closely.
It's too noticeable.
In this case, I'll just paint the door with this paint.
Oh no, it's broken.
If it's like this, I'll paint it with this.
This too?
Damn it.
How about this?
Again?
I won't give up!
How about this?
It's not in its best condition.
It's the worst.
Oh my god!
How about this?
I know a repair shop nearby, so you should get it repainted.
I've earned 50,000 yen!
50,000 yen?
No, it's nothing.
Alright, let's go there.
I'll borrow the key from the manager.
Manager, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I really want to try driving that car.
Nakagawa will drive it, so can I drive it for about 3 hours?
It's a useless guy.
Well, if it's Nakagawa's driving, it'll be fine.
Don't hit me.
I just bought it.
Of course.
Don't worry.
Nakagawa, I'm back.
I'll fix it in 3 hours.
Then let's hurry.
Senpai!
The president isn't here for dinner.
I'm sorry he's not here.
Find him no matter what!
Got it.
Then, Senpai, please wait in the car.
Oh, come on.
The manager is lost.
He's buying a new car.
I can't believe he's buying a new car.
I'll sleep until he comes back.
Which one is Mr. Yamada's car that the president asked you to destroy?
This one.
It's dirty and the mold is old.
Alright, let's carry it.
Bye!
Goodbye!
Stop!
It's not a car of the accident.
Anyway, the paint is fine.
It's not a good thing.
The owner must have been shot.
President!
It's me.
Huh?
Senpai!
Mr. Yamada's car is still here.
It's not a good place.
Where did he go?
There's no car.
What was that?
Don't be silly.
It's an earthquake.
Stop!
Hey! Stop the car!
Boss!
In the van there's someone!
What?
Sir!
Hurry!
Thank God, he's still alive.
Burn all the bodies.
And take them out.
I... can't believe it.
Ouch!
I was pressed when I woke up. What happened?
You're safe.
You've lived in that space a lot.
You're like the second Hikita Tenko.
The head of the club, Beetle, has become a dango bug!
It's impossible to regenerate.
Do something!
I can't do anything about it.
Take off the body and stretch it out.
Make it the original shape.
Bring it back to Beetle.
I can't do it.
Shut up. Let me go.
I understand.
Let's try to reproduce it.
I'm sure.
I'll be killed by the head of the club.
There are only about 360 cars that look like this.
They look the same.
The size is completely different.
Shut up.
There are only two hours left.
I don't care about the details.
But, boss, the engine is dead.
I see.
I have no choice but to install a different one.
Then install the Porsche engine.
It's impossible.
How can you install a Porsche 300 horsepower engine on a Subaru?
Shut up!
The 300 horsepower engine will make the head of the club happy.
Don't forget the wagon emblem.
I understand.
Is it really okay?
We have to work together.
I'll call you back.
But you'll get to know me soon.
Tomorrow the wind will blow.
Let's go.
Ryo!
How did you feel on the ride?
It was the best feeling I've ever had.
I thought you would go to the other world with such a good feeling.
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
You look a little smaller.
What are you talking about, chief?
Beetle has always been this big.
Oh, I see. Because I've been watching you from afar.
Please look at me closely.
See? It looks big.
It's the illusion of the eyes of the telescope.
I see. It's a misunderstanding.
Huh?
The shape of the mirror is different.
No, no, no. It's the same. See?
The emblem is Volkswagen itself.
That's true, but...
Huh?
How do you open the door?
Chief, you're just kidding.
Beetle has a common front.
I see.
Nakagawa, I'm sorry.
We can't keep chasing oil.
Let's go to the patrol.
Yes.
Wait!
Ryozu, the steering wheel has changed to the right.
No, I can't let you fool me anymore.
No, I can't.
The chief had the right steering wheel from the beginning.
It's my car.
I mean, this is the chief's car.
No, it's not my car.
Please look at me.
Look, Porsche's engine is running.
This is amazing.
The chief is a drag racer.
Cool.
What happened to my car?
No, if you're in this car, Kogyaru won't leave you alone.
I want to know what happened to my car.
My car...
But I'd rather not see it for my own sake.
All right, come on!
Stop!
Hey, hey!
Well, we're going to...
This is my car.
The shape is a little different.
But there's a big shadow.
The door on the left is there.
The engine is in the black part.
I'm glad it opened.
Well, I have to reverse here.
I'm annoyed.
I know.
Very good.
I really don't like this state.
This is the car.
Hey, you...!
It's my car!
Stop!
You little...
You're a passenger...
For once, stop!
The door didn't open.
You're amazing.
It's a fast car!
WS-senpai! The steering doesn't work!
I can only go straight!
What?
I'm in the way!
Chief! It's a speed violation!
Shut up! You're under arrest!
Stop! Stop!
I'm going to stop!
Idiot!
If you keep going, you'll get away!
I'll kick you out!
Idiot!
I'm in the way!
Shut up!
It seems like something terrible has happened.
Good morning!
What's the matter, everyone?
I have something to say.
Chief, you're the best at this season.
Shut up!
Why are you making me and Nakagawa
so busy for you?
I'm sorry!
Good morning.
Uncle!
What are you doing?
♪ The power is greater than anything ♩
♪ Everyone gather here ♩
♪ It's like a dream, the final energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday, draw the universe ♩
♪ If you stand on the ground, the planet with the turtle will come ♩
♪ And you'll get the peace of the world ♩
♪ I'm sure it's good ♩
♪ There's no reason to be happy ♩
This year, too, the bonus is coming!
The shop has been planning to withdraw the debt from us this year,
but, what?
I'm the one who has the most debt!
Next time, Bonus Negotiation 3!
Oh, it's already the third time!