What Iiam Matt
"When you're watching TV"
"Please make the room bright and look away."
I wasn't a good child so I didn't know what a girl was like.
I kicked the ground and flew to the pit
I wonder if I'm going to be paid for it
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is only a thorn
There is no change in my yawn
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of the Tongari City
The sun sets to Taishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
If I were to be the Kazushika
I would be so happy
I was so stupid that I realized
I was the one who lost
Absolute destiny, the final episode
One hour, eight seconds
I'm not going to do it.
I understand.
I understand the position of the staff.
Yes, you two.
I'm stressed at work.
Isn't it?
That's right.
I'm stressed.
The boss is a bastard.
Look at that face.
Tsukamoto-kun.
It's not good for the brain.
I told you.
If you're a brain,
It doesn't matter about quality.
You bastard.
Right?
That's why I'm stressed.
How about a full-time job?
It's cute.
That's perfect.
I'll find you a good job.
A good job.
All right.
Iketa-kun.
Tatsugi.
I'll be your friend.
Yes, sir.
Please come in.
Come in.
We have a guest.
Captain.
You're here, too?
That's unexpected.
We're a parent business.
Please come in.
Stupid.
I'm not here as a guest.
I'm here to report that there's a person
wearing the police uniform and calling me.
Are you the one who came to see me?
What are you doing?
It's my part-time job.
Is it?
Why do you have a part-time job?
It's for the convenience of the people around here.
That's because you're using games and radicons,
don't you?
No.
My business is...
Captain.
If the director finds out about this,
my company will be in trouble.
Just come.
Just wait, I need to work for an hour or I won't be able to get a part-time job.
Shut up, you troublemaker!
What? He called a cabaret while he was working?
In this outfit?
Ryo-sama, I'm not the type of person to work in a place where there are so many girls!
Don't you have any self-awareness as a policeman?
I'm not the type of person to work in a place where there are so many girls!
Life is so hard.
I have no choice but to be happy!
Ryo-sama, you're so pitiful.
I know, Maria.
But work is a violation of the rules.
If you continue, you'll be fired.
If you don't work, you'll die, so it can't be helped!
If I continue, I'll be fired.
If you need that much money, why don't you work in a office?
How about working on a part-time job or helping with the internal finances?
In the office?
But I can't go home without money.
I'll do it! Let me do it!
The chief is a true man of life!
That's too much!
Well, that's much more reassuring for me!
I won't forget your kindness, Ryo and Kankichi!
No, not at all...
A part-time job is like buying a car,
but it costs 360 yen for one car.
I hate it.
I don't know. I need to fill up the gas tank.
It's a pain to move the car one by one.
Oh, right.
I'm so smart.
Wait a minute!
Ryo-tsu! Kankichi!
It's dangerous! What's the matter?
Oh, you're being considerate.
I wonder if the number one man who was hated has changed his mind a little.
Here's a mixture of dried shiso and fruit.
Thank you!
It looks delicious!
I've finished eating.
Well, then, here's your bill.
Your bill?
Yes, the consumption tax.
It's 15,750 yen including tax.
What is this?
There's no way I can pay for this!
Oh, you can't pay for this.
This is a problem, sir.
I'm saying that you can't pay for this.
The ladies are doing a lot of service.
Isn't it too much to say that you don't pay?
Yeah.
Now, pay while you're being nice.
Idiot! You're the worst!
Don't joke around, you idiot!
You stinky shijin!
Don't play minicompo alone!
Damn it! I ran away!
I'll remember that!
Huh?
Chief!
Ryo-tsu! What were you doing?
Were you watching me?
Chief, you're a bad person.
If you're here, you're here.
Idiot!
You're the one who said that you're the catcher in the book!
You idiot!
But my life is worth one and a half hundred and sixty yen.
That's...
Shut up!
You're useless!
Oh, no!
The gas!
Ryo-tsu!
Hold the bird!
Damn it!
I'll do it myself!
Ryo-tsu!
Go!
Oh, dear!
You know, the other day...
Ryo-tsu!
Oh, dear!
Hello, Akashi!
I apologize!
I'm sorry!
I'm truly sorry!
I won't!
Thank you for the trouble!
Subtitles by Subdiver
Ohara, what's going on?
Ryozu did this...
What are you talking about?
The boss threw me out.
I did that because you did that.
What are you talking about?
The boss made me write the deadline.
I got a bonus.
You're not going to get a deadline because you don't do it.
You idiot.
Idiot, idiot.
That's one of the reasons why I'm an idiot.
Don't call me an idiot.
You're a guaranteed idiot.
Stop it, you idiot.
It's your responsibility.
You two will take responsibility for this.
What?
Ryo and Ohara?
The boss threw me out?
That's right.
The boss and Ryo will be transferred to Hirani.
They'll be transferred to a different place.
I'm glad you're done with that.
I was worried you'd get fired.
I'll definitely go to see Ryo for lunch on my high school day.
That's impossible.
Why?
There's a problem with that transfer.
Problem?
If I had to go to that place, I'd rather get fired.
Where are you two going?
To the end of the world.
What?
To the end of the world?
That's right.
The end of the world is an island without a map, a legendary place on the island.
The island is surrounded by cliffs and you can't get close by boat.
It's a disaster.
Once you go there, you can't go back alive.
You're a fool.
There's no place to go.
Move.
Now.
You
What was that?
Not now.
Tixie.
What is this place?
It's a jungle where no one has stepped on.
It doesn't matter if there are dinosaurs or birds on the ground.
This is the end.
It's a jungle where no one has stepped on.
It's like a dream.
Is this the place where people live?
It's so dusty.
Oh, it's the west.
The last date is...
10 years after the Great Shogunate.
No one's coming.
I don't have time to play.
I need to get a pass.
Who's a pass?
Then I'll decide on patrol.
If you go out alone,
you might not be able to come back.
Then I'll go to the mayor.
It's an island without people.
Only the two of us live here.
Oh, oh, oh.
Then what would the two of us do?
Then I'll tell you.
The first thing you should do in an islandless life is that...
That is?
That is to be sure of drinking water.
Drinking water?
For humans to live, water is first required.
If it's an island like this, there's a difference of spring and water.
The first thing is to find it.
That's the first thing.
I see.
That's very informative.
Okay, then, water.
Bring me some water, Ryotsu.
Huh?
No, I'm not saying "huh".
I'm telling you, Ryotsu.
Bring me some water, now!
Chief, no, Ohara-kun.
O-Ohara-kun!
You've become a hira-junsa like me, Ohara-kun.
I hope you don't have to order me around.
We're on the same side, so we have to do everything equally, Ohara-kun.
Okay, let's go together.
Is this okay, Ryotsu-kun?
If you don't want to, you can go by yourself, Ohara-kun.
No, not at all.
Wait, don't go by yourself, Ryotsu.
No, Ryotsu-kun.
Wait, Ryotsu-kun.
Huh?
You're the one who's counting on me for survival.
You?
No, no, it's Ryotsu-kun.
You're counting on me, Ryotsu-kun.
What's wrong, Ryotsu-kun?
No, I can hear a faint sound of water from the other side of the bush.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, Ryotsu-kun!
What's this place?
A lake.
But somehow, it's getting a little quiet.
It's like we're in a Nessie movie.
Ryotsu-kun, something's coming out of there.
I knew it, Nessie.
No, it's the end of the island, so it's the end, right?
What a boring thing.
It's just a tree, isn't it?
Let's go back home with some water, Ohara-kun.
Let's do that.
Ohara-kun, let's take this bucket.
If we lose at rock-paper-scissors, we'll have to hold it for 500 times.
What? Rock-paper-scissors?
No?
No, not like that.
497, 498, 499, 500.
Rock-paper-scissors!
We won again.
Let's go.
Wait, Ryotsu-kun.
Can you let us rest a little longer?
I can't help it.
Just a little longer.
Typhoon No. 17, which has a large and very strong force,
has changed its course from east to west,
and is approaching the Japanese archipelago.
If we keep going this way, the typhoon will hit the end of the island.
Will we be okay, Lord?
It seems to be a pretty strong typhoon.
Are we going to hold it in such a shabby house?
We've reinforced it anyway.
As expected of you, Ryotsu-kun.
You're so reliable.
But the problem is this.
There's only this much we can find and eat.
Come to think of it, I'm hungry.
I haven't eaten anything since I came to the island.
So if you eat it as you desire,
the food will soon be there.
R-right.
I think it's good to put together all the food we brought together,
and then share them a little by little.
I see. That's a good idea.
But I only have this much.
I only have this much.
What's this?
There's only manga and plastic.
How rude.
See? I have a can.
And...
a candy.
Only those two?
Yes.
Alright, now we have all the food we need.
That's almost all the food I brought.
For now, the disaster prevention equipment is okay.
And then...
And then?
To save our stamina and not make us hungry,
we have to sleep.
Sleep...
Let's do it!
That's annoying...
So!
Chief!
You really thought this was it?
No, I just want you to check the contents.
I just wanted to help.
You can't believe that!
This is the farthest place from you.
What the hell?
Be careful, Ryotsu!
Ryotsu!
Chief!
Half of this house is on the sea!
What?
It's not strange for it to fall into the sea after breaking the balance.
You don't have time to rest, Ryotsu!
Hurry over here!
Ryotsu!
Don't eat that!
What are you going to do now, Ryotsu?
Look, Chief.
The floor to the door is about four meters long.
It's a distance that can reach two people if you connect them vertically.
I see.
All right, come on!
Now!
Come on, I already got you.
Hurry on!
Hurry up!
I'll take care of it for you!
Okay!
It's with you!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Stop!
Wait, hey!
What are you doing?
Go ahead and do something!
Go take care of it.
Come on!
Crap, I'm going to получилось...
Yay!
Once more...
Ugh!
If two people go there at once, they'll turn around.
Let's go outside first.
I'm sorry because you're going up.
I understand.
It seems to be fine.
What's wrong?
I can't go back.
This way.
What should I do?
Don't come here.
I don't need this bag.
No, sir.
I don't need it.
It hurts.
I don't want to die.
Sir.
I'm so hungry because I moved so much.
I'm dying of hunger.
Sir, let's eat.
I can't stand it anymore.
Idiot, go back.
Do you really want to die?
But if you can't move, you'll die of hunger.
I'm hungry, too.
I want to eat.
Idiot, go back.
Let's do this.
Let's get closer to each other at the same time.
Then the balance won't fall.
Let's do this.
1...
2...
3...
4...
5...
15...
16...
18...
19...
I'm dead!
It's like yesterday was a lie.
It's a typhoon.
Ryo, are you okay?
I caught it.
Don't say that.
It was a long time ago.
The captain is a typhoon.
What?
You are my prey.
I'm hungry, so I'll stop.
That's right.
Or else.
I'm hungry, so I'll stop.
This is my brother's evil power.
Will the captain's evil power stop?
I can't run.
It's not over yet!
What?
Next time, I'm the star!
Hoshi Touden, you bastard!