Episode Two: The
Father-in-Law
Oh, now she's a date?
That's right, Nana-chan and I are dating, huh?
Why'd you put your work place on hold?!
I work.
Oh, this is just for your tip though.
Sorry for being late.
*Gunshot Noises*
I was just here, too.
I've been waiting for them for an hour.
I bet you need to count the papers.
I just gave it to Ryusei-san.
Ah, hello everyone.
Hello.
It's a big deal.
The relationship between the Shirobai staff and the manga artist.
That's right.
Nana-chan is very busy.
Right?
No, not really.
But she hasn't broken the deadline once.
I'm impressed.
There are many manga artists who don't keep their deadline.
By the way,
Senpai, are you still working on manga?
Of course.
I'm a signer of the weekly Sapphire.
Then Nana-chan is the deadline.
Ryo-chan too.
Ah!
I got a call several times.
I never get a call.
Come on, Honda.
I don't want to.
I'm going on a date.
No, no, no.
Go, Honda.
Go, Nana.
Honda.
When you watch TV,
make your room brighter and look away.
Come with me,
if you don't have money.
I don't have money either.
But I'm worried.
Look,
it's blue.
White clouds in the sky.
It's white clouds in the sky.
It'll come to some.
You know?
You know it.
Then don't say anything.
Follow me.
Is it really as good as I thought it would be?
Well...
Ryuu-senshi! do not let Honda run!
Game Over
Now you'll pay!
Why won't you give me my bike?
My bike!
Mike! Mike! Mike!
Mr. Ryo! What are you doing?
I'm the one who wants to know what you're doing!
You're trying to trick me into stopping my series, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I didn't tell you that today was the deadline!
You don't need to be the fastest.
The speed of the brush is the best in the industry.
Oh?
Please believe me, Patricia Kanko.
Hmm...
Whatever.
Hey, you got anything to write?
What? No way!
You're going to write here?
It's okay if you shake a little.
Huh?
You're holding it, aren't you?
No, that's not good!
What? A new manuscript?
Hmm?
Come to think of it, when a serial writer drops a manuscript,
there's a new manga on it, right?
Ugh!
It's a misunderstanding.
I'll take this!
No! Give it back!
I'll take it!
No!
Huh?
Up!
What's wrong with that?
You're no good!
Well, that's all there is!
No!
That's great news!
Here.
Please have to take it back!
I quit!
Especially since it's my debut work.
I knew it.
Of course.
There, it's complete.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's for the first time to read a manuscript written behind a copy paper.
By the way, where are you going?
Where are you headed?
It's Midori-sensei's apartment.
Midori-sensei!?
You mean that 4-frame cartoonist Midori-sensei!?
Yes.
I'm so lucky to meet the real Midori-sensei!
Midori!
I've been waiting for you, Ryu-sensei!
Midori, how's the work going?
It's all done!
You look like lovers.
You're so sweet.
Awesome! I'm so hungry!
You did a great job this time, too.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
How about some wine to celebrate the work?
That looks delicious!
I'm sorry, but there's still room for more.
What!?
Food! Wine!
This is a great success!
Natsuki Mimi-sensei, thank you so much.
Again?
You're so good at winning the lottery.
It's true.
It's a great success in history.
Then, shall we buy a car to celebrate?
Look!
I prepared this car for you.
I'd love to, but it's still too late.
It's too late.
What's wrong with you?
Next time, you can go out with me.
Sure! I'm happy to do that!
I hope you can give me a pen as soon as possible!
I'm so happy!
I'm the only one who's not happy with it!
Ryu-sensei, you're all ours!
Hey!
Hey, I'm begging you to give me a pen!
Yes!
Senpai, can I go on a date with Nana-chan?
What?
What did you say?
Is what you just said true?
Y-yes!
If the date is canceled, the next manuscript may be affected.
Mr. Honda, please go on a date right now!
Y-yes!
So, I'll let him go soon, Miko.
See you again.
Thank you, Ryu-sensei.
Ryu-sensei, you always think about us, the cartoonists, the most!
Stray!
The editor is a great job!
Being surrounded by such a beautiful woman is like being in a harem!
Let me do it once!
No!
The editor's relationship with the author is important!
No matter what!
Yes, Ryu-sensei!
It's been a while, Chaka-bon!
What?
The editor's hand is missing?
It's changed!
It's Ryu-sensei from the super editor!
No!
Of course, it's OK!
See you tomorrow!
Here.
Ryu-sensei!
I need help!
Is there a problem?
The French publishing house.
Here it is.
It looks like it's going to collapse eventually.
Ryu-sensei told me about it!
I was out of help.
I also wanted to borrow the cat's hand.
What a reason...
The weekly magazine of men is important now!
It's all about jouissance!
It's so far from the harem.
Huh?
Don't you have a relationship with young girls?
I have.
Actually, Nagisa Shiratori, the photographer at SIMO ait resistance at my place,
is Billy-san's man!
What? Nagisa Shiratori is a super popular idol who has been on TV a lot lately.
Yes, if this photo book hits, the French publishing company will be a member of the best publishing company.
Good, I will be in charge of that photo book. When is the shooting?
I finished it in Hawaii last month.
This is the photo book.
Oh, it's a pretty good picture.
If I put it on the Internet auction, it might sell well.
What? There's a UFO outside the window!
What? Where?
No, I was mistaken.
What?
Then, please take care of the work.
Oh, yes.
-Kouhei! -I'm home!
-I'm sorry to bother you! -Please wait.
-Send this fax! -Yes, yes!
-Kouhei, are you still there? -Yes, I'm home!
-Hurry up! -Yes!
-Hey, Baito! -Yes!
-Kouhei! -Yes!
It's already 11:00 in the morning.
What's that?
I can't!
I'll work hard on the part-time job.
-We're in trouble! -We're in trouble!
-Baito, you can do it now! -You're good!
Sorry.
No!
-I'm sorry!
-You can't do it! -I don't want to be a thug!
-What's that? -Sorry.
-No! -You can't do it!
-I can't do it! -I'm sorry.
-It's a great relief for the staff! -I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Listen to me.
I'm really sorry about this.
-No! -No!
Wait a minute!
I'll do something about this manuscript!
It's the manuscript of the most interesting manga artist who's got the main manga of the week, "Nandemo Goraku"!
And the 8 pages of it are burned to the ground!
If the teacher's manga wasn't on it, the readers wouldn't buy it!
No worries, no need to worry.
Really?
Yeah.
There's no page after this, right?
No.
Then let's look at this manuscript first.
W-what are you doing?!
Shut up!
Yes!
In this way, divide the 5 pieces of each page and look at the first two.
This is...!
The first page—it's already out!
Now, it's the car.
The other side.
Widen it.
Okay.
2 pages are completed.
You can see the stopped scenes from the second page.
Only one page...
This isn't just anybody's art!
It still says more 5 pages!
And there's this little frame left here!
What do we do?
Now we've got five pages.
DRIVE!
COPY!
The manga will expand little by little, and it will gradually come closer from the other side.
This is the second page of the right-hand side.
Move forward to the first page.
One page further with the face up.
And the last is continued with the eyes up.
What a powerful last!
So everyone, the 16-page manga is complete!
Awesome! I did it!
Awesome!
It's amazing!
It's the help of heaven!
Thank you, Mr. Ryotsu.
Now our car will be saved.
Oh, my gosh!
Of course, Omonnai-sensei's manga is also burning!
What?
I can't do anything about it.
Only two pages remain.
Two pages?
Of course, Mr. Omonnai-sensei's work is also a work of entertainment along with Mr. Mangaichi's work.
No more!
Is this the end of our publishing house?
No, it might be fixed.
What?
But only two pages remain.
It will be fixed.
Fortunately, it's a conversation scene.
Hmm.
I made it!
It's true!
That's all.
I see.
Then say it once again.
What?
Say it.
Sorry.
I can't do anything about it.
One more time!
Wow!
It became a proper manga!
Next, it is a danke.
A nuk?
That's all.
I see.
Hmm.
Wait, it's a danke!
Oh, I made it!
Thanks.
Well then...
Oh, again!
Damn!
I made it!
Oh, I made it!
Thanks.
Well then...
Oh, again!
Damn!
I made it!
Wow!
This is amazing!
We can continue with step by step,
if we combine this "one more time" and "discord".
Wow, that's great skill!
Mr. Boss!
Could I also try?
This too!
But this is...
Leave it to me!
This conversation will be a laughing matter.
I'll make the volume of the volume bigger here.
Turn this picture over.
Expand this.
He's really a reliable person.
So, I went to get my manuscript.
It's over.
We can somehow release it with this.
Please pay for my part-time job.
Of course.
I've read it again.
I'm sorry for using it for nothing.
From now on, call me Super Editor Ryozu.
Yes, Ryozu Super Editor.
Would you like some coffee?
I'd like some Japanese tea.
This is bad!
The film of Nagisa Shiratori's photo book!
This is almost burnt!
I should have printed it on the first page tomorrow morning!
We can't release the photo book with this.
Why?
What is this?
It's the end!
It's too early to give up!
But there are only 5 photos left to use!
Don't worry.
For example, this cut.
Up.
Reverse.
Do the layout.
It's like another photo!
MSM.
Or from a different photo and...
A combination.
Well, they were good!
This must be a couple of photos!
Let me have a look!
Oh, I think I saw it.
It's your favorite photo!
I have no choice!
If you do more than that, you'll get as many photos as you want!
As expected of Super Editor!
This will fill up a photo book in no time!
But there's not a single photo of the important swimsuit!
That's right! It won't sell without the swimsuit!
Swimsuit, huh...
By the way, I remember there was a photo of Nagisa Shiratori in the magazine last week...
That's it!
This is it!
Oh, that's perfect!
I'll take this!
It's a photo of a magazine from somewhere else, so it's not good!
I know!
If you keep it like this, it'll be bad...
Change the pose...
Arrange with the real thing...
Change the photo...
Change the pose...
And then change the color of the swimsuit!
If you keep it like this, no one will notice!
Is there another one?
This is good, but it's black and white.
Leave it to me!
This is easy with the computer.
Take this!
OK!
Find a photo that everyone can use!
There's no enough background in Hawaii, so I'll just make it to the whole world.
Is there no other photo?
This is all of it!
There are 20 pages left!
All of them are difficult...
Umm...
During the Hawaii shoot,
I have some snaps I took during the shoot.
Oh, that's great. Bring them here right away.
Nagisa-chan, I don't see you much.
It's just the manager and staff.
Is it still no good?
No, let's go with this.
You can draw a girl's-like circle.
It's a setting called the real album.
I see.
There are 16 pages left.
Put the real thing in.
It's written in the idol's photo book, right?
What's wrong with love? What's wrong with love?
It's like a plot.
It's hard to get the real thing.
I'll draw it little by little.
The blue sky is beautiful.
The white clouds are beautiful.
The favorite food is steak.
It's a barbecue restaurant.
Nagisa?
Is it okay?
It's an emergency.
There are two pages left.
Okay, it's a book service.
Nagisa Shiratori's real-life story.
The last page is a foot.
It's like a snowman's foot.
Nagisa Shiratori's image is...
Good morning.
Chocobon, wait a minute.
Yes.
What is it, president?
How's the progress of the photo book?
That's already...
That's good.
Actually, I was wondering if I could double the page and make it a luxurious book.
What?
Well, I will take it.
This is the manager of Nagisa-chan's production.
I was asked what to do with the president.
I'll ask you for your great photo book.
But I'm not going to finish it overnight...
I'll pay you.
I should have taken a lot of pictures, so it's okay, right?
But...
Leave it to me, president.
How about you?
I...
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi, the super editor who was specially hired to make the Shiratori Nagisa photo book.
I see. That's very helpful.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
In return, Mr. President, would you like to give us a special bonus for selling the photo book?
Oh, that's great.
That's great. As expected of Mr. President.
It will be a 100-page book.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
What are you going to do? You're so cheap!
There are no more photos!
Leave it to us. Everyone bring as many photos as you can!
What?
Can we use this?
Believe my skills.
You don't know the faces of elementary school students, so I'll let Mr. Nagisa be in here.
All old photos will be for the family.
That's terrible.
Lend me the company's pamphlets.
What are you going to do?
I'll put Mr. President's words on the first page of the photo book.
It's like a graduation album.
I'll introduce KANTO COLOR to the company and add an advertisement for hiring employees.
And the profile and family introduction of the president.
That'll fill 20 pages.
No way!
And I'll pay for the novel "Jirocho Gaiden" through 30 pages.
I'm gradually leaving idol photo books.
Can I publish this?
No one will buy it.
It's okay.
Idol photo books are sold.
What will be in the book, the fans will buy it.
All right, the contents are all here.
Everyone, finish this up tonight.
This one is for the aunt.
And the rest is for the president's daughter and his little sister.
Well, the number of copies has expanded.
This is difficult.
Hey, is this the photo book?
But this is...
You're just like a relative.
I guess someone is looking for you.
Ah, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I would like to have a cup noodles .
Here you are.
All right.
It's done.
Hey, Mr. Ryotsu.
You're really helpful.
Huh?
What is this?
Doesn't it smell weird?
Oh, I see.
It's all burned up.
It's over.
What the hell?
This is...
This is Nagisa's Pocifilm!
Ryo!
What the hell is this?
That's...
What?
Why did it get in my pocket?
It's weird.
What?
Ryo!
I'll show you my photo book!
This is the popular photo book by Nagisa Shiratori, a French publisher.
It's a book with 400 pages of photos,
but the fans buy at least three of them for display, assembly, and storage.
I can't believe this is a hit.
It's a book for display, assembly, and storage. I can't believe this is a hit.
I don't know it.
This book is a hint to how Ryo would devise his own product.
What?
Isn't it kind of cool, Ryo?
It's a shadow laborer.
Everyone was happy to get a special bonus.
I should've run away.
You should've run away.
This is Nagisa Shiratori's photo book.
"Akai no Dairo"
Let's go!
There's a wall over there
There's a wall for sure
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What?
Two billion yen of property is with me?
But if I don't use up half of it in a week, the rest will be taken away?
What? I won't lose to anyone!
Next time, I'll be a millionaire!
See you!
There's a wall over there
There's a wall for sure
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!