Exclusive - Summoning the Super Saiyan
I'm the Super Saiyan!
Here I come!
If this is the case...
Now, let the mob have a toast to the peace of the world!
You're really better than the last one.
This one, this one!
That's it.
That's it!
You're out, Mr. Monster!
Hey! How long are you going to keep sleeping?
Mr. Monster!
You fool!
When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away.
"I'm not going to sleep."
Come to me, you poor thing.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'm sure it'll be alright.
Do you understand?
I do, I do.
If you do, just shut up and follow me!
Mine Only: Katsushika Pro-Wrestling
Oh, dear.
I'm in trouble.
I didn't think a real person would show up there.
But even if you tell me to get to work, the world is peace itself.
Katsushika Pro-Wrestling?
I've never heard of this organization.
Let's take a look.
Wait.
What kind of old-timers are they?
What the hell are they?
"I'm a furu! I'm a furu!"
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
What's the point of threading a fabulous story like this?
Let's do some other things.
I'll kill you!
What?
What kind of old-fashioned wrestling is going on in the era of fighting?
You can't call your guests with that kind of wrestling!
I found you!
You there!
You mean me?
Yes. Can you come up to my ring?
What?
Actually, I've been keeping it a secret, but my Katsushika wrestling has been going on for a long time.
If I don't, the organization will be gone.
You can see it by looking at the secret.
That's true. I've loved wrestling since I was a kid.
I got rid of it last year and finally started my own wrestling organization.
For some reason, my legs are still not straight.
I guess so. No one would want to see that.
Why? I'm doing my best all my life! Why? Why?
First of all, wrestling itself is old-fashioned.
That's the same as wrestling in Rikidouzan.
But that's the kind of wrestling I liked.
That's not good.
The martial arts world is evolving every day.
Your wrestling is clearly different.
It's a time-lapse.
Then what should I do?
I see.
Okay, leave everything to me.
Well, then...
I'll become a wrestler and a producer and rebuild this organization.
Really?
However, half of the sales will be mine.
What?
Pro wrestling?
That's right. I'd like everyone to lend me a hand.
Why do we have to wrestle?
I don't want to do that.
I don't like it either.
How pitiful.
You guys are such cold-hearted people.
I'm so pitiful that I'm about to cry.
Senior.
Ryo.
There was a man once.
He loved wrestling more than anyone else.
And one day, to make his dream come true,
he started a wrestling organization himself.
That's what Katsushika Wrestling is.
However, due to the ups and downs of the world,
his business collapsed.
He had to give up his business.
But I want to say this.
Do you have to give up your dream?
No, it's not like that.
It's definitely not like that.
You must never give up your dream.
But, but...
You guys...
Why do you care?
You became a police officer.
Isn't it to help the people in trouble?
The man who dreamed of wrestling.
Let's make him a beautiful man with our hands.
Isn't that right?
You guys...
Senior, I was wrong.
You're amazing, Ryo.
Ryo, I'll do my best.
All right, that's what I expected.
I'll give you lots of money.
All right, I'll give you lots of money.
I'll give you the rest of the money I have.
Just answer the phone.
If you can promise me,
I'll go there and make sure
I'll go and replace you with someone else.
But, uh...
I have different opinions.
Mapo, please!
He say you're a good person.
A good person?
A good person?!
I see, I see. That's great.
I'll teach you that pro wrestling is in America.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, everyone's here.
I'll hand out costumes and scenarios to everyone.
I'll read them carefully until the match.
Scenarios?
Pro wrestling isn't just about matches.
You need a drama to get there.
You need a wrestler's character and a drama outside the ring.
I see.
You're wearing this?
Do I have to do this?
I don't like it.
Idiot!
You're in trouble.
You're not going to let me go?
Why did you become a cop?
I was wrong.
You're great, Ryo.
Ryo, I'll do my best, too.
That's what I'm looking forward to.
Let's go!
Everyone at the venue.
From today, I, Katsushika Pro-Wrestling,
will be reborn as the new Katsushika Pro-Wrestling.
The new Katsushika Pro-Wrestling is about to begin.
Now, this is where--
Get out of here, you poor people!
What's that?
What?
Nice to meet you all, the poor people at the venue.
I am the owner of the gorgeous mask,
Shinkatsu Shika Pro-Wrestling.
I'm the owner of this store.
Today, for the sake of all you poor people,
I will show you the best wrestling.
Because I have money!
What's wrong, former owner?
Pick it up without hesitation.
You're in trouble with money, aren't you?
Now, owner, pick it up quickly.
Or do you want more?
Here, how about this?
Stop!
I won't forgive anyone who uses money to spoil the entertainment of the common people!
Oh, no. The poor man has come up to the ring.
Go home quickly.
Here, your train fare.
You're a bunch of rich bastards.
You won't let me do whatever you want with this new ring!
I got it.
Then, let's have a match.
If you win, I'll give you the seat of the owner.
I'll accept the challenge!
Red corner, 190cm, 120kg.
Mad Volvo!
Blue corner, 168cm, 82kg.
Kabutori Kamen!
B три.
Go!
Come at me!
You can always win in the match.
Shut up!
KittyKitty!
He really can play pro-wrestling?
And he's pretty good.
So good!
Now, today's main event.
Huh?
Masked Gambler, where are you?
How are you, Minnanoshu?
What are you doing? It's time for the match.
The match doesn't matter anymore. Look at this!
Oh, that's the company's money.
What's going on?
Wasn't he on the owner's side?
Yeah! Money is everything in the world!
Well, goodbye!
That's mean!
What a guy!
Get up, I'll blow you up!
It's too late!
Let's go!
You're good, Masked Gambler.
This is for everyone!
You're the best!
I-I'm...
I'm...
I'm... a...
I-I've never received so much applause!
Hehe.
Everything is in the script.
Thank you, everyone!
Thanks to you, we were able to promote the new Katsushika Pro-Wrestling.
Well, we just did what we had to do.
Well, let's talk about the next match.
The next match?
Huh? The next match?
Hey, owner.
The customer just arrived.
He-He left early.
Oh, really?
Huh?
Hey, what's going on with the next match?
Isn't that the last one?
Ryo, it's the owner's last match.
He said he was going to the end.
Hey, you idiot!
Today's match is just the beginning.
The new Katsushika Pro-Wrestling is just beginning.
You can change your mind in a little while!
But you guys...
I-I know.
Oh, really?
Well, I hope you understand.
Nyehaha!
Pro-wrestling is awesome!
Good morning!
Huh?
By the way,
Ryo's really not here,
nor is Nakagawa and Reigo here.
Good morning!
I-I'm sorry.
I was late.
Oh, no, you're not late yet.
It's unusual for everyone to go to work together.
Yeah, well...
Senpai, it's impossible.
Touring around the country while working...
Don't complain.
I managed to make it in time, so it's okay.
I can't let go of such a big chance.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Yes, what is it?
That article is...
Our game yesterday...
There's been an interesting pro-wrestling lately.
Have you seen it?
No, it's my first time.
How about Nakagawa?
How about Reiko?
No, I didn't know either.
Is that so?
I didn't know.
I see.
The president and everyone at the office went to see it.
It was quite interesting.
I'll go see it once.
Reiko!
No, pro-wrestling is...
It's been since the Rikidozan on Gaito TV.
Senpai, it's not good.
If the chief finds out...
Don't worry.
The chief didn't even find out, so it's okay.
But Chief Ohara is surprisingly good at thinking.
R-right.
This is the ticket sales area.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's a ticket for Shinkatsu Shika Pro-Wrestling.
I'm sorry.
It's sold out.
What? All of them?
Yes.
Shinkatsu Shika Pro-Wrestling is as popular as a giant battle ship today.
It's on sale and on sale at the same time.
Oh, is it that amazing?
Oh, that's dangerous.
Oh, hello.
I'm sorry.
It's a ticket for Shinkatsu Shika Pro-Wrestling.
All the tickets for today's sale are on sale.
Oh, no more.
Last one.
Huh?
It looks silver.
Too bad.
Here's your tissue.
What?
That's a bad one.
That's not good.
How should I move the ticket?
Hello, you there?
You have a findings on having a chance to be able to watch pro-wrestling, don't you?
Why do you ask me that?
But, you must not watch pro-wrestling.
Why?
if you go and watch it, you will be unhappy.
Understand?
You must not go and watch pro-wrestling on the good stuff.
No, it's not.
Ahahahahah! If you keep it that way, the head of the club won't come to see you.
Ryotsu-san, what are you going to do in the next match?
I've already made a plan. Look at this!
Oh! This is a champion belt!
It's a title match of all the players participating in the Battle Royale format.
The one who remains in the ring until the end is the champion!
It's a size called "Champion"!
That's great! It's the best!
That's right! That's right!
All right! I'll make it fancy next time!
What a thing to do!
It's unfortunate to see a professional wrestler.
Well, I can't get a ticket anyway, so I'll go see it.
Thank you very much.
Here you are.
Oh? This is...
Hey!
This ticket...
What does it mean?
Oh, that's...
Look! Please take a look at that.
No, it seems that the venue of the shopping club was pushed together, so I'm giving it to the person who bought it for free.
What?!
Thanks to everyone, the venue is full!
I'm going to be more excited than usual today!
Oh!
And it looks like I'm going to enter the venue and say "Good morning. How are you?"
Come on!
That was great!
Well...
And finally, the dealing of the first dome.
This is the first time ever in recent years.
It's the first time for this match.
How will they enjoy this match?
Welcome to the venue, the poor people!
I didn't expect to get a ticket at such a place.
I'm lucky too.
Tonight, we'll have our first title match.
Who will be the strongest wrestler?
Let's go!
I got the belt!
Move!
You move!
I got the belt!
You coward!
Go!
Come on!
Senpai!
I'm a masked gambler.
Please take a look at the ring side.
Huh?
Hey! Don't take a rest!
Back off!
Why doesn't the manager pay the trains ticket?
What to do?
At least I didn't get Masked.
What should I do Ryo-sama?
When you come to this,
So, we have to make sure that the true identity is not revealed.
Everyone, let's start the infection prevention operation of the chief of Ohara.
Wait a minute. I feel like I've seen that wrestler like a bird somewhere.
Please, Sagonji!
What? Damn it! You're not the one who did it!
Hey, hey, hey! Can't you see?
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
I feel like I've seen that wrestler somewhere.
Sir, you are Ohara, aren't you?
Oh, yes.
We have a visitor who wants to see you, so please come to gate 131.
What?
But...
There's no other way.
All right, it's all good now.
It's finally 72.
If we don't hurry, the match will be over.
It's finally time to settle the score.
I won't lose! The belt belongs to me!
It's a dead-end. There's no gate 131.
Come to think of it, why did he know my name?
Oh, dear!
I didn't expect Chief Ohara to come.
Really? Really?
We're just doing wrestling. It's not fair to us!
You!
Hey!
Chief!
I showed you everything!
Now, I'll explain everything!
1, 2, 3!
We did it! I'm a champion!
"It's the champion!"
"He did it!"
"The Masked Gambler has finally become the first champion of the Shinkatsushika Pro-Wrestling!"
"Now, the champion belt is about to be wrapped around the back of the Masked Gambler!"
"Wait a minute!"
"Huh? Who's that?"
"I don't remember writing such a scenario!"
"What are you doing?"
"Wow!"
"I was hearing you from the first thing in the morning!"
"You're getting everybody involved in the pro-wrestling industry?"
"That's your own business..."
"You're getting agreements that you'll get half of the profits!"
"Look who's talking!"
"I've got to rescue some people!"
"You can't make a profit off of your friends!"
I will never forgive you! I will beat you up again!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Give up, give up, give up!
Wh- what the...
W- what the!
The man who entered the audience took the tap out from the champion!
The second champion is a mysterious male guest!
That's impossible!
The man who entered the audience or...
...he's a monster...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
...that's impossible!
The man who entered the audience is a mysterious male guest!
Give up, give up!
The four of us, and the champion entered the audience and...
...the champion entered the audience too!
I'm not interested in it
Even if I lie and cheat a little
I'm helping someone
Baby do you know me?
I'm headed for tomorrow
I'm in a nice breath
Don't be sick
I'll do what I have to do
I'm in a cute breath
That's right I don't want to show you
Isn't it better than looking down
Living the dream of the future in a hard way
That would be in the end
It can't be helped because he's the son of a monk
The name of a monk's son is "Goribanto of Life"
By the way, what's the relationship between that and stamp rally?
Next time "Stamp Rally for Dad Who Can't Run"
See you!
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!