Thank you for listening!
I gazed at the rising sun
that swivels over Inakakawa
When the love stone was kicked out
it flew away to the shoes
From the water tank in the Tungari-boshi
To the sea of Kai-shaku
The sun sets
Tomorrow, it'll be over already
Katsushika, Shibamata, and happiness
I lost them and realized
I'm such an idiot
Shut up!
You're in the way of my work!
Sorry, I slipped
You can't be satisfied with just one cup of tea
You can't go to your wife's house
Look around you
Hiromi, Keiko, Kaoru
They all went to their wives' houses
That's why
You'll end up with just one cup of tea
If you notice that
What?
You're so stubborn
I tried to make you some tea
You're trying to fix it
You can't go to your wife's house
You can't go
You can't write a death note
What?
You...
Shut up!
You're such an idiot
Seriously, what the hell is it?
Oh my goodness
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Reiko!
You must be kidding me.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hey, is he alright?
Ouch, he hit me hard.
What should I do?
Papa, you're...
Papa?
It's Reiko's papa.
I can't believe you're the president of such a big company.
Ouch!
Papa, you alright?
Are you okay?
Oh, Reiko.
What's up?
I was on the phone, but I was always off, so I was on the way to the office.
The office is a mess.
I can't work in this situation.
It's your fault that it's messed up.
If I were the manager, I would have made it a great office.
If the police are civilized, please buy the office.
Is this Reiko's desk?
Yes.
It's a cheap desk.
It's terrible.
I can't stand it.
The chair is the worst.
Oh, what a poor kitchen.
What an unhygienic bathroom.
It's not a place where humans can work.
I didn't expect Reiko to be beaten so badly.
Did you come all the way from Kobe to complain?
Yes.
Hey, Takeshita.
Operation 189, start.
What's going on?
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, wait.
Hey.
Hey, Dad.
I'm on my way to the office, so please go on patrol.
Dad, open the door.
Hey, open the door.
Oh, my God.
I don't understand, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Hello?
Hey, what's with the hideout?
What's the purpose of the hideout?
Well, I can't handle it.
It's always like that.
Oh, it stinks.
Oh, my God.
I wish I had been a teacher.
Ms. Seiji and the others both intend to stop the call.
I hope it's not about that.
Oh, please, don't stop.
It's an emergency.
We have a new defense device.
It's so fancy.
This is the old one.
This is a new one.
It's a new type.
It's warm.
It's a system kitchen from West Germany.
Wow.
Hey, Reiko.
What's this?
My daughter always takes care of me.
I'm Akimoto Pyunpyunmaru, Reiko's father.
Oh, thank you.
Wow, it's very powerful.
Very good.
I can build a cup noodle house in a second.
Reiko, how did you like it?
Reiko has been rehabilitated to make it easier for her to work.
Please, make everything as it was.
Make everything as it was.
You made it easy for Reiko,
but you're going to make everything as it was?
Of course.
What did you come here for?
Oh, that's right.
There are so many pictures here.
I got them from the bank and the bank account.
You can just look through them.
There are so many.
It's going to take days just to look through them.
Hey, Reiko.
How about this?
You can see Reiko at a party.
Sorry, but please don't do that.
I don't want to get married yet.
What?
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
I see.
I brought the pictures just because you asked me to.
The life of Reiko is deciding who you choose.
I believe in you.
Papa.
Hey, clean up.
Thank you.
I'm just a father that knows what I'm talking about.
That's right.
I've got some things to do at the bank.
I can't refuse without saying no.
Please be with me.
But...
President, it's about time for the meeting.
Oh, I see.
Papa!
I'm counting on you!
Oh, Papa, you're such a...
A 32-year-old son of a real estate agent,
and a house of 2,000 square feet?
He's like a cucumber.
A 700 billion-year-old company.
I can't help it.
I'll just refuse him.
You'll refuse him?
That's a waste of 7 billion.
It's not about the money.
But if the other person really likes you,
I think it's even worse to refuse him.
Yeah, it might be rude.
Huh?
What should we do?
I'm worried.
Don't worry.
If Reiko goes out with him,
she'll be afraid and refuse him.
Ryo, what do you mean?
You have to stop it.
I'll kill you, Ryo.
If you make this stupid Reiko angry,
I'll fold you and throw you into the river.
Come on, Ryo.
When did I ever do that?
What?
That's it!
Reiko...
You're late, Akimoto-sama.
Yeah, you're right.
It's already been an hour.
I just want to pee.
Wait, Katsuo.
Anyway, I know.
There are so many things I have to do.
The Akimoto family is different from us.
Maybe you'll inherit that wealth,
you might end up becoming your own one, you know?
Good!
Even if you have a bad personality or have some shortcomings,
you should keep an eye on it.
I understand, Mama.
Oh, sorry for being late.
Hello, hello.
You're here.
Reiko's father caught a cold,
so I, the uncle, came to take care of him.
Nice to meet you.
It's Reiko. Nice to meet you.
"The
"The picture is completely different from the picture.
"This is definitely a firecracker."
If we succeed, we'll be able to conquer Tsurukabe Prefecture.
So, is that Reiko?
Yes, it's Reiko. Do you have a question?
Well, it seems that the picture you're looking at is a little different.
Oh, it's often said that I'm bad at taking pictures.
Reiko is quite...
You're talking about a lot of firecrackers, aren't you?
Yes. 500 cigarettes a day.
I've been drinking too much shochu and beer,
and now I'm talking like this at karaoke.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, Reiko, you have many hobbies, right?
I love horses, especially horses.
And then, I like carpentry, mahjong, pachinko, fencing,
karate, boxing, and I like fighting.
Even if I'm in a fight, it's the best.
Everyone is full of blood and...
No, Reiko-san is good at jokes.
Oh, you're serious?
Then let's show him how it's done.
Hey, later you won't get hurt by Reiko-kun's criticism, so be careful.
The purpose is to make him refuse to meet her.
I have to be careful.
You're quite a lively young lady.
Hahaha, I'm raised in freedom.
Mama, Reiko-san is scary.
I told you, you should close your eyes when you see a little problem.
A little?
I had so much fun with my little partner the other day.
Ryo-chan...
Oh no!
Oh, my throat is dry.
Wow, you're a great drinker, aren't you, Kazuha-san?
Y-Yes, I am.
I'm glad you like it.
Damn it.
Then...
It looks delicious!
It's delicious!
Reiko, I'm so happy!
I can't stand it anymore!
Reiko, you can't!
I'm so full.
You're eating so vividly, aren't you, Kazuha-san?
Yes.
You're eating so vividly.
Health is the most important thing, after all.
I like it even more.
This is tougher than I thought.
It's like this.
Hmm, I can't help it.
Well, it's about time.
Leave the rest to the two young people.
What?
Kazuha-san, let's go.
Mama, I'm scared.
Come on, you bastard.
Then, I'll go there.
Enjoy it.
Mama!
Good luck, Kazuha-san!
Well, I'll play with you a lot.
Mama is gone.
Just me and Kazuha-san.
When will you return?
You bear it,rade.
I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
I'll leave.
I'm leaving.
I will come back with you.
But I'll never begin.
I'll return with you.
But I'll leave with you.
Come on, nervous.
What's this?
It's something like an air-conditioning çaque made in a long time ago.
That is a whip.
I can't believe it.
Wait, hey.
I'd rather have a gorilla.
Who's a jerk?
You don't deserve to be called that!
You're a big bastard!
I'm sorry!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, I mean...
Reiko-san is a very aggressive person.
I wonder.
I always get angry when someone says something bad about me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, right.
I have a request for a classical concert from my mother.
Classical?
Andre Heilrichten, Johann Autobahn,
Humboldt, The Undelgern Concert, No. 348,
"The Song of the Forest"
It's six hours long.
I'm sorry, but I hate classical music.
I'll play it again next time.
I don't think you like it.
What should I do?
If you don't like it,
you can just say no to the concert.
Really?
Don't worry about it.
I'll give up because I thought there was no chance.
Then, I'm sorry, but...
Yeah?
About this...
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, excuse me.
Yes, Mom.
Oh, Kazuo-san.
You're doing your best at the concert.
You're going to make it work no matter what.
I know, Mom.
I'm getting along with Kazuo-san, so don't worry.
Don't worry about me.
Hello? Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I slipped.
Hello? Hello, Kazuo-san?
So?
What?
You said you would say no to the concert.
No, it's ridiculous.
Oh, really?
It's not a cheap woman's strategy.
If this happens, it's the next step.
I have something I want.
Can you buy it for me?
Of course.
480,000 yen?
Well, it's a nice bag.
This one?
Yes.
I'm scared.
No, I want it. I want it, Kazuo-san.
You have a good sense.
I understand.
Hey!
He's got the wrong number.
It's 480,000.
Here you go, Rekou-san.
Here you go.
Thank you.
He paid 480,000 for this.
I'm glad I can see it now.
I want a jewel, Rekou.
A jewel?
I want it. I want it.
Ishikoro Takaga is so scary.
I don't know what to buy.
Please choose whatever you like.
Choose whatever you like.
Here it is.
This big one.
1, 1.2 million yen.
Here you go.
Damn it.
Look at this.
I'll buy it to the point where I can't pay for it.
This red one.
The green one next to it.
This big one.
I'm sorry.
No, you can't.
This one and this one.
Sir.
No matter how beautiful a person is,
it would be a waste if he was so cold to me in the first meeting.
Well, it was a success.
Can I have all of this?
All of it?
Yes, all of it.
It's 158 million yen in total.
One million?
It's 58 million yen.
What?
Excuse me.
Yes.
Can I have a little?
Why do you have so much money?
My father gave me a company last year.
I'm the president there.
Is that so?
I don't have the courage or the strength,
but I have more money than anyone else.
So don't worry, Reiko.
I'm just doing this for a cup of katsudon.
Damn it.
Next strategy.
It's a failure.
I can't believe it.
It's our turn.
Do you have anything you want?
No, I'm fine.
What's wrong with that woman?
She's a man, too.
But it's a miracle that a man is here.
Oh, really?
Hello, Reiko.
How nice to meet you.
Oh, it's you, Kei.
Huh?
I'll give you some money to work with later.
Um, Reiko, are you a friend?
She's my ex-boyfriend.
She's cool, isn't she?
What?
Reiko's always been charming.
No way.
I can't stand her.
I'm so worried about the fire.
Hey, Reiko. I missed you.
No, it's Honda-kun from before.
Before?
Reiko, in my car...
I'm doing this for you.
But...
Can you fly me to Haneda in my car?
No, I'm flying you to Yokohama in my car.
Sorry.
I'm at a wedding, so I'll see you later.
See you later, Reiko.
I love you, Reiko.
Bye-bye.
I can't believe it.
I'm so worried.
I'm so fat and I'm so skinny.
I'm so sick of it.
You're so pretty.
You're so kind because you've been living abroad for so long.
What?
You're a perfect match for the president's wife.
I have few friends, so I envy you, Reiko.
It was so hard.
The plan "Go, go, cheating girl" failed.
What?
It's the final plan.
Do your best, Terai-senpai.
I can't believe it.
Soon, my seniors will come here.
And then...
Hey, brother.
Help me.
I don't like people who don't trust me.
Goodbye.
Now you can refuse.
I'm sorry for him, but he's going to refuse this time, so I'm sure.
This way.
Where are you going, Reiko?
It's a good place.
It's strange.
I'm sure they're standing around here.
It's too late, Ryo-chan.
Where did they go?
This is the first time I've walked in a place like this.
Hey, brother.
Where are you looking at?
What? Are you there, Terai...
Who do you think we are?
That's real.
Help me, Reiko.
Help me.
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
It's not what I planned, but I can refuse this time, so I'm fine.
I can't believe you're asking for help.
You're a fool.
Hey, brother.
You don't have to apologize.
You guys, stop it.
What's wrong with you?
You're a fool.
Who are you?
You and I are fools.
I had a good day today.
But I'm a mean, rich, manly man.
I'm not your wife.
Don't worry about it.
I'll say no without hesitation.
Reiko.
Yes?
Please marry me.
What?
Reiko is my ideal woman.
At first, I was a little scared.
But I'm strong and reliable.
I'm good at everything, and you're perfect.
I can't think of any other woman but you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Reiko!
Did your father say anything after that?
No, nothing.
So the wedding was a success.
I feel like it's a waste.
Thanks to everyone's cooperation.
Especially Ryo-chan.
Thank you.
No...
I'm sorry, Reiko.
Congratulations, Reiko.
You're engaged to Kazuo-kun, aren't you?
What?
Reiko!
No way!
What's going on?
Ryo-san!
Kazuo-san!
Reiko!
What?
Reiko-san!
Let's go buy a second-rate helicopter today.
I'm so happy.
Reiko will be able to fly the Atlantic!
I want an Italian high-end metal helicopter called the Atlantic.
Kazuo-san, buy it for me.
What?
What are you thinking?
I don't think this kind of lie will last long.
What is this?
Reiko will marry Kazuo-san and live happily ever after.
Let's go, Kazuo-san.
Yes, Reiko-san.
Hey, Reiko.
I have other things I want.
Anything is fine.
I'm so happy.
You fool!
I'm so happy!
Humph!
pacifist.
No, please!
It's like a
I'm getting off for taking a light meal.
I'm sorry.
Thank you on the plane.
Good morning.
I'm ready.
I'm rumored to be a woman who can't do anything
But there are so many things I want to do
I want to ride on a bike through the vast desert
I want to be free more than a bird
A lady's dream that changes at the speed of light
I'm sorry, I'm losing my love
I'm going to dive into the future of the panorama
You understand, don't you?
I'm sorry, I'm losing my love