《One Seventh Girl》
Melody
Te, te, terebi wo miru toki wa~ When you watch the TV
Heya-wa garukku shite hanare te mite ne- Try to be in your room and leave it
Nakagawa ni ukabu naru hi wo megakete Swim across the river and catch the sunset
It's so kind.
From the tapestry of a capricious hat
To the taishakuten, the sunset falls.
Tomorrow will end like this, won't it?
If you're a Katsushika, you'll be happy again.
I realized it after losing you.
I'm such a fool.
Kankichi did a good job, didn't he?
Exactly, Kikichi.
He made the school go crazy and the thief followed him.
Everyone is happy to be with me.
Of course.
Kankichi, you got scolded by the principal, right?
Yes, the temporary teacher.
Kankichi is really into it.
Ah!
You guys were like that, too.
Thank you, teacher Yoko!
Ah, I remember.
You opened the door to the new place.
Yes, but that was in junior high school.
I only remember good things.
It's been a long time since we've seen each other.
Don't you have any good memories?
No.
The only memories with Kankichi are
when you were scolded or scolded.
You're so bad!
I'm so sick of him.
Here we go.
Oh, no!
You don't have toственно either.
I'm not!
Do you know the reason why Kankichi's so hard?
I mean, he was that big,
and he was so big!
He even slept on his back when he fell asleep.
régnement,
you know.
One day, he opened the city gates,
and he was like this.
I don't remember his face,
because he's so silly.
Oh, yeah! What was the name of that movie theater?
Hey, Kankichi!
What happened to Ken-chan?
Shinkichi, why are you so quiet?
You didn't know because you were a police officer?
What are you talking about?
He was arrested.
Huh?
That's a joke, right?
That's not the kind of thing Ken-chan who studied the most would do.
He was a police officer.
I was on the train for a while.
Why would Ken-chan do that?
He was a Yakuza officer.
What?
Ken-chan?
I'm going home. I won't come back.
Hey!
Kankichi!
Ryo-chan!
Didn't you go to class?
Yes. Do you have any news from yesterday?
If it's a full-pub, it's next to the stream.
Ken-chan.
Did something happen to the police?
Why?
I don't know.
I go to class.
Ryotsu!
Chief.
I thought I was arrested in my office, but Ken...
Murase is...
I think he was transferred to Asakusa
who's responsible for the cooking case.
Ryotsu!
What's wrong, Senpai?
It's different than usual.
Ken-chan!
Kacchan!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Ken-chan!
Ken-chan, why?
You...
I don't know!
Hey, stop it!
Are you alright, Ryotsu?
Get in!
I know.
Ken-chan!
Wait for me!
Hey, can I try one?
Of course.
Ken-chan!
a illegal idea.
I have a question.
I asked the police, but he was working in a group with the Odaiba gang.
The police said he was hiding his hidden face.
The Yakuza now don't have the same kind of personality as they used to.
Yeah.
Ryotsu, you may have been a good friend, but the Yakuza are Yakuza.
The world we live in is different.
Just forget that you didn't see them.
That's right.
It's not like you and I are friends.
We're not friends.
He wasn't like that before.
He was rich and smart, but he was strange.
I wonder when he was.
He was scolded by his father, and he left home.
Kaonkichi!
Are you still going to the Edo?
I'll eat you alive!
You're so good at drinking.
I'll ask Mom if she has been drinking.
Our world was no different.
Mom, you were beaten down by your left hand.
What happened to you?
-It hurts! -Come on!
-Come on! -Come on!
Ken-chan.
What's wrong, Ken-chan?
Did the food not suit your taste?
No.
I'm envious of Kan-chan.
Me? I'm joking.
We live in such a big house,
and we have to take care of the car.
My house is like this.
Dad is a violent person.
Mom is a mischievous person.
No, no, no.
Ken-chan is better than me.
No, no.
I've never had such a fun meal with my family.
What? Why?
It's not a big deal.
Anyway, Ken-chan.
Come to my house whenever you feel lonely.
What? Really?
I don't have any tips, but I'm very welcome to your house.
Thank you, auntie.
Uncle, this is the way, right?
It's a good meal. I like it.
Let's have a drink.
You!
He was a good guy who knew the customs of the city.
Where did he come from?
I went to the station to pay for the drinks.
I'll check the cook.
What? Murase has escaped?
Nakagawa, wait.
I this is Ohara.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
The Katsushika office has requested for an investigation.
Nakagawa, let's go.
Yes, sir.
I'm coming with you.
It's a secret. You're good.
I'm coming.
You might hit your friend in the hand.
I'm a police officer.
Ryotsu.
I understand.
Change into your uniform.
Yes, sir.
Murase has strong potential to escape to the police office where he betrayed himself.
Firmly surround the Asakusa police office and its surroundings.
30 people from the Katsushika office have come to support you.
Yes, thank you.
The culprit has taken the gun and is running away.
Please be careful.
So what is Murase's clue?
He will appear at this place where the police office is located.
You can't catch him at all.
Yes, sir.
There.
Senior!
If you're Asakusa, you should know the name of the island.
I can't find it.
Wait for me in the police office.
There's a man.
He's a police officer.
Watch out for him.
Ryotsu...
You are familiar with me, aren't you?
Ken-chan
Shut up.
Don't come closer to me.
Ken-chan.
You used to play with demons around here, didn't you?
Can't you hear me?
If you come any more closer, I'll shoot you!
You're playing with the gun.
How nostalgic.
Come on.
It's not me. I'll shoot.
I hear a gunshot!
What?
Over there!
Hurry, Nakagawa. It's definitely Murase.
I'm sure it's Murase.
You're pretty good.
Now let's play some pro wrestling.
You're kidding!
That was a good punch.
Are you trying to get in my way?
Of course!
Get him!
Damn it!
Don't move, Ken!
I don't know what happened, but you're the one who lost when you lost your life!
Shut up!
You idiot!
You're still fighting like before.
Well, I guess.
Captain, let's arrest him.
Wait.
What?
Leave it to him.
Ken.
Why did you become a yakuza?
Well, I'm sorry.
As Junior High school He is a slipper.
I'm young, but I'm in a different league.
I wanted to come here to see my mom.
My father wouldn't let me go.
And my father was drinking at the well during Junior High.
He was in a famous college of New school.
I was famous in high school, but I was bullied by my father.
I couldn't stand it and sent him to the hospital.
The rest is a life of falling down like a picture.
When I realized it, I was a gold badge.
Don't be so greedy!
Don't blame your life on others!
Don't blame others!
Your life depends on yourself!
Did you forget about the "Beigoma"?
"Beigoma"?
That's a lot!
Kanchan, can I have one?
No, no!
This is my treasure that I bought at the market.
You can get better at it if you want.
But I don't like "Beigoma"...
I'll make it for you!
Really?
I can't do it...
You have to be more energetic!
One more time!
Okay...
That's right! Be energetic!
Be energetic! Be energetic!
Listen, don't blame others!
Yes!
Of course!
Do it, Esuke!
Begin!
Ten-chan won!
I did it!
She's strong and weak, and she's strong!
Damn it! Remember that!
I'll be your opponent anytime!
Look, Kanchan!
The "Beigoma" that I won has grown so much!
One, two, three!
Yeah, it's amazing!
Kanchan's "Beigoma" is a special "Beigoma" that has a large size!
Also, it's a left-handed, so you can't lose!
Really?
Yeah!
I have 100 of them!
What? 100?
That's a lot more than me!
Wow!
I used to have only one "Beigoma"!
If you can't beat me, you're out of the town!
Tomorrow, let's go on a trip to the next town!
Yeah!
The smile you gave me when you won with your own strength!
It was the best!
By the way, something happened.
Do you remember where that "Beigoma" was?
No.
I still remember it.
That was the day before you moved to Shibuya.
I'll give you the "Beigoma" that you've won so far.
Really?
To enter the private junior high school.
I have to go to the cram school to get it, so I can't play with it.
We've gathered 100 of them, but it's a man's military record!
This "Beigoma" is...
Yeah, but if I find it, I'll be thrown away.
That's right!
I have a good idea!
Let's bury it under this tree as our treasure!
Then we can put it out whenever we want to use it!
I see! Tan-chan is smart!
Brother!
This is it!
Hey, I heard you took the "Beigoma" from your brother.
I didn't take it, I was playing a game!
Shut up!
That's it! Give it back!
It hurts!
Hey, stop! Let go of my hand!
You're a naughty kid!
Kan-chan!
You were naughty and bad!
You're a big, thin beast!
What?
Brother!
You're back!
You're really strong, Kan-chan!
You defeated the sixth-year students!
I won't lose to you if you fight!
With your strength, even if you become a villain, I'll become a lawyer and help you!
You're tough, Ken-chan.
I said that, but I became a yakuza, and you became a police officer.
The world doesn't work as you think, Kan-chan.
If you say so, I'm the Prime Minister!
That's not true.
I don't care about the beating.
I'll do as you say, Kan-chan.
I see.
You have a good head.
You can start over.
I guess I'm starting way too late.
Hey, the police are over there!
I know.
I want to stop by.
I'll definitely take action before the sun sets.
Can you let me go, Kan-chan?
You finally called me like you used to.
I got it.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting in the office!
Senpai!
Nakagawa!
Senpai, are you sure you want to let me go?
Why didn't you arrest me?
I'll take action.
What? You believed him?
It's okay, Nakagawa.
Chief!
Ryotsu, you've shortened the distance between us, right?
Yes.
Senpai, it's almost sunset.
Senpai!
You're so noisy.
Don't worry.
I'll go on my own.
But...
Are you a kid?
You took back your gun.
Why didn't you arrest me?
I'm Yakuza.
If Murase doesn't come on his own,
I'll have you take full responsibility.
I understand.
Wait!
Ryotsu.
Yes?
It's okay.
You can trust Murase.
But...
Thanks to you, I'm used to writing self-criticism.
Chief...
The sun's already set.
Looks like you can't write well.
Hooray!
Ryo will definitely come on.
O...
Ohara...
Why were you there?
I'm very sorry to have ruined your reputation
after wishing you the best luck in my life.
It's nothing.
Why?
Why do you're coming back?
Genki...
I'll send my kind to Asakusa
to make you sit on work.
The city is yours now.
Let's go apologize to the chief of the Japanese Ministry of Justice.
Senpai, look!
Huh?
Ken-chan!
Kan-chan!
You're late!
You're worrying me!
Sorry. It's been 30 years since I last came here, so I got lost.
I must have gone the wrong way.
Kan-chan.
You idiot.
How could you blame someone who came here to help you?
Let's go.
Chief...
Yeah.
I think it was around here.
It's after I dug it up.
Found it!
A letter?
It's about the good-for-nothing Kan-chan.
I'm sure Kan-chan will come here too.
Thanks to meeting Kan-chan, I regained my heart from 30 years ago.
I'll borrow a 100-person bagel bar for a while.
It's my pride.
2001 may not be possible, but I'll make sure to get better the next time I see you.
I look forward to that time.
Kenji.
That guy.
Let's open this treasure together when the 21st century comes.
Yeah.
What will Kan-chan do in the 21st century?
I wonder what he'll become.
Of course, I'm the Prime Minister.
Ken-chan is smart, so he'll be a lawyer.
Yeah.
Kan-chan, don't forget to move.
We'll be friends forever.
Of course.
I'll never forget it.
Yeah.
I can't wait to meet you here again in 2001.
Okay.
Let's dig deeper.
Don't let us find you.
Well.
Since we're in Asakusa,
you want to come to my place?
Yeah.
Well.
They're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they
they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together, and they're all together,
The End
What? My younger brother Kinjiro is getting married?
I didn't hear anything at all!
And he's invited to Nakagawa for the wedding,
but he didn't even send me my brother's invitation!
What the hell is going on?
Next time, "As a Brother!"
Hey, Kinjiro!