When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and look away
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
I walked looking back
I held my mother's hand
As I walked home
I felt
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk
On the black tile of the arcade
I was a child once
But everyone was a child
I was a politician with a big face
And a blue aunt
Look around
At the corner
You can meet everyone
There's a wall over there
There must be a wall
Come on everyone
Let's go to our town
Thank you!
Good morning.
What?
Did you drop the contact lens?
I'm looking for the spine of number 52.
What is that?
It's a dinosaur model.
I need one.
OK.
You guys
During work
This is
Ryo
Captain, just like that
I found it.
This is it.
This is the spine of number 52.
This completes the Brontosaurus.
Don't make such things during work.
Captain
Senpai is a teacher at elementary school
I'm made by being asked.
What?
The number of parts is 148
Because it is a precise model.
I can't make it with an amateur.
It's like a jigsaw puzzle.
To make it exactly
It's more difficult than jigsaw.
Moreover, Captain
This morning I separated the parts from the runner
When I painted and dried it
I was very surprised
I was surprised
There was a problem
I haven't seen you in a long time.
I have never seen it.
Thank you.
I think it will be a bad expression.
I can't see it.
I've seen it in a long time.
I don't know the Death-Sword
I have never seen it.
The pain of Saraha
Kouji
Let's go to the tent.
It's too much to pay for it alone.
I thought you had a problem with the change of the mayor.
Of course not. It's the duty of the people.
-Okay? Pay it properly. -Okay.
Oh, that's right.
Senpai, our Nakagawa Enterprise is going to hold a dinosaur exhibition.
Do you want to come see it?
Really? I'll go.
Pay the tax and then go.
Okay, I understand.
I don't want to be complained by the people of Chiba.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
I'm going to patrol Ryotsu Prefecture.
That idiot.
After all, the real thing is different.
It's different.
I want it.
What? You can't.
I'm not saying I want this.
I want a mold.
A mold?
Yes, a mold.
It's possible if you help me.
Let me have a look.
What?
I killed it.
Senpai, don't break it.
It's okay. Don't worry.
What would you do with a bone mold?
I want to make the same thing.
When I say that, I don't want to delay.
It's terrible.
That's the end of the Prontozaurus.
Let's go back.
What are you talking?
I'm still waiting for this.
Are you doing it?
Next is the Tyrannosaurus.
I'll never have a chance to take a mold from a real thing.
I'll take it all this time.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I go every night.
To the bone marrow.
It's been a while since I took a break.
I guess I'll go on a date with Nana-chan today.
Mr. Honda!
What's up with you since early in the morning?
I'm in the garden.
Oh, Mr. Ryosu is building the skeleton of the dinosaurs.
Huh? Senpai is?
I really wanted to have this as an object in Ryo's garden.
With this size, I can decorate five or six bodies.
I see. You're like a senpai.
Hey, Honda.
You must be bored today. Help me.
No, I was thinking about dating Nana-chan today.
Hey, Honda.
Who was it that made you date Nana?
Oh, that's...
Who was it that comforted you when you were being dumped?
Senpai.
When humans are happy, they forget about the past.
I see. I'll help you.
I'll help you.
What? I'm sorry, Honda.
I'll bring you the biggest bone there.
All right. I'll bring you the biggest bone there. I'll bring you the biggest bone there.
I'll bring you the biggest bone there. I'll bring you the biggest bone there.
No, no. I can't carry myself all alone.
Your bones are huge. What are you talking about?
Oh, it looks light, but it's still light.
It's made of lightweight plastic. And it's got strong insides.
I see.
All right. Put it here.
Put this back on and hold it tightly.
That's great.
I'm a model maker.
Can I bring my friends and show them?
Bring them here.
Bye!
The children will be happy.
Ryo, are you going to make money?
No, don't say that.
This is just a personal hobby.
I'm a model maker.
I have sharp insight.
Wow, you're really good.
You made not only the skeleton,
but also the skin around it.
How is it?
Isn't it amazing?
If you complete the Brontosaurus,
you can open it.
It's more powerful than our dinosaur store.
It's because it's expensive.
I made it with the help of a model maker.
I don't pay for the tax,
but I had a lot of money.
No, it's all debt.
This is for the children to see their happy faces.
And it's not a profit.
It's not a profit.
But it's like a real thing.
It's light for what it looks like.
It's hollow inside.
I see.
I made a mold based on the cast iron I took the other day.
If you have a mold,
you can make as many ponpon as you want.
You can make as many ponpon as you want.
As expected of Senpai.
Listen, this is a secret from the director.
Yes, sir.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
By the way, director,
please look down.
There is a wheel on the foot.
It can be moved when used widely.
I see. You have a lot of ideas.
I do it when I do it.
Hey, Ryo!
Ryo!
The order is coming from all over the country.
More than 10 million black cards.
Oh, no.
He is weak in numbers.
He is mistaken.
He is a trouble.
Pay the public tax quickly.
Yes, sir.
Look,
he made lots of orders from all over the world.
He makes a lot of money.
Whether it's public tax or public tax,
I will pay it.
The typhoon 55,
is approaching Kanto region
along the north-eastern route.
We need to be careful.
It's a strong wind.
It's not good to have typhoon in this season.
OK, I'll go out.
Are you patrolling in this wind?
No, I'm going to see the dinosaurs.
If they fall and break,
I'll be in trouble.
You are a person who is easy to be fooled by money.
I'm not going to lose to typhoon.
Damn it.
Ouch!
Ryo.
You came too.
I'm worried about the dinosaurs because of this wind.
OK, let's hurry.
Ouch!
Ryo.
What?
It really flew away.
Ouch!
My design is great.
It's because I made the inside of the bone hollow and raised the cost.
I'll raise the price of Pteranodon's replica.
No, no, no.
It's not the time to say that.
Oh, no.
We're in trouble.
It got away with it.
Aww.
Oh, no.
詠
-Azeo is stuck!-
This feels like a怪獣映画!
Here is the Tokyo suburb!
The typhoon 55 that is approaching Tokyo Bay
is even stronger than that!
Huh?
Mr. Camera, how far can you go?
Behind you!
Don't you know what happened?
The typhoon, no, the dinosaurs have landed!
This is bad!
What is it?
The city is in a panic because the dinosaurs have appeared in the suburb.
What?
Dinosaur?
I'm sorry!
I came to pay the public tax!
Due to the typhoon,
the dinosaurs of the Dinosaur Park in Sumida were blown away,
and the suburb was hit by the typhoon.
The whole city is in trouble.
What happened to Ryotsu?
He got on the Pteranodon and ran into the suburb.
He made something terrible.
Hey, what are you doing?
The T-Rex has destroyed our roof!
We are Block Bay!
You should pay for it!
Because the typhoon is so powerful!
You guys are talking!
Give me the president!
The president is not here!
I won't forgive you!
I will bring the president here right now!
Damn it!
Hey, I'm in a pinch!
If we continue like this, we're going to be gone.
The order came from around the nation.
To get 100 million golj Merci, right?
So, with this incident,
We have cancelled everything.
What?
There is only one way.
We can manage the order if we take an order from all over the world.
But it's not a simple thing!
The debtmonitor is coming to our house!
Herro-san, please make something of it!
It can't be helped!
It was a mistake to calculate the typhoon.
When the sky turned red, you promised to hold half of it.
What is it?
Look at this!
"Discovered at the end of the century? There was a living dinosaur?"
"At the island of the surprised peach, the dinosaur's footprints were discovered?"
It's a lie!
It's the same as Nessie of Nesco, Cushy of Kushiroko and Ishii of Ikedako.
Look carefully!
Nessie was upset at the picture of the pinball, but this is different.
There are footprints and it's clearly in the picture.
What if it's real?
I'm going to catch this dinosaur.
If you capture a real dinosaur, you can become rich overnight.
Just by showing it, it will become popular like when the panda first came to Japan.
Next, I will make a gay into a circus flower.
Can't you make a gay into a dinosaur?
What are you talking about?
Godzilla also made a gay into a dinosaur.
I don't know about that.
What? It's a monster war.
You don't know about that?
That's a movie story.
My dictionary doesn't have the word "impossible".
In the end, I will use the current genetic science and increase the number of dinosaurs.
If I make a dinosaur park like Jurassic Park, I will become the richest person in the world.
I'm happy with it.
Senpai, are you seriously looking for a dinosaur?
I'm not serious.
I can't move my neck because of debt.
I just want to make a fortune.
Why don't you take me too?
You surprised me.
"Nessie'sGANZIGRAPHY GENERATED"
It's not an island with dinosaurs, it's more of a tourist attraction.
Well, senpai, please contact me if you catch any dinosaurs.
I'll come pick you up.
They're pretty huge dinosaurs.
Please make a big boat when you come pick me up.
Understood.
I'll be waiting in the north!
That idiot, he doesn't believe me at all.
Alright, I'll catch anything and anything.
Hey, Honda!
I'm here to have a beach date with a Paskin gal and a Koora star.
Idiot! We're not here to go sightseeing!
We're here to catch dinosaurs!
Let's go!
Yes.
You're starting to get a little weird.
Well, how's that?
You're starting to get the hang of it, aren't you?
Huh?
What's with that crowd?
Oh, I don't think the dinosaurs have been caught by now.
We can't go in from here on.
What are they?
They're the inhabitants of this island.
Oh, you're Japanese?
Mitsurin is a sacred place on this island, so humans are in the way.
What?
I'm not kidding.
We're here to catch dinosaurs from Japan.
We'll let you in and catch anything and anything.
Hey, senpai.
Wait!
Shut up!
Let go of me, you-
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Senpai!
What's that?
Is this sound a dinosaur?
It's the sound of our queen!
Open the door!
What?
What the hell is that?
Listen carefully and remember!
I am the master of this island, Princess Onoroke.
Princess Onoroke?
You mean the relative of Princess Mononoke?
Whoever goes into this cave will surely get the wrath of the guardian god of this island.
They must not go in!
The guardian god?
I'm Nusshi, the surprise prank.
What?
Nusshi?
If you're going to say it, you should say it from the beginning.
So, what is that Nusshi?
What are we looking for?
I think this nell is the mysterious dragon!
You think so?
Then there is this dragon!
Right, more and more fights are starting now!
Are you not listening to me?
Anyone from this island has finally entered this dungeon and returned safely.
Stop looking for dinosaurs and enjoy your vacation on this island!
Princess Onoroke Sisters!
What?
Princess Onoroke!
Queen Onoroke!
Wow!
Let's enjoy our island life more than dinosaurs!
We are working for the hotel "Amazing Fruits".
Please come to stay with us!
Everyone, let's dance together!
Wow!
Hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing? You're stretching under the flowers.
You can't do that.
Let's find dinosaurs by ourselves!
Let's go!
Disgusting, Branders!
"Amazing Fruits".
How about "Dinosaur Dumplings and Dinosaur Sambal"?
The winners will get the chance to see the most beautiful sunset in the world.
I want to go!
You want to get my sambal?
Yes!
I want to get your "Dinosaur Dumplings".
Hey, don't you have any more?
Thank you.
What are they doing here?
Everyone, it's showtime!
Ah! That's "Digital Digger"!
Hey, "Digital Digger"!
Oh, it's Ryozu.
Long time no see.
What are you doing here?
I'm on a vacation with the special police officers, the Dolphins and Moon Diggers.
I'm free, so I'm here with the Onoroke Brothers.
I knew they would come.
And why are you here?
I'm looking for dinosaurs, of course!
Unlike the free people on vacation, I'm busy.
Let's go, Honda!
Yes, sir.
See you!
Wait, Ryozu.
What?
I found something here.
Hey, hey, hey!
Take this.
What is this?
It's a shell.
Blow it when something happens.
It'll come running to you.
No, no, I...
Don't hold back.
I'm not holding back!
See you later.
Hey, everyone, sorry to keep you waiting.
Say that again!
Damn it! Who's blowing this?
Oh, hey, hey!
Senpai, I don't know what's going on with the dinosaurs.
Shouldn't we have them?
Then you should have them!
Let's go!
Yes, sir.
Hey, princess!
We don't have money to play, so I'll help you find the dinosaurs!
Hey! Wait!
Owner!
Princess Onoroke...
Whatever.
If she finds out the horror of the jungle,
she'll wake up and come back right away.
Senpai, I'm starting to get scared of you.
What are you talking about?
You're a man, so you're pathetic.
Let's go back!
Let go of me!
You're a hopeless person.
But I'm hungry.
What's that?
It smells like food.
It's true.
It's over there.
It's food!
Look, Honda!
What's that?
I'm sure there's a party in this jungle
looking for dinosaurs other than us.
What?
That party was partying here.
I'm sure this is that thing.
You're talking nonsense.
Senpai, this is too unnatural.
What?
This is usually called a trap.
A trap?
That's right.
You idiot!
Why didn't you tell me it was a trap?
If you thought it was a trap,
why didn't you tell me sooner?
I'm sorry.
Senpai, that's...
Huh?
Hey!
You guys got caught in a trap, too?
Damn it.
Who the hell is this guy doing this?
It's foolish to get caught in such a simple trap.
Huh?
You're the real Dad, aren't you?
You're Ryochi Kankichi?
You didn't come here to look for dinosaurs, did you?
That's right.
I'm going to use my Hon-dara-genpo as a bait to catch dinosaurs.
You have the same mentality as Senpai.
Shut up!
Hey, Hon-dara-daddy!
A dinosaur can't learn such a vulgar-genpo.
If you can't do it,
you'll have to pay a fine and make a profit.
See? It's the same.
Hey, you!
I'm going to catch the dinosaurs!
You're the one who's the one who's going to catch the dinosaurs!
You're the one who's going to catch the dinosaurs!
Shut up!
It's useless! It's useless!
Those knifes won't be able to cut iron!
We'll take care of the dinosaurs!
Let's go!
Okay!
Hey, hurry up!
Look at Hon-dara-daddy now!
It looks like he's having a hard time.
Well?
Shall we help him?
Hey! Come on!
It costs 50,000 yen a person.
What?!
What? 50,000 yen?
Please pay the cash first.
Don't joke around! Don't get involved in business if you're weak!
-Hey! I'll pay for it, so help me! -What?
Here! Since there are 4 of us, it'll be 200,000 yen!
-There's no other way. -Yes, for me.
Princess Onoroke, 200,000 yen has been added!
Okay, cut it up.
Yes!
-Please pay for this, too! -We'll pay for it, too!
Smile!
Go! Go!
Senpai, we don't have 100,000 yen, so are we going to stay like this forever?
If we do, we'll escape without a trace!
Honda, get the backpack over here!
-What? -Like this?
Yes.
-Okay. -Okay.
What are you assembling?
The Takahida Kiryu I bought at the market the other day.
-It's a red-leafed cutting scissors. -A red-leafed cutting scissors.
Okay, I'm done.
"A Red-leafed Cutting Scissors"
With this, you can buy a high-priced branch.
Hey, how's it going?
The money you pay is worth nothing.
-Let's go, Honda! -Yes!
He's pretty good, that gorilla guy.
Honda! Don't let Mr. Hondara get ahead of you!
Yes!
Mr. Hondara, I'll pay you back for this!
I'll make sure you pay me back!
"A Red-leafed Cutting Scissors"
I found it!
This footprint is similar to Tyrannosaurus.
I wonder if there's a dinosaur after all.
I'm sure the tree was knocked down.
Honda! Don't let Mr. Hondara get ahead of you!
Yes!
"A Red-leafed Cutting Scissors"
Ah!
You're gonna get in trouble, Senpai!
Damn, you crossed a river, huh.
Senpai, what's that?
Hey, give me a hand.
Hey, Mr. Hondara!
Ryozu, you're out of here already?
I'll repay you for everything you did!
Let's go!
No!
Not at all!
Go!
"Ryokutsu Kankitsu"
Are you alright, Senpai?
That bastard!
Give up and go home!
Shut up!
I won't give up at this rate!
I have a trump card!
A trump card?
Where did you get that?
From you!
Me?
That's not it!
That's it!
That's it! Grab the stick!
That's not it!
This feeling is...
Alright!
That's it!
You're holding on tight!
Let's go!
Go!
You're all useless!
Speed up!
Sh-Shiga!
They're coming at a tremendous speed!
I won't let you!
Wanihameha!
What kind of special move is that?
Did you see that, Wanihameha, the sword of the Hon-Dara?
What?
You're all useless!
What kind of special move is that?
I just threw a stone!
Senpai, you shouldn't say that.
What?
This is the end, Ryotsukan!
Goodbye!
Senpai!
Damn it! Is there anything I can do?
Oh, yes.
What is it?
This is the thing!
A song about...
An unknown sea...
Senpai, what about this song?
He's here!
I love the sea and protect justice.
Who read this?
Poseidon.
I'll put it in a tank.
I'm the captain of the Marine Corps,
the sea's Do-dai-moon.
The boring Yashio Hikato is the trademark.
Dolby Moon!
It's a long factory as always.
Ryotsu, I'm tired of this, so it's all right.
You're showing off your art, Biker!
Well, I've been doing this lately,
and my subordinates don't listen to me.
That's enough, so help me.
Help me!
Oh.
Hahaha!
Whoa!
I'm going to die!
Hey, that's too rough!
I was able to help you.
Don't complain like that.
I've heard you're the best in the world.
Then, have a nice day!
Have a nice day!
Anyway, I was able to save you.
Honda, I'm going to follow your father!
Well, let's go home.
Idiot!
You can't come this far and quit.
Let's go!
I understand.
I'm here.
Hmm?
Oh?
What's this?
What's that sound?
It might be the sound of the dinosaurs' footsteps!
Right?
That's right!
It's definitely this way!
Let's go!
Oh, no...
Senpai, the desert...
What's going on on this island?
But the footsteps of the dinosaurs
are certainly going to the other side of the slope.
What's that sound like?
It's definitely the sound of the dinosaurs' footsteps.
Wasn't it prepared for the desert forest?
If it's like that,
I'll be even more late!
Let's go, Honda!
What are you doing? Come on!
Yes, yes...
I can't stand the heat.
Damn it!
My body!
Hey!
Honda,
give me some water.
Senpai, give me some water.
What's going on?
Senpai, let's go back to Japan.
I can't go back by myself.
If we cross this slope,
there might be water.
Let's go!
Honda!
I'm the disciple of Hon-Dara-Oyaji!
It's Hon-Dara-Oyaji!
He's also a toho.
Alright, Honda,
let's catch up with him!
Huh?
Hey, Honda, what's wrong?
I can't walk even a step.
Hey, be strong!
Just a little more!
Hey!
Hon-Dara-Oyaji!
You're so strong!
I'll catch you!
I won't lose!
You're so annoying!
You're a pervert gorilla!
You're so smart!
You're a perverted pervert!
I can't stand it anymore...
What?
You again!
You seem to be tired.
There are mineral water, cola, juice, oolong tea,
and anything in my Oroki oasis.
Have a drink!
I'll drink!
What are you doing?
It's 10,000 yen per cup.
10,000 yen?
Are you trying to trick me?
10,000 yen per cup.
Take it, thief!
Don't pay!
Thank you.
Here you are.
I'm alive!
Look at this dangerous man!
I'll drink it even if I have to.
Damn it!
It's dirty.
Honda!
Oh, I see.
There's a
Someone, bring it on!
Please!
Stop it!
I don't have that power!
Huh?
That's...
"The Great Barbecue"
It's not just about the barbecued fish.
When an incident happens on the land,
you can solve it with a single barbeque.
The Great Barbecue, Haraiwa, is here!
You came back well, the Great Barbecue!
What's wrong? What's the matter, Ryo-tsu?
As you can see, my throat is dry.
My stomach is dry.
I think Honda and I are going to die.
Help me!
The barbecued fish I made was useful.
All right.
Here.
Why can you make ramen from a place like that?
Don't worry about the details.
Now, eat.
It's a special seafood ramen made by Kaipan.
I wish it was a cold Chinese ramen.
Hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
It didn't suit your taste.
I see.
I've been studying the best ramen lately.
Don't eat the best ramen at a time like this!
Give me some water. Water!
You have a lot of orders.
Well, then...
Now, drink.
Drinking
I'm not surprised what comes out of the bowl.
But even if you tell me to drink at the first place...
I told you not to worry about the details.
But...
Drinking
Now, drink.
I'll eat it! I'll eat it!
Drinking
I'll eat it!
Anyway, I'm saved.
Let me thank you, Kaipan.
Thank you.
If you have a problem, call me anytime.
Well then.
Farewell.
Drinking
Senior, you really saved me.
Yeah.
He's a pervert, but he's a nice guy.
Yeah!
Let's find the owner once we get back.
Yes!
The footprints are all over here.
Hmm... So you climbed up this cliff...
Hm?
Ah!
Huh?
Father Hondora!
What's wrong?
You're so quiet!
Hey, you!
You're going to catch up, so get ready!
I won't let you!
Oh!
Honda, rope!
Yes!
I'm going to catch you!
I won't let you!
Hey!
Huh?
Oh!
You're caught!
Let's go, Honda!
Yes!
You're such a stubborn guy!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm going to fall!
You're going to die!
Stop!
You!
You're a loser!
Ah!
Oh...
Oh, I'm saved.
What's this place?
A bird's nest?
Huh?
It's an egg.
Okay.
I won't forgive you, Father Hondora!
Hey!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh!
This time, I won't let you go!
Ah!
Oh, dear!
Oh, dear, I don't want to see you again!
Ah!
Oh, dear!
Ow!
Ouch!
Stop!
Eh?
Ah!
It hurts!
Okay!
Let go! Let go of me, you fool!
Now then...
Uangik, it's my turn.
That was close!
Gasp!
Oh my.
Nice!
I can't believe you can self-destruct with your own sword.
Huh?
Man!
Thank you so much.
So where are you off to, mister?
Hey, cool guy?
-What? -It's Nus-C!
There's no mistake!
We finally caught up with Nus-C!
-Let's go! -Yes!
This music...
Long time no see, Ryotsu!
So it's you, Captain Bugryu!
Why are you here?
I'm here to capture the dinosaurs by American policy.
What? You must be joking!
You've come all the way here to do this!
No matter what happens, I won't let you have Nus-C!
I can't help it.
Then I'll take it with all my might.
Stop, Bugryu!
Give up and go home.
No!
Damn it!
Honda, come here!
Yes, sir.
I don't want to call you, but I'll call you the Specialist of the Sky!
The moon's energy is in your back, and the sticks of justice are in the dark!
If it's the case of the sky, I'll let you handle it!
The Moon Giant is back!
The same goes for Assistant Venus Giant!
I'll take care of the rest!
What's with them?
They're in the way!
Take this!
They're useless!
I'm going to die!
Our moon is...
It can't be helped.
Transform, Big Venus!
Yes, sir!
Moonlight Power!
Make up!
Master Tetsumaru!
By transforming the Moon Giant into a female mouse,
he can run faster!
He can run faster!
Oh, he's gone.
But even if a man dressed up as a female mouse,
he's still just a mouse.
He's just a mouse.
Oh!
No!
I'm going to kill you!
All right!
I'll use the power of the Three-Sword Bear!
Yes, sir!
All right!
We'll be dead before you know it.
A forest is deep.
I can see them.
All right!
What are you going to do?
I'll make Captain Bugryu blow it up.
Alright.
Honda!
Pull that rope as hard as you can!
Alright, stop!
Listen, Honda.
When Captain's Apache comes back, release that rope!
Now!
Captain Bugryu!
Prepare yourself!
What?
Idiot!
I cut another boring thing.
Sto...
I'm going to crash into Nusshi!
Senpai, this is bad!
Captain's helicopter, Nusshi, is going to crash!
It's going to explode!
What?
It's still alive?
Captain!
Hey!
You ruined my Apache!
W... What is this?
She got scared!
Did Nusshi make this?
Hey you, you!
What's going on here?
I... I'm sorry.
There are lots of things happening here.
Well? Explain yourself!
No! That's all.
Oh, my God!
What?
A " vibration? " What
did you say? You
see, this isn't a twilight fairy but a twilight witch! Hey!
What is the meaning of this? There's
been a real increase in potential visitors to the island recently. That's
why we're going to get some show-offs, and get
everybody to join our plan. What?
We're
not going to let you get away without us!
Abo-chan!
Damn it! They're so fast at running away!
Hey, Captain! Let's go too!
What are you going to do after letting my Apache fall?
B!
Farewell!
Hey, you! Stop!
We're gone...
Senpai, what are we going to do?
What are we going to do?
I don't know. Let's have Nakagawa come pick us up.
Ryo-chan, what are you going to do?
Let's go!
That's why I'm not going anywhere right now.
You shouldn't come back here right now.
How about staying over there until the fire goes out?
I can't help it. I'll live here for a while.
Damn you!
Senpai, that voice...
It was in the air, right?
Let's go!
That was a really long flight.
As expected, a real dinosaur doesn't survive in this world.
Let's try it again next time.