Want to see the program?
There! There!
When you watch TV
Make light of the room
And try to get away
A light rises over the river
In the direction of the sunset
I looked at the stone
I kicked the stone
and it flew to my shoes
I thought I would go
to the gym
but I was laughed at
as if I was a kid
Even if I try to cheer up
I'm only good at playing
and my yawns are the same
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the water tank in Tongari-boshi
to Taishakuten
the sun sets
Tomorrow
I will be
a free bird
If you win
or lose
don't worry
I can do it
What is this?
A baseball bat
I used to play it when I was a child
I used it when I was in high school.
How do you play?
What? Don't you know?
The rule is the same as baseball.
Pull this lever.
When you let go, the pitcher throws the ball.
Hit it.
If you get into this hole, you're hit.
It's very simple.
Anyone can do it.
Right?
How about losing a game and having lunch?
Sounds fun.
Let's do it, senpai.
Good luck, Kei.
The game is a tie.
It's all about luck.
But, Gitchon.
The baseball is very deep.
Let's start the game.
I'll go first.
Sure.
There are other levers.
It's just a decoration.
Let's get started.
Okay.
Home run!
It's on.
Okay.
It's a change.
It's a two-point behind.
It's okay.
You can turn it over.
I'll do my best.
It's easy to turn it over.
Let's go.
The ball is bent.
What's going on?
Lucky.
It's just luck.
It's on again.
I'm sorry.
I'm back.
Good job, Mr. Terai.
It's a baseball version.
I remember it.
I used to play a lot.
Terai!
Ryo, be quiet.
What's going on?
It's a change.
The ball is iron.
You need to move a magnet under the game board with a lever and throw a curve or a shot.
Senpai!
Ryo.
Ah, I just remembered!
Yeah, yeah, I was thrown the change ball too.
That's so funny.
You were cheating, weren't you?
Well, well, that's true.
Then you can use the change ball too.
Damn it, that Terai.
It's unnecessary.
But I still have a way.
Then, here we go.
Try moving the magnet again.
Ah! It's a magnet.
Now, move it while looking at Ryo-san's eyes.
He's reading my hand with the magnet.
It's a classic trick of cowardly.
I see.
What should I do?
Do as I say.
What's wrong?
You're still two out.
Ah, yes.
Sorry for the wait.
Here we go.
It's a curve, isn't it?
Damn it!
Yay!
It's a change!
Ryo-san, this is the right side.
I think he didn't notice that I was looking at the magnet.
Yes.
This time, I'll use it in reverse.
What?
I still have a lot of lead.
You're going to shoot it?
Here we go.
Yes.
There.
Yay!
Wow!
It's a home run.
Damn it.
You hit me by accident.
This time, it's a curve.
Take this!
There.
This time, it's a three-way.
Ah!
Why?
Wow!
I'm almost there.
And it's a reverse.
Goodbye.
What's going on?
Hey, Terai!
You've become strange since you came here.
What did you teach Nakagawa?
I just taught him a trick that a coward does.
What?
You did something unnecessary even though you were on a lunch break.
Ryo-chan, stop it.
It's the fault of the senpai who cheated.
Let's continue.
Damn it.
I'll be defeated in the ring.
How could I not have...
No, no.
I'm too excited and my baseball bat has been broken.
Well, let's make a lunch break for the draw.
I can't accept it.
That's right.
If we continue like this, Kei-chan will win.
It can't be helped.
It was broken.
I broke it purposely, but...
I didn't do it purposely.
I understand.
I understand. Then let's settle this with the Super Real Simulation Baseball.
Oh, it was a game where you became the owner of a professional baseball team and raised the best baseball team in Japan.
Let's transfer it to the big screen of our theater.
Sounds fun. Let me join you.
Actually, I'm also into it now. It's good to pile it up.
I'm not that kind of game.
Are you running away?
What? You're going to the master of the game, aren't you?
Okay, I'll stand up for you.
Let's start the game.
Mr. Terai is still...
Apparently, he's lost in the garden.
The security helicopter is searching for him.
Oh, dear.
Sorry, sorry! I thought you were going to talk to me!
Wow! You're going to transfer it to this screen, right?
Yes. It's very nice.
It's also very realistic and powerful.
Well, I can't win any game.
What should I do first?
In the controller, you can set the owner registration, name of the team, and uniform.
I scanned your photos beforehand and took them.
Next, you can set the name of the team.
This is a serious game.
Well, the name of the team is...
Ryotsu Zenyaris.
Next, the uniform is...
This!
The team's management fund is 100 million yen.
Based on that, players, directors, and coaches are collected.
Okay.
The pitcher is Higashiguchi from last year's Sawa-mura Show.
And the great magician from the mountains, Sasahara Nito.
The catcher is Hachiryo Yashiba, a former MVP.
Ryo, if you collect players with such high annual salaries, you'll be disqualified.
If you're disqualified, you'll lose.
I see.
At first, the players with high annual salaries are divided into two.
Then, the new players and players with low annual salaries are gathered and raised.
At first, there are only three pitchers.
It's troublesome.
When the team is completed, the game begins.
Well, today Nakagawa Concerns...
Oh, it's a pretty good atmosphere.
Ryotsu Zenyaris' traditional match will begin.
Play ball!
Why is Nakagawa in the game?
The owner should register himself as a director.
If he registers himself as a director, he can participate in the game.
If that's the case, go ahead.
I'll be the owner's director.
Now, the pitcher turns around and throws it.
Hit!
Oh, a home run.
Another home run.
Oh, again.
If it goes like this, the pitcher will be disqualified.
Eh? Again?
Shut up!
What are you doing?
There's no pitcher to disqualify.
At first, you said up to three people.
Eh? Then the pitcher is...
The pitcher is Yamada of the right.
Eh? There's no way to use it like that.
Shut up! You're doing a great job.
Pull this hamster back in.
It's suddenly going really well.
Really?
Now, the game is resumed.
The pitcher throws and hits!
Hit!
The pitcher is disqualified.
The catcher is Furuki.
After seven games, it's 38 to 0.
It seems that there was a match.
Eh?
What should we do, senpai?
I'd rather give up the game.
No, not now.
Ah!
Senpai!
Ryo-chan, you're dirty.
It's my first time, so it's okay.
Kei-chan, freeze the reset button so you won't be beaten again.
Roger that.
Ryo-chan, it's a big deal to make the catcher a pitcher.
Don't do it anymore.
I have to raise more pitchers, senpai.
Eh, I'm frustrated, but it's a good thing.
I don't like to do it.
It's troublesome to raise humans.
I got it.
I'll go to the pitcher to raise the pitcher.
Nakagawa-kun and Reiko-san, will you play a match?
I got it.
Kei-chan, let's do it.
Eh?
Now, Ryo-san.
It's basic to raise the player who won the draft.
I got it.
Anyway, I'll reinforce the pitcher and train hard.
It's a poor ground.
I can't spend money on it.
Hey, don't miss it.
It's too hard to practice, so I can't keep up.
What? You're against the coach.
You two are in trouble.
Ryo-san, if you do that, the pitcher will disappear.
Oh, I see.
It's reset.
This...
Nakagawa-kun did unnecessary things.
Terai, how can I get a pitcher?
You have to get it again with money.
How much money do you have left?
Only 5 million.
Then, it's very...
No, there must be some hidden tricks.
The owner can do a side job.
Oh, it's a field.
I have prepared a method for myself.
But there is a possibility that you will be an obstacle.
Who do you think I am?
I'll make 5 million a hundred times...
No, a thousand times.
After the 9th round, the score is 3:2.
Akimoto Beauty is the leader.
But Nakagawa Consolence is also behind the 9th round.
Two out and two runners.
Alright, a hit and a tie.
If it's a home run, it's a comeback.
I can't do that.
Kei-chan, it's a game.
I'll throw the pitcher and...
I can throw it.
I'll throw it.
The pitch is growing.
Yes, it's a comeback.
Goodbye, home run.
I did it!
What?
Ryou-chan, you are cruel.
I also lost a comeback.
Don't misunderstand.
I got 10 billion yen.
10 billion yen?
Now I can change a good pitcher from the big league.
It's time for another play!!
4. To beat a nouvelleboss
Take 1 billion and jump right away.
Look.
Look at this. It's so green.
5. This game is really cool
I'd like you to play it in Japan.
If 100 billion is the penalty, I'd be glad to think about it.
It's too high.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't be stupid.
Don't say that! Japanese people are always rich!
What a great negotiation!
It's like he's threatening us!
I beat him to a pulp!
Look! I have 10 pitchers and 10 batters!
It's the strongest squad!
Even if you bring them that much,
the foreign team is only up to three people.
What? I will change that rule!
What?
I will give you as much money as you want!
I will be the commissioner, so you should retire!
No!
Hey! Even this!
I don't want to!
Of course!
You can't change the rule of the commissioner!
Then I will attack you!
Go! Go! Go!
I will change the rule of the commissioner.
All right!
Now the foreign team is out!
He's using a great trick!
It's Ryo!
Now it's time for Ryo and Zenialis!
Who is the opponent?
It's a three-way battle with Terai!
What?
It's kind of scary.
Play ball!
All right! Let's attack!
Now, the first ball!
It's hit!
It's a home run!
I did it!
Did you see that?
You can buy your abilities with money!
The world is full of money!
What are you doing, Terai?
Throw it!
Wait a minute.
I'm taking notes of the foreign players.
You're imitating the bad-eared guys.
It's useless!
When the data is gathered,
I will change it to a new foreign player.
No way!
Well, your son-in-law's name is a life-saving band.
I believe you can live with it.
There's no way.
Go with that attitude.
Together!
Gakun!
In that respect, I'm a home run man in life.
I don't imitate the band or the squeeze.
Sign is a home run!
I am a home run man!
All right!
Game set!
79 to 0.
You won a match!
Hahaha!
You're determined to play the second round, aren't you?
I think it's a waste of time, but...
We will play it.
In the first game,
Noran Reiner is also tired.
Do you use the same pitcher again?
That's right.
We have to take a break on the fourth or the fifth day.
He has over 500 million.
I'm not going to let you rest for a day.
There are some soldiers who can be crushed by a chain.
Ryo-chan only thinks about herself.
Play ball!
All right, here we go.
Now, the first ball.
Take it!
Ah! I was hit!
You bastard!
What are you doing?
My shoulder hurts, I can't get up.
Let me rest.
What? Don't be so careless!
Throw it so hard that your arm breaks!
That's the right way!
I threw a pitcher of that kind!
Ah! It's a home run!
That bastard!
You're fired!
There are so many pitchers in the world!
It's Gonzales!
Gonzales has returned from his wife's business.
What? Then it's Thomas!
Thomas suddenly has business too.
What?
That's why I said it.
He uses it so badly.
He's a big man.
He's so good at that!
Terai Chimichis has scored 4 points and still has one out.
He threw a pitcher!
It's a quiz!
Oh my!
Tasty!
One point more!
Terai!
Don't give points to the real band!
Life is a band of gifts!
Well…
OK! It's a change!
I'll get the points back!
It's a home run.
Go, go!
I can't believe he really did it.
I can't believe I'm losing.
-Slide! -Out again!
Damn, Gaijin is in a bad shape.
No, Senpai.
It's because Terai has been taking data from Gaijin.
He's reading the course that he's not good at.
What? Terai!
I can't spend money like Ryo, so I have to fight in strategy.
He's using his little strength to make good use of teamwork and strategy.
That's right. It's natural that he's strong if he uses hundreds of millions.
Terai is taking care of the players one by one.
And Senpai is...
Hey, don't make any mistakes.
Oh, I'm usually a good player.
I'm not good at defense.
Shut up! There are as many substitutes as you want!
You're a nut!
Hey, throw it already!
If I throw any more, my shoulder will break.
Please answer me.
Idiot! You're a nut!
I'm using 300 million for my head.
I'll throw it until I get the base!
Senpai is a one-sided attack.
He doesn't think about the players' posture,
and he's going to make them throw good investments and destroy them.
It's a big deal.
If you're happy now, that's all you can do.
That's right.
If the players don't like it, they'll collect it with money again, right?
Shut up!
You're a big help.
If you think you can reflect on that opinion, you're wrong.
If you say no, I'll do it back with 100 times the power.
That's my idea.
Next time, I'll use the money again.
First, we'll do a money trade with the players from the team in Nakagawa.
What?
I'll pull out the ace.
I don't think it's possible.
Please come to my house for a trade.
I refuse.
I see.
I see. How about this?
Take it, you idiot.
It's 1 billion yen.
I'll make a contract.
Look.
If you pull the other person's cheek with a killer in the world,
I'll give you a lot of money.
It's all my idea.
I'll get a star athlete.
Sorry, but it's not a player who can move with money.
Then there's another way.
I'll get you a lot of money at the CF as well as the annual bonus that you give to me.
That's not all.
You can have a time with a beautiful announcer.
What?
I'll make a contract with him.
No way.
I've been looking for your interest in sports.
You don't collect baseball data.
I'm not going to collect the data.
That's what you call a woman's mouth.
From the big league, you call things and choose something.
It's a renewal of one billion.
There are 20 pitchers alone.
I'll cook you a quick meal of 160 kilos.
Why did you get hit?
That was a good course by the batter.
There's no mistake in the home run.
How about that?
What?
No way.
I thought this could happen.
I paid 5 billion yen and renovated the stadium.
You're cheating, Rai.
Be a referee.
That was a foul.
Do it again.
No, I can't.
Because I'm the star.
I'm not just the star.
I'm the star of the team.
What?
When did you...
All the judges are disqualified and I'm registered.
Ryo.
Money is the world.
No matter what you do, I win.
I don't need to lose.
Right.
Let's stop because you're the winner.
Then I have to win.
Please wait.
I earned 20 billion yen from a stock exchange.
What?
I'm going to take down the senior commissioner.
I don't want to be taken down.
I can't take this anymore.
Money! Money!
Nakagawa, you're the commissioner!
You're so weak in the game.
Now I'm the commissioner.
I'm not going to run the stadium anymore.
And I'm going to take down the other judges too.
What?
I'm the last one.
Good, now we can fight to the end.
Ryo, let's continue.
Wait a minute.
We still have 5 billion left.
I'll call a team of Terai-san to help us.
These are the Brains who won the World Series last year.
Now, Terai-san.
Break the senior who uses dirty hands with this.
We have the data.
We can win this game.
Oh, no.
If we keep this up, we'll lose.
There's no way to win.
Ryo.
Hey, time's up.
Every game has its ultimate trick.
This game has its own trick.
Let's find it.
You're not doing well, Ryo-chan.
It's no use doing anything.
Shut up.
You're not...
What's this?
All the players, change!
What?
What's this?
You're all Ryo-chan?
There's no rule that says an owner shouldn't be a player.
Then, let's restart the game.
Play ball!
Ryo, you're good.
Can't go.
You'll get hit.
Hey, stop.
Be careful from here.
I thought you would say that.
We'll be over till we make it.
Okay.
Don't let it get out.
No, man...
I could align with you, Ryo-san.
Hey.
I've been waiting for this!
Everyone, go!
Oh, it's a lantern!
You're kidding!
Everyone's here, even the audience?
What's going on?
We're going to make some money too!
Let's go!
This is the ultimate trick!
This is crazy!
They're fighting so hard!
We're going home too!
We'll win with our games!
Bye-bye!
It's been a hundred years since I last won!
Who's next?
Where did everyone go?
Huh?
Hey!
We still have a match left!
No one can beat Ryo!
Really?
They were trying to fight seriously.
Hey!
Come back!
Komachi and I are getting married?
This is a misunderstanding!
Dad! Mom!
No, this "Dad" and "Mom" is...
This is not what I meant!
Next episode: This is the person I like!
That's why I'm wrong!
Next time:
The next episode:
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Thanks for watching!