LOL
When you watch TV
Make sure to look into the room and look away
飴 about to float on a river
♪ I looked at the sun ♪
♪ And kicked the love stone ♪
♪ I flew to the shoe ♪
♪ I wonder if I should go to the gym ♪
♪ I laughed at the fact that I was still a baby ♪
♪ Please cheer up ♪
♪ Even if I'm a kid, I'm a
♪
I came here to take a class.
I miss you, Katsushika.
Katsushika Space Station
I missed you, Katsushika.
A robbery occurred at the Shimae Bank.
The culprit is in the bank with a hostage.
The police are on the scene.
Let's go, Nagawa.
I'll take care of the rest.
Roger that.
Be careful, you two.
Wait a minute.
What is it, Chief?
In order to solve this case,
a security police officer will be sent from the main office.
You will be sent to that command center.
What kind of person is he?
I don't know the details, but his name is Hoshi.
He's known as Hard-Boiled Deka in the main office.
Hard-Boiled Deka?
That's a cool nickname.
He must be someone who appeared in the Hard-Boiled movies.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Huh?
Think about it.
There was no one better than this police officer.
Kaipan Deka.
Moon Deka.
Venus Deka.
And Dolphin Deka.
I don't know.
That's right.
Then, this time, too.
I'm sure some strange guy with our reputation will come.
Hard-Boiled means a hard-boiled egg.
That's right.
Then, he always eats boiled eggs.
He may have a smooth skin like a boiled egg.
No, he may be wearing a huge egg shell.
He's not a normal person anyway.
You'd better be prepared.
He's stupid.
A strange police officer would never come.
You're so naive, chief.
Have you forgotten all the bitter experiences you've had so far?
He's Kamado.
Could it be that he's one of them?
I'm Hoshida, from the main office.
People call me Hard-Boiled Deka.
He's a normal person, isn't he?
I can't let my guard down.
Here comes the boiled egg.
What's that? Isn't that a cigarette?
No, I don't think so.
He's probably hiding something.
I'll show you this time.
What's that? Isn't that a lighter?
He just wanted to smoke, didn't he?
You're overthinking.
Then, everyone.
Let's go to the scene.
It's definitely a hard-boiled egg.
Won't you give us the boiled egg?
Hey!
You're making me look like a gag.
What's with the boiled egg?
I'm Hard-Boiled Deka.
Why do you have to do that?
Even if you ask me why, I'm just...
I'm just not satisfied.
What are you talking about?
You boarded Kamado and appeared at the scene.
Suddenly, you had a happy strike.
You lit a fire with a lighter from a Garche.
And now you're making a cool face.
Cool? I'm too cool.
I'm sure I'm drunk.
Is this enough to make you look like Hard-Boiled?
I'm not drunk.
What is this?
This is like a daily comedy.
I can't show my Hard-Boiled charm enough.
What are you talking about?
This background is bad.
Change it.
Okay.
This is a background that is suitable for Hard-Boiled.
Next is...
You should make your appearance more realistic.
I'm realistic.
This is...
No way.
What's going on?
This is like a movie.
A terrible person appeared.
This is a Hard-Boiled world, suitable for a Hard-Boiled man.
Now, I'll do my appearance scene again.
I'll do it again.
It's time for a new one.
Hey!
You don't have time to do something so ridiculous!
Ryo!
What?
The clock is back to three minutes.
If you don't do it again, you can't proceed.
Is that so?
I can't help it.
I'm sorry, but I have to do what he said.
What did you talk about three minutes ago?
I think I said that I was not just a person.
OK.
Then, let's start from there.
Everyone, go back to your position.
Do I have to do it too?
Of course.
If the chief is gone, the conversation will be difficult.
Are you ready?
OK!
OK.
Then, Hard-Boiled Deca appearance scene, take two.
Ready, start!
Anyway, it's not just a thing.
You should be prepared.
What?
I'll go first.
A strange detective will come soon.
You are too naive, chief.
Have you forgotten your bitter experience so far?
Kamaradesu.
Maybe he is inside...
*snort*
I'm Hoshida from the main office.
People call me Hard-Boiled Dekka.
You're satisfied now, right?
Now, let's get to the real thing!
Wait a minute!
What? I've already redone it with Hard-Boiled!
No, I feel like you're still missing the Hard-Boiled-ness.
*snort*
That's right! Let's turn the screen into a sepia tone and aim for the sharpness!
It's like a Hollywood movie from the 40's.
It's kind of cool.
Let's change the setting of the screen into a 40's style.
Why me?
What?
Alright, let's do that scene again.
Are we doing it again?
Then, let's do the Hard-Boiled Dekka scene, take 3!
Ready, start!
*snort*
Anyway, it's nothing but a piece of cake.
Yeah. It's better to be prepared.
*snort*
You're so stupid!
It's no use for you to be a detective!
You're so naive, Chief.
Have you forgotten how painful your experience has been?
*snort*
*sneeze*
It was Kamalo!
Could it be that in here...
I'm Hoshida, from the capital.
People call me Hard-Boiled Deka.
No! I don't know what this red cauldron is!
Let's figure it out first!
I'll color it after all.
It's back!
How can I make it look like a Hard-Boiled movie?
Just give up already!
Don't you think that the size of the screen is different between TV and movies?
The size of the screen? That's it!
That's unnecessary.
I'm sorry.
Alright, let's change the size of the screen.
Cinesco size!
You guys are lying on the outside of the screen!
I'm sorry, Ryo-sama.
They're such a pain in the ass.
Just do it.
Alright, Hard-Boiled Deka, scene 4.
Ready, start!
The End
At any rate, it's not easy.
You better be prepared.
This is ridiculous!
It's amazing that a weird detective came all of a sudden!
Hey, Honda!
Why are you here?
Isn't this Chief's line?
I didn't do it because I wanted to!
I just came to see Senpai, but Chief Ohara suddenly...
gave me this script, and asked me to do it.
You're cheating, Chief.
You ran away on your own!
You're really shut up.
Hey, don't change the cast.
Don't tell us. The chief has escaped.
Chief Ohara, did you say anything else?
I can't go on anymore. I'm tired.
We don't want to go on anymore.
The chief is gone, and there's no more of this scene.
Idiot! This is the scene where the leading character appears.
Are you going to say that it's gone?
But the chief is not here.
I can't help it. You have to play the chief.
Make-up!
Change the camera angle.
Don't show his face.
That's good.
Now, take 5 of the scene where the hard-boiled giant appears.
Ready, start!
All in all, it's not just a piece of cake.
Yeah.
You'd better be prepared.
I can't believe that a stupid, crazy, and strange detective came.
You're naive, chief.
Have you forgotten the bitter experience you've had up to now?
It's Kamalo.
Could it be that in here...
It's Hoshida from the main town.
People call me the hard-boiled giant.
It's finally decided.
Well, where am I?
The camera went negative.
The main character is gone.
But you didn't see it because it was hidden!
Everyone is now completely hidden.
That's true.
Now, I know what you're talking about.
And now I know what you're talking about.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What's wrong?
What's happening?
There's something I like about the main character and him.
He's being so columnsome for making such a stand.
It's such a pride.
He doesn't know that.
He's truly not playing.
Now, it's your turn.
It was a wonderful scene.
And are we still in the exit?
We used all the first half of the Hoshi's appearance scene.
Thanks to you, the story hasn't progressed at all.
We'll get up to speed in the second half.
But it's still hard-boiled.
I understand. So please proceed with the story.
All right.
Um...
What?
Can I just pull it in?
Is it okay to pull it in?
Um...
It seems that the chief Ohara has no more lines.
You can go back now.
Yes.
Well then, I'll excuse myself first.
-Good job. -Good job.
So who and who will be under me?
Is it already started?
It seems so.
I'm asking who and who will be under me!
I'm asking two people!
Y-Yes, it's us.
It's Nakagawa Keiichi, the inspector.
It's Ryotsu Kankichi, the inspector.
All right.
Get in my car, Ryotsu Nakagawa.
I'll be right in front of Kameari Station.
Yes.
It's decided.
This time, it's decided on the first floor.
I'm going to be happy.
I'll go to the next scene like a thief!
Start!
Wait a minute!
Hey, don't stop suddenly!
No!
This scene is NG!
Huh?
There was nothing strange.
The starting point should be the biggest showcase.
It's the place where you have to be the most hard-boiled.
But something was missing.
Are you going to do it again?
What is it?
That's right!
It's the 10-day high school!
10-day high school?
What is the 10-day high school?
You'll see if you watch it.
Put the 10-day high school in the scene now and do it again.
Hard-boiled or starting scene take 2!
Ready, start!
Start!
What?
Why is it night?
I don't know.
Is this the 10-day high school?
It's cool.
But why is it suddenly night?
To make the 10-day high school shine beautifully, the background has to be night.
A robber entered the bank in front of the station.
It's not a good time at night.
Shut up.
If you arrive in the other side, you can go back to the daytime.
That's such a selfish thing.
Excuse me, but where is this car running?
It's the 10-day high school.
It's heading for Kameari Station.
Why is it in the 10-day high school?
It's noisy every day.
Hard-boiled movies are running in the 10-day high school.
That's so stupid.
It's a harder game than you think.
Wait a minute!
What is it this time?
It's no good.
Something is still missing.
I think it was hard-boiled enough.
What do you mean?
It's the music.
The music?
At times like this, the background music of the program can be used as a theme song.
If you say so.
That's true, but...
I'll add the theme song to this scene one more time.
Are you really going to do it?
Of course.
Hard-boiled movie scene take 3.
Ready, start!
Start!
Didn't you say that the tempo would be up in the second half?
Is this the third time?
All right.
What the hell are you doing?
I can't turn this around.
We have this theme song.
I told you so.
No, there's another song.
Yes!
Music start!
No.
What is this?
Wrong!
No!
I'm not a woman who can't do anything
This is not it either!
Ah, summer has come again this year
Summer has passed, enough! No music here!
Let's smile anytime
I said no!
Summer has passed
Hey, it's really noon, what's going on?
No matter what happens, I'm not surprised
The criminal's request is still nothing
I see
It's been a long day
Nagawa-san!
Hey, don't raise your voice there!
It's a hard-boiled evolution!
What?
Because Nagawa-san is cool!
It can't be helped
Cool?
This guy is?
Why is this weak man
This guy is not cool at all!
This is why people who can't understand hard-boiled are troubled
If you are really cool, you are talking about a cool man like me
Not at all, not at all, not at all cool at all
It's okay
I'll make it easier for you guys to understand
I feel like the star's face suddenly got deeper
What's going on?
Look closely
Zoom up!
What's this?
Isn't this mitochondria?
No, no, it's too high
Let's go back a little
Look closely around your eyes
This is?
What's wrong?
The shadow is three-stage
You seem to have noticed
By making the shadow three-stage, you can create a deeper shadow and give a hard-boiled expression
Our shadow is?
One-stage
Furthermore, four-stage
Five-stage
Six-stage
How about this? This is the hard-boiled coolness
It feels good!
It's too real, it's creepy
Even if there is only one shadow, Nakagawa-san is better
You guys who don't understand hard-boiled, it's a waste of a single shadow
Become a two-stage character without shadows
What is it?
Shut up!
You guys have no business anymore
Flavor Art!
The intruder is gone
Now we can go through the hard-boiled world
Damn it, I can't bear it anymore
You can do whatever you want to a guest character
Now I'll show the actor's power
What should I do to solve this place in a hard-boiled way?
You can hear the footsteps of a gag manga here
I think I heard something weird just now
It's my imagination
After all, I have no choice but to rush into the canyon
The footsteps of the robot anime
I heard something weird again.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Hard-boiled Dekka is the greatest master of all.
And now, the old lady's laugh.
What?
There's no social window.
And no clothes are torn.
I'm sure it was a bad omen.
A man like me who lives in a hard-boiled world
should never laugh at an old lady.
I'll laugh at her again.
What was that laugh?
You!
Don't laugh at me!
Shut up!
You've always done what you wanted to do.
You're the star of this show.
I'm the star of this show.
I've done what I wanted to do.
What's so funny?
You're the star?
You're not the star of this show.
What?
Watch this!
It's the opening of the show.
What's wrong with this?
Read the title.
I don't need to read it.
"This is Katsushikaku Kameyari Park's opening."
Yes.
This is the title of this show.
There's no such word as "Ryotsu."
Shut up!
The main character of this show is the opening,
and you're just a side character.
I see.
I wasn't the main character.
You finally realized it after two years of broadcasting.
You fool.
What?
Wait a minute.
Even if Hatsujyo is the main character,
it's still a building, so he can't move.
That's an animation.
You have to put your hands and feet together.
This is Hatsujyo-kun,
the Hatsujyo-kun of Katsushikaku Kameyari Park.
I'm Hatsujyo-kun.
Nice to meet you.
Hatsujyo-kun is running.
Hatsujyo-kun is falling.
He fell.
Hatsujyo-kun is standing on the slope.
Nice shot.
Hatsujyo-kun is eating ramen.
Hatsujyo-kun is watching TV.
Anji, Anji.
You're still a kid.
You happen to be a Hatsujyo-kun,
so you can act like a main character.
If I become a Hatsujyo-kun,
it will be a story that I will be very active.
Are you going to play my role?
I just thought that a hard-boiled man like me
was more suitable for the regular.
I will never let a regular work for a guy like you.
Absolutely.
What do you mean?
What?
I prefer a dragon.
Get me a new one.
Don't say something like that when you make an ending pose.
It's the hard-boiled man's obsession.
In this case,
the fact is whether you are suitable for the regular.
So,
it's better to arrest the criminal who is hiding there.
I'm sure I'm going to win.
Let's start the game!
The culprit has been arrested!
It's already evening.
What's going on, Director Takamatsu?
The broadcast time was too short, so I cut out all the scenes of the culprit being arrested.
What?
Then what about the game?
What about the game?
It's the next opportunity, so...
No way...
What's going on?
My place of appearance is...
What? The background disappeared.
You always ask for too much, so the background ran away.
What?
The color disappeared, too.
It seems that Mr. Saishiki also ran away.
What?
Hey, isn't it strange to move?
I'm talking, but my mouth doesn't move.
The person in the video also ran away.
What's this number? It's annoying!
That's a cell number.
And this whistle!
You can talk according to that.
It seems that the film is not in time, and it's like a recording site.
What's this line?
At last Gengaman also ran away.
Hey! You don't know what this is!
So what happened to Mr. Hoshi?
I don't know. All the pictures have disappeared.
I don't know where he went.
This story was a mess.
I don't want you to come out again.
So, what's next week's lunch?
What?
What? Hey!
Don't come out without permission.
No!
Damn it! I'll definitely come out again!
Thanks to you, I couldn't read the comments.
Next time, "Love's Bodyguard".
Thank you!
♪ Stop and run ♩
♪ Fly away ♩