The
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and
look away.
Meow meow
Come to me,
you poor guy!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky,
and the white clouds.
I wonder what will happen
in the meantime.
You get it, right?
You get it, you get it?
If you get it,
then quietly come to me!
then immediately come to me!
Meow meow
The worst escape ever!
What time is it?
It's dark.
I feel like my head's going to break.
It's so dark that I can't see anything.
Where am I?
Is it Volvo?
Ryotsu.
Don't make such a loud noise!
My head's going to break!
It's me, Honda.
Honda?
Thank goodness, Senpai.
It's so dark when I wake up.
I feel so...
What's wrong?
Someone's falling!
Wait. I'm coming.
Volvo!
Damn it.
I can't move if it's this dark.
Huh?
But why is there a lighter in my pocket?
Who's MH?
Mr. Sakonji!
Hey, Sakonji!
Saori!
Idiot, I'm not Saori!
What's this?
We don't know, either.
What is this?
Is this a cave?
No, it's not.
This wall is made of metal.
Huh.
The wall is 5-60cm thick.
The ceiling is 15, 6, 7, 8 meters.
Hey, we don't have a window or a door.
Where did we come in?
Maybe UFOs were sent by aliens!
No!
The antenna's not working!
I can't use the phone!
Let's save gas.
Let's turn off the light.
What's wrong?
I'm scared of the dark.
I'm so scared!
Apparently we were locked in a complete room.
Hmm.
What?
Is the power out?
The power's out?
It's not working.
Looks like Ryo turned it off.
It's probably in the room.
Wasn't it your birthday party yesterday?
Yeah.
It was a very manly guy's game.
Yay!
I'm glad I didn't have to go.
Pardon me, but we're going to the second floor.
We're going to the second floor.
But you're free to stay a few more days.
So you'll be free to stay for the next two days.
That's not the point.
Remember our foot steps from last night.
If you know where this is, you'll find the way out.
It doesn't matter how small it is, just remember what you said.
Last night, Sakonjiro and I gathered at the yakiniku shop on his birthday.
It's good so far.
The green onion and salt kalbi were delicious.
The stone-baked bibimbap and yukhoe were also delicious.
But the dessert, the shiratama kinako ice cream was amazing.
Enough talking about food.
Go ahead and finish up.
After leaving the yakiniku shop, I walked around the garbage shop several times.
I remember the third time, but...
It's Saori! The fourth time, it was a store called Saori!
Oh, but the store's mother is...
It's Saori!
I see.
Thanks to you, Sakonjiro is doing well.
It's a nightmare!
What are your memories from then?
Hmm...
In the end, there's no clue.
All right, let's think of a way to escape on our own.
Yeah, that's your specialty.
I'm counting on you, Bulbo.
All right.
Everyone, take out your belongings.
There may be something useful for escaping.
I'm going to take out my belongings.
Hmm...
How's that?
Can you pull it off?
I can't.
Huh?
Don't give up!
Use your ex-GreenBerry history.
It's a Hollywood movie, right?
Combine these junkies...
...and you'll come up with a weapon you haven't even considered.
Ouch!
No way.
Listen, Ryotsu.
In the case of movies, the junkie calculated in advance to be able to make weapons is available.
But...
This is a piece of junk, so it's impossible.
If you explain it to me, I'll get angry.
It's a professional to make delicious food with the excess in the refrigerator.
It's a professional who is particular about the material.
What?
This is the last way.
Open the wind hole on the wall with this ...
Hey, idiot! Stop!
If you blow this up in such a small place, we will all be blown away.
I can't.
The face of Saori's mother is stuck in my head and I can't remember my beloved Saori's face.
Saori!
This is a dream.
It's not a dream! It's not a dream!
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to forget the police notebook.
I started to get drunk and take it off.
Haven't you gone home?
Ryo hasn't been home since yesterday.
Honda and Sakonji?
Ryo and his wife haven't gone home?
Ryo and his wife?
All three of them are not in the room.
Are they?
Then, Ryo and his wife left the store at 3:00 a.m.
All four of them were drunk, so I was a little worried.
I can't contact my wife.
Your wife doesn't contact you either.
Didn't you say you were going somewhere after that?
Well...
Oh, right.
Someone said they wanted to eat ramen.
I told him about a delicious ramen shop nearby.
If you use your useless power, you will lose your appetite.
Are you saying you have to wait for Mira to be quiet?
If you do this, someone may notice you.
You may be right.
Listen to me.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
You heard the sound?
It's noisy there. Nobody can notice it.
Really?
But there are people out there.
Here it is.
Help me.
Help!
Damn it!
Are we going to die here?
Don't be stupid! Someone will come to save us!
Nobody knows we're here!
4 of the same name.
Hey, who is the marketing department of the Toyo Telecom?
Who is the marketing department of the Toyo Telecom?
Hm? Hatakeyama?
I don't know.
I don't know either, but...
What about Sakonji?
I don't know.
Hm? Hatakeyama Mamoru?
The initial is MH.
This lighter seems to belong to this Hatakeyama guy, but...
Who is this guy?
The lighter's fire!
That's why I told you to save gas!
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
It's so hot.
Do you want to do something to get rid of your heat?
I'm so drunk.
I'm so drunk, Sakonji.
I...
I'm so drunk.
I'm in hell.
I...
Shelt down.
We're out of luck.
I'm out of luck again.
I'm out of luck...
Dang it!
Don't do that!
My badass leg...
It's decaying.
A hornet...
I've yearned for this...
L-Logoku...
Stop saying "Kuwabara, Kuwabara!"
This isn't a play!
Why are you all saying such mean things?
You're getting on my nerves!
Then, I'll go with "La" from Kuwabara, Sakonji.
You're going to continue?!
It's easier to get on my nerves when you're focused on something.
Alright, go with a bright mind!
You're going to get on my nerves when you're focused on something.
"La" right?
Lionel Richie!
Who's there?!
Come here!
What was that voice?
There's one more person.
Listen up! Don't move until you know who the enemy is!
Enemy?
A long time ago, there were seven men.
There are seven men, right?
That means that there are 25 enemies in total, right?
There are 28, right?
That's right.
I knew it! It's an alien!
No, it's a salaryman.
Ah, hello!
Hello!
Ah...
Ah!
Hello...
Are you perhaps...
Hatakeyama Mamoru?
I've been completely soaked.
I'm really bad at drinking.
I have to go to work every other day and the following day is the second day.
My head hurts...
Um, Hatakeyama-kun knows about us, right?
Ryo-san, Sakonji-san, Honda-san, Volvo-san.
Right?
Well, I had fun yesterday.
That's right, that's right!
He was at the ramen shop we went to!
Hey!
Hey, Suni!
Hey, Dad!
Let's go to the ramen shop!
Hey, Suni-chan!
How are you?
Saori!
Yes?
At first, I thought they were a little scary, but when I talked to them, they were really funny.
Saori!
Uh ... what are you doing, you?
Yes!
Saori!
Uh ... what 's this?
I haven't played that much for a long time.
Do you remember where this is?
Here?
Mm ... yes...
Um ...
Yeah ...
Yes ...
Where is this place?
I knew it.
I don't remember how we walked here, but I think I saw a mountain far away.
A mountain?
Did Kazushika see a mountain?
Maybe we came to a place far away.
But there's a limit to how far we can go with drunk blood.
I don't know why I'm getting more and more confused.
Hatakeyama, do you remember anything else?
Other than that...
Huh?
I think I had something important to do today.
Umm, umm...
What was it?
Oh!
Excuse me, what time is it now?
The clock...
12:30.
Huh?
My phone is gone!
I'll borrow this phone!
Oh, dear.
Unfortunately,
I can't make a call here.
I'll use it later.
Oh, I have to go home.
I'm going home!
Huh?
Well, where's the exit?
That's what we've been looking for a long time, but it doesn't seem like it.
There isn't?
In other words, we won't be able to get out of here for the time being.
I'm in trouble.
I have to go to the head office at once.
Where?
There's a wedding.
A wedding?
Whose?
Who?
This guy?
I'm going home.
I'll go with you.
I'm going home!
Well, that's a good news.
I don't know what's going on.
That's all I need.
My sister's getting married.
I'm going home.
Hm? What's wrong with Ryotsu?
Are you going on patrol too?
Y-Yes...
You're going on patrol, aren't you?
U-Um... Y-Yes...
Hm.
Your good side is that you never tell a lie, right,
you old man?
That's right, I'm late for work yesterday.
I'm late for this, but
I was so annoyed by the screams of those mean men
that my cute Charis-chan woke up...
I was in a big trouble.
Really?
Were they your seniors?
Probably.
Ah, that's right.
Somehow, I heard the girl's name a lot.
I think...
Sa... Sa... Sa...
Saori!
Yes, Saori!
As I thought.
I won't tell a lie!
I skipped my work because I was drunk,
and I worried about my friends,
and I was annoyed by people's hands!
What a bad guy!
Y-Yes...
Don't worry, Terai.
Tell Nakagawa and Reiko to return to their normal jobs.
But...
I have to go to a important ceremony from now on.
When he comes back,
I'll make sure to squeeze the oil out of him later!
Tell him that.
Y-Yes!
Hey!
Somebody help me!
No, no.
We've done a lot of things, but nobody noticed.
We're just hungry.
That's why we're just staying still!
I'm sorry, Yuriko!
This isn't for Hatakeyama-kun, is it?
What?
Ah...
If she gets this,
she'll be a writer.
I see...
We have a responsibility to get him involved, don't we?
Even if we didn't know,
we brought him here the night before the wedding.
No, I think we heard you.
What?
You're getting married tomorrow?
Yes!
It's a big deal!
So, if she gets this,
will she be a writer?
Yes!
It's included in my initials!
That being said,
I'm early tomorrow,
so I'll be going home now.
What are you doing?!
Getting married tomorrow
means tonight is the last night of my life!
But I'm going home soon!
If you get married,
you'll be left behind by God!
You'll be with me until the morning!
I'll take care of this writer until then!
No, please give it back!
Shut up!
Hey, hey!
Bye!
Shut up!
No, no, no!
What's wrong?
Then,
it's all our fault, isn't it?
Yeah.
I have to get him married somehow.
But what do we do?
Huh?
What the hell are you eating?
Um, gum.
You ate it all, didn't you?
What?!
You ate the only food?!
I'll give it back to you!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Huh?
SHAow2
SHOW2
Your hand is frozen.
SHOWS
What's wrong?
I see.
Reiko, isn't this the president's work?
What?
It's been 25 years, but it's changed a lot.
I went to see the work of Miyashita Jinko and Esumi Eimei's Kumashiro Tatsue,
but Kameyari Meikazawa isn't here anymore.
There have been many things in the past 25 years.
I'll give you some instructions.
I'll be old and remember the old days.
That was a great speech, sir.
I heard you could see the governor, but it seems you haven't seen him yet.
I see. I'm sorry.
I wanted you to hear my speech.
What?
I heard you could see the governor, but it seems you haven't seen him yet.
There's the president, too.
Kei, what's that?
I wonder what it is.
Well,
I don't know.
let's begin the
Senior, hurry!
I'm in a hurry.
What?
Let's start!
Ready, set, go!
Alright!
Go, Hatakeyama!
The monster is angry!
No way!
Why?
I have to calm it down!
I did it!
It's out! It's out!
What is this?
Is this...
...a...
...ghost?!
Why is it in this place?!
It's a mountain!
Ah!
Here, here!
I got it!
Give it back to me!
It's my lighter!
What's wrong with you?
It's a mountain! Alright! Let's climb the mountain!
Oh, you're giving me the light back!
Here, take this!
Alright! Alright!
Good!
Here I go!
What!!
Th, that's how it should be!
amorph~
Nj xu chal~
That's stupid!!
Hey, Hatakeyama! The wedding is--
It's coming, in no time.
Let's go, Hatakeyama-kun.
Yes. Everyone, thank you very much.
Please tell Ryotsu-san about this.
Yes.
Let's go.
How is it going?
It seems it's better to pretend that nothing happened.
That's right.
Take this!
The ceremony will start in five minutes.
Five minutes is enough!
Hey!
You big idiot!
Even if you say that, I was locked up and I was about to become a Buddha.
It's your fault, you idiot!
You idiot!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being so mean!
Shizuna Ooi
An old man who also played with his old muffler.
It seems to be back now!
Shizuna Ooi
Oni-chan, the зр.
It seems to be a little tricky…
Shizuna Ooi
It's a good feeling
So I walked on the black side of the Akegokai
I walked on the black side of the Akegokai
Everyone was a child at least once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with great-looking faces
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll meet everyone
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Please subscribe!
One hundred million yen!
Why is the bonus being paid one hundred million yen?
Wait, even if it's wrong
The one who entered my account once is mine
I'll withdraw all the money and pay back the debt I've earned so far
Next time, Bonus Battle Six
Thank you!
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Thank you!
I'll use one more
Please subscribe!