In the middle of the sea, dawn was falling
I picked up my love stone and flew in my shoes
From the water tank of the "Tongari-boshi"
To the "Kai-shakuten"
The sun sets
"It's already over tomorrow"
"Katsushika, Shibamata, and happiness"
I lost them and noticed
That I was the fool
"Sakuretsu! G-san Power!"
I'm here at Kameyari Park.
What?
You're a G-san?
Why do I have to go see what's going on?
Why don't you go see it?
What? Is there something important?
Anyway,
"Senpai Ryo-san"
Ryo-chan, I'll tell the headmaster.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey!
Ryo-san's grandfather must be over a hundred years old.
Oh, my!
A hundred and sixty?
He's still living alone at a young age?
Anyway, no matter what my father says,
Tsukuda-jima won't move.
It's like a mirror for my grandfather.
I have a lot of affection for Tsukuda-jima.
Well, well.
There are few places in Edo-jocho that remain.
Hmm...
Huh?
What?
I see.
Well, Tsukuda-jima was the fishing town
that the Tokugan-eyasu formed in the Edo period.
Oh?
The Shirauro-ryo family of the Shogunate
was the pride of the fishermen in Tsukuda-jima.
So, did your grandfather also used to be a fisherman?
No.
My grandfather was a shoemaker who bought the fishing rod
and ran the fishing house.
So, your father had the shop.
I see.
Well...
It's been a while since I last came here.
Tsukuda-jima has changed a lot.
It surely is different from what I imagined.
My grandfather's home was around here.
I see.
I can't find the name Ryotsu.
Hmm...
If it's a turtle, we can change it.
What? I don't have a turtle.
But where is a turtle?
Nobody has one.
There's a cave in the village where you can't enter.
There's a cave where you can't enter.
If you flash and go in there, you'll find it.
What? Really?
Yeah.
By the way, do you know where Ryotsu is?
What?
Huh?
I don't know.
Oh, Mr. Ryotsu, you're in danger!
Are you all right, Mr. Ryotsu?
What the hell is this?
It's not a multipurpose gun.
Who did this?
I'm sorry...
Huh?
Gramps!
Gramps...
Uh-oh!
Thank goodness! My plane is safe!
Don't worry about your grandchild!
Grandchild?
Oh! It's not my grandchild's family!
Hello!
Could it be...
...that this is your...
I guess there's something I've made.
A-A grandfather?
Is it you, grandfather?
Wasn't it Kito-kun?
Kito-kun?
Who?
I got a call from my father this morning that my grandfather is Kito-kun!
Oh!
I played the game at night and I got a great score!
I told everyone!
Kito-kun! Kito-kun!
A record score!
I'll take it easy...
Kito-kun...
Don't make such a fool of yourself!
You don't need to pay attention to me.
Nagagawa, Kaeru!
Let's go, Nagagawa.
Huh? Kaeru?
He's just arrived!
When will the guests who visit this place come again?
They won't come...
That old man...
Senpai, why don't you take your time?
I'll talk to the head of the club about it.
I want you to meet someone.
I'm sure you've met someone.
They won't come...
Since you're here, how about having lunch with me?
Lunch?
Are you going to treat me?
Yes, I'm going home!
I'm in pain.
I've been suffering from a disease that's been relapsing.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, but...
Esta-
It's okay.
I can't see clearly.
I can't see.
I can't feel.
I'm sorry.
I have a life of only 106 years.
I've been in a lonely place all my life.
I'm going to my chief's office, tomorrow.
What?!
But he said he wanted to meet the prince!
Then, who is he?
He's a bit shy, isn't he?
You're right!
We got it!
I got it! I know a place I want to go!
Is this it?
Look! It's on the information sheet!
This is the most popular place for gals!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh! I see!
Oh, I see.
This is delicious!
Hey, if you eat it so hastily, you'll get a stomachache!
This Kororata is really delicious!
Is that Kororata?
It's a word for a lamb called "roast rata".
In short, Kororata.
I got it from Kazuo, so it's even more delicious!
I'm Kankichi!
Oh, right, right.
I'm Kankichi, the son of Kingoro.
I'm a boss!
I'm Ginji!
Yes, yes, I'm Ginji, Ginji.
I run a ramen shop in Aoyama.
It's a Tsukudaniya in Asakusa.
Stop it! I won't eat it anymore!
Give it to me! I'll eat it!
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I have 24 grandchildren.
Forgive me.
Oh?
Kanpei! It's Gya-pami!
What?
I can see a gal's pants.
To put it simply...
Don't joke around!
Just eat it!
Tsukuda Island has changed a lot.
You can build new buildings one after another.
There's nothing to be sad about.
Come to think of it, I was a kid and I was stupid about the skyscrapers...
There was no Tsukishima either.
What?
What's going on here?
Hey!
This is about 100 years ago.
What the hell?
Why is this one different?
Back in the day, there wasn't even one Tsukuda.
Yeah.
I heard that you had a boat.
Yes.
I traveled from Akashi-cho to Tsukuda in only four to five minutes.
It's close to Ginza, and I've used it a lot.
You're riding on your own baby.
Really? I don't remember much.
That was when I was still working at the Tsukudaniya.
Your mother came to get the ingredients for the Tsukudaniya.
I was going to take you to Asakusa.
I dropped you on the surface of the ship.
What happened?
The ship came out like nothing happened.
What?
I found you floating on the surface of the ship in the middle of the river.
Oh, no! The baby's drowning!
Now I remember.
Don't forget to drown!
Oh, there's another Gyappa!
It's Kankichi!
Was it around here?
What's wrong?
My house is gone!
What?
It was on fire for a few hours when I left my sight.
You idiot!
No way!
My house is over there.
What?
That's the high-rise apartment!
Where did you get that money?
The neighbors next door gave me a lot of money to live with.
I love expensive places.
No.
He's not even attached to me.
What?
No, I didn't rent it.
No, I didn't.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry!
I don't have any, either.
Stop doing that.
Kankichi!
What happened, Kankichi?
Stop it!
Yeah.
Who's that?
What's with the long hair?
The man next door likes cooking.
I'll make him eat Indian curry later.
Cheers.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, Mottou.
Yeah.
Can I borrow a Lacrosse racket?
Mine's from Ikarijima.
Oh, don't bring it to me, Mottou.
That old man has a Lacrosse racket.
Kansan, you're not going home.
Good work.
Leave it here.
Can't you lock the door?
I've never locked a door in my life.
First, I forgot where I left it.
You're too careless living alone.
I'm not.
I'm free to go out like Nagaya.
I don't think Nagaya is safe.
Don't say that.
What if you get caught?
I'll be fine.
Thank you.
That's cheap.
I won't.
That's the problem.
You can buy it at the market.
What?
The horizontal route.
Right.
I want to travel to the from Anna and Kansai.
Wait a minute.
We're going to do a trip there.
From here, why would you do it?
It's too gentle.
Who's there?
From here, I'm going.
I've never seen a game like this before.
Of course.
This is the new game software I made.
What? You made a game software?
Alright, I'll try it.
If you want to play, I'll charge you 1,000 yen.
You're such a big-ass old man.
No!
I'll just serve you a beer and a snack.
Let's see...
Yakiyami...
It's pretty good.
I'm done with the bug-tripping.
I just need to sell it.
It smells bad.
Really?
You're taking too much of my time.
Hey, Kanta! Kanta! Kanta!
Kanta!
I'm Kankichi!
I finally woke up.
What is this?
I was tied up by that thief earlier.
The Entire Tome of the Land...
The Entire Time of the Land?
You're not hurt, revil?
I'm fine...
Besides, I've stolen something precious to me.
Something more precious than my life.
Damn it...
I'mashiro Haya...
What?
A plum!
Uh-oh.
So, they just hung up.
That doesn't scare me.
Just who do we lock them in?
Kajira!
Someone get in!
You won't get any!
This place is completely blue!
There's no point in doing this, let's just leave it there.
Roger!
carton!
Roger, Roger...
What an idiot!
You're acting too strong!
I'm back!
I can't move my legs!
The fire will make it worse!
Where is the fire extinguisher?
You have to buy a fire extinguisher four days before a computer!
I can't take it!
Huh?
Whoa! A cockroach!
Whoa!
I thought I was dead.
I'm relieved.
You're being too kind!
Hurry up, Ginpei!
Just hold on!
I'm putting a lot of pressure on you, Chouji!
Hey!
Hold on! Hold on!
You're using me as a cover!
There he is!
I found the culprit!
All right! Let's go after him!
Wait! This way is faster!
The apartments in the basement are quite well-placed.
What?
Skydiving!
Poor Ryosuke!
Digit Tracing!
Hey!
You're going to fall asleep faster than an elevator!
You want to kill me?
You're going to run to Tsumiyoshi Shrine, aren't you?
Damn it!
I'll catch you!
You idiot!
There's a shortcut.
What?
Isn't it too narrow?
It's easy for one person, but it's hard for two.
You idiot!
You're going to die!
Did something happen?
I did my best.
Don't go sideways.
Go vertically.
I see.
Ouch!
It hurts, Kazuo!
Shut up!
Damn it!
Wait! Give me my gold!
Where's the guy who told me to wait?
Idiot!
What are you talking about?
You're going to die!
I'll leave that thief alone!
I don't even know where the gold is!
What are you talking about, Kanta?
There are many memories of the old man and the old woman in the safe.
I can't live without that!
Is it a very important memory that this old man is so particular about?
I understand! I understand! I understand!
You just have to catch me!
Kanta...
I understood you.
You're just like that!
You're like that!
You're a stick!
That's right!
I'm saved!
Please, untie me!
What's wrong, Kanta?
The thief killed me.
It's a horrible tragedy.
That's right!
By the way, the racket I borrowed this time was pretty good.
I see.
I see. That's good.
If we don't hurry, we'll lose the thief!
Don't worry.
Go, Shinden Bulldog!
You even had this?
To escape from this Tsukuda Island,
we must cross Aioi Bridge, Kachidoki Bridge, Tsukida Bridge, and the Chuo Bridge.
He's somewhere on the back of the bridge.
I'll catch him!
There he is!
Don't underestimate my lightning skill!
Run this thing!
W- Wait a second!
Kansarou, are you all right?
W- why not?
How many times do I have to kill you?
That's absolute nonsense.
I almost forgot that there's a chainsaw at that bridge.
Huh?
Kinpei, he's running away!
Wait up!
They're persistent.
That means he's a pretty good sleeper.
Hey, give me back my wallet!
Don't come near me!
Wait!
What the hell are you doing?
Stop!
You idiot!
Damn you!
Get out of my way!
If you don't, I'll tear this place down!
Understood?
I-I won't let you do that.
I'm begging you!
You bastard!
The safe!
Thank you for your hard work!
Take this.
Thank goodness!
Thank you, Mr. Yuka!
Just in case, you should go back inside.
Wh-wh-what is this?!
This game software is really hard to get right now.
Thank you, Kazuo!
Huh?
This is a model of the the memory siemprezation box of your grandma!
S-sorry, my grandma and I used to play this game software when we were kids.
I played it a lot!
A hundred years ago, there was such a thing!!
You fucking liar!
Aaaaaahhhhhh!
F coisa!!
Damn it. You guys are out of your mind.
You loser!
I won't come back to you.
Listen up, everyone.
I'm on behalf of the lady from the hot spring trip.
I will be closely taking care of them, and from now on, I'll do my best to help you work the land nine-toed.
Please, remember that I told you, I'll do my best to protect you.
Next time, you will be wouldn't welcome alone, but I do.
See you then!
I have a lot of things I want to do
I want to run through the vast desert on my bike
I want to be freer than a bird
A lady's dream changes at the speed of light
I'm sorry, my love, I lost
The future of the panorama is a dazzling light
I want to be freer than a bird
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me