Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♪
♪ I want to pass through the new era ♪
♪ I want to dive in with my yellow-green hair ♪
♪ I wanna dive into paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing all the trendy clothes ♪
♪ I'll be ten times more handsome ♪
♪ Let it rain ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Let's run and do it ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the next world tomorrow ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if it's a little dark ♪
♪ I don't want to say it ♪
♪ I'm excited and excited ♪
♪ I want to be strong and tall ♪
The End
Ryo, I'm in training now.
Good morning.
Don't be so scared!
I'm surprised.
What's wrong, Ryo?
The truth is...
Hm?
Ryo is trying to get money from the president.
I asked him with a serious face, so I lent him the money.
I have the money next week, but I don't have any money.
How much did you lend me?
About 70,000 yen.
70,000 yen?
Ouch! What are you doing?
Chief!
You're a rich man!
I'm not a rich man. I don't want to be pulled out of the castle.
When did you get the money?
I read it in the newspaper.
Is that wrong?
Maybe it's my misunderstanding.
I'll call you even if you die!
Ouch!
I'm more reluctant to love than usual today, chief.
Of course!
You tricked the director and borrowed the money.
You tricked the director?
That's why I bought a 70,000 yen plum.
What?
Chief, please don't misunderstand.
I bought this with the money I had.
Really?
Of course!
Hey, you!
Get in bed and lie down.
Inside, your arms.
Yes, sir.
How can I do this?
Excuse me.
From tomorrow, you are going to be from my place.
It won't take long.
I'm going to go train as a diver and take the money from you.
Does that sound like me?
Yes.
My master said you're not the best at it.
Okay.
Thank you, everyone.
Please take care of my training.
Look, Ryosuke!
I'm only asking for your help.
I'm doing what I like.
Get out of here!
What is all this?
I've been wearing this for 10 days.
I can't sleep well when I change my pillow.
You're not going to the Amazon.
Show me.
Do you think you can train with this?
That's why I'm trying to be myself so that I don't feel like playing.
Shut up.
I'll take care of everything.
I understand.
I'm a man of my word.
I think you'll get it back anytime.
Mr. Ryotsu.
Yes.
I'll name you Chinnen instead of Zoku.
Chinnen?
Then I'll name you Sennen and Mannen.
These two are Chinnen's teachers.
Start training now.
Thank you.
You guys...
Please.
We've been training for a week.
I'm Zannen.
I'm Munen.
Nice to meet you.
You're eating the same food.
Let's get along.
Just leave it to me.
Yes.
Throw away Zannen from your head.
You'll sit in the chair without regret.
Start.
You've been trapped in Zannen.
Why do you know?
If you train like me,
you'll understand what people like you think.
I know.
What?
You just thought I was lying, didn't you?
I didn't think so.
Don't make things up.
What's wrong with you?
What the hell are you talking about?
What?
I'll beat you.
Don't underestimate me.
Damn it.
I'll kill you!
You!
The temple is under unlawful authority.
So you can't come here.
They're running away!
Um...
Glory!
Rise!
Y-You did it wrong!
I thought you could cut my heart off!
Just get changed and let's go.
Unfortunately, I'm the manager,
so please take care of the corridor.
Damn!
Now that Maruta's pillow is this bad,
why are you telling me to stay here?
Can you believe how long I've always been hiding
The corridor of this temple is very difficult.
The front part is more hazy, so you can't see, right?
Wait, wait!
It would be a waste of time to do that.
But...
Yeah.
If you make a lot of corridors like this, you can finish it in one go, right?
You go that way. I'll go this way.
But if you do this, the platform will...
The platform is scary and you'll get hit.
If you go around at full speed, you'll finish in 5 minutes.
Go that way!
What? You're done already?
Yes, completely.
Don't be stupid. I'm not done yet.
It's only been 5 minutes, right?
That's over, meow.
Okay, if you say that, I'll check it out.
But if you're lying, you'd better be prepared.
Yes, sir.
Here, eat, eat.
What's this?
Is this all?
It's just food and a pee.
It's a temple's specialty, so we don't use meat or fish.
Vegetables and all that stuff are the same as Kirigiri.
You're really putting up with it.
It can't be helped.
This is also a training.
Now, let's eat.
I hid it in my pants and brought it here.
You guys can eat it, too.
No, no.
It's forbidden to eat meat.
I'll give you a punishment. A punishment.
I see.
That's all you've got.
If you guys don't eat it, I'll eat it all by myself.
Let's eat.
It's delicious?
You guys really don't need to eat.
Let's eat.
Thanks...
Good.
That's right.
That's right. You have to be honest with your desire.
You guys have a good view.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Master Chen.
It's a pity that the guy has a terrible feeling.
I stopped him desperately, but he didn't listen to me at all.
No way. This is Mr. Chen.
Shut up!
You can't blame someone like that.
Cut!
I'm responsible for the company.
You can sit in the corridor until nightfall.
No way.
Cut!
Damn it. My legs are stiff.
I should sit in the corridor.
Now I say.
You guys should be responsible for this.
You're the ones that must help me go to sleep when I'm sleepy.
I don't have a good sleep.
You guys think I'm a bad sleeper?
We don't have a good sleeper.
I'm not sleeping right now.
It's so annoying.
I have got nothing else to do but sleep!
I'm not sleeping!
You've got nothing to do but sleep.
Never let me sleep!
Stop it.
I can't go.
It's okay. It's night.
If we get through here, we'll be...
What? A cat?
It's a big cat.
No way...
No way!
We can't go on like this.
Piranha!
B-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b-b!
Hey, Jin!
I won't let you escape!
That's not what I meant!
Please do something about them!
Huh? Ryo-san's not here?
I came here to ask you about this game's strategy.
I'm sorry. Ryo-chan is currently in training.
Tch.
Ryo-chan is surprisingly popular.
He's been asking for you to repair toys since yesterday,
and tell him how to play the game.
Kids come to see him a lot.
He's a good example of that.
He is.
I wonder what he's been up to lately.
I'll leave the rest to you.
See you later.
What happened?
It seems like a big guy has passed away.
He said he was going to get the staff from Tokyo.
Great! Then I'll be the only one today!
Twist, twist, twist without any other people.
But you have to do the training properly.
Twist your hips.
This is the one I need.
Hehehe.
The Rally-Bong was of great help.
I made a lot of money, and I'm so glad I could get both of them.
This is terrible!
What happened?
I got a notice at 10 today.
I thought it was tomorrow.
What did you say?
Why didn't you tell me that it was important?
What should I do?
It's my responsibility.
Let me know.
Wait, wait.
I don't want to be held accountable for the Rally-Bong.
I'll tell you that I'm the chief.
You?
Are you sure?
I'm good at lying.
Leave it to me.
How do I look?
I look like a chief, right?
Yes, if you tell me.
I'll go then.
Well, then.
Let's go.
See ya.
Oh no!
I'll be dead if they find out.
I'm the chief.
Huh?
"Heart of Koin " Now
... this way. Yes,
sir! Damn it!
It's burnt to the ground!
♪ Yaren, Soren, Kita, Senju, Ayase, Kameari, Kanemachi, Matsudo, Ryogoku, Asakusa, Akihabara ♪
That's all.
Eh?
Your majesty!
Oh no! They found us!
I'm impressed. We don't even know your religion.
Yeah, yeah.
Eh?
Thank you for your hard work!
It's nothing.
Then, Amen.
I'll take this.
I did it.
The books are all in kanji, so they can't be useful for amateurs.
By the way, how much did you pay for this?
Wow!
Hoshido.
I didn't know you could get this much for a book.
Welcome back. How was it?
It was perfect.
I'm glad you came today.
That's good.
Let's get going.
Order 10 servings of sashimi and 10 servings of meat for sukiyaki.
It's a party until the masters leave.
But, Daikin...
Idiot!
You can't think of such a stupid thing as becoming a monk.
I can't.
You can't be a monk.
Order a 2-kilo bottle of beer for the bar.
Thank you, sir.
Cheers!
I'm turning it even more than usual.
That's great!
Jinmen-san, you're the best!
Hahaha...
You're on the phone.
I see.
Red Snake, come on!
Here, kiss of fire!
Hey, you! Why aren't you coming out?
There's no way you can do it!
Jinmen-san is the best!
Hey, now you do something.
What about me?
That's right.
If you can't do even one of the secret arts, you can't become a great monk.
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
Jinmen-san, the master just...
Call him Jinmen-masho.
Ah, Jinmen-masho...
I got a call from his younger brother.
He said he wouldn't go to the temple he was asked to go to, so I thought he'd go instead.
All right.
If I go, answer me.
Yes.
Jinmen-masho, is that really okay?
Leave it to me!
If you refuse the temple, you'll be punished.
You can't go against the Buddha's path.
I-I see.
Everything is part of the training.
You can follow me.
Yahoo!
How much are you going to pay this time?
Wait for me!
I-I found it!
It's here, Jinmen-masho!
Hmm.
Huh?
Why is the chief here?
Oh, Master, I've been waiting.
Oh, no.
Isn't this the chief's brother's house?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for the trouble.
No, actually, I have to go.
Hey!
Listen, hey!
It's my brother.
Hello.
This is the chief who came with us this time.
Please, let me in.
Oh, this way.
This way.
Huh?
Yamada-todi.
What's wrong?
You're a baby.
Come on.
What's wrong?
You've prepared a lot of food.
I don't think I can escape with this.
Oh!
Huh?
What's wrong?
I was in a hurry, so I took the bag with the
headband and the party goods.
What?
Did you make a mistake?
But I can't go back.
I have to get rid of it somehow.
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
Don't come with them.
What?
They're like us.
Don't be silent!
They're like you.
Don't touch me.
How could I allow you, my brother?
You say that I am your brother who has the right to eat?
How can I be your brother?
Then I'll never overlook.
But you have a death sentence.
I'm sorry.
That's all.
That's how it works, huh?
Yeah, that's one big idiot at Ryotsu.
Well anyway, it's time to hang up now.
Before we get to current business, I would really like to ask someone for a favor, but...
What?
When you give your blessing, you have to turn three times and cry.
What for?
I told you the frequency is different, right?
Do it. You'll get a punishment.
I won't do as you say.
But, brother...
Just go!
Here we go.
No...
James!
What?
Open your mouth wide and run while you drool!
Do you understand?
No...
You can't go any further!
It hurts, doesn't it?
It doesn't hurt if you just take a deep breath.
It doesn't hurt if you just stop and hit me.
What?
Oh, I remember something.
You said you hit me without showing your cute face.
If you don't confess honestly, everyone here will get a punishment.
I'm sorry.
You remember something?
What's wrong, Daijiro?
Ah, yes.
How scary!
Because of him, everyone will get a punishment.
Daijiro, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for confessing in front of a great prince from Shotenji.
I'm sorry.
Shotenji...
Excuse me.
Could you take off your glasses?
What are you talking about?
This is the characteristic of my sect.
I can't do it.
Yes, yes.
Can't you hear me?
I'll beat you up!
Hmm...
Hey, Daijiro!
Ryotsu!
There's 10,000 yen there!
What?
Where is it?
Where?
G-g-g-g...
Hmm...
What's wrong with you?
I knew it.
Ryotsu is the one who's talking nonsense!
No, it's just a misunderstanding...
Ryotsu!
I'm going to get you!
Stop!
Why are you doing this to me?
Somebody help me!
Hey, hey!
What's wrong?
Stop it!
It's fine, you get the money!
What's wrong?
Hey, stop it!
Hey, shut up!
Get out of here!
You get a bottle of alcohol on your hands!
Can't you let your brain relax?
What's wrong?
Created by the Ino visit,
And the lion will become a cat again.
I don't have enough training.
Mr. Young Man.
S-s-s-save me!
7 hours of work is too much!
I'm going to die!
You, old man, leave the new My Home to me.
I'll find you a better place than the manager's house!
I'm a professional buyer after all!
Next time on Our My Home!
♪ Even if I try to stop the clock, ♪
♪ time will pass by. ♪
♪ Don't look down on me. ♪
♪ I'll laugh my way out of this and live on. ♪
♪ Even if it rains today, ♪
♪ tomorrow will be sunny. ♪
♪ Bye-bye. ♪
♪ I'll wash my hands. ♪
♪ I'll say goodbye to the things I hate. ♪