"Taiko Sensei"
When watching TV, make sure the room is bright and see how far you can get.
The poor thing, come to me!
I'm here too, and I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
They'll be alright in a while
If you don't have a job, come to me
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red cloud
They'll be alright in a while
You understand, right?
You understand, you understand
If you do, just shut up and follow me
How'd you like to drink your own sake?
How'd you like to get drunk?
Greetings, great ancestors!
What's that?
The old man that was caught with just a glass of sake is calling the Ryotsu of Asakusa?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. That old man...
Could he be...?
Okay, I'll go anyway.
Ah, Mom.
Where did the old man from Kanbei on Tsukuda Island go?
Ah, he said he was going to Morujibu.
Morujibu?
It's a very high-class place, isn't it?
Then, the place where he ate and drank without permission is unrelated to me.
That's right, he'll come back to visit, right?
Well, I'm busy, so I'll cut it, Mom.
If you don't take care of your ancestors, you'll get a punishment.
Okay, okay.
So, have you found out where the old man is?
Anyway, what he's saying is meaningless, and he says he was born in the 6th year of the Kaiei.
Kaiei? What's that?
Speaking of the 6th year of the Kaiei, it's probably the year of the Edo period.
But that would make him 160 years old this year.
What?
My grandfather used to call me Ryotsu Tamekichi, but I guess he doesn't have a heart.
Tamekichi? I've heard of it somewhere.
He's your relative, right?
I don't know.
Anyway, please help me for a while until we find that old man.
Then, I'll go back to the dressing room.
Why do I have to find an old man who ate and drank without permission?
It's not unrelated.
It's me.
Honoyama!
Ryotsu Tamekichi is your grandfather?
This is the end of the relationship.
What?
Old man?
He's been creating trouble every day.
He was a very important person, but he's still a child who will escape from heaven.
Escape?
Listen, you, his grandson, will be responsible for finding Tamekichi immediately.
Me?
That's your job.
Look at this.
You'll go to hell after the second origin.
If you go to hell, you'll be a turtle forever.
You'll be in hell forever.
Hell?
But if you find Tamekichi and give him to me, I'll give you your rights.
What's this?
Where is this place?
Ginza?
This is Ginza?
Before I knew it, it looks like the west.
Everyone's dressed up.
I see.
I'm back to life.
I'm doing it on a daily basis, so I'm giving you a reward.
Finally, I'm in heaven.
Don't stretch out.
I'm going to die.
In other words, an old man who has lived through the end of the Edo period is wandering around there.
But you're a magician, aren't you?
Can you catch him?
It's a very difficult job to find someone who is not from this world.
And it's dangerous to bring him back to my head.
Don't listen to what you're saying.
What?
In other words, the reason why Tamekichi escaped to heaven is your responsibility.
If you don't bring him back before your boss finds out, he'll be in trouble and your head will be in danger.
That's what I'm saying.
I gave up.
What?
What's wrong?
I gave up looking for that old man.
I gave up.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Not only the end of the Edo period, but also the reward.
If you do that, I'll find you.
I'm going to be in trouble.
If you don't want to.
Wait, I got it.
What do you want?
The Edo period until now will be the end of the Edo period.
In addition, there will be no Edo period for 100 years.
What?
I don't think I can do that.
You're not a man.
Then...
I got it.
Then the contract is signed.
Yeah.
But the car has been moving for a while now.
What?
Yeah.
I tried to avoid the old man who suddenly jumped out of the car, but when I stepped on the brake, the car behind me crashed.
I tried to avoid that old man, but when I stepped on the brake, the car behind me crashed.
Old man?
Hey, what kind of old man were you?
Um, in a kimono...
I was in a pink photo.
How was that?
No doubt.
I feel like I'm going to be in big trouble if I don't catch him soon.
He looks good on you.
Yeah, this is also good.
Also, this is a tennis coach who just entered yesterday.
Hey, I'm afraid, but please don't stick to the windows.
What?
Huh? Can I have a udon-kutta-yaoya?
N-no! Please don't!
Okay, okay. I'm a strong woman.
The yauya-san and udon-ya-san are also around the traffic light.
Please go over there.
Where's the sake shop?
There is, probably.
I see. Yes, yes, this way.
What the hell are you doing?
Excuse me.
Here are the other new products for this season.
Here are the new products for this season.
It seems that they're not here either.
I was searching for them one by one.
I can't wait. Let's split up and search.
What about your magic wand?
I hurriedly took it out, so I forgot it in the locker of the heaven police.
Then you can't use magic. You're just an old man.
I'm sorry, I'm just an old man.
I'll get the wand.
If you find a place to stay in the meantime, please catch me.
Can I run home?
Of course.
But there's no better way to find your grandpa.
Huh?
Oh, I see. It's sake.
Hello.
Good evening.
It's time for the "Kondate".
This is very polite.
Today, I'd like to make a simple and easy-to-make "omotenashi" dish,
called "chirashi-sushi".
Yes, I understand.
Chirashi-sushi is nice.
You all like it, don't you?
Yes, I love sushi.
Then, I'll take the frozen one.
You can have the ones we buy.
Please prepare the eel.
What? Eel?
Eel...
Sorry, I have something to do.
Grandpa.
What?
It's the TV.
Oh! I feel like I finally met someone I know.
Who are you?
You know...
I'm the extra of Bakumatsu-den, which is just around the corner.
You can have it.
You...
You!
The Extra of Bakumatsu-den
We can see a lot of documents from that time.
Oh, it's pretty good.
Oh, that's...
Ryoma-san!
I'll return the car later.
Yes!
With this amount of money, we can call that old man.
It's me, Tamekichi from Tsukudaniya.
Did you forget?
I'm the Tamekichi who always followed the death of Ryoma-san.
Please take a good look at this!
Hey, Ryoma-san, please say something.
Sensei, I'm looking forward to working with you.
Oh, yes.
Then, I would like to talk to Professor Oyamada, the organizer and observer of this Bakumatsu-Ten.
I'm Oyamada.
Oh, I'm old now.
I was a 12 or 13-year-old boy at that time.
I don't know, but it's not impossible.
It's pretty good.
You're talking a lot, Ryoma-san.
Hey, old man.
This is a doll made by me.
What?
A doll?
Oh, is this a doll?
Let's interview the visitors.
Are you also a fan of Ryoma Sakamoto?
No, I'm Tamekichi from Ryotsu.
You like Ryoma Sakamoto, don't you?
I used to go to Ryoma-san's favorite Tsukudaniya Ryotei often.
That's why I like him.
As you see, this is the mother of Bakumatsu.
Now, she left a deep impression on Japanese people.
That's why I went to deliver this doll to her.
Oh, I remember this photo very well.
I was around here.
Do you like Bakumatsu?
Yes, this is the era I lived in.
There's no such thing as like or dislike.
Oh, I remember this.
I used to watch this around here.
The photo is fine.
It looks like a thunder, but it shines a little.
I'm a little afraid.
But I've seen a lot of your pictures.
What? Is that true?
I went to see it when you came to Edo.
I can't believe it, but I'm sure it's not a loss.
Back then...
This is...
It smells like alcohol.
If it's true, I'm going to light a fire to welcome you.
But I'm an old man, so I'll have to drink alcohol.
There's another one here.
I didn't know there was alcohol on the road.
It's heaven.
There's another one there.
What a dirty drink.
There are legs in ghosts.
Are you done drinking?
Look, old man.
You opened the Ittodaru by yourself.
What? Ittodaru?
It's a little bit left.
It's a scary drink.
It makes my face red.
What's your name, old man?
Me? I'm Ryoma Sakamoto.
What?
No, no.
I'm Ryo and Tamekichi Moshinosuke.
I knew it.
I heard you escaped heaven.
Hanayama changed the order and was looking for you.
Hanayama?
I don't know.
He's the old man of the magician.
He's from the heaven police.
That's him.
I was drunk at work.
Who are you?
I'm your son, Kanbi.
Your son, Genji.
Ryozu, Kankichi.
Your grandson, Kankichi?
I didn't know.
I don't know.
Because you're born after you die.
Oh, that's true.
Kankichi, is there no more alcohol?
You drank Ittodaru so fast.
There's no more.
Half of it is enough.
I can't drink it, so I'll drink it.
It's better to give it to Hanayama as soon as possible.
This old man.
Mr. Ryoji.
I have a precious photo of the explosion.
A precious photo?
Not just a photo.
There are many other things.
It's my treasure.
Please show me the picture.
If you don't mind, I would like to buy it for the appropriate price.
What?
Buy, make money, drink.
I can drink alcohol.
Yes, it's good.
Thank you.
Do you have such a precious thing?
Yes, it should be in the house of Asakusa.
What? Tsukudaniya?
Yes.
Before you go back to heaven, you can make a fortune with this old man.
Is it already the end of the year?
That's right.
If you are tired, it will be autumn.
From today,
I will report "The first store of the year from the end of the year that is open in Ginza".
Are you a fan of Ryo Sakamoto?
No, I am Mr. Tamekichi Ryozo.
I am Mr. Tamekichi Ryozo.
Now, I am ready.
When the old man becomes a monk,
he comes back early,
when he returns, he rides a bull and goes slowly.
When he returns, he rides a bull and goes slowly.
I used to go to the temple of Ryouma's favorite tsukuda.
You are strange.
I can't believe it.
You haven't changed at all.
Oh, Kankichi, are you a guest?
You are my mother.
You are Ginji's wife.
Yes, I am.
You can go home sometimes.
That's right. We live in the same Tokyo.
What?
What happened to your father?
My father died.
What?
What is this?
Is this beer?
You are drinking alcohol again.
Don't be stupid. Beer is like water.
It's Tamekichi.
What's going on?
Don't worry.
Your father is back.
Really?
Yes, he is back.
Mom.
Good morning.
The taste of tsukudani seems to have not changed.
Uncle, is the alcohol good?
Yes, it's good.
I see.
I'm glad.
What is it?
There was nothing in the garden.
Hey, Uncle.
I'm looking for something to eat.
Help me.
It's time to come to the mountain.
What are you looking for?
It's a treasure.
A treasure?
Hey, that's it.
What? Really?
I'm coming.
Then, let's see.
It's a photo.
It's quite old.
A chocolate?
It's nostalgic.
What is this?
Sassanoha?
It's all nonsense.
What is this photo?
This is a photo taken by Ryoma.
It's me.
Is that so?
Is there a photo of Ryoma Sakamoto?
No, there isn't.
No, there isn't?
Don't make a fuss.
Well, let's see the other one.
This is...
Oh, that one.
That's the one of Saseki Natsume.
Saseki Natsume?
This one looks like a piece of paper.
It's Higuchi Ichiyo's.
Is Higuchi Ichiyo the one who drew that bamboo comparison?
You're so stupid, Kawa.
Is that Ichiyo's manuscript?
No, it's not.
What is this?
It's a letter from Higuchi Ichiyo.
What?
It's a leaf of a sassanoha cut by the Prime Minister of Japan.
What is this?
It's a chocolate I drank last night.
I'll be off then.
Wait a minute.
If I search more, I'll find more treasures.
There are many of those of that era.
I'm not just saying they're old.
If you find real treasures, please contact me anytime.
Then...
I don't mind.
Thank you for your help.
Damn it!
I didn't know there was an old man like that.
Where did he go? The toilet?
He's so useless.
You're right.
You know, the old man left the back door.
What?
That's strange.
I think it's around here.
What's wrong?
He's here!
Oh, old man!
Hey, Kankichi!
Old man!
You're worried if you disappear!
There's no Shinnanoya.
When I came here, I always had a drink with a drink.
Shinnanoya?
This is a convenience store.
Oh, are you going back to your hometown?
Oh, I see.
This is a bar.
Yeah, I can't do business with just alcohol these days.
Was Shinnanoya the name of the bar?
No.
No, I'm from Mikawa.
Wait.
The bar my grandfather used to run was Shinnanoya.
I knew it.
Then, the bar that the classmate Yasu opened was near Shimidagawa.
I see.
Then, where is Kiku?
He's over there.
I see.
He's a customer.
Then, see you later, Ryo.
Kiku!
Grandpa, that's 100 years ago.
Nobody lives here anymore.
It's boring.
Nobody knows me.
Aren't you happy to meet your grandson?
Hanayama!
I found you.
Take me to heaven.
I want to drink more.
I don't want to go home yet.
Wait, my grandfather is here.
I have a request before I take my grandfather home.
What is it?
It's not your business.
It's another request.
Then, do it.
It's only 15 minutes.
Then, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Go!
Oh, Ryoma.
What's up?
Are you Ryoma Sakamoto?
Mr. Ryoma.
Who are you?
I am Tamekichi, a tsukudaniyan.
Wow, Tamekichi!
He is really a nice guy.
Teacher, it's a problem.
What's the problem for you to rush?
The real one is over there!
The real one?
How is he?
Ito Hirobumu is there. Naosuke Ii is there.
Even Perrin and Harris are there.
Takumoku Ishikawa with the sand of the evil Natsume.
Wow! YÅgai Mori is there.
After that, the woman is Akiko Yosano.
It's like she's dreaming.
It's not a dream.
Oh? Ryo-san!
What do you think? You are all treasure hunters, right?
This venue is full of guests.
No way, you're...
Yeah. There's a little acquaintance in heaven.
Heaven?
It's not a place for you two. Please wait a moment.
Don't push me!
Yasu, I miss you.
I miss you too.
Tamekichi-san!
Oh, Kikku-chan.
I'm glad you're here.
It's a gift from me.
I'm here!
Who are they?
I think they are the popular ones.
Minju-pair.
Someone's come out here.
What?
It's dangerous.
What the...?
It's alright.
Isn't it good? Isn't it good? Isn't it good?
I didn't know Japan was like this!
No, it's a big deal.
It might have been a mistake to leave the country.
No, it's the right answer!
Isn't it good? Isn't it good? Isn't it good?
We're almost there! We're going to return everyone to heaven!
Wait for me!
30 seconds is enough!
Let me say goodbye to Grandpa!
Okay, hurry up!
Thank you!
Grandpa, it's time to say goodbye!
Oh, is it time already?
Grandpa, thanks to you, I was able to offer a fun obon!
Bring back the obon next year!
I've prepared a lot of drinks!
The time is now!
Grandpa, see you!
"A reunion of Belasque and Ryo Sakamoto"
"amas who have lived in the era of The Deceased since the end of the World War 30"
"The oligarchs of the old period have gathered their hearts and minds"
"Due to the occasional festival outburst"
"A path of panic by the lawn"
What? No
Mummy!
You don't have money?
That's not what you promised!
I promised!
I'm fixing the venue and I'm working day and night!
I want to get the repair fee!
Yesterday, you said you met the real Katsu Kaishu and Sakamoto Ryoma!
You were so happy!
It can't be real!
Ugh!
That's why you're so stubborn, you're a bad student!
Damn it!
Senpai, did you have anything to do with this?
Really, Ryo-chan?
N-no, it's nothing at all!
Nothing at all, huh?
Looks like my habit has changed.
That's right.
You're back again!
What?!
I said I'd be back next year!
Yes, welcome!
Please!
Oh, you, you, you, you!
Sorry, could you do it?
Well, I've got to get my jacket wrapped up,
my salad wrapped up,
my everything wrapped up,
what should I do?
Ah, that's right.
Do you have California Maki?
Uh-huh.
There's no California Maki!
This isn't America!
I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
Um, excuse me.
Welcome.
So, Kushiage, Kakiage, Katsuage, whatever, Ageage, what was it?
My recommendation is...
Just be careful with Katsuage.
Huh? Is that a gag from your dad?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I don't get it.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Seriously?
Yes, welcome.
Please come in.
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
I know some people think our dorm is hot,
but it's a mirror building right in front of me.
Shit.
I have to do something about this heat
I will be a firefly before the end of summer
Next time, blow the fire away
Thank you
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you