Kaoru Satake
I look at the rising sun floating in the middle of the river
If I kick the stone of love, it goes flying over my feet
I wonder if I'll go and save up
I laughed at the fact that it was just a
♪ ♪
♪ Tomorrow, it'll end like this ♩
♪ If you're lucky, you'll be happy again ♩
♪ I've lost my mind ♩
♪ Because I'm such an idiot ♩
♪ Bibi's Revenge Recipe ♩
♪ The sixth floor is Chinese, hohoho ♩
♪ The fifth floor is Japanese cuisine, hohoho ♩
♪ The fourth floor is French cuisine, hohoho ♩
♪ The third floor is Italian cuisine, hohoho ♩
♪ By purchasing a large amount of all the ingredients ♩
♪ You can make a cheap, and not-so-waste dish ♩
♪ We, Tabe Daore, are a chain restaurant with a chain restaurant in Japan ♩
♪ We have everything we need ♩
♪ There's no problem with the menu ♩
♪ Of course, everything is on the menu ♩
♪ Oh, we're really grateful ♩
♪ You're really helping us, right, chief? ♩
♪ Oh, you always have lunch ♩
♪ We were in trouble before, but ♪
♪ our office is given a hefty discount! ♩
♪ Yes, I'm still missing other people, so I'm having a hard time. ♩
Ah, even in the end, not even a lack of people is a lack.
Especially, we're lacking guests.
What do you think, Ohara-kun?
Do you have something to say?
A... Okay!
When I meet you next time, I'll be sure to.
Thank you so much!
Ah, no need for that.
It's our job to help the residents.
We're all adults. We help each other when we're in trouble.
Thanks to Mr. Tamedaore, we can use our working hours efficiently.
Hard! Hard! Zex Hard!
Yahoo! I finally got it!
Ohara!
What the hell is that idiot doing?
Awesome! It's the Zex Hard!
I got it!
I finally got it!
I was so desperate that I gave up!
Wow!
Awesome!
I was so surprised. I thought I had it in the morning, but I was actually going to buy this.
Yeah, I saw it on Hachioji's
I can't help but get it.
What's that plastic model? Is it a bonus?
That's the biggest sale of Zex Hard.
It's got data chips in it, and if you connect it to the game console, it's the same as a plastic model.
Ryo, let's play a match.
Let's do it!
Okay, wait. I'll make it right away.
Awesome!
So fast!
That's enough.
Zex Hard!
Okay, I made it!
What's that all of a sudden?
Chief!
It's a good thing that you're playing with such a toy during your work.
I don't want to, Chief.
Chief! I'm just saying that I value the relationship with the citizens.
What?
Chief, what are you doing?
I don't think that's a good excuse to use.
Please stop, Chief!
Shut up! This is a good thing to do!
My seniors have a lot of business to do.
What a bad boy.
Ryo said he had to go to Hachioji by bicycle to buy it.
What?
Renko, you're so stubborn.
You idiot!
What's that?
It hurts, it hurts.
Ryo, can I borrow your Zaxxard?
I want to borrow it!
Wait, I'll do it myself!
If you really want to care about the relationship with the citizens,
then help me with the business of the restaurant next to the office!
No, Chief!
It has nothing to do with the police!
Don't worry!
I'll ask the chief to treat you to a special pay.
Did he have any pay left?
That's not true, right?
I asked Mr. Ohara about it.
The chief is so stubborn!
This is the center where you can work.
What is this?
It's like a communication command center.
This is the center where you can work.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The first floor of the fourth floor, Kameari 4th floor.
The third floor, Kameari 4th floor.
The fourth floor is very heavy.
You'll be waiting at the exit.
What is this?
It's like an eel dormitory.
The fang is in charge of Katsushika-shi.
What?
I'm going to the office?
You know best about the store, right?
Of course, but...
- But... - Please wait on seat 13.
OK.
Please take care of me.
Cheers!
This is it, eh?
It's pretty cramped.
Please accept the tale of farming from the sender.
Here it is.
Number 13 coming in.
On display.
Oh, wow! It's like a secret robot and anime place!
By Number 13, takeoff!
Let's go!
I can't stop!
Ryo!
I'm here to eat!
Yes, I'm here to eat!
Where's the ramen?
Hey, give me the ramen!
Leave it here!
Don't spill it!
I'll wait for the ramen!
Ryo!
I'm sorry for being so rude with just one ramen!
Where's the ramen?
Yes, it's mine!
I'll take it myself!
I see.
This is just right!
This is easy!
Isn't it?
Here it comes!
Ryo!
Kankichi!
What are you doing?
You guys should go eat!
Thank you very much!
Hey!
Don't come in!
What?
Come and get it!
No, I'm saying, do something yourself!
You say whatever you want!
You stupid girls!
Take that!
What are you doing?
What are you doing, you bastard?!
You're so pushy!
Stop it, it's time for the ramen!
Next, the fried rice!
The fried rice!
How's that?
Did you remember?
Here you go!
Hey, Yoko!
Remember!
I'll find you, Mr. Ohara!
Sorry to bother you!
I'm sorry to bother you!
Hello, Ryo!
Tell us your name!
I don't know!
There has to be one! Tell us!
I said I don't know!
Here you go, "Katsudon."
Thanks a lot!
This "Katsudon" will change your mind!
I can't eat this virus!
Hey, you!
Trying to mess up my food!
What the hell are you doing?
You!
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
This is bad!
Shut up!
Don't get in my way!
I'll show you what's really bad!
Saki, try it!
Hey, who said I could eat it!
I still have miso soup and takoyaki!
You're overdoing it, Ryo-san!
I can't tell which is better!
S-Save me, Mr. Kaiji!
Just stop it already, Ryo-san!
It's still in the bowl!
I'll tell you the names of the accomplices, but you have to do something about him...
You know what I mean!
You have to pay for the broken bowl!
I know, I know, Mr. Ryo!
You should be a good servant to the one who pays for it.
Cheers!
I'm done eating!
Oh, no one's here.
What should I order?
A special one-bite cutlet and five rice?
Are there any customers?
I'm getting hungry.
I'm working hard without eating lunch.
This is a natural rule.
It's delicious.
As expected of a special cutlet!
If there was one more, I wouldn't know.
I'm already full, so I'll have some more.
I ate it!
I really ate a whole cutlet.
I have no choice.
I'll reduce the amount of soup and cabbage according to the amount of cutlets.
And the rice too.
Yeah.
This is the real cutlet and rice.
It's a super-diet food.
It's just right considering your big appetite.
What a good-natured subordinate I am.
Oops, I forgot.
Oh, no!
The plate you put in such great care!
I can't help it.
I'll use the yakisoba plate to trick him.
He won't notice for a while.
What's this?
This is my death certificate.
It's hidden in such a place.
I'll dispose of it in secret.
Maybe there's something I've collected.
No, next to the book...
Oh, no! He's back!
I'm also...
It's not good to go out right now.
I'll hide it here for now.
This man is the most troublesome person in our book.
I wish he could be a clerk as it is.
Damn it!
He's so mean!
The delivery has arrived.
What? What's the lack of this amount?
It's Ryo's doing.
He's the only one who can imitate this childish thing.
Sir, the plate that was baked by Arita...
What?
The plate that was used for delivery has been replaced.
That's the one we received from the head of the district.
Oh, I can't help it that it's locked here.
Who is it?
Ryo?
Damn it!
I can't take it anymore!
Ohara!
Are you alright, Ohara?
How could you escape from that place so quickly?
Damn you, Ryo!
I knew it.
I knew this is the best place.
Is it alright for you to sell oil at such a place, Ryo?
You're so stupid to do this.
You can't do this anywhere else!
Look! I've made some barley tea for you.
Phew!
I'm so sorry.
I should have been more careful.
Oh, it's hot!
It's hot!
Ryo!
Thank you for your hard work.
You're welcome!
Oh, thank you.
Huh?
Are you sure?
What are you doing here?
What?
Nakagawa!
It's not mine.
It's not mine either.
It's mine.
So I'm the one who's collecting plates?
Ryo, you're delivering again? You look busy.
No, I'm not!
What's with you?
You're eating so much.
You should be a part of the collection.
I'm collecting only plates.
I have to take care of what I left behind.
Modern people must know what they're doing.
The importance of food!
But he's a super-yontil, right?
Wow!
Oh, what kind of kind people are they?
They're so meticulous.
They're so hardworking.
Who are you?
Who made you do this?
You made a sacred bowl in place of a dishcloth!
You?
No, Ryo.
You're a scoundrel.
It's not mine.
Who did this?
It's not mine!
You!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was just being hostile.
What a scoundrel!
Even if the Lord allows it, the Lord's sister can't do it!
Watch your mouth.
Yes...
Oh, come on, I can't do this anymore.
Since I've been fired on that catapult so many times in a day,
I've lost my mind!
Hey, Yotsu! What the hell have you done?
The whole country has been complaining about you.
Don't worry about that. I did it properly.
Don't lie to me!
Chief!
I'll take all the reports you've done.
I heard you went around everywhere, not just the office.
No, that's because the attitude of the people is too cruel.
You idiot!
You're living the most selfish life in Japan,
and you have no right to criticize people's attitudes.
I don't know what you're thinking,
but I'm going to deduct your salary for bothering this shop.
No way!
If you're paid for your work,
you don't know why you're working.
I don't know why you're working.
Then, you have to be serious about it.
Apologize, Yotsu!
No, no, no, no.
It hurts, Chief!
Well, Mr. Ohara,
you don't have to do anything.
No, if you have any problems,
please contact me.
I... I understand.
This time, I'm introducing Mr. Ohara,
and I want to get even a little help.
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Mr. Ohara is working as a cop.
You don't have to work.
I don't know why he has to work all the time.
I don't know why he doesn't work.
You don't have to work.
I will tell you what I mean.
You, you will not get any job after that.
You'll have another job.
How about that?
What does that make you?
I had a bad feeling when I was called by Senpai.
This shop is quite good.
Oh, it's a guest. Honda, go!
Manager, please come to the reception room immediately.
The head of the Kazushika branch, Ohara, is here.
What?
You're having a reception from overseas?
Yes. I know it's impossible to come to the reception room tomorrow.
But I'd like to use this place.
I see.
Oh, it's not about me.
It's a request from Mr. Ohara, not anyone else.
Let's do something about it.
Then...
Yes, leave it to me.
Thank you very much.
This is a chance to revenge!
What?
All the members of the national team are on leave?
Yes, I just got a call.
They suddenly got sick and are on leave.
Oh, what's going on?
There's a reception at the Kazushika branch today.
I found a hand-out construction in the shop building.
I'll have to take a break tomorrow.
Don't worry about it.
There's actually someone who used to work for the head of a famous hotel.
Really?
Yes.
And he once beat up the iron men in a cooking competition.
What?
I'm putting a knife in his hand right now, but he'll come to me as soon as I ask him to.
Please call him immediately.
I understand.
Leave it to me.
However, he hates to be seen cooking.
Please don't go into the kitchen, even if you're the manager.
I understand.
I swear I won't peek.
You're late, Mr. Cook.
There's no way someone like you would be here.
What?
Then what are we going to do with today's dish?
I'll cook it!
I'll make it!
No!
What are you talking about?
I can't believe it.
What?
You changed your mind!
That's why I cried.
Hahaha!
Chief, let's eat.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, you're doing it seriously.
Of course.
What is this, Ryotsu?
It's our special menu.
There are top chefs in this restaurant.
Please try the most delicious food you can eat.
Please eat before you wake up.
Then, I'll start eating.
What is this soup?
Ryo, what kind of soup is this?
The chef said that this is a special recipe
that uses French cooking techniques to make a soup
that is full of unique flavors.
Oh, that's right.
Next dish.
Oh, I love sushi.
There's chocolate inside.
It's a traditional Japanese dish.
It's a combination of sushi and yogurt.
The top is made of cocoa.
Please enjoy the taste of Japanese food.
He's eating.
Everyone ate well.
I'm sure he'll be satisfied.
I have a feeling that a top chef is cooking.
The bottom of a human is not good.
Okay, I'll prepare the next dish.
Oh, tempura.
It's a tempura with jelly, gummi, and natate cocoa.
Please enjoy the unique texture.
Please, the chief and the chief, please eat.
Actually, it's nothing.
It's a spicy steak.
It's not spicy.
It's super spicy.
Meal is crazy, isn't it.
It's a mix of sweet and bittersweet đượcal.
Oh, that's great.
I thought it was something inside.
What's that smell on the floor?
What's that?
Mr. Ohara!
Did you have a good time?
Oh, it was a unique dish.
I'm just surprised.
I'm happy to be pleased with you.
I'm so glad.
Ryo-tsu's acquaintance is a chef.
So I've never eaten it.
What?
Actually, all of my cooks are on leave for 9 seconds.
What's wrong?
Damn you, Ryo-tsu!
Dessert is a flower-flavored cake.
It's a taste that pops in your mouth.
And put a lot of cream on it.
It's a cake I made.
You can't make it smoke.
I'm so excited just imagining what's going to happen.
Is that so?
Ryo-tsu!
Chef!
It's you again!
You're not going to eat it?
I won't forgive you for today.
If this happens, I'll have to apologize to everyone.
What should I do?
What's wrong with you?
You're so ungrateful!
It's just a preemptive act!
It's a fire!
Don't panic! It's the fire extinguisher!
Yes, sir!
Ryo-tsu, get the gas back.
Hot.
Chief, look! I got it!
I thought I was going to die.
Ryotsu!
Chief, are you okay?
You bastard!
Please stop, chief!
Everyone makes mistakes!
Your existence is the mistake!
Please stop!
So this is what happened.
Chief Donra.
I'm glad I got to introduce you.
Don't ask me.
I know what you want to say.
Ryotsu!
You bastard!
Chief, please stop!
It was not on purpose!
Please help me!
The money for the letters...
...was buried in the grave.
The lights in the room disappeared.
The traitors...
I don't think anyone believes in ghosts anymore.
But I want to see the real ghost.
Next episode: The Ghosts Make A Lot Of Money
Subscribe here!
The Ghosts Make A Lot Of Money
The dream of a lady who changes with the wind
I'm sorry, I'm losing my love
The dazzling brightness of the future of the panorama
You know that, right?
I'm sorry, I'm losing
The dazzling brightness of the future of the panorama