"When watching TV, please make your room bright and try to be away from it."
Come to me, you poor fellow!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I wonder what will happen to them.
Come to me, you poor fellow!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the red clouds and the red clouds.
I wonder what will happen to them.
You know it, don't you?
I know, I know!
If you know, then just shut up and follow me!
Make money with the healing system!
Her girlfriend is a healing system, isn't she?
She's a healing system, isn't she?
Welcome!
Which flower should I choose?
I'll take the big one!
You like flowers, don't you?
I love them!
Oh, right! I found a Cosmos flower this morning.
Isn't it very cute?
It's really very cute!
It's really cute!
Every day, every day...
You just come here and buy flowers that you don't even care about.
You're going to be healed, aren't you?
Did you guys get that much hurt in the first place?
I get hurt every day!
Why do you get hurt so much?
It's because of the pressure from work and relationships.
I don't understand.
We're not as strong as Ryotsu.
You look strong at first glance, but you're actually as delicate and weak as a glass piece of art.
We're easy to get hurt.
Glass piece of art?
What's so delicate about that muscular body?
The delicate part is here.
It's the heart, senpai.
Ryo-chan, why don't you learn from Mr. Honda and buy a bouquet of flowers?
They don't care about flowers.
I don't know if it's for healing or something, but I just want to see Hana-chan's face at work.
Senpai.
Welcome home, Kei-chan.
Speaking of Hana-chan, I heard that she has a boyfriend who's a college student.
You guys were here?
I just happened to hear the manager of the flower shop talking.
I don't know.
Hana, sorry.
I'm tired. I didn't want to hear it.
What should we do, senpai?
Don't worry.
I'll be Hana-chan and heal you guys.
How?
I'm a man who's been called the healer of the turtle.
I've never heard of that.
How are you doing?
Stop it.
You're going to have a dream.
I'll heal you.
Don't hurt us anymore, Kurie.
I'm trying to comfort you guys.
There's no such thing as a feeling of comfort as a senpai.
What?
Most of our stress is not an exaggeration even if Ryo-chan is the cause.
That's an exaggeration.
You're trampling on people's feelings.
Ryo-chan.
Shut up.
Shut up?
Reiko-san.
What?
Ryo-chan's shoulder is also hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm back.
I'm late.
I have a souvenir.
What's wrong with that persimmon?
The third-year grandmother of Yoshida-san brought it to me because there were so many of them.
Oh, Sakonji-kun and the others were also here.
Hmm.
It's still hard.
This one is a Shibugaki, a servant.
I thought so.
If you thought so, say it.
Well, Ryo-san, you're going to eat it when you're going to say it.
If I make this to be a Hoshigaki, I'll be able to eat it, right?
I'll wash it.
What an old-fashioned guy.
That's funny.
Yes.
It's so relaxing to have you around.
It's like you're being healed.
Yeah, it's healing.
Well, then, we should get going.
Sorry for the trouble.
Cheer up!
What?
The crow that just cried is already laughing.
I'm glad you came back, Terai.
You're right.
Now we're done.
Whoa! You scared me!
What's wrong, Ryo-san? Do you want some tea?
No.
You're acting strange, Ryo-san.
Are you a healing person?
What is this place?
It's a healing research facility.
A healing research facility? What is that?
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
The head of the All Japan Healing Research Association, Dr. Taizo Iyashi.
40 years of research.
I'm an expert in healing research.
To survive this harsh modern society,
there must be a healing facility.
I see. I see.
I'll go and find it.
These are all pictures of those in the healing research facility.
Healing research facility?
So, you mean the healing research facility of the Terai?
From what I've seen,
it's 93 to 98% of the healing research facilities.
Is that amazing?
Or is it not?
Generally, the healing research facilities of the dolphin are 150.
And the healing research facilities of the healing talent, Inoguchi Haruko, are 98%.
They are said to be the highest in the world.
So, you mean they're pretty good?
I don't get it.
Then, let's get right into the experiment.
The healing research facility of the dolphin
Please look.
The brain waves of the experimenters are sent to this monitor.
What about this red wave?
This wave is the energy that is generated when the brain is in a nervous state.
The green wave just came out!
This wave is the alpha wave generated when the brain is in a relaxed state.
So, do you mean that student is being healed by just looking at the picture of the Terai?
Yes, absolutely.
You!
You.
You said you wanted to talk but...
Wow, another wave has risen!
Wonderful! You!
This is a far more surprising result than I expected!
Really?
If you doubt it, why don't you experience it yourself?
I'm always with the others in the office,
and now...
Stop!
Look! The alfalfa has already come out!
It's true! I feel like I'm being healed somehow!
Ryo-san, let's go home!
Look, look, look! There's so much!
I feel like I'm being healed!
Ryo-san!
I'm being healed!
The alfalfa has been confirmed to have 30 times more healing abilities than the alfalfa!
What?
That's why I'm always with the alfalfa.
Reiko and Nakagawa and I don't know any stress.
I've been living in the east, and it seems like I've finally dug out a gold vein.
The alfalfa's healing abilities
have been researched from various angles,
so let's start researching.
No, that's enough.
Wait a minute, the alfalfa!
He's calling me!
Now that you know that the alfalfa has healing abilities,
you should help him earn money as soon as possible.
The alfalfa doesn't want money,
but he wants to help people.
That's true, but...
From now on, you and I will help people
who need it the most!
The alfalfa!
What's with this outfit?
It's a simple approach, but first I'll make a photo book of the alfalfa.
My photo book?
No, that's embarrassing!
Don't be shy, alfalfa!
If you're going to heal people,
you've got to be embarrassed!
Well, let's go!
Nice.
That's nice, alfalfa!
That's really nice!
This is the healing alfalfa,
who has combined alfalfa and alfalfa.
It's a healing character, the alfalfa.
Alfalfa?
Is there really any healing effect
by making something like this?
It looks like him!
He's smiling!
If you give us your opinion as a monitor,
we'll give you a present.
So cute!
He might be healed!
If you think that the real people have been healed,
the healing will be successful!
Oh, the tea pillar is standing.
There are seven of them standing.
It seems like today will be a good day!
You're going to be healed!
Okay!
Then, please start from the head!
Yesterday, I had a dream that my house loan had been extended to 80 years.
I thought I might drown in my sleep.
If you're lost,
come to the Hashi-jo in front of Kameari Park.
Again!
It's the GD of Terra Ichi!
I'll always be there for you!
Now it's time!
If you bought the healing-type
GD,
we'll give you these cute GD-only novelty goods.
If you want to be healed,
hurry up!
Please!
Over there,
is the GD of the healing type, Terra Ichi!
It's Terra Ichi!
Huh?
There's a senior too!
Hello!
The healing effect of the GD of Terra Ichi is 10 times the effect of a lemon,
and 30 times the effect of a dolphin.
It's scientifically proven.
And you are?
I'm sorry to inform you,
but I am the manager of Terra Ichi,
and the healing advisor, Ryo-tsu.
Healing advisor?
If you want to heal,
please consult me.
Please.
I'll be in your care.
Ryo-chan,
you said that.
Are you sure you're okay?
Please do your best!
Thank you!
I'm cheering you on!
The healing expert, Terra Ichi,
will heal you,
both today and tomorrow,
with his spiritual power.
All kinds of Terra Ichi goods
are on sale!
Are you okay, Kano?
He-he-he-he...
Please take a look!
P-does he mean...
I can don't believe you!
Look at his face!
Just look at him!
Perhaps something's wrong with him...
Who...
Who?
Is in pain.
The healing expert?
Sorry to ask,
please take a look!
Thank you!
Is it alright?
I'll be in your care,
and the healing advisor, Ryo-tsu,
will heal you,
Y-Yes...
Ryo-san, if you have the power to heal people,
I want to heal as many people as possible,
but I don't want to use it as a tool to make money!
Um...
Listen, Terai.
To heal as many people as possible,
you have to sell a lot of your CDs, photo books, and stuffed animals.
It takes time and money.
If you want to save that precious time for yourself,
you have to get the reward of the funeral.
But I...
I told you that I would pay you for it!
Are you going to heal me?
No way!
Terai-kun, let me heal you right now!
Please let me know what you want to talk about.
I'll help you if I can.
I've tried a lot of things so far.
I bought all of Terai-san's healing goods.
I was healed for a while, but then again...
It's not coming yet!
What?
What do you mean?
Terai-san.
The person sitting behind you...
You haven't even brought water yet, have you?
He came into this store with us!
What?
What is it?
The beta wave is rising again!
That's it, Ryo-san.
It's a special brain wave measurement device.
So why are you carrying that on your phone?
If I have this, I can see for myself if I'm healed or not.
It's only a matter of seconds.
Okay, just tell me when.
Today's patients are unibtius.
The According to the research, it can't be healed to one person.
It doesn't mean it'll explode if you shake the meter off.
W-wait a minute!
Why did you ask me to do that?
Goomurice.
A large order of rice, please!
That's all from ourhale, いすまん.
Please get us some rice at the third seat.
Thank you!
What a big sperm!
Thank you, Mr. Mr. geni.
Here! Like this?
Kindly.
Is this enough?
Thank you very much.
It's like a dimensional bomb.
Talking to a monk is very healing.
Move a little!
That guy stopped the taxi!
It's going up again!
Wait a minute!
Taxi!
Please!
I'm glad.
I stopped the taxi.
Thank you very much.
If you keep doing that, you'll get stressed out.
Hey, what's next?
My eyebrows are connected.
Hurry up and stop the taxi!
Taxi! Taxi!
Where are you taking me?
I'm going to take you home.
If you do this, you'll be in trouble.
Listen, don't look at anything until you get home.
Don't listen to anything.
Just be normal!
Here?
What a house!
I'm going to take you home.
Please go up.
I'll put some tea in.
Not a single drop fell.
Yeah.
It's quiet.
Where is your family?
My father and I live together.
Please.
There's nothing here that threatens a peaceful life.
No.
When I was little, I was in the house.
I'm just flustered and I can't calm down.
He doesn't have the healing ability of a monk.
Even if the chopsticks fall, he's in a state of stress.
Is it Ryo's room?
It's probably a miracle room.
I just imagined it.
I'm stressed!
I'll take it out.
Yes.
I feel sorry for him.
I wonder if we can save him.
Ryo.
You said you'd give me as much money as you can, right?
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
Come on!
Come on.
Okay.
I'll make you a healing store.
And I'll offer you a ride.
Okay.
Please.
Ryo.
Yes.
I'll give you a ride.
Okay.
I'm taking it.
I-I-I-I-I-I-I-I---
This waterfall's made of Minus-ions!
Come and heal yourself!
I-I-I~ hook it up!
Hey, start to pour!
"I'm going to get you!"
"You're doing too much, Miss!"
"You can even listen to Ogawa's tesseract!"
"You'll be healed!"
"Help me!"
"Healing!"
"What's next?"
"I'm going to heal you!"
"You're healed!"
"You still can't?"
"Here's the final weapon!"
"Alright!"
"Go!"
"W-What the hell?"
"If your healing ability is 30 times that of a dolphin, you'll have to fight with a dolphin and a whale!"
"You'll have to fight with a dolphin and a whale!
"Go!"
"Hello!"
"That's healing!"
"Help me!"
"No! No!"
*Bang*
*Screaming*
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...
*Cries*
Ryo-san! Teruo-kun!
Damn it...
Where's Teruo-kun?
Eh?
*Crying*
*Panting*
What the hell was I doing?
*Crying*
It's been years since I felt like this.
It feels good.
*Crying*
Teruo!
Dr. Iyashiki! Dad!
*Crying*
Teruo!
Dad!
*Crying*
Teruo, are you okay?
Dad, it's my fault.
It's fine. If you're okay, then...
*Crying*
I didn't know you were the professor's son.
I was too obsessed with research.
My family collapsed.
My son fell into a deflector spiral.
What's that?
*Screaming*
The more I heal, the more I feel stress.
Without healing, I can't live even for a second.
I'll build a bicycle to heal even more.
*Crying*
*Splat!*
I started to do more healing to save my son.
Your son is fine.
*Splat!*
I'm sorry to have worried you.
I've healed him.
Now, let's get to the cash.
Unfortunately, I don't have any money left in my house.
You don't have any?
The assets I inherited from my parents disappeared,
including my research expenses, my wife's medical bills, and my son's tuition.
The land is also a debt deposit, and only this house is left.
Don't call it a debt deposit!
And another thing.
I found a flaw in the brain wave measurement device used in the healing ability experiment of Mr. Terai,
so all the experiment data will be an error.
What?
Everyone has been healing like that until recently.
I told you that I was going to be healed!
What are you going to do, Senpai?
I have no choice but to apologize to everyone.
I thought you didn't have any special abilities.
I hate healing!
I'm sorry, I didn't know that.
Or you further call it peppering.
Where are you going?
Please wait a moment, I just need to use the microwave.
Oh!
Ah...
What's wrong?
I was amped up.
Oh, no, thank you.
Ah...
now?
I walked through the city's black alleys
Everyone was a child once, but now they've forgotten
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt in the eyes
Look up at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle over there
There's definitely a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What's with this weird old man?
I don't know if it's Gosho-Gawara or something, but he's been picking up kids
Everyone's in trouble, right?
And why does he read a book every day?
Next time, "The Troublesome Old Man Gosho-Gawara"
See you!
There's a turtle over there
There's definitely a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!