One More Time
When watching TV, light up your room and look away.
Those who are broke should come to my place!
Come here!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen
I know! I know! I know!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
I wonder what will happen
I know! I know! I know!
If you know, come to me quietly!
Yay!
Senpai
Damn it!
I can't do anything today
But
But what are you going to do, senpai?
You spent all your salary this month in just one day, right?
Yeah, I spent my salary yesterday and I only had one day
Anyway, I'll be dead by the time this is over
If I can't do anything
Take back the treasure!
Idiot!
You don't have to be so arrogant!
I don't have to be so arrogant!
What do you mean by being arrogant?
I spent one day of my salary and I only had one day of my salary!
Hey, that means you've lost it all
You're lying!
I've used it all up with the K-Ring, the Pachinko, the Keiwa!
Wow, you've lost it all
Hey, you idiot!
You idiot!
You were so mean today
I was so mad
But, chief
I have 29 more days
What should I do?
Do you want to eat the K-Ring?
Oh, sure
You're such a coward
I wanted to say that, but
Listen, Ryotsu
I won't gamble again
If you write it in the yearbook, I'll lend you a special time
Yearbook?
Yeah
If you don't write it, you'll eat the root of the tree
I can't live with that, right?
I have to eat rice
You write it?
You don't write it?
I don't write it
I understand
I'll write it
I, Ryotsu Kankichi, will not gamble again
Is that okay?
That's not enough
After that, write this
If you break your promise and gamble
I'll give you all the profits you've earned from the gamble
All of it?
Yes, all of it
Any complaints?
I understand
Ryotsu Kankichi
Is this okay?
Yes, half of it
Okay, that's good
Then, let's start with the foreshadowing
This
What is this?
It's a 2,000 yen note
That's rare
Only 2,000 yen?
You said you wanted to eat rice
If you have 2,000 yen, you can buy it for a month
You can buy rice
You can do something with that
That's not true
Senpai, what are you going to do for a month?
It's only 2,000 yen
If this is 2 times, no, 3 times, 10 times, 100 times
That's impossible
Money doesn't increase like a clone
What?
Is there a bank here?
Well, well
Everyone who's lost their dreams in this foreshadowing
Tomoyashi Bank has released a new treasure
You have only to enter seven numbers and your dream will come true
How about that?
Tomoyashi Bank is a name with no physical strength
That's not true
Bean sprouts grow nowhere and it goes well with anything
This foreshadowing is the perfect food for the Ristora era
This bean sprout lottery is safer than any other treasure lottery
It's safer than lottery
Should I choose 7 numbers?
It's the same as lottery
But lottery is a combination of 6 numbers
If there are many numbers, there is a high probability
The first one is 400 million yen
What? 400 million yen?
Yes, the lottery is today next week
Bring the lottery ticket to the bank at 2:59:59 the next day
I won!
But Senpai, this is a gamble
The lottery is not a gamble
It's the same as buying a lottery
I guess so
You can't eat it for 2,000 yen anyway
I'll bet on Ichikabachika
That's what a man is
Should I mark this?
I'll get 2,000 yen
Thank you
First, Ichikabachika, please
1846497
Is it okay?
You've lost a lot of weight
I heard Kasumi and Kinone are the only ones who eat
What happened to the 2,000 yen borrowed from the manager?
Well
I'm going out
Are you ready?
Yes
Ryoutsu
I'm asking if you're ready
I told you yesterday
What?
Yesterday?
From when to when?
I'm so hungry I can't understand
What's that?
What about the 2,000 yen I borrowed?
Oh, that's right
By the way, where are you going from now?
I'm going to inspect the new bank's security system
Recently, the bank robbery and the Napolitans' crimes have been going on frequently
Isn't there a funny magic combination?
That's Napoleon's
80 billion yen for the pumpkin bank
20 billion for the Petit Tomato bank
Even the Goya Bank has been robbed of 5 billion yen of bonds
Even the police have to prevent the next crime
That won't work
I don't know
2,000 yen and a few billion
Oh!
Ah, get a hold of yourself Ryo-chan!
Senpai, are you alright?
You're such a miserable guy.
If you don't do something, I'll leave you in the bank's safe.
This bank is a super-rich bank that has been trading with Nakagawa Concern and Akimoto Group.
We are paying the utmost attention to the security.
Confirmed.
It is also necessary to verify the elevator that goes down to the safe room.
Except for me, only a few people can get on the elevator.
Now, please come in.
The safe room is on the 15th floor.
It is safer than the accelerator.
This is the safe room.
This is...
This is amazing.
This is the latest type of safe.
Now, I will turn off the infrared sensor.
When I touch this infrared sensor, the hypersensitivity gas immediately evaporates and the thief falls asleep.
But you can remember so many passwords.
I can almost remember the fingers.
The sensor has been turned off.
Alright, let's go.
It is big when you get close.
Furthermore, when I confirm my ID card,
I can confirm the password.
Confirmed.
When the panel opens, another sensor appears.
The right side is the sensor that checks the password and password.
Hmm.
Time is money, money is also money.
Confirmed.
It was my own choice.
And finally, I will confirm the password with the left sensor.
Hmm.
Confirmed.
It was time to confirm the password.
Now, I will open the door.
Now, now, I will open the door.
The door will open.
Please get down down.
Oh, come on!
Well, as long as I don't built it, it is impossible to get it, isn't it?
It is really ingenious.
Yes!
Oh, it is really spacious inside.
Ah, I am hungry.
My eyes flush.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
Oww.
I got something stuck in the box.
This is...
It's a bullet!
It's one hundred million yen.
One hundred million yen?
Don't put it directly on the floor!
Someone must have forgotten to take it.
Please put it next to it.
Let's go further.
There's about three hundred million yen in gold.
One hundred million yen...
If only I had this...
Ryo-san!
I know.
I knew it wasn't mine, but it suddenly got heavier.
Ryo-chan, you're...
It's not common to fall for one hundred million yen.
It's because you don't have enough attention.
Come out now.
Yes, yes.
Then I'll close it.
Yes.
You're kidding, right?
I'll close it manually.
It's locked now.
All that's left is to turn on the infrared sensor.
Then no one will hear you.
If this is the case, you must be totally relief.
If I make a mistake and drop it in the house key, it'll be really hard.
It's impossible for the real Neapolitans to do so in that warehouse.
No. First, it'll be fine.
That's amazing, sir!
This is hard!
I did it!
Don't get me wrong!
Oh, Senpai, the bean paste you gave me last time!
What?
What? It was a bean paste?
Idiot! You'll find out from the chief!
No, it wasn't a bean paste.
He said he hit the bean paste and broke his stomach.
That's right.
I thought it was a gamble if you didn't hit it.
No way!
Let's go to the hospital.
By the way, chief, the treasure chest is for gambling.
You're still saying that?
There's no way to win either a treasure chest or a soccer chest!
No way!
Did you really hit it?
Look at this.
Where?
I wrapped it with a red pencil.
Senpai said it was a one or eight.
1846497...
One...
4...
5...
1...
2...
4...
5...
3...
4...
Oh, that's right.
Listen, Honda.
This is a secret from the director.
What?
What if you get 400 million and flee overseas?
It's my business.
That's right.
Honda, I'll give you 400 million.
400 million?
That's stupid!
Instead, be quiet to the director.
Yes, I'm glad.
Let's go to the meeting room immediately.
Oh, I have to go soon.
Oh, what?
Is it here?
Senpai?
You're kidding me, right?
What?
I can't believe it.
It's not here.
Hey!
It was here before, but it's not here.
Where did you drop it?
Please remember it.
Oh, that time!
Oh, right.
That time.
What time is that?
It's in the bank's safe.
Hey!
I guess it's that time.
This time, it's the first time to drop it into such a hard-on-the-se rods safe.
What are you going to do, Senpai?
You'll end up without going out until 3 p.m. tomorrow.
I'll be in big trouble if this happens!
This program is called "Project Object X."
I would like to learn about the secret behind the success of the director Yamamoto.
Is that so?
First, take a picture of steel for anti-theft.
Let me take a photo of you
Ah, wait a minute
Here you go
Then, I'll go
Yes, thank you
Next, can you write your name and last name on this paper?
And also your name and last name
Last name?
Yes
Well, the person who succeeds is different from the hand
Oh, right, Mr. Manager
Can you read this last name to the camera?
Oh
Here you go
Time is money, money is also money
Yes, it's okay
Print this eye image
And then,
I'll make a contact lens
The last name and last name are used for the recorded image
Do you want to dub it in MD?
Yes
Time is money, money is also money
Okay, it's okay
Next is the first letter
This is the hand
I took it in with a scanner and put it in my computer
Now, I'll make a glove that looks like this
It's like a really cool movie
My hand doesn't work
The rest is the infrared sensor
You can make it through well
Easy, easy
This is the real burglar
It won't change
Shhh
Now this is the real deal.
The gloves for the
I've confirmed!
All right.
Wow, this is amazing.
Is this the safe?
This is the problem.
I didn't have time to check the complicated passwords.
You should put them on too.
All right.
I can see it clearly.
My waist.
Senpai, are you okay?
Can I come this far and play the game over?
Okay, senpai.
I'm here.
Come on, come on.
Yeah.
That's amazing.
All right.
That's where I came in.
I've confirmed.
This is next.
The time is a money.
Money is also money.
I've confirmed.
All right.
All I need to do is put on the contacts made by the director's curtain.
I've confirmed.
All right.
I'll put on the contacts made by the director's curtain.
The door is opening.
I did it!
It was a great success!
If I think about it, this place is worth more than 400 million yen.
Senpai, that's not all.
I know. I wish it was worth 400 million yen.
Why are you so late?
Speaking of spaghetti...
Napolitan!
I love Napolitan more than meat sauce or tarako!
We are the Napolitans!
Napolitans?
I'm so tired. I didn't expect to sweat so much here.
You guys must be tired of breaking this safe.
Well...
I'm sorry.
What are they doing?
No way!
Sensor disabled.
All right.
No way!
Oh, the infrared sensor is gone.
By the way, I have something to ask you.
You opened this safe, but...
If the infrared sensor doesn't work, it's impossible to take out the things in here.
So, what do you think?
This is a mountain range.
Mountain range?
Yes. It should be worth 500 billion yen.
500 million yen?
Senpai.
I know.
Or maybe it's better to make a lot of money and make a small profit?
No way! Let me talk to you.
By the way, if they turn their back on you, I'm gonna jump on them.
Y... Yes.
Here we go! The mountain range with the four of us!
That's a nice choice.
Let's open it a little more. You go ahead.
I'm sorry. I'll go ahead.
I'll go ahead.
Akiman!
It's a trap! Do it!
What?
Keikonko! That's right!
Kai Sou Napolitan!
I'll arrest you for breaking the bank!
Wait!
It's 4 billion yen!
Senpai, help me!
You!
Damn it! What are you doing? I can't run away!
Wait!
Honda, hurry up!
Damn machine!
4 billion yen!
What?
Damn it!
Are you okay, sir?
I'm okay! Don't slow down!
Alright!
Take this!
Bastard!
What?
I caught you!
Ouch!
What?
It's painful!
It's still chasing, big brother.
How persistent they are.
Well! Let's go with strategy B!
Roger!
Whoa! It's worry!
It's there, Honda! Go back!
Bastard!
You can see the car there!
I can see it!
Over there!
You!
Get him!
Look!
He's trying to escape by plane!
Damn it!
What?
Hold on tight!
Stop!
What a great year!
But this is the end!
Honda! Over there!
Honda!
Yes, sir!
400 million yen!
Sir!
What an achievement!
It was a great achievement to arrest the Taito Napolitans!
Well, well...
Ohara!
Let's have a ceremony!
Senpai, 9 o'clock is perfect!
That's good!
What time is it now?
It's 9 o'clock in the morning.
Ryotsu!
The president will hold a ceremony.
Let's go back to the office.
Eh?
But I...
Don't hesitate!
Your nose is so high!
Hahaha!
I'll handle it my way!
Useless!
Hurry up!
It's 2 o'clock.
We have less than an hour left!
Then, let the Taitoípon from Ryo-tsu Honda go to the venue.
Please say something you hate about us all!
Ahahaha!
Senpai, you have to hurry up.
Ryo-tsu!
Ah...
Ah, president.
I'm so glad, Ryo-tsu.
Congratulations, Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
I'm happy. I'm not as excited as I was today, Ryotsu.
Chief, I'm sorry. Let me go to the bathroom.
What? Ryotsu, I'm going too.
Chief, I'm the big guy.
Is that so?
I have to hurry. 4 billion yen is a lot.
I'm going to die.
All I have to do is deliver the tarimaku.
4 billion yen!
Wait!
Ouch!
I don't want to do this. I have to hurry.
I did it!
I can still make it.
Now I'm a millionaire.
I'm going to die!
I'm going to die. 4 billion yen!
Ouch!
Hey, I have to hurry.
Today's business is over.
No way!
4 billion yen is...
Damn it!
I hate the treasure!
To be continued
- Why? - Why?
Why do I feel sad?
It doesn't matter
The title of this anime is so long
This is Katsushikaku, Kameyari Koemai, the first appearance
Why do I feel sad?
It's only women's Puchipato vs. Angel Seven
What's with the outfit?
You can't tell if she's a police officer or a race queen
Angel Seven is the main character?
Damn it!
We can't lose!
Next time, Angel Seven vs. Wild Yaro Tai
Don't miss it!