"Let's Go Home"
When you watch TV, make your room bright and keep your distance.
Come to my house if you have no money.
I don't have money, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll get through this somehow.
Come to my house if you have no work.
I don't have money, but I'm worried.
Look at the red clouds that are burning.
I'll get through this somehow.
Come to my house if you have no work.
I know. I know. I know.
Yeah, I'm going to pay you.
Oh, I see.
Now?
Yes, right now.
Good.
That's...
Where are you going, Ryo?
No, no, recently my body is so tired that I thought I'd do some exercise.
You're the next-ditch, so you're looking too sweetly.
You'll get something in the end, Ryo.
That's why I said I wouldn't pay, right?
Maybe it's around the next bonus.
Can you trust me like that?
Let's go to the bank right now. Pay it right now!
No, right now...
Now!
I got it. I'll pay.
That's a horse-drawn horse.
It's a horse-drawn horse.
The 9th and 10th most popular horses I bought by chance
were a miracle 1, 2, and a win-win.
It's a super big one, a 30,000 yen horse-drawn horse.
What? 30,000 yen?
So how much did you buy it for?
10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
10,000 yen x 300 times...
30,000 yen!
That's right.
When you change this to cash,
you'll get a lot of money even if you pay it back.
Well, be careful of your boat trip.
Wait with the intention of going on a treasure boat.
Okay.
Then, change it to cash right away.
But the cash register is off today.
Um, Mr. Oomari.
Yes?
I have a little discussion.
What? Discussion?
What is it?
Well, actually...
Oh, that's bad.
Well, then, I have a mission in this ship, so I'm sorry for this.
Let's go. Let's go.
Kameyari and Narita were tricked.
Kazumi Haruyama, 25 years old.
A few days ago, I was at Kameyari Station
and lent a transportation fee to a troubled person.
So, how much did I lend?
It's 3,000 yen.
He said he would definitely pay it back, so I told him my contact information.
So?
Even if it's today, I don't have a contact,
so if I call the number I asked him...
You didn't get through.
Yes.
It's a typical fraud.
Fraud?
You're caught in such a hand.
Then, this money can go around the world.
Be strong.
Yes.
The bad thing is not Mr. Haruyama.
It's worse to abuse the good of others.
Here.
Thank you.
Actually, when I was young,
I was often deceived by others.
Is that so?
But I didn't have any money,
so I didn't lend it.
Then, the good people are combined,
so the temple can be changed.
I have to study horseback riding.
Only horseback riding.
I understand.
Actually, I'm going to Winning
where the world's violinists are gathered.
A contest in Winning?
Yes.
Hey, Ryo, did you hear?
This is the final race.
Did you say something?
I think it's on the newspaper.
Really?
Ryo, please make it a newspaper.
What are you doing?
I can't help it.
Leave the competition discussion.
Well,
I found it.
It's there.
The new violinist,
Toriumon.
The international violin competition
will be held in Winning the day after tomorrow.
The winner is expected to be
Haruyama Kazumi,
who is 25 years old.
Haruyama Kazumi?
It's the same person.
I met a famous person, Ryo.
Please give me a hand.
Well, you're famous.
I'm still a beginner.
Which one?
By the way,
the prize money for the competition is 10 million yen.
10 million yen?
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
You're talented.
Hey, it's a phone call.
Yes.
In short,
you're expected to win.
Yes.
It seems that the previous reputation is high.
Some people say that the winner is certain.
The winner is certain means...
Is it the real place of Nijumaru?
The real place of Nijumaru?
The real place?
If you are the horse of the competition,
you can bet all your fortune right now.
Yes, I understand.
Hey, Ryo.
The third time,
the old lady dropped her wallet
in the drain.
I'll go there for a while.
Yes, go ahead.
Leave 10 million yen to me.
10 million yen?
Well then,
please do your best.
Yes.
Then, I'll go.
Well,
I have to go now.
Are you going already?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
But,
I have to talk about 10 million yen.
Huh?
What?
What's up?
I don't have my wallet.
What?
Look for it more carefully.
You must have left it somewhere.
In my wallet,
I have my all assets and
the flight ticket to Wien.
What?
Lend it to me.
What's the meaning of this?
If you don't have that,
please lend me
the money
and the money
to Wien.
What?
If you win the competition,
I'll double the prize money
and,
no,
I'll pay you back three times.
But,
I can't bring it with me.
You don't have the cash,
but you have the ticket.
The ticket?
Why?
I got it.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Is your house near here?
What if you borrow money from your family?
I haven't seen my parents for years.
My father is an entrepreneur who runs a few companies,
but he was impressed by the fact that I started playing the violin.
Besides,
I was always busy practicing the violin,
so I don't have any friends,
and I have no choice but to give up.
What?
The competition.
Are you giving up?
It's the real chance of winning.
You can get 10 million yen.
Because I have to have money.
In that case,
what will happen to the prize money of 10 million yen?
That's for sure
someone else's hand.
What a thing.
It's 10 million yen.
10 million yen.
It's right there.
The winner knows it.
Where are the stupid idiots of the race?
Well,
Leave it to me.
I'll lend you theちゃうじき.
I finally found a wallet.
I'm home.
Mr. Tegai,
Welcome home.
New clearance?
Yes.
Oh,
Huh? I think I saw it somewhere...
Whoa!
You're sure it's Hariyama, right?
Yes. I'm sorry for letting you go.
It's too late to go around the
The dispatch office is too late to go around the
It's a bad habit to tell the real person.
But what does it mean that Ryotsu disappeared with Hariyama?
What does it mean that Ryotsu disappeared with Hariyama?
Did you know he was a fraud and was being arrested?
I don't think so.
Is Ryo-chan a fraud target?
No, no.
That's right.
Even if there is a debt, there is no savings.
Is there any?
This is for the shopping street.
Ryotsu is a loser, but what is that?
No, no.
I said I made a loan of 3 million yen all in this competition, so...
Ryotsu, did Ryotsu make a loan of 3 million yen in a Hearing?
Yeah, but if you're not there
Could it be that you don't dive?
Ah, hello
3 million yen?
I didn't say a word that I made a loan of 3 million yen in a tomorrow game
What's going on?
Someone explain
Doctor!
That means that Hariyama, who was looking for a turtle...
Yay! I got 10,000 yen for 3 million yen!
...was able to find a senior who had happened to have won 3 million yen at a racing race in the city.
That's not bad, is it?
Yeah.
But will that senior be fooled by the scammer?
No, no.
Um, where are you going?
To buy 10,000 yen!
What? What did you say?
You're going to buy 10,000 yen for money, right?
Wh-wh-what did you say?
I said...
I see.
I guess a high-priced turtle can only be caught at a racing track.
So you're heading to Nakayama Racing Park, right?
...
Huh?
Ah! Over there! The racing track is over there!
Don't worry! I'll take you to Narita Airport!
...
I'll take you there!
Why, why Narita?!
...
Stop it!
I don't know how long it will take to get to Narita by bicycle!
Don't make such a pathetic voice!
If you do that from now on, you won't be able to win the competition!
This is a joke to me, but I want to go to Hitchi-san, but I'll lose to you in a big way, so I'll just take 10% of the prize money.
So don't forget about that!
Why are you doing that?
Something is wrong.
If this happens, we'll change the strategy!
I'll take advantage of the opportunity and steal 10,000 yen!
All right...
Ah, it hurts! It hurts! What's wrong?
I haven't eaten anything since morning.
My stomach hurts too much.
Please!
Please let me eat something rich at the high-class restaurant!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
I don't have time! I can't wait!
I can't! I'm about to die!
Ah, you're exaggerating! You're eating a whole meal!
...
I can't do it anymore...
Hey, Haruyama! Get a hold of yourself!
...
Ah, I can't help it anymore!
Okay...
Wait a minute!
...
What?
Um...
What are you doing?
There are some grass that can be eaten in places like this.
...
Now, eat it!
There's no way you can eat that!
Hey, don't hold back!
I will hold back!
...
Please stop!
Don't say that! Try it! It's delicious!
Hey!
Please stop! It's not delicious!
...
What if you eat that and break your stomach?
Oh, I see!
If you break your stomach and can't participate in the race, the prize money for 10 million yen will be zero.
Ah, that's dangerous!
...
Did you eat it?
If you win this competition...
First of all, the prize money of 10 million yen, plus a solo concert and a commercial.
...
む
Damn it, I'm so busy trying to get that Manba sword.
Please take care of that for me.
Alright, I'll feed you.
Here, eat slowly.
Thank you.
You're giving me rice, but you only have one onigiri?
One, two, three, four.
Hey, do you know how to roll seaweed?
The one you pull out from the bottom.
Oh.
Alright, now all you have to do is pull the vinyl here and you'll get a rice ball.
I knew you were a kid.
As expected of a world-famous artist, a winner is certain.
Don't hold back.
Here, eat.
Even though I've waited for three million, how clever are you, old man?
This is what it's like to catch a fish with a shrimp.
And it's super thick.
If this happens, I'll be able to do it.
I won't wait for the opponent to give me the Manba sword.
If you wait, you'll be the sun of the sky.
Huh, that's dirty.
What?
No, it's the Y-shirt.
Where?
Then take off your shirt.
I'll wash it in the water in the convenience store.
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
I was about to wash it.
I've only worn it for about two months.
With this container, your Y-shirt will dry out quickly.
Then please.
Yes.
Oh, by the way, I'll wipe the dirt off your jacket.
Oh, sorry.
No, no.
Easy.
Well, I'm going.
Oh, what's this? A sword?
When did you...
Oh, I don't have time if you don't hurry.
Oh, yes.
Damn it.
I don't have a sword.
Here.
Yahoo!
Thanks to you, the shirt is cold and feels good, Haruyama.
That's welcome.
Oh, damn it.
I ate the grass and my nose got smaller.
How good it is!
Not at all.
You'd better be better.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Okay.
I'll try again.
Huh?
There was a hell here.
It was before.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
I didn't do anything.
Hey!
Ouch!
Are you hurt?
What a scratch.
If you wear a cane, you'll get better soon.
Right?
What are you doing?
See, you can run.
You don't seem to be injured.
Hey, is the important business tool safe?
Business tool?
Ouch!
It's okay.
I see.
You're seriously injured.
Hm...
Huh?
Ouch!
What?
I don't want to do it anymore.
Alright.
I can run now.
Let's go.
I can't do it anymore.
It's useless to go.
Let's go home.
Huh?
Wait.
Just leave me alone!
Huh?
What's wrong with you, Haruyama?
Haruyama?
I'm not Haruyama.
What?
I'm not a violinist, a pianist, or an exorcist.
So, I'm going back to Tokyo.
to Tokyo.
Haruyama.
I told you I'm not Haruyama!
I told you.
Hey, what are you doing?
What's wrong?
I give up.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it anymore.
Ouch!
You idiot!
What?
Liar!
What's wrong?
Calm down.
Take a deep breath.
Do you have a stomachache?
I'm sorry.
*sigh*
I can't do anything about it anymore.
I've become a weird old man.
Huh?
I don't care anymore.
I'm pissed off, damn it!
*cough*
Don't worry.
I'm with you.
Huh?
*cough*
Don't worry. You can do it if you try.
Take it easy.
And use the powers of the heavens to do your best, Haruyama.
*cough*
Once you've decided to do it,
throw it out.
Don't lose it!
Okay?
Got it?
Y-Yes.
Alright.
*cough*
I'll definitely,
definitely,
take the Manbaken away from him!
*pant*
Watch out!
Where's the Wingy?
*pant*
Where is he?
Eh, uh...
Over here...
No, not here.
*pant*
Don't you dare to think this is a real Wingy.
Look through the data in your own devices.
The name of the reservation is Haruyama.
*pant*
I'm not letting a Wingy go!
E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E-E
N-No way!
Haruyama-san!
Haruyama Kazumi-san, please tell us what you think about what you just said!
I'm very nervous.
Haruyama Kazumi-san, you have the confidence to win the competition.
You just have to do your best.
Haruyama?
You...
Ah, wait!
Hey, who are you?
I'm the scum of Manba Prefecture!
What?
I'm Kobuhei Hayashiya from Rakugo!
Where's Kobuhei?
He went that way.
Kobuhei, look!
There he is!
Sorry, I'll take this sword!
Ryoma-san, are you okay?
Damn it! Wait!
What?
Are you running away?
I just...
Wait!
You fool!
What?
You've been tricked by me!
Damn it!
I've been tricked a lot!
Ryo-san, are you okay?
I'll return your sword here to you.
No!
Then return it!
None sincerely honest.
Humans to know.
People are sometimes not honest, aren't they?
Hmm.
I see, I see. Ryo-san finally became a little more like a man.
I bet he's really right.
He's got a lot of tricks up his sleeve.
No way!
The Takarazuka anniversary?
The Takarazuka anniversary? That's more than 4 months ago!
The Sagi-Shi is quiet.
The Takarazuka anniversary in June?
The 60th anniversary of the anniversary?
Yeah! Then it's the Hasureba sword!
You tricked me!
I didn't!
It so happens that the Hasureba sword was in your pocket!
No, it's not that...
Well, that's just how it is...
Get all the guards at the entrance!
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
The Takarazuka anniversary has begun!
Ah! Here he is!
Li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-lii-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li-li
The Sagi-Shi is not a normal police officer!
I knew it, Ryo!
You're trying to trick the criminal.
But then again...
Things are getting weird.
He escaped!
Why would Ryo run away?
Ryo-san!
Good-bye!
You little moron!
-Sage! -It's Hariyama!
What? Shit!
Wait, you bastard!
You should pay 120 yen for buying rice balls!
Pay the money!
I'll pay the next bonus!
You bastard!
The End
as if someone was calling me
I walked while looking back
My mom was holding my hand
I felt something strange at that time
So I took the arcade tile
and put it in a black place
I walked
Everyone was a child at one time
but everyone forgot
A politician with a great face
and a blue aunt above their eyes
Look up
at that corner
You'll see everyone
Everyone
Let's go!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
11/11 is the battery day?
If you write it in kanji, it looks like + and - The
show is held on the day of the battery I
don't know what it is, but
I'll always work hard for luxury goods
Next time
The final battle
I'll look forward to it!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!