"When watching TV, make the room bright and look away!"
"Come to me, you poor guy!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried about you."
"Look at the blue sky and the white clouds."
"You'll be alright one day."
"You get it, right?"
"You get it, you get it!"
"If you get it, then come to me, quietly!"
"I'm sorry!"
"Hey, hey, what's up with you all of a sudden?"
"Oh, well, I guess my son-in-law did something wrong again."
"I'm really sorry!"
"I've been making things up all day long."
"It's not like I called you all here because you did something wrong."
"Huh?"
"Well, I know you're involved with Ryotsu-kun, but..."
"What do you mean by that?"
"Actually, Interpol is now opening a competition to decide who's the world's number one police officer."
Now, Interpol presents...
The World Policeman Championship!
"Huh?"
"It's a competition to decide who's the world's number one police officer,
by gathering the most competent police officers from 179 countries that belong to Interpol."
"So, it's like a police officer's Olympics?"
"That's right."
"That's interesting. No, I mean, it's a wonderful idea."
"From the Interpol headquarters, we've appointed a special detective,
the North Police, as a lead player of our country."
"W-What do you mean by the North Police?"
"Well, you see..."
"It's Kaipan Deka."
"Although he's not wearing his uniform,
he's been keeping his 100% authority for the past 10 years,
so of course he's the world's number one police officer."
"I see."
"In addition to Kaipan Deka, Interpol has also asked for two police officers from Japan to be recommended."
"So we used our computers to investigate 100% authority police officers,
and we were able to list two of them."
"And those two are?"
the head of the Katsushika office of police."
"Oh, is that so?"
"D-Deputy, what a strange thing to learn."
"Ah. And who are those two?"
"One of them is decided by pathetic Nakaakawa Keiichi."
"Ah, perhaps you are not his son-in - d, or your subordinate."
"Well, maybe not. That's all."
"And the other one is..."
"Huh? What, Ryoutsu?"
"Huh. He's by mistake, right?"
"Precisely.
Well, the Ryotsu Police Department was 100% responsible, just like the Kaipan Department and the Nakagawa Police Department.
Well, even if it's an incident, it's a criminal offense such as "eating and running away", "dirty and dirty", and so on.
That's why we're going to have Nakagawa and Ryotsu participate in the competition.
Please wait, Deputy.
Nakagawa, anyway, if you let Ryotsu participate, the Japanese police will be ashamed of you.
Please leave this problem to us.
We will not do anything bad.
Please.
I never dreamed that Ryotsu would have been elected as the Japanese representative for the world's No. 1 police championship.
I didn't know that the reputation of the person who wrote such a death note was 100% 100%.
The problem is how to make Ryotsu participate.
Yes.
I wonder if there's anything good for you, Ohara.
Well, that's right.
Well, how about this?
Hmm?
If you say that you will give 100% of your reputation as a reward, you will be given a week's rest during the competition period.
Oh, I see.
Ryotsu is already using up his paid vacation this year, so he should be happy to jump on it.
Yeah, let's go with that.
I'll give you a hot spring trip in the meantime.
Oh, that's good.
I'll get more and more.
SOME CURSE
I heard you, you son-of-a- sad wasp fathers.
World's No. 1 police championship, huh?
This one looks interesting.
The president and the director won't let me participate in it.
Watch it.
Nakama-kun, you know what?
The Japanese representative of the World's No. 1 police championship, huh!
That's right.
Yeah, well...
Really? Isn't that amazing, Kei?
Well, it's just that last year's review rate was good.
Nakagawa-kun, do your best and win!
Eh? But the opponent is a great police officer from all over the world.
If you win, what will you get?
Eh?
If it's such a big tournament, you'll get a lot of prize money or something, won't you?
Yes. The prize money for winning is 100 million yen.
What? 100 million yen?
And you'll get free pasta that will allow you to use the first class of airlines from all over the world.
And you'll get a gold card that allows you to eat all the free meals at three-star restaurants in the world.
Wow!
Isn't that amazing?
Well, it's not related to you, Ryo-chan.
You're the most distant police officer from the representative.
Shut up!
So, do you have any other Japanese representatives?
Special police officer?
Special police officer Kaipan Deka.
He's been a 100%
Good morning.
Chief, I heard about Nakagawa-kun.
That's amazing!
Nakagawa, I hope you'll do well.
Thank you very much.
And Ryo-chan, I have a good story for you.
Oh, for me?
Well, I didn't notice it at all, but your reputation is also 100%.
Huh? Ryo-chan?
You're just a coward and a coward.
That's unexpected.
The chief is also very surprised.
Well, he's happy.
He will give you a special prize.
Oh, is that the chief of that place?
What? Aren't you happy?
No, no.
So, what are you going to give me?
Well, don't be surprised.
It's a one-week vacation and a free hot spring experience.
Wow, I'm so happy.
How was it? Were you surprised?
Wait a minute, chief.
If your reputation is 100%,
you're also the world's number one police officer.
Don't say such nonsense.
What's the matter, chief?
Oh, nothing.
Well, I wanted to give you a special prize, so I told you to come to the office.
Come on, come on.
Well, I'm going.
Please don't be rude to the chief.
Say your thanks properly.
Yes.
Oh, come on.
"I hope you will be happy."
I want you to prove Kojiro's strength.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
Ohada, Ryozu's definitely on a vacation, right?
Yes.
I went to the station yesterday.
I screened a video of it at the station.
So I don't be worried.
Well, then.
Please wait.
What?
R-Ryo-tsu!
Senpai?!
Inspector!
R-Ryo-tsu!
What are you doing?!
I'd like to ask you something, Inspector.
W-What is it?
Hey!
You're rude to the Inspector!
Didn't you go on a trip?
I was very grateful, so I went to the gold shop to get the cash back.
W-What?!
Inspector!
I heard that the last Japanese representative was chosen as the best in last year's census.
Is that true?
That's correct.
Everyone in the press!
Actually, Ryo-tsu Kankichi was also selected as the best in last year's census.
That's right.
He was selected as the best in last year's census.
However, for some reason, I wasn't selected as the representative.
What the hell is going on?!
That's right.
Wait, Inspector Ryo-tsu.
The standard for selecting Japanese representatives is not only the authority.
You don't need to be good at shooting or fighting.
Stop!
Nakagawa.
Last year's police chief.
In the shooting competition of Kendo, what was my ranking?
Yes, you were the 2nd place with Mr. Saigo, who was the winner.
What about the national police judo championship?
Mr. Sakonji lost the court decision in the end of the competition, so he was the semi-winner.
By the way, in the kendo competition...
I was the winner.
Yes.
Thank you, Nakagawa.
Nevertheless, I wasn't selected.
Why is that, Inspector?
That's...
Because you were reported to be in danger.
I'm not in danger!
But, from Tonda-kun, it's true that...
Chief, what do you mean?
It's...
Shut up!
It's because you can't let a bad police officer who has written over 100 pages in the death certificate for a year enter the competition!
Oh! Then I will ask the executives who chose the representative,
"Did the report that you should put the number of the death certificate in the priority standard from INTERPOL end?"
There was no such report.
Even if there was no such report, you were not chosen.
Depending on the situation, I think I should go to INTERPOL.
I understand, Ryo-tsuku.
This is my mistake.
I will make you an additional entry.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Thank you very much!
Ah...
This is the worst situation.
He's so cool.
Ryo-tsu, are you going to enter the competition too?
This is getting interesting.
Let's do our best to aim for the championship.
Sure!
He's a big-mouthed guy.
Hmm...
We will win!
I'll win for sure!
Hmm.
Why do I have to go to France?
Hmm...
Shut up!
The next line will be,
"I was on a date with Nana-chan, right?"
I'm tired of listening to you every time.
What!?
You had to force me to come here?
That's terrible!
Hmm...
Huh?
According to the rules of the World No. 1 Police Championship,
it's good for the participants to have two people as their assistants.
I asked for it from Mr. Volvo and Mr. Sakonji,
but who are the other two, Mr. Honda and Mr. Senpai?
I've prepared them properly.
An extraordinary trump card.
An extraordinary trump card?
Hehe, we'll see about that when we get there.
We are in the police officer spirit and in the spirit of fighting all the way.
What is that in the coffin, Senpai?
Ah, this?
I didn't have a Boston Bag,
I didn't have a bag, so I just brought it instead.
Even so, you don't have a nurse, do you?
What do you mean you can bring? You're free, don't worry.
Before moving to Monaco, where the first event will be held,
Let's introduce the Teed players of this tournament.
First, Italian representative Ferrari Deca.
Ferrari Deca, Nakagawa. I got your box.
That's why I brought a special putter car tuned up with Porsche in the first event race.
Next, Chinese representative Ramen Deca.
Are you a ramen man?
Australian representative Crocodile Deca.
Kenya representative Savannah who loves nature.
I'm a man!
English representative Scotch Deca.
American representative Manhattan Deca.
Russian representative Cossack Deca.
You surprised me, you guys.
Last, Japanese representative Kaipan Deca.
Hey, hey, hey.
There's no one here.
Who's that guy?
He's going to the opening ceremony.
He's late for the opening ceremony.
When a hate incident occurs, not just a small problem,
Kaipan Deca solves everything in one go.
One of the Japanese police chiefs, Special Prosecutor Samba-Galas,
Kaipan Deca is now born.
You're a demon!
The first event of the world's number one police championship is
a race to compete in driving technique with a putter car and a white horse
using the course of the F1 Monaco Grand Prix.
In today's race commentary, we have the Japanese police chief, Katsushika Shoyori,
and the chief of police, Oohara Junsa.
Please come in.
The pole position is this event's champion, Italian Ferrari Deca.
And the second grid is the Japanese police chief, Nakagawa Nakagawa,
who is driving the special Porsche putter car.
When chasing the criminal, he is expected to face many unexpected obstacles.
This race is a race that requires the police to make a quick decision
and to avoid the obstacles prepared on the course and to reach the goal as soon as possible.
It is a race that requires the police to make quick decisions and to have the appropriate driving skills.
Savanna Deca loves nature, and she will dare to participate in the race with a putter.
Oh, Ryotsu Ryoichi.
He has just been in the old type of putter car.
The Ryotsu Ryoichi is completely unsatisfied with the preparation.
That old type of car is not very profitable.
Moreover, the car is not a putter car but a taxi.
The top 16 people will enter the next event.
It is a survival race.
The 32 drivers will start at once.
Ferrari Deca and Nakagawa will do a fast dash.
He's going to crush the tower!
Oh no! What's going on?
The winner, Kaipan Dekka, is being pulled out one by one!
Huh? Kaipan, why aren't you speeding up?
First, let's see what everyone has done.
That's...
Oh no! It's an accident all of a sudden!
The number one candidate for this event, Ferrari Dekka, is crashing!
He's putting oil on the course!
If he wants to escape, he shouldn't be doing that!
Well, I don't think there's anything he can't do.
Phew, that was close.
Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
Amazing!
Hehehe! Even if this happens, the remodeling is perfect!
It's a snap!
Oh, Senpai!
Nakagawa, first!
Hehehe! Everyone, first!
This is the power of the fish.
As expected of you, Senpai! I didn't know you were doing that kind of remodeling in such a short period of time!
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Now, the players who have cleared the first obstacle are gradually increasing their speed.
The course is up the hill from here.
Oh, no!
Suddenly, a huge iron ball appears!
ARA Gigantic Thunderclap вод
I've made them run away!
If you're a policeman, you should avoid the iron ball attack of the culprit.
If you're an escaped criminal, you should use this iron ball.
Way to go, Dekka!
And he managed to counter the
Hey, you're not even a dog!
You're just a little kid!
Oh, you did it!
You did it!
Oh, how's that?
Ryotsu, if you've been doing such a great job,
I'm going to give you this!
I see, so that's how it was done.
Kaipan Deka has cleared the iron ball with his skillful driving!
Nakagawa and Manhattan Deka will also clear the iron ball in the same way.
And the other players will also clear the iron ball in the same way.
I see.
So when the criminal attacks with the iron ball,
they have to use this technique to avoid it, right?
Y-Yeah.
That's right.
Now, Savanna Deka has cleared the top-of-the-line tunnel!
He cleared the hairpin!
Alright, now all that's left is the last corner!
Hey, Nakagawa! Don't get too cocky!
You'll still be injured!
Nakagawa, you're so young.
Oh, no! The last obstacle is the road that's going to be hit by the waves!
That's impossible!
How am I supposed to run on this course?
Huh?
H-How amazing!
Hey, look! Just as I thought!
Look at this!
Click!
Nakagawa, you're the best!
How's that? Did you see that?
How's that?
This only seems like a breakthrough.
All right!
There!
Big Kaipan!
H-How amazing! Big Kaipan!
All right! Me too!
The guy who's been playing is really good!
Japan's representative Kaipan Dekka is now at the top!
The 2nd one is Kenya's representative Savannah Dekka!
Next up is Japan's representative Ryotsu Nakakawa!
They're in the goal one after another!
As expected, SEED's goal is almost a goal, but...
Huh?
Japan's representative Manhattan Dekka is standing in front of the course!
H-How forceful!
Manhattan Dekka!
Let's see if it's SEED's will!
He's in the goal with a pretty rough technique!
In the end, only 12 people made it to the goal!
He's telling us how tough this race was!
The match is just beginning!
I'm going to get 100 million yen for sure!
Kaipan Dekka gets 100 points!
Now for the world's number one police championship!
The second match is here, at the Naska Park in South America.
The 12 people who won the first match are going to be fighting.
First up is the champion of the first match, Kaipan Dekka!
With 100 points for the first round!
Next up is Japan's representative Ryotsu Nakakawa!
"Kaipan Dekka"
Ready?
Ryotsu Nakakawa! 95 points!
Ah, I missed a little.
Ryotsu Nakakawa wins!
He finished with 95 points!
Hey! What are you doing?
Oh, Manhattan Dekka!
He's out of Ryotsu Nakakawa's way!
Huh? What's with that gun?
It's the latest type of laser gun that the FBI has jointly developed with NASA!
There's no way you can win!
All you have to do is look through the target through the goggles, and the computer will process everything and automatically fire the laser!
What?!
Oh!
That's amazing!
Now, start it up!
Wait a minute!
What?
Isn't this kind of computer-involved gun a crime?
If it's a self-made gun, then it's a rule that doesn't matter. It's not a crime!
Don't you have any pride as a policeman?
Then, you're not the one using the gun, but the gun is the one using you!
Ryotsu is right about that.
Yeah. This competition is about the skill of the gun, not the performance of the gun.
As long as there's no violation of the rules, there's no problem!
I'm going to continue the competition!
Get out of my way!
Ow!
Now, start it up!
Damn it. Now that it's like this...
Um, I was making a mistake.
Ah, excuse me for a moment.
Yes, hello?
What's the matter?
I called the Manhattan department.
What?
The Manhattan department! The Manhattan department!
Hm?
There's a phone in the room where we're recording.
What's with this time?
Excuse me.
Please.
Ah, I'm the Manhattan department of the New York District Court.
What?
Three ramen and three dumplings?
I'm not a Chinese restaurant!
It's a wrong number.
I see.
Hmm.
Did you do something?
I didn't do anything.
Now, start!
What?
The data is falling apart!
Let's get out of here!
Oh my goodness!
What kind of accident is this in Manhattan?
He suddenly left!
He's retired!
I knew it. You did something.
No, I didn't do anything.
Even I want to get rid of him as soon as possible.
I'll cover my eyes.
That's why I said you didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything.
Actually, at that time...
Mr. Manhattan! Mr. Manhattan!
What's this at a time like this?
I thought this might happen, so I made it into an electric cube.
This computer virus generation device.
Um, please give me three ramen and three dumplings.
What a big helping hand.
Noooooooo!
Take this!
Nakagawa's assistant, Borubo Saigo's brilliant shooting skills canシルク!
*Push, push*
*Rее*
Crocodile Deka 98 points
Cossack Deka 96 points
Ramen Deka 97 points
Scotch Deka 99 points
After the second match, the third match has 8 top players
Kaipan Deka, Nakagawa
Savannah Deka, Scotch Deka
Crocodile Deka, Ramen Deka
Cossack Deka, Ryotsu Deka
In any case, the winning candidate, Mahattan Deka, suddenly retired
I wonder what caused it
Chobari
Nakagawa and his assistant Sakonji used the third match to break through the competition
Crocodile Deka has a wonderful backdrop
He broke through the Savannah Deka with a backdrop
Ryotsu is good at Kendo and attacks fiercely
Ramen Deka is on the defensive
3 minutes have passed
Hey, wait a minute
You did it, Arun
What is it?
Here it comes
Arn
What?
I'm not going to lose my energy if I eat ramen
Arn
Kono
the semi-finals!
If you really put in the effort, you'll become superhuman!
Now, the final match is between Japan's Kaipan Deka and
England's Scotch Deka!
Who will remain in the semi-finals?!
Here I go!
Golden Claw!
It's decided in an instant!
Kaipan Deka wins!
Oh, that again?
That again?
Oh, crazy!
Now, the world's number one police championship!
The semi-finals are held in the South Pole,
in a five-hour-long penguin-spawn race!
The rules are simple!
If the penguin robot that runs away succeeds in a five-hour-long spawning race,
it can advance to the final round!
What? That's easy!
A-Action!
However!
The penguin robot will be close to everyone within a radius of 30 meters,
and when it comes closer, the penguin automatically turns around!
The penguin will fail if it is recognized by the penguin!
I, as its assistant, will accompany the Kangaroo Deka!
Golgol!
I'll go with Honda, too!
S-S-S-S-Cold!
On the second and third matches, Nakagawa has used every of his secret members.
I understand. I'll do this alone.
Kaipan Deka, what will you do with the secret members?
I may call them later, but I'll leave them alone for now.
All right, the 5-hour endurance penguin beauty race starts!
Run away!
Run!
The players will follow the respective Penguin robots.
The cold is more severe than I expected.
My body is freezing.
Action!
The next day.
Nakagawa has failed.
Oh no!
Nakagawa has retired in a hurry!
Nakagawa was the only one who was a good son of the Japanese police.
We won't let you escape!
I'll show you the strength of the Australian
fishing duo!
Go, Kangaroo Deco!
Kangaroo!
I'll finish you off!
Now, I'll show you what I can do!
Let's chase the Penguin!
Kangaroo!
Crocodile Deco!
You're disqualified for losing sight of the Penguin!
Damn it!
That red penguin!
What a speed!
If you let him go any further, he'll lose sight of you!
Honda!
Change your plan!
What?
Oh, no!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
You can't do that.
I've prepared a good one for you!
Here you go!
Hey, Honda!
Hey, dog!
Don't run around like that!
If you lose sight of the Penguin, you'll be in trouble!
Now, we can enter the final without a doubt!
Oh, no!
You are dead!
Really?
Ah-ha-ha!
Yes, it is!
We did it!
We made it!
We found it!
So manyć more to go!
Ah, I'm playing sperms.
The mark doesn't make it!
Huh?
There!
You saved me, Dolphindecca.
Now that I'm here, it's all good.
Now, the 5-hour endurance penguin light race is finally over!
Only 5 seconds left until the end!
3, 2, 1!
Goal!
Yay! We did it!
Ryotsu from Japan has successfully advanced to the final round!
Ah, I'm left behind again.
In addition, according to the information we received just now,
the Japanese seed, Kaipan Deka, borrowed the help of his assistant, Dolphindecca,
and successfully completed the goal!
What?!
That means the final round is...
R-Ryotsu and Kaipan Deka...
Right...
These two are the top-ranked teams
of the super-awful Japanese gang
and were trapped in the city 3 days ago!
The final round of the World's No.1 Police Championship...
The final round is decided by...
...these two super-awful gang members,
who will be arrested within 12 hours from now!
I see, looks interesting.
I don't mind helping, but...
Why would we have to dress like this?
If we talk about the final round of this event,
maybe there are also taxis on the roof of a skyscraper!
Maybe there are taxis on the roof of a skyscraper!
It's like an Ultra Quiz.
By the way, if we can arrest those two, we'll get 100 million yen in prize money, right?
Of course! Please look behind you!
Hm?
Oh, wow! 100 million yen in cash!
I get it.
You're really into prize money.
What are you going to use 100 million yen for?
I'm going to buy the same model as the one I'm wearing for the rest of my life.
Buy it yourself.
Do whatever you want.
Are you two ready?
Hm? Wait a minute.
The only clue to the culprit is that face.
Huh? Is that so?
What? That's all you need.
Hahaha!
If you can't get it, you can get off.
What did you say?
Hmm...
It seems like it's time to give out the last trump card.
Here you go.
The last trump card?
Ryochi,
what are you going to give out?
Now, it's your turn!
Oh!
Mr. Sunflowers!
Hey, Sunflowers! Get up!
Get up!
L-Let me sleep a little longer.
Huh? Get up!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Hm?
Huh?
R-Ryochi, I feel like I'm not sleeping enough.
How old are you?
I'm in the year of the Olympic Games, so it's definitely 2004.
I'm just doing the women's marathon right now.
Shinoko, the Japanese woman, came to the main stadium as the top.
Please listen to this statement.
Until the gold medal in two consecutive competitions, the end is after.
I heard this voice somewhere.
Do your best!
Huh? That's a misunderstanding.
You're just awake and you're just standing there.
But more importantly, you should get to work.
Huh?
Mr. Ryochi, he's another help.
Are you a assistant?
That's right!
Huh?
Where are they now?
Use your supernatural powers to tell me.
I want to drink hot coffee.
What?
You only work once every four years, but you're going to work for a lot of money.
But when my head is empty, nothing comes to mind.
Oh, my God.
Huh?
Look!
A beautiful bunny girl is looking forward to your supernatural powers.
Huh?
I see that you are very motivated.
What?
That's right, I like to do it.
If you take a little train, you can be advisable, and if you have time, you can choose to run with it.
Huh?
Oh, I have something.
I'm sure that I can help you.
Let's go.
Look.
But this is not the bell that you used.
Super special sign.
If you get caught up in big trouble, it's going to work.
That's why I want to apologize.
No!
Let's go home.
Let me go!
What are they doing?
There's something on the roof over there.
What?
On the roof over there,
there's a World No.1 Gang Championship.
What?
A lot of bad guys are gathering.
And the prize money is double the amount of this.
So, the gang members were doing the same thing.
So, the culprit is in there.
Okay, we should be quick then.
Yeah.
Wait.
The culprit is closer.
What?
Hey, help me.
Hey, chief.
What are you doing here?
And you're naked.
I came here to check.
I thought you were hit in the head by someone and fainted.
Then, who is the chief here?
Don't move!
Chief!
When did you...
Who are you?
You're a criminal!
Did you switch with the chief?
I didn't realize it until now.
Hey, Bunny Girl.
Bring me the 1 billion dollar Duralumin case.
Yes, sir.
Hurry up!
Wait!
Chief!
You're another criminal!
This final battle is about taking your prize money.
I'll take this 1 billion dollar!
Damn it!
If we lose the prize money, there's no point in fighting.
I'll take it back.
Let's make it a big deal.
Let's help each other and take the prize money back.
Sounds good.
Hey, I'll use my second assistant.
Yes, sir.
Here you are.
I'll ask the principal to support me.
What?
I'm a little bit worried.
I'm muitos worried.
Do you have any ideas?
What?
Well, the old
man's going to
You can't do it. You do it!
If I'm the assistant of the assistant, there's no point in being the assistant.
If you're not going to do it, I'll go home!
I got it! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Not just a beautiful transformation!
Put the energy of the moon on your back!
The stick of justice, the darkness of the sky!
If it's that kind of time, leave it to me!
Master of the Moonlight, Gekkon Deka, has arrived!
Me too, Venus Deka!
If it's like this, I'll burn you!
W-What's with them?
Z-Za...
Leave the machine guns to me!
Take this, you gangsters!
I don't need that kind of machine gun!
H-Hey!
Don't be so funny!
I'll just follow...
Z-Za!
Z-Za...
I don't need to kill anything!
Listen!
When the sun sets,
you'll be with us.
Let's go home, all of us!
What the hell is going on?
Don't!
It's dangerous!
Hey, hey, hey! Remember what we did earlier!
Alright, Ryotsu! Let's transform!
What? At a time like this?
Make up! Moonlight Power!
Let me explain myself here!
By transforming to Ocho-Ogujin, the Moonlight Deity,
you can throw an incredible Vanguard Serve!
Ball, you say?!
Let's go, Hiromi!
Are you Hiromi?!
Oh! We're going down to Shinjuku Fishing Park!
Hosted by Mano Ocho-Og迷
Whoa! It crashed down!
It's the Egg Fishing Istagram!
Senpai!
R-Ryotsu...
Senpai?!
I'm glad you're all right.
I did it!
How was that?
Two people were arrested and
they took back 100 million yen!
Senpai...
The winner is the Japanese representative,
Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
I did it!
Congratulations!
Senpai, congratulations!
Ryo-tsu!
I can't believe he's still alive.
It's a great achievement.
I'm the loser.
Now, let's go to the Special Investigation Department.
All right, I'll do it even if it's for three years.
That's a good idea.
So, I will award this.
On April 6, 2003,
the Interpol Director General.
2003?
Huh?
Oh!
Oh, Higurashi!
You're not even old enough to go to the Olympics,
but you're still making me wait.
W-W-Wait! Calm down, Higurashi!
I won't do it again!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Not yet!
Is this the place?
Superb!
It's a place...
Where are they?
It's rain...
Well, let's get changed.
What is it?
I heard it's raining here~
Ah, it's just cold.
It's a big deal.
Ryotsu, you can't make a profit with 100 million yen.
Am I making a profit?
Of course.
No way.
I'm getting sleepy. Good night.
What?
I can't make a profit with 100 million yen.
I like historical fiction.
Why?
The butterfly's wings are so small.
When riding a motorcycle,
I change my personality.
Why?
I've only slept in the sun for four years.
Nakagawa loves both.
Why?
♪ I don't lend money to Reiko-san, but ♪
♪ I can easily lend my tank or machine to her ♪
♪ Why is that? ♪
♪ Reiko-san is a very rich person, but ♪
♪ Why does she work at the sewage? ♪
♪ Why is that? ♪