Translated by 方 Hou.
I look at the sun that floats in the river
If I kick a love stone, it'll fly to my shoes
I wonder if I'll go to the taiku school
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are only patsushika and Kameari
Even if I have a bad breath, it doesn't change
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the waterway of Tongari-boshi
I go to Kaishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow, it's already over
I lost my happiness again
Because of the patsushika and Kameari
I realized
I'm an idiot
I'm a fool
That's why
I'm not an idiot
I'm an idiot
The
No, it doesn't work.
Did you say what?
What?
Didn't you say what?
Don't do it again, are you a snake?
That's why accidents don't happen!
I couldn't feel the accelerator because of my body.
Whether it's a new car, an old car, a dump car, or an F1 car,
speed over is speed over.
Then...
Is a bicycle okay?
What?
B-B-B-B-Boom!
Uwaan!
You got it!
Ryochi Kan-kichi!
Oh, yes.
I've got to go to the bus station.
Why do you need to go to my place?
Shin-shin!
I want to go to your place.
I don't want to go either.
I was ordered by our director Ohara to be...
following the traffic safety rules.
Barber safety-
So, the transportation department...
How do I read it?
Ishiatama Tetsui?
Ishizu Tetsuo!
Yes, Ishizu!
He has to take private instruction.
What kind of...
What's wrong?
I just want to ask about the director.
You're going to ask about the director?
Yes.
You were at the director's...
He was a nasty guy like a cockroach.
Poor thing.
What's with that reaction?
I don't know.
I might never see him again.
Goodbye.
Hey, wait!
I don't get it.
What's going on?
What kind of old man is he?
No way.
He is going to the director?
So what's with that reaction?
I, Maria...
I'm never going to forget about you.
Hey!
Goodbye!
What's going on?
The next morning
I came to see you, Director Ishizu.
What can I do for you, Director Ishizu?
I'm here to get a traffic safety instruction.
A traffic safety instruction?
Where am I? Who am I?
Again?
Hey, what kind of person is Director Ishizu?
What kind of person is he?
Tell me what kind of person he is!
Is he that scary?
Sorry, can you pass me there?
I'm trying to get in.
Director Ishizu...
What?
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What? You look like a nice old man.
Come here.
Director Ishizu?
Yes, Director Ishizu.
I came to see Detective Ryotsu
at the acid mine outside Kamiwari-koen.
Oh, well.
It's really a difficult job.
You're going to the arcade, too?
I'm a very passionate racer.
I'm glad I'm starting to understand you.
Let's carry out this aritincality
together in the arcade.
Let's get a traffic safety teaching!
I thought I'd do it on purpose.
Traffic safety instruction?
I'll get it ready.
Are you going to change?
For the market?
What's going on?
What's that?
The time has come.
Human beings are facing a crisis of extinction.
In the battle of the traffic war...
But!
A savior has appeared!
What?
What are you?
35 years of running traffic.
Traffic safety instruction master class 7.
Ishizu Tetsuo Kenzan!
Is he the chief of Ishizu?
Yes.
He's like a different person.
You just said something that was not related to traffic safety instruction.
I was just talking.
You're the police officer who leads the citizens.
I won't forgive you!
Yankip's Yankip!
This is annoying!
I'll let you go!
Driver, stop the car!
Let go of me!
Don't let go of me suddenly!
I'll give you a lot of traffic safety instruction.
Be prepared!
Why do I have to dress like this?
That's the uniform of traffic safety instructor class 7.
Traffic safety instructor class 7?
What's that?
I decided to spread the correct traffic safety to the whole country.
By the way, the armor is allowed to the first class.
The traffic light and the siren can only be allowed to those who are allowed to the first class.
The siren is a sign of the first class.
Shut up! I can't hear anything!
You're a beginner, so first class 7!
Every time you master the traffic law, you are promoted to class 6 and 5.
No one has ever been promoted to class 6.
Ishizu-style traffic safety instruction.
First, the way to cross the pedestrian crossing.
Do it.
There's no car on the pedestrian crossing.
You just have to cross it quickly.
No!
What?
What are you doing?
I should have learned this in elementary school.
When you cross the pedestrian crossing,
look right, look left, look right again, raise your hand and cross.
Do it again!
I got it.
Look right, look left, look right again, raise your hand and cross.
Look left, look right again, raise your hand and cross.
This is fine, right?
You're so naive!
I did it as you told me to do!
Do you think you're really prepared for safety?
And when there's a flag, put it out properly!
Where's the flag?
Huh?
It was a flag, wasn't it?
You have to be prepared to check whether you're really safe or not.
I'll show you a sample.
Look closely!
How to cross the right pedestrian crossing.
Confirm the signal.
All green, clear.
Confirm right.
No driver.
Confirm left.
Confirm safety.
All clear.
Left hand!
No german flag.
The angle of the right hand is 75 degrees.
It is a good angle for the driver in the back.
The light is painted with fluorescent paint on the iron frame, so it looks bright at night.
It's been 35 years since the car was called a "driving car".
This is the way to cross the right crosswalk in the first grade!
I can't believe I'm doing this much just to cross the crosswalk.
You are not serious enough.
It seems better to actually go out into the city and teach.
This is my favorite car!
What is this?
A large back mirror that can better confirm your safety.
A special winch that is designed so that the opponent does not look down on you.
A support ring to prevent headlamps.
There are also various other ways to prevent headlamps.
This is the 98 version.
The final version of the safety measures.
It is the Ishi-Zu-ryu Hyper Shirobai.
It's a ugly bike for its name.
Idiot!
It is safer than you think.
Looking at the history of the 20th century, there are too many accidents that were caused by the safety of the driver.
It's a period of traffic accidents.
Yeah.
The 21st century is a period of traffic safety.
As the first step, I spent my money to modify this bike.
Of course, I tried to modify other bikes, but why do you all hate it?
I'm a policeman, but I'm too low on traffic safety.
This Shirobai is too heavy and dangerous.
Do you have a license for a single-seater?
I have it for the time being.
I'll tell you how to ride a single-seater like Ishi-Zu.
Try it.
Yes, yes.
How is it?
Idiot!
If you ride a single-seater, you can put on a seat belt right away.
I've never heard of a bike with a seat belt.
It's on my single-seater.
What?
It's true.
Is this all right?
That's not all about seat belts.
What?
There are double seat belts?
As expected of a bike in the 7th generation of the road safety and driving market.
That's not all.
Is there more?
There's more here.
More here.
This is the ultimate safety.
It's a 36-point seat belt.
This can withstand shocks from all directions.
But I can't move at all.
So, next, try to hold the steering wheel.
I'll show you how I actually drive.
How is it?
Wrong!
Ouch!
What do you mean, wrong?
Listen.
First, your back is 90 degrees.
Your neck is 78 degrees.
Your arms are 65 degrees.
Your feet are 115 degrees.
Your knees are 62 degrees.
This is the correct way of riding a tank.
I'm going crazy thinking that it's a human body.
What?
This speedometer is only up to 60 km/h.
Of course.
The maximum speed of the Japanese roads is 60 km/h.
You don't need any more than that.
That's for the public roads, right?
What about the highway?
The highway?
It's made to protect the speed you set,
and to protect your life.
It's made to be able to speed up on purpose.
What is the government thinking?
There's such a thing, so it's not going to reduce the number of accidents.
I'm going to ride with you.
I'm not going to use the highway.
You're a very aggressive person.
Now, let's get out of town.
Where's my bike?
You idiot!
In Ishizu-style traffic safety guidance,
you can ride a single car from the third floor.
Then what should I do?
People in the seventh grade should run.
What?
Wait, Chief Ihitsu, what?
Hurry up and follow me.
It's dangerous, so let me go.
This is not a joke.
No!
It's annoying.
What? Did you wait for me?
In front of the seven-stage Ishizu-style traffic safety guidance,
You are now forgiven.
There are some discriminatory tickets here.
People wearing red tickets.
You do what I do!
It's a traffic light bug.
Yeah, but in myule, when I passed, I was blue.
You look like , don't you?
Why didn't you see with a rear view mirror?
I passed before I turned red!
You fool, don't you know what i mean?
Hmm, you'll turn red soon, won't you?
No, it's not!
Come on!
First, when you are already in the
crossroads,
if the signal goes off,
you must cross it quickly!
Oh, dear...
Isn't the armor too heavy?
This is something
that will protect me.
I can't let go of it.
Do it yourself.
Let me go.
And before you enter the crossroads,
you must stop.
Shut up!
Chief Ishizu!
Damn it!
There are people like you,
so the traffic laws in Japan
are going to be messed up!
Please stop! It's red!
Are you okay?
Oh, thanks to the armor,
I'm not hurt at all!
This is Ishizu-ryu!
You wouldn't have fallen
without the armor, would you?
This time,
I'll cross the crossroads.
Try it!
It's basically the same as the crossroads.
Give me your binoculars!
No, you can't!
You can use your binoculars
from level 1!
I'll check it with my naked eye.
It's pretty detailed.
Right!
Left!
Right again!
I'll cross it!
Wait!
Ouch!
I'm sure you've checked it!
In the case of a crossroads,
you need more procedure.
The train is much faster
than a car.
It comes in no time.
Huh?
I'll listen to the train
and check.
This is the Ishizu-ryu
crossroads!
Do we really need to go that far?
Huh?
Hey! Get out of the way!
I'm in the middle of
a traffic safety operation!
Wait for me!
We're in a hurry!
What?
Drivers like you
mess up the traffic laws!
If you're in a hurry,
you'll be a driver!
You're a driver,
you're in a hurry!
Did you get it?
What?
How can a modern man
be in a hurry?
The Ishizu-ryu
traffic safety guidance
is available to everyone!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Thanks to your armor,
I was saved.
I guess I didn't notice
the warning because of the armor.
Hey!
You're in a hurry!
Drive safely!
You are a good driver!
What?
What did you say?
I was in a hurry!
Hey!
You're a good driver!
I was in a hurry!
You're in a hurry!
What's wrong?
I'm in a hurry!
Don't give up!
You're in a hurry!
What?
I don't think that's the time to be talking about that.
I'll protect the traffic law at any time.
This is the Ishizu style.
Uwaa, Matsuri!
I told you to wait!
You lost sight of me, didn't you?
Don't worry.
I'm using radar.
Huh? Radar?
I'm detecting the weak radiation of the self-made paint of this armor when I jump.
You're a lot of junk.
But you're using all the high-tech methods wrong.
Huh?
Ah, it's moving away!
Please speed up!
This road is 30 km/h.
I'm making sirens ring.
This is a good time.
Whatever you say, the speed limit is reduced.
That's the Ishizu style.
Don't talk.
What are you doing?
Speed up!
Stop!
Uwaa!
Idiot! Stop! Stop!
I won't stop!
Stop! Stop!
Uwaa!
What's going on?
I've never seen such a good track record.
Uwaa!
Stop!
Ahhhh!
Damn, damn!
Ah!
Light, light!
This guy's got a bad sense of direction!
It's close, it's close!
There!
Stop that car!
Oh, no! It's a white rider!
Ah!
Don't worry!
Don't worry about it!
Fire the smoke bomb!
I can't see anything!
I can see everything!
Ishizuri's Car-Stopping Jutsu!
Ouch!
Fire the smoke bomb!
Who are you?
Did you see that?
This is Ishizuri's Car-Stopping Jutsu!
Gah!
Hm? What's wrong?
What have I done so far?
What?
You did it again...
You still don't remember?
When I exceed the speed limit, I can't stop the car-stopping jutsu because I hate car-stopping.
You're the cause of the accident.
This is because...
...everything...
...is caused by the traffic law!
What?
This traffic safety instructor, Tetsuo Ishizu...
...will definitely...
...make Ishizuri's traffic safety a priority for the entire nation!
So that I won't be able to run wild!
Ah, this is amazing!
Ryo-chan, it looks like you had a hard day yesterday.
Well, the traffic safety instructor is already tired.
Sorry!
Chief Ishizu!
Huh?
What about this guy?
What's the matter, Chief Ishizu?
The traffic safety instructor is already done, right?
Good job on your work yesterday.
So I decided to make you...
...the one who will make Ishizuri's traffic safety instructor...
...from level 7 to level 6.
Ryo-chan, you're amazing!
I'm glad to hear that, Senpai.
No, I'm fine...
What?!
Don't hold back!
Ah, I get it!
From level 6, you can drive a tricycle.
Then follow me!
I'm a patrol!
This is better than running!
Hey, wait!
Don't go first!
Damn it!
I didn't want to rush!
Popopo!
It's not the time to sing "Hatopopo!"
Why can't I become a special detective...
...or a "Hatopopo" detective?!
...or a "Hatopopo" detective?
I'm a special detective!
Please do something without me...
...and steal my rifle!
Head-sign: I'm a special detective!
Head-sign: You've just killed the police!
Head-sign: You're just a little pirate...
...and you stole our boat!
Head-sign: You were a special detective!
Head-sign: You can't go that way!
Head-sign: Now do a good job!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Beep!
I'm so excited!
Bingo!
Booyah!
I'm so excited!
Beep! Beep!
Bingo!
I'm so excited!
Can you introduce your stuff?
Bingo!
A drawing of the
characters that you called in the last episode!
It's a sketch of me finished my diesease
A sketch of me finished my dessease
And a drawing of your beauty!
And an announcement to the viewers!
Can I have a picture?
This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to real people, living or dead, is coincidental and unintentional.