Dette! When you watch the TV
move your room a little bit
and try to make it separate
epidemiology
you'll be watching
The cityscape that never changes is so kind
From the waterfront of Tongari-boshi
To Taishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
If I win this time, will I still be happy?
I realize it's because I'm stupid
Another
Oh, that's unbelievable, with those hair spoons.
This is good, isn't it?
I'm impressed with you guys!
No...
I'm sorry, one more time!
Here's 100 yen.
You also won in the goldfish rescue with me.
It's ten years too early to compete with me.
The golden fish is saved carefully and bravely.
Well, I've done this 10 or 20 times, so this secret is...
Kei, you're amazing!
What?
If you get the hang of it, you can save as many as you want.
Kei, you have a good sense.
Mr. Nakagawa, bravo!
Jody!
That's ridiculous.
The secret I've been seeking for years has been destroyed in a few minutes.
How could I lose it in a few minutes?
Here, Jody.
Thank you, Mr. Nakagawa.
That's great, Jody.
You're cute.
Mr. Nakagawa is the king of the lower town.
The king of the lower town.
The king of the lower town!
I didn't know he was the king.
It's so nice to have a sunny day.
Last year, the typhoon hit directly.
In Tokyo, around here,
there were foquinnas.
What's all this time?
I'm okay.
How cute.
Hey, where can I get this?
I want a souvenir.
Eh, Ojizou?
No souvenir shops.
I know.
Ryo-chan!
Well, you know King Nakagawa of the underground town.
What are you talking about?
If you don't sell it, I'll take it home.
I'll take one that has a lot of things.
Oh, no!
I can't buy this.
It's small but cute.
Thank you, Mr. Nakagawa.
Recently, there are many things in the souvenir shop.
I thought maybe.
As expected of Kei-chan.
As expected of the King of the underground town, Mr. Nakagawa.
Oh, no!
I love the underground town of Japan.
Where are you going next, Mr. Nakagawa?
Well, next to Shibamada Taishakuten is Asakusa Kaminari-mon.
I'm going to a famous tourist spot that nobody knows in Japan.
I'm going to take a tour of the underground town.
If you're going to be so stubborn, Ryo-chan will escort you.
Oh, Mr. Ryotsu will guide you this time.
All right.
There is a place where you have to go to know the charm of the underground town.
That is here!
I have to go to the underground town without entering the castle!
Wow, I wanted to go to a Japanese bathhouse once.
I don't think Nakagawa, who grew up in New York, has ever entered the underground town.
Yes, I have.
I'm going to enter the underground town once.
Anyway, there's a problem when I enter.
There are many places that are counter-shaped in the near future.
The first battle of the underground town was a great progress.
No, it's not.
Mr. Ryo, the business is from 3 o'clock.
It's still 2 o'clock.
It's still open. Don't say something so hard.
But I have to keep the time.
Senpai, let's go out again.
Oh?
Where are you?
What's wrong, Ryo?
Are you going to go in, too?
Yes.
Oh, that's too bad.
No, I didn't put the foreigner who came here to put it in the bath.
It's a turtle bath.
Come on, let's go.
Please go in slowly.
Thank you, Mr.
This is the charm of the underground town.
It's the charm of Japan.
That's how the old man makes a fool of himself.
Tte.
1st bath is the best.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Oh.
Is the turtle bath closed?
Mr. Reiko and Mr. Jody are here, too.
It seems to be fun.
I'll be there soon.
See you later.
I see.
You're still wearing heavy armor.
You're not rusty because you put it in the water?
There are many guards in the hot springs.
I'm using an all-stenless revolver that doesn't rust even in the water.
Don't shoot! It's just a water drop!
Sorry.
My body reacts to the reflection.
What's wrong, Takagawa?
Why are you putting a towel around your waist?
No matter how much you're a senior, you don't want to be forced into the bath.
When I was a kid, there was a guy like that.
How did you deal with him?
Watch me.
Stop it, senior!
I'll tell you, you'll be worried about it.
If you don't take it off, you'll think it's something ridiculous.
That's not true.
Then show me your pocky and come in.
Exactly.
It's natural for a man to come in while showing his balls.
Pocky?
That's amazing.
I'm more particular about one hand.
Senior.
The bath feels good.
See, I know you don't hide your Honda at all.
What?
Nakagawa is discriminating against us, the small citizens who raise pocky.
No way.
You're making fun of pocky.
That's not true.
Then try it like I did.
Put your hands on your shoulders.
Show your front.
Hey!
How's the cake?
It's good.
And then...
...and then.
Okay, now we're even.
You have to try, when I tell you.
That's a no.
Don't forget...
Look here.
This is a real pie.
You have to show your balls at all times.
A real pie?
What?
I'll show you.
I'll show you, too.
Show me your balls.
No.
Noooo!
He is making a much bigger trusted example than expected.
I have great expectations.
What is he expecting?
I'll place it here.
Welcome.
Mr. Toyama,
how are you doing?
How are you feeling?
I'm not feeling well, but I'm not feeling bad.
Instructor Honda, I'm going to shampoo.
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This is a great idea, Mr. Honda.
It's a common sight in the downtown.
What a great idea.
This is a great idea.
This reminds me of my childhood.
I went to the bathhouse after school and played for hours.
Momoko, wash your body.
Okay.
We're in the same bathhouse because we're neighbors.
I was excited when I saw a naked classmate on the other side of the wall.
It's a sweet memory in the downtown.
I grew up in New York.
I don't know the world.
I can't believe I'm in the town.
It's okay.
It's about the town.
Please sit down.
Jordy has a big chest.
Amazing.
No, Miss Reiko is bigger.
His nose is different.
No, it's long.
It's Seigo.
Seigo is bigger.
You know how he talks.
I was told how I feel and I'm lying like a man now.
What do I do?
I must vent my heart into the women's bathhouse.
It's in the boiler room.
The men's and women's bathrooms work in that room.
I'm going to meet my crush, Jordy and Nana.
What?
Senior, the nose is the opposite.
I don't understand you growing up in New York.
You, the one who grew up in the country, can't understand it.
It's a greeting like a low town.
Get lost.
Ah, is that so?
Please do it yourself.
Don't make a sound alone!
Ah, everyone is so shy.
Can't you go, brother?
Huh?
I'm so nervous.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
There's no one here.
Ryo-chan.
I knew you would come.
You're all dirty.
Don't put on a bath towel and go to the bathroom.
Ready?
Wait a minute, Yose.
Again!
I'm sorry.
Do you need anything?
I knew it.
Kokichi!
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Kokichi!
Nagagawa, you have such a hobby.
No.
Kokichi!
What are you doing?
Please be firm.
I don't understand why New York kids are doing that.
Please Subscribe!
It seems that he calmed down, but it is very dangerous if his blood pressure rises again.
Don't let him get too excited.
Yes.
I'll come back to see you later. Take care.
I don't know what New York adults do when they open their eyes.
Right, Bulbul?
Yes.
I want you to not shout in front of the patient.
Right, Mr. Honda?
Yes.
Mr. Toyama seemed to be fine when he came to the bath.
What happened?
When he saw my face, he called me Koukichi.
Koukichi?
I see.
I thought he looked like someone when I saw you.
Who is that Koukichi?
He is Mr. Toyama's only son.
Son?
Yes, he is.
He is the son of Mr. Toyama.
Oh, he looks just like Nakagawa.
Mr. Toyama was a skilled carpenter in the old days.
However, due to the times, he lost his job and started drinking alcohol.
On the contrary, he never followed after his son, so he had a quarrel with his only son Koukichi.
I don't want to see your face.
Go away!
The child is notano.
What's your story?
Now that you've seen Nakagawa, did you think your son came back?
Woo!
You're not so terrible.
My blood pressure is rose already.
After all, we fought a lot, but have been weak-willed lately.
I feel I did something wrong ...
Stング!
Yes, it is a great chance based on Makagawa.
If you knew it was a misunderstanding, you would be disappointed, right?
Yes.
He noticed.
What do we do?
Where is this place?
I'm glad, boss! Your precious son, Koukichi, is back!
Senior! Koukichi! Koukichi!
I'm glad, Koukichi. You finally met your father, whom you've wanted to meet for years.
Koukichi!
Then we'll leave without water for the rest of the day.
Is that okay, Ryo-san?
-No, no, no! -No, no, no!
Senior!
Maybe he still remembers that he lost the goldfish scoop.
What?
Dad, I'd like to ask Ryo-san to stay.
I want to give him a small reward.
Oh, I see.
As you can see, I can't do anything good in my life,
so please take it easy, Ryo-san.
That's what I'm trying to say!
If you erase my son's identity, I'll have to face the dead Kakao!
Then we'll go first.
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
Wait!
Koukichi!
Dad is also free, so please take it easy, Senior.
Yes.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
I'm thirsty.
-Thank you for the food. -Thank you for the food.
What the hell is this?
It's a special bancha with Koukichi's favorite natto, miso, and sugar.
I wonder if there was less natto.
I see. Koukichi's.
It's delicious. It's delicious.
I don't think there's anything else to eat.
I only have the croquettes I bought this afternoon.
This one looks delicious.
I'll take one word from you.
Koukichi likes to stretch the croquettes and pour the sauce until they turn black.
No, just like that.
If you're a man, you should not be stingy.
You should pour the sauce all at once.
Now, Koukichi, eat up.
Wow, it looks delicious.
It's good.
Oh, it's good.
I'm sorry to eat such a delicious thing alone.
Senpai, have a bite.
No, I'll take it.
Yeah, you're the one who likes spicy food.
So stand up the chili pepper.
Hey, you're not wearing your mittens.
Now it's just the spicy taste of your taste.
Now it's your favorite spice.
Who would be happy about that?
To be able to meet a good brother like you now.
I couldn't say anything about the way it was in the old days.
I couldn't say anything even if I was silent.
Let's drink.
Damn it! That bastard!
Then, Koukichi, are you also a boss?
Yes, well...
I see.
Koukichi has become a boss.
I was thinking that you were working somewhere bad again.
I was worried about you.
Senpai, are you still awake?
Yes.
I came all the way here with the intention of staying with you.
But we're doing a good thing, aren't we?
I used to fight with my father and left Tsukudaniya.
I thought that my father was lonely, too.
I've only met my father five times before.
Then, have you ever had a fight with your parents?
Yes.
Your family has changed a lot.
What should we do from tomorrow, senpai?
Yes, we have to do it for a while.
What's wrong with you?
I'm so tired.
Your father is really strong.
I can't stand it.
Koukichi, you've become a very polite person.
Koukichi, you've become an adult, too.
What's wrong with you?
In the past, you called me a bad father and a stubborn old man,
but now you've become a stubborn old man.
Stubborn old man?
I'm afraid you're not like me.
After a long time, you've become a good person.
I'm sorry.
Actually, I'm...
Koukichi, I'm sorry.
The doctor said you were excited.
I'm sure you're excited.
If you talk about the truth and your blood pressure goes up again,
I don't know what's going to happen next.
Senpai, I can't deceive Mr. Tayama anymore.
Do it.
If you tell me about your red-haired old man's son,
I'll be in trouble.
Father!
What are you doing?
I'll go and clean up the room.
That's how you talk in the past.
I'm sorry.
Listen to your son.
That's right!
I'm not like my father.
I can't lose to my son.
You're a good-for-nothing boy!
Mr. Tayama seems to be healthy.
I feel good today.
What a good night.
I will never forget him no matter what.
What are you talking about?
I'm not that stupid.
What did you say?
I'm tired of being a servant.
What's wrong, Kokichi?
Are you going to take a bath?
What?
You're always so excited when you come to the bath.
Look, Ko-chan!
I'm coming!
He's coming...
Show me what you got, Kokichi.
What?
No?
Well...
I see...
You're still not used to it.
You only care about the tip of your tongue and the bottom of your heart.
Boss!
Hey, what's going on?
What's wrong?
Calm down.
Hey!
Kokichi...
When did you come here?
I'm the real Kokichi.
Sorry, Dad.
Kokichi...
Kokichi!
Dad...
I thought I'd have to go home before you gave me a bath.
But I still feel dizzy.
But...
I'm sorry.
Don't say that.
You're the best.
I'm...
I'm glad you came, Dad.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you came.
It's...
It's not your fault.
Dad, look!
Look!
Then who is that?
Hey, it's me!
What? It's real!
Well, it's fine.
Look, Aito-chan! Look!
That old man's heart easily took the Nagagawa Tenegui that we couldn't even take by force.
It's a good story like the north wind and the sun.
The north is great!
We meet again, Professor Tondemo.
What? You're going to the moon this time?
So why do I have to go to space with you?
Next time on Unspeakable Stories: Ryo's Journey to the Moon.
See you!
Surprised.
Quiet.
Shaking.
Warmth.
And ...
Sudden.
and flicker.
Shake.
and gather.
and take action!
And fly.
It feel like they have more power than anything.
With everyone being together!
If we eat here,
Like a dream, the final energy
Looking at tomorrow, believing in yesterday
Drawing the universe, if you stand on the ground
The planet of the turtle will spin and draw a circle
Isn't this good?
There's no good reason!
Thanks for watching!