Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the passing seasons ♩
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♩
♪ Crossing the youthful era ♩
♪ Diving to the city with a yellow-green car ♩
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♩
♪ Rather than just wearing the trendy clothes ♩
♪ I'll decide the sales by my face ♩
♪ Let it be ♩
♪ Everybody can do it, start running ♩
♪ Dreams don't always stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♩
♪ Love you, love ♩
♪ Everybody can do it, even if it's a little dark ♩
♪ It doesn't hurt to spit it out ♩
♪ With a loud curiosity ♩
♪ I'll make it strong and high ♩
♪ Jump up the slide ♩
♪ Holding the torch with our souls, it doesn't matter ♩
♪ Nothing can leave ♩
♪ So what you can do now, just jump ♩
♪ Jump and see, and see ♩
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♩
♪ "'13" to TED ♪
I'm sorry.
Yes, we are offering free print seals to the customers who have made a special offer at our store.
Ryo, let's go play the "Hina Matsuri" winning game.
I hate March 3rd!
Get out of my way!
What's wrong with Ryo?
Let's light the candles.
I see. Today was the "Hina Matsuri".
Yes. Isn't it cute?
It seems that the "Hina Matsuri" is a happy thing for girls no matter how old they are.
Good morning.
What's wrong with Ryo?
He went on a patrol.
A patrol?
He must be playing around somewhere.
Ryo doesn't seem to be interested in the festival.
Even if it's a festival, it's a "Hina Matsuri" today.
It has nothing to do with men like Ryo.
Who did it?
It's Ryo, as I thought.
This is strange.
What's wrong, chief?
It's a great discovery. Look.
Here it is.
March 3rd?
It's Ryo's...
It's Ryo's birthday.
That means it's today.
It means...
Ryo's birthday is a "Hina Matsuri"?
Oh, no!
Ryo's image doesn't match at all.
It's impossible to say that you're laughing.
What's wrong, chief?
It's the local police chief, Ryo.
I see.
Good morning, chief.
I was on patrol to be able to protect the safety of the local residents.
I see.
Of course, the chief of the police probably took it with him.
That's already a very important thing in his pocket.
That's strange.
Did you put it here?
See. It fell off.
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
By the way, isn't today someone's birthday?
What?
Who was it?
Oh, it was the temple.
It's May 5th.
It's a boy's birthday.
Oh, that's a good birthday for a boy.
Right, Ryoatsu?
Well, yeah.
Reiko's birthday is...
July 7th.
Oh, it's a festival.
A festival?
It's a good day to be romantic like a girl.
Right, Ryoatsu?
Yeah.
But there are days when you can be more romantic like a girl.
For example...
March 3rd!
You said it was a festival!
I knew it!
It's my birthday on March 3rd!
Oh, I didn't know that.
I knew it.
Don't worry about it.
It's a boy's birthday on March 3rd.
It's a boy who's so romantic.
I just didn't like his image.
I don't mind that.
But a boy's birthday is not something you want to do every year.
At first, yeah.
I was in elementary school.
I tried to make a doll for a girl in my neighborhood.
And I found a cardboard doll in the stairs.
I slipped
He slipped and fell down a terrible staircase.
Oh my.
When he was in middle school, he drank white alcohol and got drunk.
He fell into a river and was washed into the sea.
When he was in high school, he was found by a girl in the class of H-pong.
He was beaten and put on the back of a washi.
He couldn't be invited to the Hina Festival after all.
If he gambles, he always loses a lot.
He runs away from the debt collector and loses his salary.
He is attacked by a crow and falls.
He runs away from food and is caught by a dog.
He is caught in catch sales.
My birthday is cursed.
He can't be with me anymore.
It's all a mess.
I hate March 3rd.
You don't have to worry about it.
He hasn't been with me until now.
I'm going to a Hina Festival party today.
I want to go.
I'll invite you.
What? A party?
I'm going.
He said he only likes Kei.
I feel sorry for him.
Will you have a feast?
Of course.
I'm going to eat sushi that he likes.
Great.
I can eat sushi for the first time in a long time.
Yes, this is Hachijo in Koenmai.
Yes, sir.
Chief, an accident happened at the 4th store.
What?
At the house of a rich man in Koenmai.
Let's go.
Me?
Don't be nervous.
Let me go, chief.
I was invited to the party for a girl.
I want to eat sushi.
He is really not with Ryo.
Listen.
The police's duty is to prevent any crime by considering the safety of the people.
Do you understand?
Come here.
The house of a rich man in Koenmai is here.
I can't believe I can eat sushi.
I don't have it.
I bought it.
Thank you.
Do you have the grape?
Yes.
What?
There is a girl's dormitory behind it.
The moon hasn't yet fallen.
Ryo, hurry up.
Yes, I'm back.
The night of the night.
Ryo, let's go.
You want to eat sushi.
I want sushi.
Is photography a good job?
Yeah.
N-No, I didn't mean that.
I'm so worried about you now,
I can't sleep at night.
O-Of course.
The police are responsible for preventing any crime.
Yes.
But stealing a doll is a stupid crime.
It's a prank.
Ryo!
If you're talking about my doll,
then you're not the one who's there.
Huh?
I have 500 million yen!
I'm sorry!
500 million yen!
Ha-ha!
That one is 200 million yen,
and this one is 300 million yen.
It's a cheap one.
200 million and 300 million?
Hey, don't touch it!
I just want to see it.
Hmph!
So, what about the doll?
I asked the girl for it three years ago,
and it's finally finished.
This is all I have.
Let me tell you what I think about it.
The girl's got a lot better with the doll.
Oh, really?
But now I like you better.
Please come in this room.
7th generationumo
Too dazzling.
там goろ
Sure is beautiful.
"The beauty and the tradition
of the tamagoro"
and specialiek shop shop!
Showme clothing
Toilet slices
Samples
Doing all the good jobs
They say
There are a lot of people make experts cry
The one in the back is a gold-plated
For a golden-plated
To use the ruby
Laid-back head
Diamond ring for the ring finger
Dap
Sapphire
Emerald
Love
I have to count to see
Huh!
Where are you going?
You idiot! Even if you break this line, you won't get your salary!
I know, I know!
Haha, don't worry. I'll be very careful.
I'm counting on you.
I'm thirsty.
Hey, get me some tea!
It's the usual gyoza with gold leaf!
Gyoza with gold leaf?
Thank you!
What are you talking about? I'll drink it.
I don't want to waste your tea!
I paid the tax, so I can keep it for free.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, how stingy.
The party is about to begin.
I'm sorry, I have to go to the bathroom.
Hey, the toilet paper is up to 10cm!
I can't run anymore! The corridor is going to be damaged!
The female staff is right there.
They'll come back before the chief notices.
But is this really a bathroom?
What?
Did you call that turtle's primitive man?
He's the worst! He's the best!
Yeah, yeah.
It's okay. It's Ryo's birthday today.
You have to be patient.
But he's a security guard. I don't know if he'll come.
I don't know about that.
He'll come out like a cockroach.
Yeah, he'll turn around and be right behind us.
A cockroach? That's bad!
He looks like a
What?
If you're going to complain, go home!
Yeah, yeah!
Don't make a fuss!
Let's start the party!
Ryo, are you okay with being a security guard?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What's with this taste?
Are you guys cooking properly?
Stop laughing.
What do you mean?
Yum-Yum!
I'm proud to be a security guard.
Well, I'm the security guard's assistant.
No!
What?
I'm very nosy.
I'll have to run away.
Ryo!
Thanks, Chanyu!
No, thank you.
I'll have a drink to calm him down.
I don't want that.
Ugh!
Please, give me 30 more.
Yes.
Oh, I don't mind.
Thank you.
Hey, Reiko!
Do you still want sushi?
Wait a minute.
I ordered a lot.
You're still eating so much?
The stomach that goes in sushi is different.
It's different.
What's different?
Your stomach is a dust chute.
It's terrible.
I hope you don't mind.
If I don't find the chief,
March 3rd this year will be a good day.
Yes, it's me, Ryotsu.
Oh, it's not me.
Yes, it's Ohara.
Chief Ohara.
Yes, yes.
Don't worry, chief.
I'm checking it hard right now.
What?
There's nothing wrong.
Oh, Ryotsu is worried.
No, I'll tell him.
He's a useful man at times like this.
Yes?
Yes, it's Ryotsu.
Ohara, are you still in the bathroom?
Yes, but there's still something that's not coming out.
What are you doing, Ryotsu Kankichi?
What?
Is someone there?
No, it's nothing.
If you're working, go back quickly.
Who is it, Ryotsu?
Shut up!
What?
Wait a minute.
I'm going now.
No, no, no.
You don't have to come.
What are you going to do, senpai?
I'll be right back.
Leave the sushi.
What's he doing?
Ouch!
I'm too hungry to eat.
Oh, my God.
Ryotsu, are you there?
Ryotsu!
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
Ryotsu!
Hey, Ryotsu!
Come out!
Hello, hello.
It's been a week.
You've been out for a week, but you're still out.
No, I mean...
I'm going to the Hina Doll's security.
Thank you.
Oh, this is the bathroom.
That was close.
That eye is completely suspicious.
A Hina Doll worth 500 million yen.
Takada spent so much money on a Hina Doll.
Even the Hina Doll he carved with his hair
is still not out.
I mean, my heart is filled with his heart.
That's all it is.
First of all,
if I had a Hina Doll like this,
it would be a disaster
just to lose one of them.
What?
N-No!
No, no, no!
Ouch!
That's awful!
I have 500 million yen in all.
Even if I lose one of them,
even if I lose one of them…
even if I lose one of them,
20 million yen.
It's not able to be paid well.
Did I get beaten up
when I went to the female security?
What?
That's right.
The female security guy.
Alright.
Ah!
What's the matter, Ryo?
S...san!
I...I'm in the washroom!
You again?
You're so upset.
Is she really coming back to us?
The sushi was here so we didn't have to kid ourselves about it.
And so, our food is ready to be served.
You're right.
Ugh, she's so annoying!
It looks so good!
Huh? What...what is this?!
It's like juice.
It's like an ama.
Is it okay?
Sushi!
You go first.
I'll go first.
My hair!
Who's there? Ryo?
I'll be fine if I don't get it.
I'm a beggar, so I won't let you touch it.
Ryo!
What are you doing?
Yes!
I'm worried about you.
I'll take care of this.
But...
It's about you.
You might be able to turn a scarecrow into a fake one.
That's ridiculous!
Besides, a scarecrow is scared of your face.
Go!
Okay.
I hope you don't get it.
You really are a genius, but you're not good at making things.
Please don't let me get it.
You really have good eyes.
Especially this eye-catching face.
You don't look at me that much.
What?
What the heck is this?
DEFENDER
What happened?
Damn, I've been found out!
I've done something crazy.
I think you did it on your own.
At this point...
Leader!
What are you doing here?
What?
No way!
Boss, the person you're talking about is a horrible person!
I just touched it a little, but I'm sorry.
500 million yen!
That one eye is worth 50 million yen!
No, no matter what, you're the main actress of the escape doll!
I won't give you 100 million yen!
How much did you pay?
500 million yen!
M-Mebina...
No way!
Boss, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kingaichi.
I will pay you back for this.
I'll pay you back for the rest of my life.
Even if you work 24 hours a day, you'll die.
My wife and daughter work, too.
Oh, what a poor boss.
One mistake and the Ohara family is destroyed.
I understand.
A policeman who must protect the people's property
He did such a bad thing,
That's unforgivable.
Ohara take responsibility.
As of today, I quit my job as a policeman.
I will pay you back with retirement money.
What?
No, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Even if you do something like that,
Don't stop, Ryotsu!
That kind of retirement money is not enough.
Eh, no, wait a minute...
Then I will pay even if you sell the house.
Uncle, will you lose your house?
There is no choice.
Miss, I was wrong.
If you make a mistake, it is natural to apologize and atone for it honestly.
The worst thing is to escape without taking responsibility.
Miss, actually I...
Ryotsu, don't bother everyone.
Then, I will go to the headquarters to make a confession.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
We were playing in this room...
Over here.
Wait.
I broke the Hina doll.
I thought you would get angry, so I wrote a confession letter and tried to make it look like the thief stole it.
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
I broke the Hina doll that you cherished so much.
Papa, what did you say?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what was going to happen.
For all those years,
Who made this Hina doll?
It was made for Amarine, isn't that right?
Papa?
Just for nothing,
the best thing is that I am taking care of you girls.
Papa...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Papa!
Oh, good, good.
But you don't have to apologize.
As you said, it's best to apologize honestly.
Right?
Yes.
Well, that's a good thing, Chief.
But, then, this Hina doll is...
Disgusting.
Could it be...
She's...
No, that's not it.
I'm sorry for the female material.
You know I broke the fake doll?
No, that's...
Mama!
I'm sorry.
I did it.
If you apologize honestly...
That's my child's story.
I'm going to work with you for the rest of your life and make you pay for it!
Please.
I'm begging you.
Hina Ryozu!
No, Chief.
I knew it.
March 3rd is not a good day!
Damn it!
I hate Hina Festival!
On the third day of the year,
there is a castle that stands undisguised,
and it is called Amoroshijou.
On this castle, there is a damsel
who has a golden scale.
All right!
I got that golden damsel!
Next time on Ninja vs Indy Ryozu
It's a pleasure!
To be continued
End of Part 2
Because time will pass
Don't stare at me
Let's laugh and live
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
Let's wash our hands
Goodbye to the unpleasant things
Oh yeah
Let's live as we like
There is something good
Outside the door
Let's go
The sun is calling