Translated by 方 Hou.
I look up at the sunset floating in the river
If I kick the love stone, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I used to do
I was laughed at as a child
Even if I try to cheer up, I can't win
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn is strangely gentle
From the water tank in Tongari City
The sunset falls to Taishakuten
Tomorrow is already over like this
I lost my happiness because of the Katsushika Shiba
I realized it
Because I'm an idiot
Koukon Gamer Sakonji
Next!
He's the one who's the boss, Sakonji Tatsunosuke.
Next! He's the one who's the boss, Sakonji Tatsunosuke.
Not only Judo but Karate, Aikido, and Taekwondo
He's the boss, Sakonji Tatsunosuke.
He's the demon of martial arts.
The demon of martial arts.
Hey, Ryotsu, I'm here.
It's almost time for the match between the chief and the opponent.
You have to train them well today.
Thank you!
Um, please say hello.
What's that greeting?
It's not that a man greets you.
A man's greeting is short and simple.
Help me, Senpai!
It's going to take a long time.
Don't shout!
I'm going on a date.
I don't care.
Dating is a gold medal.
Why don't you go on a date?
Dating?
Who said I was on a date?
You!
Do you think you can be strong by going through so much pain?
No!
What happened?
I hate girls with thorns!
You bastard!
I'm not going to teach you how to take a hold on me!
This is it for today!
Thank you!
Hey, Jonji.
I have the videos you asked me to do.
Oh, I see.
How about one more round later in my room?
Alright!
How about you guys too?
What?
- No, I mean, I'm... - D...
D... It's all right!
- A game? - No, it's just a fighting game.
But...
K.O.!
All right!
The protein after cooking is really tasty.
Protein?
How about you? You're getting muscles.
No, I'm fine.
Oh, right. Want to watch the video?
Yeah.
Video?
I took a video of Kenshin III.
It's hard to get into the right timing.
Tatsunosuke?
What was that voice?
Oh, no! I got the wrong tape!
Good morning, Tatsunosuke.
This is the behind-the-scenes story of the Doki Doki Memorial that Honda asked me to do.
Oh, it's Saori!
Doki Doki Memorial?
It's a love simulation game.
The player goes to a high school called Kirakira Academy and spends three years of student life there.
And on the graduation day, under the legendary cherry tree, the heroine Saori receives a love confession from her.
Want to try it? There's a software.
Me?
No way. But why my name?
This game is a game where you enter your name and birthday first, and the girl who comes out calls the player's name in voice.
This is a game where you enter your name and birthday first, and the girl who comes out calls the player's name in voice.
I just entered your name. I thought the player's name might change the parameters.
It's not a joke.
Tatsunosuke, are you going home now?
Eh? But this voice and this face...
They look alike.
Ah, Tatsunosuke-kun.
When I play this game, I remember the first time I fell in love with a girl.
Sakonji-san, you have a memory of your first love, right?
No, no, no, not at all!
First love is...
I-I get it, I get it!
But I didn't know you were this good. You've only played fighting games.
I'm surprised. The great thing about this game is that when you get close to me, you call me by my nickname.
What!?
Tatsu-chan.
What, do you want to try?
Don't be stupid! Why do I have to do this?
A fighting game. I'm a man among men.
I'm not going to do it!
Then give it back to me.
My-my brother wanted to do it.
Your brother? Did you have a brother?
It's your first time hearing it.
I did!
Before I die from a disease that I can't even handle, I wanted to play Doki Doki Memorial!
Why!?
He's not into it.
Eh? Sakonji-san?
He's more into the game than the guy who looks like he's not interested in girls.
Sakonji-san is more into the game than the guy who looks like he's not interested in girls.
You're gone.
That's good. No one's looking.
Well...
What should I call you? Saori-chan?
Doki Doki Memorial.
Please tell me your name.
Name?
My last name is Sakonji.
My name is Tatsumosake.
My last name is Tatsumosake.
Game start!
Good morning, Tatsumosake-kun.
Today is the start of your high school life.
What?
This is so interesting!
Hm?
I see. So you first decide your schedule.
That means you need to improve yourself.
The charm of a man!
That's a body that's been torn out!
First, you don't need to work every morning.
Club activities are a hero to all sportsmen.
When it's time to go to school, go to the gym and train your body to wipe out air!
Finally we can call it a graduation ceremony.
One year...
But three years...
I'm doing exercise with my core.
Now I can feel Saori's love for me.
You better die!!!
There's a letter in the desk?
It says "I'll be waiting for you under the cherry tree on the 3rd floor on the right side of the strait."
C-can this be?!
Dacchan... I was simply talking about you...
E-E-E-E-!
Yes! stickers! You can go under the cherry tree!
There's a Gou under the tree!
Tat-chan, please call me Aniki from now on.
Please call me Aniki from now on.
Huh? I hear a strange voice from Sakonji's room.
That's right.
I can't stand the noise because my room is close.
It's a nuisance for the neighbors.
Please say something, Ryo.
Okay, okay.
What's wrong, Saori?
I'm sorry. I have something else to do that day.
I'll see you later.
Saori, you're...
I've been on a date with her for 10 times!
Please say something!
Sakonji, it's Ryo!
Huh?
I can't watch TV.
I'm stupid.
Hey, open the door!
Ryo, what's going on?
You must be playing games again.
I can hear your whining.
Is that so?
I'm sure it's Kenshin 3.
I'm into it lately.
I'll be fine.
I don't know what you're playing, but please don't be so noisy.
I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
By the way, have you been on a date with Saori?
What do you mean?
"Doki Doki Memorial"!
Oh, I see.
I'm not interested in the game, so I totally forgot.
You shouted "Saori" just now.
What are you talking about?
Actually, she hasn't come back from her brother yet.
I'll return it to you as soon as she comes back.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do anything wrong.
"Doki Doki Memorial" is a video game.
When you go to the sea with Saori,
Saori will drown.
And you can do artificial breathing.
Artificial breathing!
When you go to the haunted house at the amusement park,
there are many other events, such as hugging each other,
or watching a movie in the fields,
and so on.
This is the real Ryo-etsu!
Hey!
Hey! Why are you getting so excited?
I-I was just thinking that my brother would be happy if I taught him.
Anyway, just do it quietly.
Yeah.
B-By the way, what do you do when Saori doesn't really want to go out with you?
No, my brother was talking about that earlier.
First, invite him to a park nearby.
He'll definitely refuse.
A park nearby? Okay!
Oh!
A park nearby, a park nearby...
Okay.
A park nearby?
Yeah, that's fine.
I did it!
I did it! I did it!
Senpai, you're more noisy than before.
I didn't want to teach you.
But you'll never forget to comfort me!
But you're more noisy than before.
You're so noisy, right?
But you're so noisy, right?
Yeah, you are!
You're so noisy, even if you were a little bit normally.
I'm really surprised!
Well, so that's it for today.
But it's hard to say that you have to study even if you know it's a game.
What?
I'm sorry.
What's with this girl?
Sakonji, you're Tatsunosuke, right? My name is Asahina Miki.
If you don't mind, would you like to come home with me?
She's pretty cute.
No, I'm Saori Hitosuji.
I don't have time to be involved with other girls.
Sakonji's room
Sakonji's room, okay?
Hey.
Ryo, what am I supposed to do?
Sakonji, what's the matter?
Saori suddenly got cold.
I get cut off when I call, and I get ignored in the hallway.
Why can't I understand what to say?
Ryo...
Stop playing games and go to bed!
I'm not sleeping.
Stop it!
I'm not sleeping!
Ryo, please, stop it!
Is this the party report about your brother?
My brother just called me, and if I don't talk to him, he'll kill himself.
I'll let you know when it's tomorrow!
Please let me sleep!
So you give up?
Please, Ryo!
Ryotsu!
Even if Saori is the real one, you can't be too cold to other girls!
Why not?
If you're too cold to other girls, you will make Saori even worse!
Is that so?
You have to be nice to other girls too.
Then the bad rumors will disappear naturally and Saori's mood will be better.
I see. Thank you, Ryotsu! I'm sure my brother will be happy!
What?
Ryotsu!
What are you doing this time?
It's Saori.
Tatsunosuke, are you coming back?
Yes!
Saori's mood has been fixed!
Hey, Tatsunosuke.
Tatsunosuke.
Finally, you're calling me by my nickname!
Tatsunosuke, Tatsunosuke, call me more!
The message continues.
Tatsunosuke, are you free this Sunday?
Yes.
Well, do you wanna go somewhere with me?
What?
W-We might be invited to a date!
Oh no!
He invited me to a date!
Saori invited me to a date!
Of course, I'm okay!
I won't include you ahh.
Hey, Saori!
I'm gonna fight with you.
Oh Papa!
Saori, look at those surprised eyes!
You're the one who's trying toité!
I'm the one who you're trying toité!
It's not funny!
The next day
Hey, Saori-chan, sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah...
You came dressed like that?
Is something wrong?
You have a bad sense of humor.
"I thought I was a man in a man's form."
I thought I was a man in a man's form.
The next day
Go, go, go! There!
Yes!
I did it!
It was a wonderful game, Saori-chan.
I'm not good at this kind of thing.
Oh, my God.
Did Saori hate judo?
My throat is dry.
Then...
This protein juice...
I'm going home.
Wait for me, Saori-chan.
Wait for me!
I hate you, Tat-chan.
Yeah!
What?
Why did you do that?
I can't do it.
I've never actually dated anyone.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, right.
This is Ryotsuni.
Wait.
Wait, if it's about a date, it's better than a ryo-tsu.
That's right, it's that guy!
Who's calling at this hour?
Yes.
Sakonji Tatsunosuke speaking.
Eh, Sakonji-san?
Huh? Is this how you go on a date?
Alright! I did it!
It sure is a noisy room.
Sakonji Tatsunosuke speaking.
Hey, old lady.
You always work hard.
Eh, are you Sakonji-san?
That's right. The door key's not working properly.
I-Is that so? I'll take a look.
Well, what's going on?
What's wrong, you two?
I've been calling Sakonji-san for days in the middle of the night.
I can't sleep.
You've been calling me for an hour now.
I can't sleep at all, either.
Here's your coffee for you.
Thank you.
Sakonji-san, do you really have any memories of your first love?
I do.
This is the best way to do it.
He had his first love when he was four.
I see.
Sakonji-san.
Yeah.
You're going to love her.
It's really beautiful.
And you're going to try to calm him down, right?
And he'll probably never like it.
So, you two not only like each other,
You sure are.
Then,
He won the finals smoothly.
And the final opponent is...
Ippon!
And he was too shocked.
He forgot to go to the bathroom and wanted to compete.
Hajime!
Ippon!
I did it!
I'm sorry.
Sakonji's first love is over.
Poor thing.
After that, Sakonji turned his back on girls...
...and started to live like a fighter.
That's right.
But you didn't get thrown off by a girl from a game, did you?
Isn't it a good opportunity to get rid of a fighter?
A girl from a game?
Get thrown off...
...and get thrown off by a girl from a game.
It's finally here.
I'm waiting for you under the cherry tree on the third floor of the main hall.
They're finally here!
What's wrong, senpai?
There's a hidden event at the Doki-Memo!
What?
Eh?!
Tachan! I've been waiting!
S-Saori...
I've always...
...been after you...
When it comes to the final confession...
...it's terrifying when you choose the option...
...to choose "I've chosen too!"
Actually, I've also...
What?
I know. Let's fight!
Stop!
I don't want to fight you!
Takumi!
I hate weak people. Goodbye!
Too late.
You're a woman!
Please forgive me!
You've gotten worse. You hate women.
Our second love ended the same way.
Horororororori!
You really got in the way of my business, Chief!
And even the President!
I'll repay you ten times, no, a hundred times!
You two, be prepared!
Next time, "Ogeretsu Shashin Panic!"
Thank you!
Chiharu
There's a rumor that you can't fall in love.
I have so many things I want to do.
I want to run through the desert with a motorcycle.
I want to run on the track
I want to be free more than a bird
The speed of the full-scale train
Changes the lady's dream
Love heart
Sorry, wait
The future of the panorama
The dazzling time
You understand, right?
Sorry, wait