Wednesday, April 8, 2010
I look at one day,
floating in the river,
Even if you're a kid, you're a patsushika
The city's waves are strangely gentle
From the waterfront of Tongari Boshi
To Kaishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
If you're a patsushika, you'll be happy again
I've lost it, but I've realized
Because I'm such an idiot
I'm more of a patsusika than a penser
I want to see you like a patsushika
Every time I am the patsushika
In order to make you happy, I have to love you
I love you, Inol
This is the Akasaka Geyhinkan station.
The car with the Kokuo family will soon arrive.
500 police officers are guarding the Geyhinkan.
In an emergency situation, the police will receive orders from the headquarters.
The first two laps have been one-on-one.
The batter is not yet a hit today.
The Kokuo car is coming.
The princess is also in a hurry.
The pitcher is in first place.
He throws!
He's hit!
What?
Let the car stop!
Oh no!
Something terrible has happened!
Ryo, if you make a mistake, you should apologize soon.
What happened?
Well, I didn't do anything.
What is this?
Soon, the home run will be hit.
The home run was hit.
That's right.
Excuse me.
It seems that my subordinates misunderstood.
No, it's really a trouble for Takahashi.
Idiot!
You!
What do you think of the national honor?
Ouch!
I'm fine here.
It's fine.
Tomorrow's your day off is over.
No!
I don't want that.
I arrived safely.
Japan seems to have become less safe than before.
Tomorrow's new security will be more strict.
What?
Oh, what's wrong, Fanny?
Well...
Even if it's not like that,
when the SP people are around,
the private schedule is not fun.
Fanny is always a child.
Oh, I'm already an adult.
Because tomorrow...
Your Majesty,
the official schedule will be changed a little tomorrow.
I see.
Your Majesty,
tomorrow is...
I've fixed the dress for tomorrow.
I'll go now.
Fanny,
the one who got the money,
don't bother her.
Be a good girl.
Everyone completely forgets about my birthday.
Where are you going, Fanny?
Princess, move!
To the toilet!
Princess Bunny will be officially visited by this Kazushika Wonderland.
The visit time is 30 minutes.
Until then, don't let the princess get in danger.
Be careful.
Be careful with the best of your ability.
It's such a short time already
You're so slow.
Ryo-san.
Eh?
Ouch!
You're here to take revenge for what you did last night.
If you listen to baseball,
I'll give you a thrashing this time.
I know.
I had a request from the amusement park.
I wanted you to avoid the disgusting security guards.
So we'll guard the princess so that the public won't notice.
The Princess Guard
I can't believe they didn't notice.
He looks weak.
And he's hard to move.
Don't say that.
Huh?
The Princess Guard
The princess looks too good on him.
Hello.
Everyone.
Are you ready?
Huh?
I asked the Torrent to teach you how to move.
There's such a thing?
Let's start with the basic greeting.
Spread your hands like this.
Welcome to Wonderland.
Next is the pose when you're asked for a picture.
The point is to lightly touch the customer.
And this is the bye-bye pose when you go home.
Pay attention to the movement of the bridge.
You're telling us to do that?
Mr. Ryo.
Huh?
What?
The pose for hello.
The pose for the picture.
Bye-bye.
He's doing his best.
So, what's the question?
Teacher, a question.
If there's a naughty child, can I hit him?
You can't.
He'll jump.
But I saw a drunk person hugging the Princess Guard.
Do you pretend not to see it even at that time?
If so, what would you do?
If so...
Such characters are harshly warned.
Idol characters shouldn't touch it.
I see.
If the customer is beautiful,
can I ask about his phone number?
I mean, before, the sleepy man who had seven boys was probably picking up...
Shut up.
Then how many Tsukki Bears are in this amusement park?
What?
In my gut, I feel like there are at least ten.
But...
Hmm...
Okay, I'll answer.
There's only one Tsukkii Bear in your hearts.
Eh? Then how many females do you have?
You! Don't call me a female, you're a Nini Bear!
And stop calling me a "hiki", "hiki"!
Question.
The Prince of Tolland played at Roppongi's Foreigner Bar.
Is that okay?
Tolland is a world of dreams and fantasy.
Don't check out those kind of places!
Ah, I understand.
Well then, bye-bye!
That teacher is so full of his moves.
Wow!
It's so nice!
We'll be there in 30 minutes.
I understand.
Ah, Yakuza!
We're free to go!
Hey, girl!
Let's play together!
Eh?
You're coming alone, right?
Hey, don't you mind?
But, I...
Let's have fun!
Hm?
What?
Bye-bye!
Oh, Tsukkii!
You're protecting me?
Yeah.
So you're my bodyguards here?
That's wonderful!
Hmm...
I'm just a boring middle-aged old man,
but if you're so boring,
I'm sure you're a real shop.
Hey, Azulim!
Let's play here!
Shut up!
Go away!
I don't have time to play with you!
You kids!
Huh?
Why do you think we're fighting?
We're playing the role of customers,
but we're also protecting the princess.
Ha ha ha.
Welcome to Wonderland!
Yo-san, your legs are upside down!
Ah, wait!
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
Oh!
Oh, welcome!
Ha ha ha!
What a fun ride!
Let's ride that!
Huh?
What?
Hurry, hurry!
Ouch!
One more time.
We'll do this later.
OK.
Cool!
That was fun!
This time it's that sound!
Here we go!
Next it's this one!
Wait!
That was fun!
I'm not going to let you go.
You're old. You're not going to let me go.
Don't look away from the princess.
I'm not going to let you go.
It's a parade!
Huh?
There's a rumor that the princess is coming.
You need to be very careful during the parade.
If you're such an important person,
you should lock the room and get out.
Wow! Cute!
T-that Trump wasn't there.
Hey! Stop that Trump!
Hey, who are you?
I'm just an attraction.
What?
Piyo!
Huh?
Who are you? Get away from her!
Help me!
Ryotsu! What's wrong, Ryotsu?
You bastard!
This way.
They're trying to kidnap me!
What? Let's go back to headquarters.
No! If we go back, we'll be caught!
What do you mean?
I'm so sad.
You're good, princess.
This way!
What's this?
It hurts.
This way!
Chucky!
Nobody's here.
Over there!
We should leave the amusement park.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Tsukki suddenly turned into a gorilla.
It was bad of him.
No way.
We just went to pick up the princess.
What's going on?
You didn't hear the order to hand over the princess to the SP?
Ryotsu!
Can you hear us?
If you can hear us, answer us!
Ryotsu!
Bring Fanny back!
That's enough!
We'll lead the way from here.
The kidnappers are running away with Princess Fanny.
Kidnapping?
Wait!
That's stupid, but he wouldn't do that!
That's right.
We should hurry as soon as we find her.
Yeah.
We can't just kill her.
What?
Remember this!
CI
Hello?
You didn't answer your phone!
Damn, they got me!
Do you know this?
Eiffel Tower?
Yeah, that's the Tokyo tower.
I have to let the chief know soon.
There's the Golden Gate Bridge over there!
That's the Rainbow Bridge.
It's not time to be watching Tokyo.
Where's the Koshuden?
It's not working.
I see.
It's faster to take a taxi and go straight to the office.
But you're the kidnapper.
Are those pirates the SP who came to pick me up?
I'm sorry.
I don't know!
What did you do to me?
What will happen to me?
Will I be beheaded?
I'll be beheaded for sure!
Tsukki!
Don't stop!
I'll pick you up, so go back to the office by yourself!
Hey, taxi!
I don't want to go back yet!
I want to stay like this longer.
I want to know more about this country.
If you listen to my request, I'll definitely thank you.
You'll thank me?
Yes.
I'm the princess of the Ejinbu Kingdom.
I see.
Princess = rich = thank you?
I understand.
If it's a request from the Princess Fanny, who is nothing else...
Really?
I'm so happy!
It's so nice.
Thank you, Tsukki.
Not Tsukki, I'm Ryotsu Kankichi.
Kankiri?
Not Kankiri, Kankichi.
You're right to choose me as your tour guide.
But I'm specialized in northern towns.
Kankichi
Look! It's a cute doll!
It's good!
Can you eat this?
It's sweet!
If you eat it, you'll have to pay for it.
I...
What? You don't have money?
Not at all?
What's wrong with you?
This is a salted bean.
It's a snack that I couldn't eat when I was a kid because it was expensive.
You're so bad.
Like this.
Yes. There's also this.
There are many other ways to eat it.
I'm Kannon from Asakusa.
I want to make a wish for you.
What about Kankichi?
When I was a kid,
I asked him to make me rich, but he still wouldn't make me rich.
Do you have any wishes for a princess?
I want to be a normal girl, not a princess.
Today is my birthday.
Birthday?
I was always alone.
My father and mother were there for me.
Uba, Ji-Jo, and SP were there for me.
But it was their job.
There was no one who understood my feelings.
My house is poor.
My parents are always scolded and beaten.
I'm sorry.
I asked them to make me a child of a different family.
I thought that a person like you wouldn't have any worries.
They must have forgotten my birthday.
I'm 20 years old today.
Okay.
Then, while we celebrate your birthday,
let's go to the garden in Fukagawa.
I'll be there, Kankichi.
Are you okay, Fanny?
No!
W-W-Wait!
Move!
Kankichi!
I found you, Fanny.
This way.
You're so good at this.
This is the party for Princess Fanny's birthday party.
What's wrong?
The princess kept it a secret for today.
The Japanese Prime Minister and the king of Japan were preparing for the party.
But the princess isn't feeling well.
Oh, no!
So the party started a little late.
Are you okay?
Kankichi, I...
That's good.
Kankichi!
Fanny!
Ryo!
Don't move, Ryo!
Let's go.
His Majesty is very worried.
You're so rude!
I asked him to guide us to Tokyo.
Get out of the way!
I'm honored to be of help.
Oh, I see.
I was worried about you all, but today was the best day for me.
Thank you, Kankichi.
You're welcome.
I'll give the car to Princess Fanny.
Okay.
Um... Your Majesty!
This is to commemorate Tokyo.
Thank you.
And since we celebrate Fukagawa's birthday every month,
I'll be waiting to meet you again.
Oh...
Yeah.
Okay, goodbye.
Ah...
*sigh*
Congratulations! Princess Fanny!
*slight sigh*
Fanny?
*Gasps*
*Laughs*
That girl,
finally came back.
Did you take care of the princess?
I was also
not able to thank her,
so I had to take care of her.
Is Ryotsu here?
It seems that Fanny-san sent it to you.
What? Fanny sent it to me?
A doll?
Fanny-san seems to have liked
in this case.
The director is also happy.
We will see how it goes.
I'm glad, Ryotsu.
Oh, Senpai!
What?
My bodyguard, Kankichi?
Thank you for your wonderful birthday.
Please come to the Ejinbu someday.
This time, I will be your guide.
With love from Fanny.
That's good, Ryotsu-san.
Fanny is in love with me!
Then, I'll go!
Ryotsu!
Don't tell me you seriously want to go to the Ejinbu Kingdom.
But Senpai, I think it's just a car accident.
Everyone, stay healthy!
When we meet again, I'm Prince Kankichi.
-Bye-bye! -Bye-bye!
-It's hard! -What?
A few days ago, the princess of the Ejinbu Kingdom
announced her engagement.
Her partner is the rumored princess of the neighboring kingdom.
her partner is the rumored princess of the neighboring kingdom.
It was a car accident, after all.
And Ryo-san forgot something.
How stupid he is!
Wait, honey!
Your beloved Prince Kankichi is coming!
You're not going to believe this!
Don't look at me like that and go away.
Daddy!
I can't believe you guys
why don't you go home?
Do you want him to put me here again?
I can't believe you guys
It's like a dream, the final energy
Tomorrow, the third day, yesterday, the new year, the universe
If we stand on the ground, the stars in the mirror will turn into a circle
This is good, right?
There's no reason to say it's good!
The film studio Orion-za
The film studio Orion-za has been in the spotlight for a long time
There are memories of my childhood
When the movie was the king of entertainment
It was hot that summer day
Next time, Asakusa Cinema Paradise
Thank you!