Translated by 方 Hou.
I look up at the setting sun floating in the river.
I kick a pebble and it flies to my shoes.
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I used to go to.
I was laughed at for being a kid.
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere,
I have to be a patsushika and have a bad temper.
The cityscape that never changes is strangely kind.
From the waterfront of a tangle hat
to the taishakuten,
the sunset falls.
Tomorrow will end like this.
I'm happy that I won't have to be a patsushika again.
I realized it.
I'm stupid.
My secret secretion is...
I did it!
You finally did it?
Oh, my days went by so quickly.
Look.
In the 15th century,
it was Portugal's Caracas Atlantika that played its role in the Western world.
It's amazing.
That's amazing.
All of this is made of paper, right?
Yes.
Everything except the rope is made of paper.
It's the ultimate paper craft.
Wow!
Are there any castles sold here?
In the case of a ship, the whole curve is important.
It's much more difficult than castles.
I made up parts and added details to the parts that weren't enough.
Seriously, you should have worked hard for this.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Oh, Ryo.
Did you bring the documents to the office?
Documents?
What are you talking about?
The chief asked me to deliver them to the office yesterday.
He said they were important documents, so he asked me to deliver them to the office immediately.
Come to think of it, that happened, too.
What?
No way!
Come on, stop it.
Where did you leave them?
I think they were on the desk.
No way!
Where did you leave them?
Why is there a chief's hanger here?
This is a document, isn't it?
Oh, here and here.
Come to think of it, when I was making this, I ran out of paper.
I used the paper that was close to me.
What are you going to do, Ryo?
You should apologize first.
You'll be in trouble someday.
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a way to get you in trouble.
Huh?
Oh, Chief.
Good morning.
By the way, did you call me?
What?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, I see.
I hope you didn't.
Ryo!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Why don't you listen?
Huh?
Did they find him that day?
Well, no, I just say that I don't think so.
Don't try to hide this.
Go big!
If you're a detective, you should understand why so many they can't see.
Yes, I know.
And that's why I create the game for you.
No.
Yes, sir.
- It's nothing! - Show us!
- It's nothing! - I said it's nothing!
- Yes, it's nothing! - I said it's nothing!
- I said it's nothing! - Show us!
- Yes, I am! - Hello?
It's me. I told you not to call me here.
I'll call you back.
I remembered something. I'll leave the rest to you.
We managed to avoid the crisis.
Isn't the chief acting strange these days?
That's true. He seems to be in a daze.
He's probably on the phone somewhere.
He's in a daze. And the phone?
What's going on?
It's terrible. I thought it was just a TV show.
But the chief is also...
What's wrong, Ryo?
It's a fire.
Don't tell me He's thinking too much.
He's probably too serious.
The chief is very serious.
You know that, Ryo.
It's so weird!
If I was to watch him, he'd be so serious
he'd think I'm very serious.
He'd leave and go on a holiday with his kids,
...and only you and your wife would have been able to do it.
But then, I realized that a man who has lived a life of work...
...has no problem with his wife.
The hole in his heart is getting bigger and bigger.
And then, a young woman who happens to meet him...
...says something that makes him feel like he's in love for the first time.
And then, it's all over.
That chief is...
That's right!
Ryo!
Long time no see!
What? The chief is cheating?
I can't believe it.
It's just a dream.
There's no evidence.
But then, the other day...
...the chief was buying paper at a supermarket nearby.
I saw him doing it.
It's weird to think about it now.
Why would the chief be buying paper?
That's absolutely strange.
It's a secret word.
The chief has already made a secret word.
N-no way!
I can't believe it.
I don't want to believe it either.
Hm?
"I don't believe it."
Well, you were a bit early that night.
Oh, you're right.
You have a thought as to why I called you.
The phone from just now...
...it's definitely one of your lover's calls.
You showed up!
Seems like you're headed for the station.
Hey, don't get so carried away.
In a way, you're a guy.
You know I don't seem to have an understandable saying like "Man," or "Wife."
But our people...
You're disguising yourself as Beck, aren't you?
If you don't act like a lover, people will think you're an unnatural person.
Hey, you stupid! Stop it!
Hey!
Oh, no!
If I were a young man these days, I wouldn't be here in this place.
Don't you know what's embarrassing?
You're embarrassing me.
That was close.
That was close. Let's go, Maria.
You're so mean, Ryo!
Are we going straight home?
No, I don't know yet.
"I don't know where to go."
I guess he didn't take the train.
No.
If he wanted to go shopping, he should have gone to a store near the station.
Maybe he doesn't want his friend to see him.
That's more suspicious.
Ryo?
Did you call your lover's house?
They're the same people as before.
They're all so careless.
It's me. I'm going now.
You're going now?
To your lover's house?
No!
Ryo!
If you're Ryo, I'll...
Yes?
You?
You're right.
That's it.
Yeah.
I'll go now.
Ryo, it's you.
Oh, he's here.
I brought a present for you.
Oh, thank you!
This is where you're supposed to be.
Really?
-Light the candles. -Light the candles.
That's right.
I should buy some cakes.
Again?
You don't have to stay friends with me anymore,
but to clear our pay...
Geez, why are you guys doing this?
We gotta keep it out.
You could take your eyes off us a bit.
You were about to find out.
Yeah, I was about to find out.
We're in the mansion.
It looks like that's the mansion of Aijin.
Yeah, no doubt.
Where is the director?
There he is. On the fifth floor.
That's...
I've finally found the decisive evidence!
I can't forgive you for making that young woman your lover!
I can't forgive you!
What!?
No way...
The director really had a secret word?
You might not believe it, but it's true.
If the higher-ups find out about this,
what will happen to the director, Ohara?
He'll be banned from his own home.
And at worst, he'll be fired.
Fired?!
No matter how many times
you talk about this, I'm not sure.
You can just shut up and go.
If the media finds out about this,
the director will...
The wife can't stand this kind of life anymore,
and leaves the house.
Aijin can't stand the cold eyes of the world,
and disappears.
But...
The director who lost his position,
and his family,
will have a sad end.
Shut up!
Thank you, Dad!
Happy birthday!
I'm so glad.
Yeah!
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I can't do this.
Oh, my.
This is so bad.
This is awful.
This is horrible.
Maria,
was this really a girl's room?
It wasn't.
I couldn't see from here.
You doubt me?
Really? There must be proof.
You can't tell with such a small screen, right?
You can't trust it until you see it with your own eyes.
That's right.
Then you should check it with your own eyes.
I'll take you there.
So you went in here, right?
Yes.
It's been more than ten minutes since we left the station.
This is a perfect place for a bad omen.
It's not decided yet, is it?
I think it's this room.
This is...
I'll open it.
No, you can't open it by yourself.
That's right.
You said you wouldn't trust me unless you saw it with your own eyes, Roman.
Captain!
What?
Captain! What's going on?
What are you doing?
Well...
You're disturbing my search activities, aren't you?
I'm sorry!
He's wrong!
Hey, you, Ryo!
You're totally wrong!
Well, he'll go there.
What?
...
It's a za-
Not gonna happen!
What?
Ouch, ouch.
It's lock-down reflection, now.
Oh, Ryo.
What'll we do?
Ui, ui...
What are you doing here?
Um, I just happened to pass by here...
Happened?
This is the fifth floor.
What are you doing here, chief?
Uh, I...
Ah, I'm glad you're still here.
Ah!
It's the secret code to the chief's ID!
Huh?
What?
N-no way!
I believed you...
Dad!
If you're going out, you should take a bath!
Oh, everyone!
H-Hiromi-san!
What?
That's why I came to this mansion for Hideo-san's work.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Setsu has done a lot of work for me.
Oh, if you have a new game, please lend me one.
This is my friend,
Malko.
And this is Megumi-san and Hanako-chan, the only daughter.
Nice to meet you.
What?
You're not the chief's lover?
What do you mean, lover?
You're an idiot, so you should take a break!
Yeah, the chief's fault.
I came to this neighborhood, and you're hiding it from me.
That's right.
Why didn't you tell me right away?
Uh, that's...
Um...
You didn't want your father to be teased by everyone, did you?
You called him "grandpa".
Why would I call you "grandpa"?
I don't have to call him "grandpa".
I think he's a stubborn old man.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
I just retired last week.
I see.
Well, congratulations on that.
Congratulations.
So, boy or girl?
Boy.
Oh, really?
Congratulations.
Why didn't you tell me, chief?
Are you talking about a pet or something?
A grandchild.
What?
I'm talking about my grandchild!
Did you have a grandchild?
So cute!
You look like a doll.
You're Daisuke?
That's a nice name.
I got a first-year degree from Ohara.
You're a single mother, aren't you?
So you're going to Ohara, right?
I decided to keep Ohara's name.
What a coincidence.
You really look like the chief.
Do you think so?
Actually, the hospital chief told me that my eyes look similar to his.
But people often say that your mouth looks like Hideo's.
I'm not that kind of person.
Wait, let me see the picture.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't get near him less than a meter away.
Don't come near me.
It's bad if you get sick.
Don't call me that.
Who is it? What's your face?
You look like Hideo-san.
It's me, Ryotsu.
I think you look like a monkey.
A monkey?
You think my grandson is a monkey?
You're wrong.
I said that I look like a monkey.
A monkey?
Yes, you're right.
You're a noble man.
You're born to be a noble man.
Your future will be bright as a rose.
Really?
I thought you had a good face.
I don't think so.
Oh, you're right.
Hey, Hiromi.
Give me the sake you brought me the other day.
Yes, yes. I'll bring it right away.
I just said what I thought, but it's not good.
Go on, say it.
You did say you were a monkey, didn't you?
As expected of you, Senior.
You're good at deceiving people.
Your sake is really good.
Do you have any drinks?
Yes, I'm doing it right now.
Hey, Ryotsu.
You should be a little more patient.
Speaking of which, I saw Daisuke's hands and feet,
but he's really a good meat lover.
That's the muscle that makes you a top athlete.
Oh, really?
Hey, Hiromi.
Give me something delicious.
You brought some caviar the other day, right?
Yes, yes.
I got it.
This caviar is really good.
Hiromi, another bottle of sake.
Here you go.
Daisuke's face is handsome.
That's the best.
I see.
Ryo, it's about time.
Daisuke, you're the best!
Oh, my.
It's all done.
Well, we'll be going now.
Senior, let's go home.
What?
We're going home already.
We haven't eaten yet.
Ryotsu.
You're going to eat?
You're such a nag.
Speaking of which, Daisuke's eyes.
They look just like the chief's.
They look so smart.
Since we're here,
why don't we all go eat dinner?
Hiromi, call the sushi restaurant.
Seven servings of rice balls.
Okay.
Chief, is that okay?
What is?
From what I saw,
Daisuke is definitely a great man.
He'll be a great man.
To hold a meal like this
for his birthday,
is seven servings of rice balls
really enough?
The history might not have it yet!
Th-That's true.
Hiromi, the special dish is 10 servings...
No, no, 20 servings.
Besides, don't forget the sea urchin and salmon.
Yes, sir!
Hehehe.
The End
Oh, it was so much fun!
Everyone came here today.
Thank you very much.
We're very grateful for this.
I wish we could do this every day.
Yeah, we're in hell tomorrow.
Hell? What are you talking about?
You forgot?
The papers that turned into a half-bottom.
Half-bottom?
What's wrong, Ryozu?
You don't seem well.
N-no, it's nothing.
Here, drink, drink.
Today's a good day.
I'm really sorry.
Ryozu!
You bastard!
You turned those papers into half-bottoms!
It was a little mistake!
I don't care about the mistake.
You're just...
That's right! Daisuke's eyebrows!
It's exactly like the president's eyebrows!
He's a strong man,
and he'll become a manly man, just like the president!
Huh?
I-I see.
Don't lie to me!
I'm talking about the papers right now!
Oh, Daisuke's ears!
What a great ear!
He'll be blessed with good fortune in the future.
There's no doubt about it!
I'm sure he'll be a great rich man!
R-right...
I told you not to lie to me!
Oh, by the way,
Daisuke's nose!
It's wonderful!
I knew it...
When do you think the president will be in a bad mood?
When he's done with his praise.
Ryo...
No matter what you say,
Daisuke's eyes are sparkling,
and he'll become a star!
There's no doubt about it!
A star?
No, Daisuke's cute hand!
That's the golden hand that will take over the world!
Golden hand?
Daisuke's smooth hands!
Daisuke's hair!
Ryo!
Daisuke's cute forehead!
Hey!
Wait, Ryo!
Daisuke's,
cute teeth!
My teeth are still growing!
Hey!
Don't do this!
Daisuke's cheeks!
Daisuke's beard!
Daisuke's lips!
Daisuke's mouth!
Ryo's...
Chief!
Chief's precious Matsutake hayashi
has been robbed by a thief!
For Matsutake's sake,
no, for Daisuke and Hiromi's sake,
I'll protect this unscrupulous Ryo Tsukankichi,
Matsutake hayashi!
Next time on Matsutake Security Corps,
let's go!
Thanks for watching!
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait for me
The dazzling light of the future of the panorama
You understand, right? I'm sorry, wait for me
Translated by Releska