Time"
"A Little Time"
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and
try to look away.
"A Little Time"
Come to me,
if you're broke.
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
I'll get you a drink.
Look at the blue sky,
the white clouds.
I'll get along with you
somehow.
"A Little Time"
Come to me, you who don't have a home.
I don't have one, but don't worry.
Look, the red cloud is burning.
It'll be all right in the meantime.
I know, I know, I know.
If you know, be quiet and follow me.
Hurry up, Ryo.
I'll buy all the wire and buy it.
Take your time.
All the wire is a little over 100 yen.
I'm just wasting it.
So I'm trying to use it carefully at the end.
Yes, yes.
Is this the standard one cup noodle?
No, ramen and dado are hard to throw away.
Then, the first place in the cup ramen ranking.
What is this program?
It's Mr. Ranking.
It's quite popular.
The product that won first place will be sold out in no time.
The first place will be decided.
The cup ramen that I, Kimezo, will be the first to win is this.
Kusaya Natto Ramen Blue Cheese Flavor.
Now, please check it out for yourself.
Kusaya Natto Ramen Blue Cheese Flavor of Yottoko Food.
Kusaya Natto Ramen Blue Cheese Flavor.
Yes.
It looks delicious.
Doesn't it smell strange?
And the color of the soup is eerie.
It doesn't look good.
What are you talking about?
The first place in the ramen ranking.
It can't be bad.
Let's eat.
It's not good.
Can't you eat it?
I think it tastes terrible.
It was terrible.
I saw it in the first time. Why is that the first place?
What's wrong, Sakonji?
I was tricked.
Actually, I was doing the ranking of the beautiful girl figure at the Mister Ranking last week.
Mister Ranking, the first place is the first place news.
The beautiful girl figure is this.
The second place figure in the second half of the second movement.
What?
What? This kind of product came out?
I've been looking for it.
And today I finally got it.
It's a big package.
This is it!
Is this Saori?
It's like a worn-out Gorgon 13.
And it's big.
I thought it was a half size, but it was a half size.
This is not my Saori.
There is one victim of Mister Ranking here.
Reiko, is that ranking really accurate?
That's what Komachi and the others said.
It's them.
Komachi, Naogo, I have something to ask you about Mister Ranking.
Ryo, Tsukankichi.
What does Mister Ranking mean?
When I hear that name, I get very upset.
Did something happen?
Yes.
Are you going to give it to me?
Try it.
Ryo, Tsukankichi.
What's that? Are you a human?
It's a chocolate that was ranked first in the Mister Ranking a while ago.
I tried to get it.
You're the only one who can trust that ranking.
We were the ones who chose that ranking and were chosen.
That's right.
When the program started, it was a pretty reliable ranking.
But recently, it's been out of the list.
That's right.
I don't believe what the first-ranked Kimezo says.
The first-ranked Kimezo?
That's the father who ranked the show.
That's why.
If you have any complaints,
go to the first-ranked Kimezo.
Go!
I got it.
Here it is.
Let's go.
Okay.
Then, hello.
Sorry.
Be careful.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Excuse me.
I didn't expect such a miscalculated lecture to come.
What's miscalculated?
I'm just saying that something bad is bad.
Do you know when the first time cola was imported?
Cola?
Many Japanese people said,
"It tastes weird. It's not something humans drink."
However, what about now?
Now, it's loved by most Japanese people.
What?
I want to say that Kusaya Natto Ramen is also like that.
My ranking is also looking to the future.
Excuse me, but your sense of taste is quite old.
Then, how about the figure that Sakonji bought?
This is...
This is not a matter of sense.
It's just a strange face.
Stop it.
You happened to get a defective item, right?
For your own good.
I thought so, too.
I bought 10 of them.
Where is this Saori?
You're unlucky.
You got a defective item.
Hey, are you still a Tomogarugi?
Oh, it's time to go.
I have an appointment with someone.
I'm sorry, but please take it.
See you later.
He's a little annoying.
Hey, Yotsu.
That guy.
Huh?
Yes, he's certainly a good teacher.
That guy?
That guy from before...
With this, you can be next week's rank.
I'm sure that our products will come to the top.
How do you know that?
Ah...
What, you?
Would you like to hear the details?
Yes.
What?
What, a defective item?
It seems that it was done on a daily basis that the Mr. Rank was ranked in the top by giving the defective item to the first place.
So that's why strange products came to the top.
I didn't know you were here.
You really let me eat such a bad chocolate.
I don't make chocolate.
Please.
I wonder if the people in the TV station are not.
I don't think I know for sure.
It's a trust problem.
Of course it will be announced.
It's not just interesting to just announce it.
Okay, this is decided up to third place.
The rest is first and second place.
Hmm.
The hungry master has 2 million.
The bad master has 1.5 million.
Gold Nobe.
I'm wondering which one to choose.
Let's put the cash priority here.
Okay, done.
Today's ranking is like this.
Yeah.
Teacher Ichi, it's time.
15 seconds before the show.
Let's get excited today.
5, 4, 3.
What?
Let's hide it here.
Mr. Ranking.
The man who decides all the rankings in the world.
That's me.
I decided first place.
Today's theme is this.
Japanese sake ranking.
Then, the Japanese sake ranking.
It's finally announced first place.
The first place is the Paraguri Shuzo's Seishu Baka Ichidai.
There's a glee in its softness.
It's the Japanese sake from the Japanese sake.
See you again at the next week's ranking.
All Ball.
There's a reason for that ranking.
Huh?
Don't fool around with that Seishu Baka Ichidai.
When are you going to be the one?
I'll give you a better ranking.
Wait a minute.
Ah!
It's happening.
Turn the camera around.
It's wrong to rank without drinking a single drop.
I'm drinking a bottle of sake all my life.
I'm drinking like I'm drinking juice.
Interesting.
This is the end of the show.
Then, let's have this person rank.
What?
I have to do that.
Hmm.
That's all.
Well then.
This is my ranking.
Oh!
This is a completely different result from Mr. Ranking.
Ah!
This is weirder.
I just lined them up as it were.
If you have a problem with this result,
you should ask the customers to drink it and decide which is the right one.
They are amateurs.
What do amateurs know?
Most of them are amateurs.
But, they don't drink that much.
Don't worry.
Now, Gonji.
Yes!
We have prepared a lot of alcohol.
Now, everyone.
Drink it and check it yourself.
This is the alcohol that ranked first?
This is good.
This is the alcohol that ranked first.
Now, everyone.
Please raise your cards which you think is the right one.
Here you go.
What?
This is a conspiracy.
They are trying to trick me.
It's your fault.
Look at that.
Mr. Ranking 200 million.
Bad backlog is 155 million.
I've Trying to hide a hidden camera in your dressing room.
Why do you always feel like
a big drunk?
You should prioritize the source money.
He's right.
It means that.
We have made the ranking according to
the amount that Mr. Ranking received.
On the other hand,
they demasiado us.
Anyway,
Go with Mr. Ranking.
There are 2 Mr. Ranking now.
Let's run away!
Ahahaha!
See? Justice always wins!
What? You want me to replace Mr. Ranking?
Yes, the last day's broadcast was very popular.
I would like Mr. Ranking to replace Mr. Ranking.
Hmm, it's not a bad story.
I want to give a good response to the program.
Until now, Mr. Ichi has been deceived and leaked false information.
Well, I don't want you to be deceived anymore.
Really?
However, the characters...
No, no, I won't allow the TV show to end.
B-B-chan...
W-W-Wait a minute.
These are the victims who were deceived by such a poor evaluation.
It's very problematic.
That's right. Please help us somehow.
The one who appeared on their show is a person to help.
A person to help.
Then, I'll ask that person.
I won't accept it.
Really?
But, no pay.
What?
No way!
I'm saving people.
I can't get paid by saving people.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ryozu, do it well.
Yes.
Ryozu Daioh's Ranking King!
Ranking King Ryozu Kankichi Daioh.
The man who will decide all the rankings in the world,
has arrived in Japan in the 21st century.
I am the ranking king of justice!
Damn it.
I'm wearing this kind of outfit, but I can't get paid.
The theme of the first episode to be commemorated is Retort Curry.
Retort Curry.
Let's decide.
Ranking King.
Eat as much as you can.
Ryozu Daioh is eating a lot.
I ate it.
He ate 10 curry in no time.
Not yet.
My motto is to eat everything and rank.
Bring more and more.
Now, let's announce.
This is the curry ranking I set.
I see.
I checked everything under me. I checked everything under me.
I will accept any complaints.
I see.
Ryozu was wonderful!
So, about next week's ranking,
I'll be eating in the middle of the week.
Why?
It's the most familiar to the viewers.
I see.
pasarimo bread ranking.
量飲料水ランキング
Convenience store dessert ranking
Daioh is ranking king!
Tonight, theщ.
Let's go to the station.
You're so popular on your show, Senpai.
I heard that the products that Ryo-chan ranked first are very popular.
Oh, is that so?
Ryo-san, aren't you happy?
Of course I'm happy.
Even if the show is popular, I can't get a single one.
Oh, I see.
It's as much as my manju.
I'm tired of eating it.
Then, how about a bath bomb this time?
A bath bomb?
What kind of bath bombs do you think we should use
to make manju?
Hmm...
Well, it's good to take a bath once in a while.
Hehehe...
Um, is that Mr. Ryo-san?
Yeah, that's right.
Please take a look.
What? Manju again?
Please refresh the inside.
Huh?
I can't help it.
I don't need to get so many manju.
Huh?
Whoa!
No!
Manju is not boring no matter how much I eat.
After all, it's this.
It's an honor to be pleased.
By the way, who are you?
Which manufacturer are you from?
Curry?
Or is it bread?
It's a bath bomb.
A bath bomb?
That's scheduled to be recorded next week.
Oh!
Then this is not an orei, but a Wairo.
No, no, no, no.
I can't take this kind of thing.
I have absolute confidence in my own product.
If you evaluate it correctly,
I'm sure we'll be in first place.
Is that so?
Please be assured and take it.
If you win first place on the show,
sales will be greatly increased.
Then I will give you an orei as soon as possible.
So, it's a gift of thanks.
A gift of thanks?
If you say you don't need it,
I'll take it home.
No, no, no.
I'm not a person who refuses thanks.
I'll take it gratefully.
Thank you.
By the way, our product is
Soda Splash Black.
I got it.
It's Soda Splash Black.
Well, the last bath bomb is
Soda Splash Black.
This is it.
It's so wet and disgusting.
Oh, this is wonderful.
Wonderful.
A black bath bath that changes the image of a bath.
The refreshing touch of carbonic acid.
I'll take it without any doubt.
This is it!
Soda Splash Black under the sleeve.
Thank you.
But, I never knew that it was the best.
I just said that good things are good.
It was actually a revolutionary bath bomb.
From now on, it may become the standard of bath bombs.
Moreover, what will be the ranking next week?
What will happen to the fridge?
The fridge?
Hello, it's a complete electrician.
I'm Ranking King Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
Actually, I'll be picking up the fridge next week.
That's all I have to say.
By the way, do you know what my future is?
Well, think about it.
Um, Ryo-tsu-sensei.
Ryo-tsu-sensei.
Sensei!
Oh, the power of electricity.
Power of electricity?
Yes.
I'm the owner of the new fridge, Sabui-kun.
I've brought you some snacks as a gift.
Oh, thank you.
Huh?
A small-sized sandwich?
You're a good actor.
Now I know why small-sized sandwiches are my favorite.
That's because the road to evil is a snake.
This year is the year of the snake.
The second is the year of the tiger.
Please take care of Sabui-kun.
Leave it to me!
Leave it to me, Sabui-kun.
The first place this week is Sabui-kun, the power of electricity.
That's...
Justice will prevail!
If you keep going like this, you'll make a lot of money.
Hey, Ryo-tsu, Kankichi.
What's wrong, you two?
I bought the bath bomb that this primitive man recommended the other day.
Then...
What's with that Soda Splash Black?
It just feels bad.
That's all.
I don't get it.
What?
When the cola came to Japan, 90% of the Japanese were saying it was bad.
What about that?
There's no one who says that right now.
That's a different story, isn't it?
Um...
Hmm?
Ryo-tsu, it's from the second generation tea.
Oh, that story is over there.
Yes.
The story is not over yet.
I'll ask you later.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Oh, Ryo-chan.
Recently, there are many customers like that.
To Ryo-chan?
They seem to have brought something.
This is...
This is perhaps...
Hmm...
The second generation tea and the Soda Splash Black are 2 million yen.
But this place is the best Soda Splash Black.
Because the person in charge is a beautiful woman.
Ryo-tsu, it's time.
Oh, I'm going now.
All right.
I'll be right back.
Senpai.
Huh?
Oh, Nakagawa.
Senpai, the story is...
It's before the real show.
I'll tell you later.
It's about the file you are receiving.
What is it about?
I don't have a single file.
But...
I don't say that often.
Ryo-tsu.
Oh, well.
I'm the ranking king of justice.
Well, well.
Oh, yes, yes.
After all it was great to convince him.
Ryo-tsu Daioh's Ranking King!
The man who can decide the rankings of all things in the world came to 21st century Japan.
I am the ranking king of justice!
Well, today's theme is Japanese tea.
Wait.
What?
What are you doing?
Listen to this.
Senpai.
Oh, Nakagawa.
What?
What is Kei-chan talking about?
It's the conversation with Senpai.
It's about the Wairo that Senpai gave me.
Wairo?
It's Ryotsu.
I thought he would definitely show his tail one day, so I was watching him in secret.
Who are you?
It's me.
That's right.
I'm the number one Kimezo who was fired from this show once.
What do you want from me?
Wait.
It's funny.
Let's continue.
What?
I'll show you something funny.
Two cups of green tea and a big cup of tea cost 2 million yen.
But this is a big cup of tea.
The person in charge was a beautiful woman.
In the end, you're a pretty woman.
You're doing the same thing as me.
No.
This is a mistake.
It's a conspiracy.
It's a fraud.
Senpai.
Oh.
Ryo-chan.
Don't look.
Stop it.
Now it's all over.
And I'm a man.
You're doing this all for your own good!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's my show.
You don't have to bring it up.
You're my host.
You're the host.
Unstable Fast.
Don't look.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Useless.
Unstable Fast.
I'm on the list of fireworks!
What?!
Hey, Reiko!
This ranking magazine is very popular right now.
Well, it's not going to work for me.
But you can trust this magazine, right?
Because Ryo Tsukankichi is the top of the list of unreliable men!
Damn it! I hate rankings so much!
If this must end now,
it's not a big deal.
See you later.
I was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and see
I'll see that kid
I'll see everyone
There is a wall there
There must be money
Everyone come to the city of parents
Thank you!
What, the magic nightclub?
Hey! Wate is a magical nightclub.
What kind of magic can you do?
It doubles the money included.
I did it! Now has big money!
Why do I only have 5 yen at times like this!
Next time,
Magic nightclub
I'm looking forward to working with you!