Let's Make A Rock
♪ The setting sun revealed on the grey river ♪
♪ Gave people hope ♪
♪ Theyiteshi wo kettara ♪
♪ Flew up into the sea ♪
♪ In order to go to that faraway land ♪
I wonder if I'm going back
He laughed and said he was still crying
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
Katsushika is a good place
The cityscape that never changes even if you have a sore throat
It's so kind
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
To Taishakuten
The sun is setting
Tomorrow will end like this
Katsushika and Shiba are happy again
I'm going to lose it
Hato Pop!
The big city, Tokyo
People, people, people are overflowing
The peace and safety of this city
Day and night, there are hard men who keep protecting it
There is also a man who takes care of it
This is what voltage detective work
Super Policeman
It's Kajipan,还帕大侠
Kajipan is an elite detective
The King of the Land.
The Moon Dekka and Venus Dekka.
They transform according to the circumstances, and fly through the moon with night-time fighters.
The King of the Sky.
The Dolphin Dekka, or the Sea Dosaemon.
He became a manga artist and a painter after becoming a teacher of the Dolphin Dekka.
The King of the Sea.
And this man is the one who takes care of the special police officers.
It's the Chonbange Dekka!
Yeah!
I'm glad you came.
There's no one else who can do it.
I want to scout a new recruit for the special police officers.
That's why I want to have one person who will be considered as a person with experience.
A person who will be considered as a person...
A person who can endure a hard job as a special police officer...
There's only one person who can do it.
Who is it?
The King of the Sky.
What?
Why are you all going to the pervert police officers?
He's a special police officer!
I'll beat you to death!
The King of the Sky.
Ouch!
Please stop!
I know, I know!
As long as you understand, it's fine.
Ouch!
But I don't have any special skills like you guys and I don't have any partners!
Don't worry.
I have something I got from the boss.
A... a pigeon?
Why are you calling me a pigeon?
It's not just a pigeon.
My special police officers have trained me with all their passion.
It's called the "Super Elite Bat".
It's a great thing!
But even though you're smart, you're not a pigeon.
You'll get a punishment again!
W... w... w... w... wait!
I've already done a lot of punishment!
You don't know anything!
Look at this.
What?
This time, there's a godly play.
I can't stand it.
A godly play contains a water candy.
Eat it.
Even if you tell me to eat it, I've seen it clearly from there.
It was the First World War.
With the German army, the French army settled in the Verdun Fortress.
The radio was destroyed and the underground phone line was cut off due to the bombing.
The German army's circle of friends was getting smaller and smaller, and everyone was about to give up.
And at that moment,
Colonel Lunard sent the first wave of the military bat to the radio.
Soon, the French support team that received the message from the pigeon arrived.
The first wave of pigeons saved the stage.
It's an impressive story no matter how many times I hear it.
Oh, pigeons are great.
Indeed.
That's right.
Pigeons are great.
Go pirate.
But, they don't move.
No, they don't move.
I've made the first wave of pigeons.
What?
I lost.
Go, Ryotsu. From today, you'll be a Hato Poppo Deka.
H-Hato Poppo Deka?
No! I don't want that!
Ujou, do something about it!
You're so annoying!
You're giving up, Ryotsu?
You're so cold!
Are you abandoning your cute subordinates?
You're not cute.
You're a demon!
Oh, no, that's not it.
Please, please.
I don't care.
Hey, what are you doing?
Everyone, back off!
I'm not ready yet!
Ujou, I hate you! I curse you!
Don't say anything.
Now I have hope in the future!
No! Don't leave me!
Reiko, Sakagawa, do something!
I don't want to be part of the pervert!
I'm so glad, Ryo-chan!
Senpai, do your best!
Damn it! Are you still friends?
I hate you!
This is a very honorable thing to do.
And if you were to be assigned to a special police department,
your pay would double now.
No!
What are you talking about?
What? Is that true?
It's hard work, but you get special treatment.
I can't even afford a costume.
I can't afford a costume.
We only need one costume.
When a pigeon is big,
you get food from pigeons.
A pigeon needs to consider itself younger.
I just want to go.
I haven't seen you in a while.
You seem to be tricked.
You haven't seen me in a while.
You haven't seen me in a fucking long time.
What's up?
How did you get here?
It might be nice to go on patrol, but this school will be a sight for everyone.
Ouch! What are you doing?
What the hell? What is it, a diet?
No! I haven't been granted one single yen, I'm a detective.
That's not the food I ever asked you for!
I'm not so sweet, I'm gonna leave my money alone and make enough for my own meals...
Hey, where are you going?
What is it?
A 100 yen coin?
I see. So they're training you to pick up and collect the dropped items.
Alright, pick up more!
If you do, I'll buy you some beans!
*Claps*
That's how rehabilitation became a human bond.
We used to be warm, friendly friends.
前輩が特殊刑事課に配属になって、もう1週間になりますね。
It sounds like его is getting better at being a darmon.
...It sounds like его is getting better at being a darmon.
Right, Ryo-chan?
I'm really peaceful for the past week.
I can't believe it!
Come to think of it, Ryo-chan will be working hard after he's gone.
You're right.
Watch me.
If you think I'm going to stay quiet, you're wrong.
Then I'll go patrol.
Go, Dengemon!
Stay close to Chief and search for the secret.
It seems that the moon is back to me after the dead man disappeared.
Here's a $5 coin drop.
Good.
Hmm...
That's good.
Yes, this is Ohara.
I'm Ryozuka.
Ryozuka?
You're already sleeping?
I won't listen to your crying.
No, chief.
I won't let you disturb the chief's ears.
Then what? I'm busy.
Chief, I thought you delivered 500 yen to the factory.
What?
Did you get your pants sewn properly?
What are you talking about?
You can't fool me.
I know everything.
The chief is also worried about something.
I can't believe it.
Who is it?
This actress.
You have a photo book, right?
It's nude.
You bought it, right?
What if your wife sees it?
I'll buy it for you.
What will happen?
Ryozuka.
I got it.
What should I do?
Well, let's see a lot today.
But don't forget.
Wherever you go, my eyes are shining.
Ryozuka.
How did she do it?
Listen, I'll feed you more.
Then you guys go scout the pigeons there.
Got it?
Look at this.
Reiko Nakagawa and Reiko who saw me becoming a special detective
are also here.
I'll make an army of spies using the pigeons.
The End
So, did you get a call from the head of the company?
Did you get a call from Ryozu?
Ryo, my client knows who you are.
He even knows about the project we're starting.
That's so weird.
You're the one who's the bad guy.
Oh, so you got a call from Dengemon.
The exit is a problem?
It seems he's complaining about me.
What's going on?
Yes, this is the exit.
It seems he's complaining about me.
Senpai!
What?
He's not nearby.
Even if he's far away, I can tell him everything.
Senpai!
Ryo, come out. Let's fight.
Let's fight?
No. We're going to show them the true nature of your lives.
Hey, Ryo.
Ryo!
Ryo...
What's going on?
Why are there so many pigeons?
It's so weird.
That's right. It seems that the original man, Ryotsu Kankichi, became the Hato Popo Dekka.
If that's true, he'll be a real nuisance to everyone!
What are you doing, you Sekuhara Hato?!
What is this flock of Hato?
It's Senpai's doing.
What?!
Then, is Ryotsu using Hato to spy on us?
That's what I think.
The subordinates are very familiar with their secret, and when I noticed, Hato was always with them.
Come to think of it, Hato used to follow my Ferrari.
That guy Ryotsu became the Hato Popo Dekka, that's a good thing!
Shhh!
Mr. Chief.
Yes?
If you're saying something bad about Ryo-chan,
you'll get your revenge soon.
It's increased a lot.
It's at least 40%.
What? You want more?
Don't be so generous.
You won't make a fool out of the food.
You're always making small profits, aren't you?
If you have any complaints, make them make more!
If you don't leave now, think about it.
If you go out there, you won't be able to buy my food.
That's why I'm here.
What?
You're being very generous.
Just because you're a fan of your brand doesn't mean you'll go to the supermarket.
You always say that.
By the way, what foods do you like?
I can have that.
Yes, it is.
I'm a fan of your porridge.
Do you have any information? Tell me!
I got it! Let's increase the amount of food!
I'll make Hokkaido's best beef beans!
What?
Yamada Nishiki is the best?
Alright! Let's go with the third Yamada Nishiki!
Now, Yamada Nishiki has come from the outside!
King Ome-guro-san won't grow together!
Yamada Nishiki! Yamada Nishiki is coming!
Yamada Nishiki is the best!
I did it!
I got 300,000 yen!
I earned a million yen with just 3 days!
It's good to see it again and again!
This touch...
This feeling...
Hehehe...
I won't let this million yen be used for a big game!
Thief!
What?
Give it back!
What's wrong? What did you take?
There's a 100 million yen cash in that case!
What? 100 million yen?
Why did you have such a large amount of money?
I only trust cash transactions!
If you catch me, I'll pay you 10%!
Of course, cash!
I won't take it!
Thank you!
100 million yen!
I got it!
Leave it to me!
Go, Ten'emon!
We're going to chase him wherever he goes!
I don't think I'll be able to get away from this Hatsupoppoteka!
Oh, no!
He has become like that before I know it!
Ouch! Ouch! What... what...
Dammit!
You're one persistent bastard!
I won't let you get away with this!
Huh?
Oh, come now!
Why are you following me?
Shit! They're afraid of me!
What are you doing?
Lady Hato Poppo
It seems to be ok
We're screwed!
Earth has an ocean
The sky is the moon
And the sea is protected by the Dolphin
Lady Hato Poppo
You protect the land and the air
Let's go!
Dengue Man! Hey, Dengue Man!
Gather your friends! It's urgent!
Hey, here, here!
I'll do anything for 100 million yen!
This is comfortable!
My 100 million! No, my stolen 100 million yen! Give it back!
Don't think you can get away with it!
What the hell is that?
Go!
Let's go!
Please be careful of Line 3. The express train will pass through.
Huh?
Wait!
You're so persistent!
You bastard!
Hey, I thought you were going to die.
Wait, wait, wait!
How far are you going to chase me?
Give me back my 100 million yen!
Come closer!
Don't be so slow!
More, more!
I won't let you run away!
No matter how close you get, this is the top of the sky!
You can't do anything else!
Where are you going?
You're a man who doesn't care about the danger of using the line of money!
Don't touch me!
Get off! I'm on my own!
Stop!
Hurry up and give me that bag!
Thief!
Who's the thief?
Hey!
My 100 million yen!
Take it!
I'll pay for your 100 million yen!
Give it back!
Daaymon!
Shit! My 100 million yen!
Do something, Daaymon!
Good!
Give it back to me!
My 100 million yen!
Cut the crap!
If you find it, I'll make you a yakitori!
Remember that!
A pigeon that buys food.
The pigeon appears.
The money this pigeon is using is a million yen.
I can't believe I'm being watched by a pigeon.
Popo, my little pigeon.
Do you want some beans?
Let's go eat something good.
I failed this time.
I had a good idea of a pigeon.
Let's hope for the next time.
Yes.
See you in the next special detective series.
Excuse me, excuse me.
You're so noisy.
Your name?
Is your name Sentaro Sumima?
That's the name.
You're just bothering people.
Next time, "Fear! God is a Long-Long Friend!"
See you.
Next time, "I Don't Know Where He's Going!"
That's my name.
Good game.
Next time, "I Don't Know Where He's Going!"
♪ Stop and move! ♪
♪ Fly away! ♪
♪ More than anything else, it's full of power ♩
♪ Everyone gather here ♩
♪ It's the final energy like a dream ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday ♩
♪ Draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ The magicly shining star will change the world ♩
♪ Isn't this good? ♪
♪ Isn't this good? It's no good, right? ♪