English Translation by
I glanced at the sunset floating in the prairie
I started dancing to my love's song
♪ Myou ni yasashii yo ♪
♪ Tongari boushi no shusuito kara ♪
♪ Kaishakuten e to yuhi ga ochiru ♪
♪ Ashita mou boushite owaru n da ne ♪
♪ Katsushika shiba mata shiawase datte ♪
♪ Makushite ki ga tsuita baka na ore dakara ♪
Uncensored! Delivering!
♪ Tabin yukeba surugano kuni ni ♪
♪ chano kaori to kura ♪
♪ Na, kekko ii tokoro darou? ♪
♪ Konaido mi ♪
♪ Kanae mitsuketa anaba nanda ♪
♪ Eeei ♪
♪ Demo ii n desuka? ♪
♪ Shigoto sabotte konna tokoma de kichatte ♪
♪ Ningen toki ni wa rifreshu ga hisuyou da ♪
♪ Koushite nonbiri onsen ni haitteru no mo ♪
♪ Rifreshu shite yoi shigoto wo suru tame na no da ♪
♪ Jya, sou nandesuka ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, washi da ♪
♪ Ya, ohayou, Ryo-tsuku ♪
♪ Eh? Kono koe? ♪
♪ salausamu! ♪
♪
Gokuro san.
There's four cars.
I've driven them all.
The police are worth the work.
I'm literally not.
I've got a job for a few days.
I got a job forWatchdog.
That's because we came to the edge of the district.
You're going to Honda's castle, right?
You should be able to come back soon.
That Honda's motorcycle broke down.
I'll be back as soon as the repairs are finished.
I see.
That's right.
Come back right now!
Those two are going out together.
I don't think they're patrolling properly.
What?
What's wrong, senpai?
The chief found out.
I'll be back in Tokyo soon.
Hurry up!
Hey, hey, hey, senpai!
If you don't hurry up, I'll leave you.
The boss of the company.
All right, go, Honda.
But you have to wear your clothes first.
I'll go first.
You will stop at the right.
Yes, sir.
Hey, don't jump out of the car so suddenly!
Mr. Omawari.
Something terrible has happened.
Come with me.
We're in a hurry.
You're going to meet someone else.
I was in the field, and there was something terrible.
Tomorrow's newspaper is definitely not the same.
You're right about the newspaper.
There's no mistake in the newspaper?
Wait a minute.
Mr. Ryotsu, I heard that there's a rumor about Tokugawa's "Maizou-kin" around here.
What? Maizou-kin?
If you do it right, you might get a few hundred percent.
Hey, give me a quick tour!
Over there?
Move, move, move!
It's the police!
Nobody move!
Hey, move over there!
So, what about the "Maizou-kin"?
What do you think, Senpai?
No!
Th-th-that's...
It's a pretty strange box.
Is there a small chest in here?
What? What's wrong with you guys?
But, Senpai...
It looks like a bomb.
What?
Huh?
Hm...
A b-b-b-bomb!
That's Tokugawa's "Mai-zou-kin"!
Nobody said it was a "Mai-zou-kin"!
That's a bomb from the war, isn't it?
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go!
I thought you were going over there?
What did you just say?
You came all the way over here and you're still not moving...?
I'll take this!
And you!
We won't let you get away with this.
No!
Don't tell me you're not going to do anything?
I know, I know. I'll do something about it.
Yes, this is the station.
You want me to do it?
That voice is...
Shut up! Don't make a loud voice.
The chief is still here, right?
I'm so tired.
I should come back soon.
I'm in trouble.
I found a bomb.
Wow, it's a bomb!
Wow? A bomb?
Why are you so excited, old man?
Yes, it's a bomb!
I'm in trouble.
I stole a single one that I bought for 500,000 yen.
Old man, I need a note.
Yes, sir.
Um...
I bought one for 500,000 yen.
You bought one for 500,000 yen?
What do you mean?
Are you saying you're going to buy a bomb for 500,000 yen?
I'm drinking soda at the cafe.
Soda.
Soda? Hey!
What's wrong, old man?
The priest said he'd buy a bomb for 500,000 yen.
What? No way!
He really said that.
Ask him yourself.
Hello, priest?
Priest?
Do you really buy bombs?
I'm an amateur.
I especially love cakes.
You love cakes.
He says he loves weapons.
There's no doubt about that.
But I didn't see a man interested in that.
Wait a minute.
His appearance, shape, glasses and weight.
He's not clear about his personality.
He's a real maniac.
Besides, it's suspicious that he bought a house away from others.
Is he hiding his dangerous hobby from the world?
Hehehe.
I like bombs.
I know what he's up to.
He's a military man with a lot of money.
Catch him!
He's a bomb maniac!
All right, I sold it.
Get the cash and wait.
No way.
Hello, Ryo?
He's gone.
What on earth happened?
Well, when I contacted the headquarters,
I learned that a bomb was still buried in this area.
So I want you all to cooperate with that investigation.
So you're going to do that with the police, aren't you?
It's your place here.
It's dangerous for me to take it out myself.
It's only natural for humans to be able to see it.
But...
It's dangerous, isn't it?
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
Budoki-san, stop it!
He's a better person than Fuhatsu-dan.
How's that? Did you find it?
No.
I don't have it.
I've searched for it so far, and only found two.
Two.
Two for a million yen.
That's good.
Alright, Honda! Carry this!
What? Us?
Of course!
As a police officer, it's a natural duty.
Did you forget?
This guy can buy a whole 500,000 yen.
But...
Mr. Omawari!
Are you sure you want this?
It's a good idea!
Put it on the whiteboard!
Pack it up.
It's done!
Let's go!
Let's stop it. It's dangerous.
Put it on the whiteboard!
If you hold the handle, the weak bugs will fly away.
What's wrong?
I'm too anxious, I can't be very strong.
Don't worry.
It hasn't exploded in over 50 years.
It's not like it's going to explode now.
Besides, I'll be with you when I die.
Sen... Senpai...
It seems to be okay.
Senpai, I told you we'd be together when we die!
Sorry, sorry.
My body moved as a result of the reflection.
STAY ALIVE
Now I understand.
Then everything will be OK.
All I have to do is drive carefully so your body won't get stimulated.
You love me, right?
Uogawa!
You and I were destined to be together in hell.
You know about that, right?
I do understand.
I guess you're a little identified.
No way...
You're not?
I was driving as instructed.
Shut up!
I was looking for a way back because you don't like to drive at high speeds.
But I can't pull a rear car with two people and load a bomb, so I can't go to high speed.
I'll be stopped at the toll station.
You can ring the siren and get through without telling me.
It's what you always do.
That's ridiculous.
The handlebar suddenly got lighter.
Is the road surface better?
I don't think so.
It's not like that.
The rear car is off!
What?
You want to get away?
Two people and a million yen!
I did it! I caught up!
Damn it! If you hit me, it's over!
Senpai, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Senpai, you're really going to carry it like this?
The rear car is gone. I can't do anything about it.
But I'm going to explode if I fall down.
You have to fall down.
Whoa!
What? Honda? Where are you?
Senpai!
Senpai! Help me!
What's that bird doing here?
Help me, please!
Is this really Japan?
Stop it! You're going to blow up!
I see...
Senpai!
Honda!
Wait for me!
I have to run away!
If I'm dropped like this, I'll be in trouble!
Honda! Don't let the bomb go!
It's 500,000 yen each!
I'm not kidding! Life is more important!
If I get paid, I'll give you 50%!
No, 50%!
Why is it tied so tightly?
No!
It's out again!
Stop it!
It's a movie!
500,000 yen!
Dad, Mom, Grandpa, Grandma, I'm sorry!
And my daughter, Nana!
Please forgive me!
500,000 yen!
I can't help you!
Stop!
This isn't good!
I made it!
Don't run away!
Please do something, Senpai!
I'm telling you now!
Gas cut...
What?
A tunnel!
Oh, no!
I'm almost at my limit!
I was saved by a horrible truck...
Wow...
Your life has shortened by 100 years...
It's not that bad!
Let's get everyone to the city!
But if you carry this around the place...
It's gonna be a big mess!
You can't work that well, too!
What's he going to do, anyway?
I need to find something...
Oh!
This is it!
How's that? It's a giant Kokeshi!
It's not going to be suspicious, right?
I-Is that so...
What the heck.
I have to wait for more than an hour until the next train arrives...
I'm just a local line thief!
Let's take a break somewhere.
That's right.
I thought there was no coffee shop in front of the station...
Well, it can't be helped.
It can't be helped.
Hey, isn't this one too?
What? What?
Let's take it with us, Peccha.
What? It's pretty heavy, isn't it?
It's because there's so much stuff in it, Peccha.
Ugh, I can't. I've finally fallen asleep.
Ah! It's gone!
What's wrong, senpai?
It's gone! Gone! Gone! Gone!
What's gone, senpai?
The instant bullet has disappeared!
Damn it! Where is it?
Two bullets and a million yen!
You!
Don't you know the instant bullet over there?
Instant bullet, Peccha?
Senpai, it looks like a Kokeshi now.
Oh, I see.
Hey, don't you know the Kokeshi over there?
If you hide it, it won't be useful!
If it's Kokeshi, it's over there in the Kokeshi Temple, Peccha.
It's the Kokeshi Temple.
Today is the day of Kokeshi Kuyo, so there should be a lot of them, Peccha.
Huh?
Senpai, wait for me!
Go! Go! Go!
Hahahaha!
Wait, where are you going?
You, heddle!
Where's this thing?
Kokeshi Kuyo...
What is this?
It's already burned.
If it's burned, there's no way to live.
Find it. It should be somewhere.
Even if you say so...
Ah!
It's there! Stop!
One million yen!
It's gone!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Ah, ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Water, water!
Water!
Senpai, are you okay?
A- apparently.
Hope you're safe now.
Now you just have to get on the train.
But I'm embarrassed in this dress.
Hang on.
This is the best way to protect your self from suspicion.
I feel sorry for you.
A poison of the forest.
I guess the bride ran away.
What a face.
He's not going to get rid of it.
How many do we have?
Stop it! I'm still single!
Oh, he's Miko's father.
That's strange.
I heard that's how it is in the city.
Dori, what does the baby look like?
Don't look at me!
It's not bad.
Don't touch me!
Ouch!
Please forgive me!
I don't mind hearing the small wishes of an old man with short legs.
Is it okay if his short legs get even shorter?
Next is Ottai Daimae.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Don't push!
No!
Are you okay, Honda?
I'm not okay at all!
Senpai!
Help me!
What's wrong, Honda?
The bomb's gone!
What?!
It's a bomb!
No way!
It's a joke!
This is...
Move, move, you stupid!
Alright, alright, just like that, over here!
Move, you! You're all moving!
I told you to move!
Don't get in the way!
He's crashing!
It's an idea!
Was that real?
Go!
My balloon!
Sorry, kid. I was surprised.
It's dangerous to be in a place like this.
I'm sorry.
That guy was a good help.
Kamehameha! Kamehameha!
I'm finally here.
Get it right, Honda.
You're one step away from the goal.
What do you mean, one step away?
Captain!
I heard that you two were in police uniform in the train,
and you caused a bomb.
I knew it.
You two.
Please calm down, Captain.
It's not my fault.
Don't worry.
I'll beat you up from the very start.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
You know my skills.
I won't bother the citizens.
But it's dangerous.
It's all messed up.
Don't let me down.
Get off me!
Don't wait!
Where's the entry ticket?
If you do this,
I'll have to hand this to the priest
and take the one million yen.
Yes, sir!
I'm home now.
Ryo!
I brought it.
I'll give you one million yen.
What's that, Ryo?
It's a coup.
I told you I'd buy one for 500,000 yen.
That's why I brought it here.
Is that real?
Of course it is.
Give me the money.
I didn't say that.
Don't lie!
I told you I bought it for 500,000 yen.
When Ryo called me?
It was windy then.
It's so thick!
It's so thick?
When the old man stole the pot.
The culprit was found soon after.
Yes, yes.
I took a note of the old man's story
and bought it for 500,000 yen.
It's so thick!
I bought it for 500,000 yen?
You must have heard it wrong.
What's going on?
I'm glad you're waiting at the exit.
Chief! This is...
Are you ready?
Please stop!
What if I hit your back?
I don't think you can say that.
The sword!
The double-edged sword!
Why didn't you say it was real?
I did.
The Chief didn't believe me.
It's because of your behavior.
He doesn't trust me, so he got this.
I can't believe it!
I don't want to go play with you anymore!
Hey!
Even if the police is going to arrest you,
if I die, this show is over!
Do you understand?
Hey, you responsible person! Come out!
Next time, "Ryotsu shitsu"!
What?
I won't forgive you!
Waf!
ununifukuchun
Tepe-tepe
To making up
Pyaa!
and stun
Sugoity
Power
without any doubt
Let's work on it!
With energy like in a dream
If you come with me
I'll capture tomorrow
and Jyuko
I'll draw up space
The turtle's star drew a circle
Isn't this good?
There's no reason to say it's good!