THE NIGHT AFTER
I gazed upon the rising sun
that floats among the rivers
I rolled up a stone
and reaped its fruits
I wonder if I should go to the gym I used to go to
I laughed at it as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somehow
There are only bad things and bad things
The cityscape that doesn't change even one bad day is strangely kind
From the waterfront of a cap
The sun goes down to the taishakuten
Tomorrow will be over already
I'm happy again with Katsushika and Shiba
I feel like I lost it
Because I'm a fool
The hair is long, my friend
Good morning, senpai
Ryo-chan, your hair is long
Huh?
Come to think of it, it didn't get cut for a while
I should have extended it and made it like Kim Taku
I'll do it like a real man.
Long hair and gangles.
It's hard to leave a woman alone.
That's a little...
I definitely don't want to!
Cut it for me!
Yeah, I got it.
What are you doing with those scissors?
You're the one who cut it.
I can go to the butcher's, right?
I don't have money.
I can't help it.
I'm sure there was a set of tools in the back, so I'll cut it for you.
Don't expect too much.
I'm not a professional.
It's enough if it's short.
But when I look at it again, Ryo-chan's hair is quite thick.
It looks like it's five times as thick as a normal person's hair.
I can use my head for my legs.
Reiko, I'll wash your body, too.
Don't say anything stupid.
Let's get started.
Oh, he's eating.
I can't get out.
What?
What's wrong?
I have to cut from the root.
He ate again.
What?
I'll borrow some with the barricade.
Oh, he ate again and took it away.
What?
Ouch!
This hurts!
Ow!
What's wrong with you?
Reiko, you're so...
I'm sorry. I tried my best, but...
You look good in it, Ryo.
Why don't you wear it for a while?
Don't joke around! It's your fault!
Hey, hey, hey, do something!
I got it, I got it!
I'll lend you money, so go to the chocolate shop!
Welcome.
Sorry, I'll lend you all the money, so please spare my life.
What are you misunderstanding? I'm just a customer.
Sorry, you were a customer?
Yes.
Sorry, but the manager is out now, so I'm from 5 o'clock.
You're here, aren't you?
Sorry, I'm still in the middle of training.
If you're ready, I'll be your training team.
Really?
Instead, it's free because it's a practice.
Yes!
I'll watch you!
Yay, I'm already paid for the training.
Yay!
I've been going to the market for three years.
I can finally use my brain!
Well, please come this way.
Hmm?
I told you I wanted to see you, but you're used to being treated like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm not scolding you.
I'm praising you.
I'm sorry.
You've been saying sorry for a while.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, well.
By the way, what's your name?
I'm sorry.
I told you to stop.
I'm just asking for your name.
I'm sorry.
So don't apologize.
It's your name.
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
But my name is Sumimasen Taro.
What?
Your name?
You're just giving me a random name.
I'm sorry.
Sentaro, I'm going to sleep.
Wake me up when you're done.
Yes, sir.
He's fast.
All right!
Cut!
The problem starts here.
I'm not good at shaving my beard.
Let's do it after training.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
I see.
I'm worried.
I'm sorry, but I have to do it to be a good employee.
It's not cut.
I see.
This person has a thicker skin than a normal person.
If this is the case, I'll do my best.
My eyebrows!
What's wrong? Are you done?
I'm sorry, I'm not done yet.
I see.
I have to trick him somehow.
Was it this kind of eyebrow?
No, it's not.
This is also not.
It's completely different.
Not like this.
What is it?
That's right!
It was thickly connected.
I feel like it's still different, but it's okay.
Yes, it's over.
I see.
Please come again.
Why are you in a hurry?
If the master finds out, he'll get angry.
I see.
Well then.
Thank you very much.
Yeah!
It's refreshing.
Oh!
Hey, Pramoya!
Ryo?
I went to see you.
You're a man now, aren't you?
Oh, yeah.
I wonder if that's the trend these days.
I went.
Oh, it's pretty refreshing.
It's cool, senpai.
I see.
Especially this eyebrow is in order.
Oh, it fell.
What?
This is magic.
Oh, my eyebrows!
If you look closely, your head is pretty messy.
The back is super rare.
That's the Minara!
Welcome.
You came again?
Get ready!
You bastard!
I'm sorry.
I don't need the police.
Here I am!
The total amount of hair Wang
And I made my Kyog εκ eyebrows with the man's eyebrows.
What do you think?
They're'll be scary.
You look different, senpa.
It looks good.
What if I do this here?
You came back to normal.
I'm back to normal.
You should do something about your hair.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm going to pass because I have Sentaro here.
A high-tech shop. Sounds interesting.
I see. It's quite high-tech.
Welcome!
How is it?
This is my computer-controlled,
RIOIST, automatic cloth-wrapping machine.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
How are you going to do it today?
I'll do a quick angle.
I see.
I'm going to sleep for a while, so wake me up if you can.
That was fast.
Hey! One-Touch Barricade, on standby!
Yes, sir!
Huh?
Stop it!
Sentaro!
Hurry up and learn how to use it!
I'm sorry.
You said you wanted to be a RIOIST,
so I hired you to be my client.
I'm sorry.
Then, set the One-Touch Barricade on your client's head.
Don't let it move on its own.
Yes, sir!
All right, that was easy.
Next, press the blue button...
And then, the cutter will be set to wrap the head.
All right!
Next, press the green button...
And then, the cutter will be set to wrap the head.
What?
It's not working!
You're jealous, aren't you?
I told you not to let it move!
I'm sorry.
I hope it's being cut properly.
This...
This man...
What?
You know him?
Then, I'll leave the rest to you.
What?
I'll go ahead and hurry up.
Hey, are you sure you don't need to do anything?
I'm sorry.
It's a service day today.
There's nothing to apologize for.
Lucky, I hope you'll make it today.
I'm sorry, sir.
That was easy.
Hey, Promo!
Yo, Ryo-san. What's up?
I went for a walk.
You look good today, don't you think?
Yep.
Oh, so that's been the trend lately.
Yeah.
I'm back.
Oh, you're fresh.
You're cool, senpai.
Really?
What's wrong with your head?
Oh, I see.
I'm sure you're trying to atone for what you've done so far.
I see.
Come to think of it, you've done a lot of bad things so far.
Senpai finally understood.
What did you say?
I don't like it.
It's written on the back of your head.
What?
What's this?
You just borrowed it by mistake.
I thought it was strange.
Bastard.
I knew it.
You're sorry, aren't you?
Was it your fault again?
Bastard.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize to the police.
I was angry.
I'm really sorry.
I made a wig with that guy's hair, maybe.
It's creepy.
He looks like a different person.
Doesn't it look so pretty with your hair?
I think so, too.
Bukimi
Created by:
Episode 6 Oblivion
Hmph, finally you've grown.
Saying that to a crowd like that, it'll be tearfully uncomfortable!
That's right.
I can't stand here.
I've been ditched around here.
Let's do this right today.
Let's find a place like that.
Hair grows fast and it's hard to shave.
I don't need to grow hair.
Then, I developed a new type of permanent hair removal.
It will never grow again.
That's good. Please make it.
Understood.
Bio? Sounds interesting.
Welcome. Please come in.
It's quite a bio-like atmosphere.
We are applying various bio-research methods to the hair.
In addition to dyeing and hair removal, there are also drugs that can permanently fix the hair.
You can do that?
The power of bio is strong.
Then, please fix my hair with a square cut.
I'm sorry, Master.
I have a call from the chairman of the town council.
Please wait a moment.
Yes, it's Kai.
A meeting of the town council?
Okay, I'll go right away.
Sentaro, please do the permanent hair removal.
Just let the hair soak into it.
Even if you are clumsy, you won't fail, right?
Yes.
Then, I'll be back soon.
Have a nice day.
Which way should I go?
I don't know how to do it properly.
I'm sorry, I'll do it now.
I'll take a nap, so wake me up when you're done.
I'm sorry, I understand.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's hard to get along with the town council.
Good luck, Master!
What's wrong with you?
It's the same guest.
He's the guy next door who does the permanent hair removal.
Is it over?
Not yet.
I see.
What's wrong?
What?
Is he that violent?
I'm sorry. I should have noticed earlier.
I hope he hasn't heard the medicine yet.
Please don't listen to him.
He's cold.
Are you done?
I still have a beard.
I see.
I'll leave it to you.
I don't want to die yet.
I'm sorry.
Sir, sir.
It's over.
It's finally over.
It's all settled.
It's as tight as if it were stuck to my head.
It's because of the power of the bio.
How much is it?
I'll give you a free service for the first time.
I see. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
I'll come again.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm going to run away, Sentaro.
I'm sorry.
That was easy.
Hey, Promo.
Ryo?
You went out for a walk.
You're a man now, aren't you?
Yes.
That's what's been a tradition lately.
Thank you very much.
I went.
How about the next time?
I'm afraid...
He was stuck in a mess at the teaware again, wasn't he?
Right?
Ryo!
What is this?
It seems you've been hit again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the meal.
That old man!
He ran away.
Damn it!
I'm not going far!
I'm sorry, Master.
It was a big mistake to hire you.
I'm sorry.
I found you!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
It was your fault again!
You did it!
You're not my friend!
I'm sorry!
I don't need the police!
What?
I'll never grow hair again!
Yes.
I'm getting rid of my hair follicles with the power of the powerful bio.
It's a good opportunity.
If you can eat up the actions you've done so far,
you can be a priest.
I'm not kidding!
It's all your fault.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry!
It's your fault that everyone is going to be working for Re-O yep.
I'm sorry.
I promise to be my companion's good friend in the countryside.
You don't know that.
It won't help if you go on as a good friend.
You have to give up now!
I think so, too.
It's your hair, but it might work.
What?
NSFW
January 5th, 2006
developed a powerful medicine for hair loss.
Even if the hair is gone, it'll grow back.
That's good, Ryo.
Now I'm relieved.
Okay!
Good morning, Senpai.
Oh!
Okay.
It's already growing back?
Yes.
It's because I'm doing it on a daily basis.
That's strange.
According to the research center, it should take about a week for hair to grow back.
Don't compare me to the average people.
My hair is special.
If you say so...
That's right.
Oh?
But Ryo-chan, hasn't your hair grown longer than before?
It's definitely grown, Senpai.
Yes.
What's this?
Hey!
I can't see the front!
The speed is too fast!
It's growing faster than expected!
Hurry up and do something!
The research center should have a growth inhibitor.
If you use it...
Wait!
This is too much for me!
Don't do it to me!
Are you okay, Senpai?
I'm glad my hair became a cushion.
I have no choice.
I'll go get the medicine.
Senpai, please don't move.
I'm counting on you, Senpai.
I'm going!
...
I guess...
I don't have any talent, after all.
....
???
You are a cancer!
But I...
I...
I didn't know I'd have grown this much.
I'm going to put out a fire right before you.
Roger that.
What's wrong?
The God is stuck in the rotor and can't be controlled.
What?
That's...
Hey, Nakagawa!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
The God has become a cushion and saved me.
But from here,
I don't think we can get out of here.
To get here is a difficult task.
Okay, I have an idea.
Senpai!
Put the medicine in the ball and shoot your head directly.
Please turn your head to me.
I got it!
It's only one shot.
If you miss it, it's over.
You know my gun skills, right?
Don't worry!
I've been using it since I was a child.
I've been aiming for the best.
I can't give up at my youth.
That's right! I'm young!
What if I fail once or twice?
What should I do?
Okay, fire!
I'm still working hard!
The growth inhibitor...
It's you again, Sentarou!
I'm sorry!
You don't have to apologize!
If you want to play baseball,
don't play like this.
Don't play like this.
Out! Safe!
Nice, nice!
Next time, we'll play baseball games!
See you next time!
It's a good goal!
You see.
Can't win!
♪