"I love you too"
A
"A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A"
Come to me if you're broke.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'm sure it'll be alright.
Come to me if you're broke.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look here, red clouds are burning.
I'm sure it'll be alright.
" Satan is living Bruno."
"You know?"
"You know, right?"
If you understand, then shut up and follow me!
Director, Ryo Tsutankichi
Episode 1: The
Everyone! I am the new official of the Kansai Prefectural Office, Ryo Tsutankichi!
You finally did it, Ryo-chan!
Senior, congratulations!
Ryo-tsu, I believed that this day would come!
I have nothing left to think about!
I don't care if I die anytime, Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu, wake up, you idiot! Ryo-tsu!
Ohara-kun...
Ohara-kun?
I don't know what to say.
I'm going to have a lunch with the Prime Minister...
Idiot! What are you doing?
Huh?
It seems like you were having a great dream.
That's also very convenient for me.
Huh? Dream?
This is reality.
Huh?
Open your eyes and look closely.
This is the report of your writing.
The number 1 looks like 7, and the 5 of 5 looks like a cow.
It's true. And it's mostly in hiragana.
There are places that are faked in the picture.
That's a very detailed thing.
You can't think like that.
That's why you've always been a junior president.
Listen, Ryo-tsu. Listen carefully.
This is not the age for just a career.
It's not the age for just a career.
The features of the social structure of our country,
the year-end-distance-distance ratio, has collapsed.
That's the age where you're evaluated based on your own ability.
Do you understand?
S-surely.
Then, you don't think we should be trying to promote you with your ability?
Ahaha!
In my dreams, I was a general secretary.
You're not talking about your dreams!
Ugh...
No matter what I say, I'm getting a year-end-distance-distance ratio in my horse ears...
Oh!
Thank you!
Ryo-tsu!
Oh, Director!
Oh, Ohara-kun. Is Ryo-tsu here?
Director, is there anything that you need?
No, nothing.
Anyway, give me a glass of water.
O-okay!
...
So, what happened?
I-I still think it's a dream,
but it's my mistake.
Ohara-kun, please read it.
Please try it.
Ah, an example?
Um, I'll be appointed as the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department...
Eh?
R-Ryotsu Kankichi!
R-Ryotsu is...
The head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department?
Y-You're the head?
The head?
I-I am?
The new supercomputer introduced by the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department
has been analyzed and determined by analyzing all the data of the individuals.
I-Is that a computer error?
I've asked the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department, but unfortunately...
There's no doubt about it.
It's not something that can't be!
As the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department said,
it's not the time for just a career to come out!
Ryo-chan, when you're on your side, there's something reliable about you.
Huh?
Hahaha!
The time has finally come for me!
...
So, what about the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department?
He was transferred to the end of the world.
To the end of the world?
Poor thing...
What? Of course!
That head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department didn't rely on anyone.
It's natural that he couldn't survive in this age of capitalism.
B-But suddenly, the head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department...
Yeah...
The head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department seems to have a position of her own.
Chief!
That's the very basis of the main idea.
Isn't it good?
To proceed without any people.
That's what we call "practice"!
The head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department also just said,
"It's time for young people to lose their enthusiasm and be evaluated for their real ability."
He just said that to me.
Uh...
But...
I don't have all the energy...
Huh?
What?
The head of the Katsushika-cho transportation department said,
What!?
What's wrong, Kei-chan?
The head of the police station contacted me.
He wants to send you to the police station.
What!?
Is that true, Nakagawa?
Yes.
It's strange for the head of the police station to be the head of the police station.
So, he wants to do something special.
I'm too shocked today.
The police station...
I don't know how to say it.
He fired the head of the police station.
I'm so touched.
Ohara-kun.
Ohara-kun?
This is called ability.
The era when only the career was good is over.
Even if you were good at fighting, you could go up.
Ohara-kun.
What?
My shoes are dirty.
They're sandals, not shoes.
Please polish them.
What did you say, Ryotsu?
What?
It's not Ryotsu, it's the head of the police station.
Ryotsu... head of the police station...
Be careful how you talk.
You'll be scared if the police station gets angry.
The head of the police station...
Good morning, Mr. Ryotsu.
Mr. Ryotsu, good morning.
That's the desk of the chief.
It's so different from the desk at the police station.
Good morning, chief.
Why are you so in the mood?
Why are you so gloomy?
Komachi-kun, Naoko-kun.
Oh, the former captain.
No, Chief.
Do you have any opinions?
Say anything you want.
It's important to listen to your subordinates' opinions.
I don't have any opinions.
No, you don't.
Oh, that's good.
No, I can't do this.
I knocked down the trash can.
I'm sorry, but I'll clean it up, Komachi.
You knocked it down, didn't you?
You're not going to fight the chief?
I'm dizzy.
I knocked it down again.
Hey, you knocked it down on purpose.
My head hurts.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
This is no good.
This is bad.
I'm sorry, but please clean this up, too.
I suddenly have a headache.
Naoko,
let's go.
Yes, yes.
Oh, my.
Why did you do this to him?
That's right.
To hide the taste.
I feel sorry for the trash can, so I'll wipe it with a cloth.
Here you are, Chief.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I changed my mind.
I'll have coffee.
Coffee?
Bring it quickly.
It's coffee.
Coffee.
Yes, yes.
I'll make you pay for it this time.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Sorry.
I changed my mind again.
I want black tea.
Here's black tea.
Stop with the black tea.
I want juice.
Here's the juice.
Green tea.
Oolong tea.
Blue juice.
Miso soup.
Why are you talking about miso soup?
I see.
I see what you're going to do.
I'm going to get into trouble.
That stupid chief.
But you'd better not go against him.
You just have to make him your chief.
Is that so?
That's right.
If you make him your chief, he'll climb the tree.
I see.
If you make him your chief, he'll be your chief.
That's right.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Good morning, Chief Ryochi.
I'm feeling a little excited today.
Chief Ryochi, your shoulders are dirty.
Really?
Chief Ryochi, your tie is bent.
Chief Ryochi, would you like some black tea?
Or would you like some coffee, black tea, oolong tea?
I've got them all ready.
Chief, you're so nice.
You're right.
He's always making a fuss, but it's good for him.
He's an example of a single cell.
Huh?
Who's parking their bike in a place like this?
What is this?
They can't pass through here.
Yeah.
Naoko.
Ryo-chan, it's your turn to do this.
Yeah.
A bike?
That's right. Do something with Ryo-chan's power.
I can do it.
Do your best for everyone.
If you say so.
Okay!
Leave it to Ryo-chan.
Wow!
That's amazing!
That's a manly man.
Yay!
Hey! Don't stop there!
This is Katsushika-shokotsu-ka, Kachou Ryotsu Kankichi!
Stop your bike at the designated place.
Hey, don't run away!
Hey, I told you not to stop there!
The old lady there said no!
You!
You're not getting away!
Now I'm going to show you my real power!
All Katsushika-shokotsu-ka will remove the bad-ass bikes!
With this strong will of Katsushika-shokotsu-ka's Ryotsu Kachou,
the residents and the residents of the station have come to a decision.
Furthermore, the Furisode Kotsu-tai was born from the idea of the Ryotsu Kachou.
Stop that car there!
F-Ferrari?
F-Furisode?
The Furisode Kotsu-tai has arrived!
The traffic violation is...
No!
O-Okay, I'm sorry.
...has been approved.
In addition, the removal of the spare traffic light,
and the removal of the waste road construction will support the reform of the transportation system.
The citizens' voices are being heard by many people.
Ryo-chan, you're a good man when it comes to doing things.
Yeah!
Katsushika-san!
I hate it!
I've got a feeling that something is coming out of him.
Yeah.
Well, well, everyone at the exit before the park.
Isn't that a great achievement, Ryo-chan?
Of course.
Without reform, there would be no progress.
No fear of failure, no humiliation, no imprisonment.
We'll continue to push forward the reform of the transportation system.
That sounds like a line I've heard somewhere.
Yeah.
But I didn't think the government would change so much.
Oh my goodness!
Komachi-chan!
It's the Emperor's first letter!
W-What?
What happened?
I-I just got a call from the transportation department.
They said that President Ryo-tsu was attacked by the president of the Katsushika-shou.
What?
Is it Ryo-chan?
It's me!
The president of the Katsushika-shou!
The President of the Katsushika-shou!
The Furisode Transportation Department is as popular as any idol, and it seems that the number of malicious criminals has decreased significantly.
It's a great success, Senpai!
No, President!
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
That's right, that's right.
But somehow the story is too good.
There is something wrong with this.
The 23rd district of Tokyo, the 8th district, the president of the Katsushika-shou.
It's here!
It's definitely me!
Huh?
This number.
I think my personal number is 410...
Oh!
It's not 410, it's 470!
Come to think of it...
The number 1 looks like 7.
I see.
When I entered the computer, the number 1 and 7 were wrong.
I'm the only one who knows this secret.
Okay!
Since I became the president, not only the transportation department but also the entire Katsushika-shou will be reformed.
What happened to the former President Tonda?
It seems that he was passed over to the vice-president.
Ohara-kun.
Yes!
The Katsushika-shou's catchphrase is...
What's the catchphrase?
Yes!
"Don't be afraid, don't be afraid, don't be trapped."
Your voice is too small.
Ah!
"Don't be afraid, don't be afraid, don't be trapped. From your grandparents..."
Louder!
"Don't be afraid, don't be afraid, don't be trapped. From your grandparents, your grandparents, your grandchildren, everyone loves the Katsushika-shou!"
Okay.
In order for everyone to like the Katsushika-shou, the first Katsushika-shou reform I thought of was...
"Come as a popular talent or a beautiful actress as a one-day reception hall."
"Grandparents and grandmothers can make free baths and use them at ease."
"Use stuffed animals to make the Katsushika-shou familiar to children."
"We will continue to make various reforms."
"The construction is also going well."
"All right."
"Anyway..."
"I will receive a special bonus of 100 million yen."
"As you can see, the president and the secretary are very close to each other."
Amazing.
How can they make such a big statue?
It's like a special vehicle.
What?
What is it?
Let's go.
Help.
Help!
"I entonces Iwagkara"
Even the chief chef is here.
He might escalate further.
He's guarding the computer room with all his might.
He's keeping everyone from entering.
That's suspicious, Ryo.
He's hiding something.
That's right.
Today's lunch is either lobster or abalone.
I'm already tired of the full course.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Oh, and the wine is from Bordeaux.
Yes.
Ryo, you're drinking wine while working?
You're the chief, aren't you?
You're trying to give me some advice, aren't you?
Ohara!
N-no, it's nothing.
That's fine.
If you just listen to me quietly...
The situation has changed, but the old chief's room...
You're a coward!
Who do you think you are?
You'll be the chief of the Pyo-tsu Kankichi.
I'm sorry.
My head fell down.
Chief Tonda!
Ohara!
Chief!
You're both...
You're both in trouble.
No, you two over there.
I have something I'd like you to do.
Phew, it seems to have ended.
Oh, well, it took six hours to get from the head to here.
Really, you two did your best.
Is it over?
Hmm...
I don't think I can find anything.
I want something that'll teach me what I see.
Yes, there you go!
You're friends.
Look at the poor Matsuro, the unfortunate one without power.
Compare yourself with my good friends.
You should compare him to a statue.
A statue?
Ryotsu, no matter what you say...
Can I listen to you?
If you get fired, you'll have to work overtime.
I'm strict.
Yeah, yeah.
You look really pitiful.
Oh, that's good.
The chiefs will be very upset about that.
I wonder if we can do something about it.
Yeah.
Reiko.
Kei, did you find out anything?
That's strange.
The data on the Katsushika Library is blocked.
And it seems that we can't access it from the super computer in the capital.
I knew it.
There must be some secret to the Katsushika Library's computer.
To become the beloved Katsushika Library,
the services we've provided so far are too simple.
We have to do something.
I think it's best if we convert it into a major leisure-land and let everyone enjoy it.
No matter how hard we try.
We've gone too far.
Without reform, we're not moving forward.
We have to change the Japanese police from the Katsushika Library.
The Katsushika Library
The tunnel going up there continues to the computer room above.
Yeah.
It's going pretty far up there.
If we don't take care of it here,
But what'll we do with it?
What's up, Yuki?
The Katsushika Library
Katsushika Library
*Aizawa waits for his turn*
Here?
Yes.
Hey, you're here!
R-Ryo!
Sheriff!
T-This is a form of a 3-dimensional image!
You're right.
I knew you guys could get this far a long time ago.
You did absorbed more data of the computer, did you not?
Unfortunately, you guys can't even get away from that matter.
If you press this switch, the floor where you guys are standing will disappear!
Sen-Senpai!
Ryo-chan!
In other words, you will return to the starting point!
That means you did well.
See you later!
Oh no! The arrow is above me, that means...
The boss!
Ah! I was the one who escaped!
Ryo-chan!
That's terrible! It's all over the place!
It's all Ryo-chan's fault, isn't it?
If we put this back, all the things that happened before will be gone!
Alright! This is okay!
You did it!
Ryo-chan!
Boss!
This is not true!
This was all done by the super computer of the head office!
You are being very rude!
Prepare yourself!
No, the computer really is...
That computer gave you a new example.
Be happy! You can become the real boss!
Eh? The boss? Me?
Ryo-chan base!
The right one!
By today, I will appoint you as the head of the "Saihatesho Yojo-hanjima" paper!
Saihatesho Yojo-hanjima!
Congratulations, Ryo-chan!
Congratulations!
Th-thank you!
Hey, isn't this really the only place that's as big as Yojo-han?
This is the same as the island!
I'm fine with the size, so please return me to Tokyo!
Why?
Good job!
Demon-chan is a kindergarten child, but she likes historical dramas. Why?
Why?
The little beard of the head office is slightly small. Why?
Oh, what?
Look at you!
Did you change your course?
Oh, you've changed!
Oh, I'm dying!
Here's an episode!
Let me just move the bar!
Enjoy!
I don't know where I live, but I like it!
Now, let's go, Yoko-chan!
I don't lend money to Reiko-san, but...
I can easily lend money to tanks and fighters.
Why is that?
Reiko-san is a very rich person, but...
Why is she working at the sewage?
Why is that? Why is that?
Why do I have to run with Ryo Tsukai and the other two?
Besides, my parents are going on a trip.
What should I do?
Next time,
Ryo-tsu and Komachi are going on a trip?
So stop it, okay?
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Oh, there's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!