Slytherin
When you're watching TV
Make sure to stay on top of the room and take off in the meantime
Soumet
I・Soument
It's so kind of you
From the water tank of the Tunganiboshi
To the Taishakuten
The sun is setting
Tomorrow is already over
It's over, right?
If I were to win again
I'd lose my happiness
I've realized
I'm such an idiot
The infinite universe
There are still unknown things there
From now on
For another thirty minutes
Your eyes will be separated from your body
And enter this mysterious time
A gift from space
Ryo, it'll be hard for the chief to find you making that
It'll be fine
I'll finish it before the chief comes
If you're so motivated
At least half of it will be for work
Okay, one more
You're eating so hard
The dessert's like a diamond
Rub it in
Oh my gosh
What are you doing?
Oh, hello
Gyo
It was you
Be careful
What happens, is it your weight?
What do you mean by "how"
I can't be stupid
Let me see
The gun was 그러면ed
Oh my gosh
A hole is open.
It looks like something fell from the sky.
I wonder if it's a meteorite.
I'll check it out.
Senpai!
It's broken, but it seems to be a meteorite.
Senpai, it's better not to get too close.
I wonder if that's true.
Even so, it was dangerous.
If it had been a little more off, it would have been a direct hit on the exhaust.
That's true.
The wild horses are gathering.
I'll contact the office.
I'll clean up.
Let's leave before it's too late.
My Zero-Sense was shot down!
It can't be helped. You were a genius.
It was almost complete.
Damn it!
What is this?
It's like a real rock.
Ryo!
Help me clean up without eating the rice crackers.
Oh, no!
I have to wake up early tomorrow and watch Otsuka on Mezamashi TV.
I'm sorry, but I'm counting on you.
You're cheating, Ryo!
He ran away.
It's troublesome to be asked about anything at the first discovery.
Are there any differences in molecular structure in the rock?
That's right.
Never-Earth materials.
Is that dangerous?
Sir.
Professor will be coming this afternoon.
Phew, I slept well!
Somehow I feel good today, though.
That's the guy.
It's light for your legs, too!
What? It seems my body just floated away!
Go away!
What is going on here?
She floated into the universe!
What?
I can't feel my weight.
What's going on?
Ryotsu!
Yes, sir?
What are you doing here?
I'd like to ask you something.
Actually...
Sorry, I caught a cold.
Ryotsu?
Yes, sir!
Get him!
Ryotsu, where did you go?
I finally stopped.
Idiot! Get away from me!
Yes, sir!
Three grams?
What's going on? I can't believe it.
I can't believe it either.
What a noisy man.
You're not only doing normal things, but you're also light.
Don't sneeze at me!
Sorry.
I'm glad you put on weight.
I'm a balloon.
But what on earth happened to you?
If you know that, I won't bother you.
What is that?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Oolong tea is the world's best drink in the world.
Professor Eizaki.
It's you, after all.
Hello, everyone in the expulsion center.
What the hell are you doing here?
Thank you.
Chashu, shumai, ginger, rose, hoikoro.
Don't say something you don't understand.
Well, I've been studying Chinese at Peking University since last month.
I finally got to speak Chinese in my daily conversation.
You're just lining up Chinese food menus.
Japanese are not good at it.
Ah, Japanese are short-tempered.
The 4,000-year teaching of China is like the flow of the Yosu River.
It's about living comfortably.
You're going to go to China again in a while?
But I think Chinese people will get angry if they see us.
So, Professor, what do you want to do today?
I heard that a meteorite collapsed near here last night.
What?
So, a special professor is coming.
Professor Ezaki?
Didn't you major in mechanical engineering?
Space physics is also a professor's specialty.
Is there something in that meteorite?
Actually, that meteorite is a special meteorite made of an unknown substance.
And then what changed?
If you say something has changed...
I think it's about this idiot's weight becoming 3 grams.
That's it!
The meteorite must be wrong!
What?
Look.
The meteorite is stuck on this rock.
Oh, that's right.
No way.
This meteorite is made of a anti-gravity substance that is not on Earth.
Because of that, the body has become lighter.
Anti-gravity substance?
What's that?
In other words, it's a substance that has the power to repel the earth's gravity.
But how did it get inside your body?
I don't know!
After all, you picked up something that was falling and ate it.
Even if it was me, I wouldn't pick up a meteorite and eat it.
Oh, by the way, at that time...
What is this?
It's hard like a real rock.
There was a meteorite in that rock.
That's right.
I didn't expect there to be a difference between rock and rock.
But it's strange.
Why did a meteorite, which should have the power to repel the earth's gravity, fall on Earth?
Rick.
Come to think of it...
There's a kind of amino acid that's affecting it.
Amino acid?
You!
Last night, after putting a meteorite inside your body, did you eat something?
Is it a lebanin?
That's right!
As a result of the fusion of a meteorite and a lebanin in his stomach,
the characteristic of a anti-gravity substance has been created.
Beautiful.
It's a little...
Is that so?
I don't think I can trust you.
What?
Hey!
Ryo!
Senpai!
What's going on?
Apparently, the anti-gravity substance has increased.
At this rate, it will soon penetrate the atmosphere and enter the space.
I'm not kidding!
Please, do something!
You're really unlucky.
Why?
Because I have a secret scroll that tells you how to make the Chinese 4,000-year-old anti-gravity substance.
Why anti-gravity?
Wasn't it in the physics of the universe?
You!
Don't underestimate anti-gravity!
Anti-gravity is to listen to anything!
That's not what I meant.
I understand.
The medicine for this man is...
Whatever the symptom, if you drink this, it will heal in one shot!
It's a medicine!
If you drink this, the influence of the meteor will disappear!
You're not convincing at all!
If that's the case, I will return to China as it is.
Wait for me!
All right, let me drink it!
I'm counting on you, Professor.
With the power of science, I have no choice but to rely on the mystery of the East and the West!
Please!
Don't abandon Ryo!
I can't help it if you're asked to teach me something cute and beautiful.
Then, let's...
Before that, let's stop here.
It's tea time.
Huh?
Ah...
This is really...
Not good, right?
That's enough!
Hurry up and do it!
The End
Here, drink it.
Huh?
You're drinking this?
It's fine. It should be easier to drink than the blue juice.
Be patient, Ryozu!
This is no time to be luxurious!
I know, but I can't help it.
The taste is unbearable.
Sen-senpai!
Ryo-chan!
It's coming down.
Yay! It's a success!
You did it! You're on the floor!
Ryozu, try on the weight scale.
I did it, chief!
It's exactly the same as before!
You did well, senpai.
Congratulations, Ryo-chan!
There's no such thing as impossibility in the history of 4,000 years of China.
Ryo-chan!
Ah-ha! Thank goodness.
Seems like what you're saying about theDrive's invention is totally legitimate.
I've finally got back to work.
Yay!
The kid is coming!
You bastard!
Wait!
Oh no! The police!
How can you run away without me tagging along again?
Huh?
Almost there.
Cease fire.
Now change!
Hurry up!
I feel like my body is getting heavier.
He's so light-hearted.
You thief!
I'm lucky to have found you, Lord Ryozu Kankichi!
What's wrong? Your body suddenly became heavy.
It hurts!
Stop!
Hey, wait!
My body doesn't move!
You're getting heavier, Professor!
How many kilograms do you have?
If I come this far...
He's chasing me!
It's like a barbell!
It's running!
It's a monster!
Stop!
It's so heavy!
I can't let it escape!
It's a downhill!
It's faster to fall down!
What?
I got it!
But stop!
Stop!
You're so heavy!
What?
800 kg?
No way!
Are you alright, senior?
I'm not!
Uhhh...
Ahh! I've passed the limit!
Huh?
Even an elephant can't break the weight scale!
Cycling! Cycling!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
So where are you going to bring that extra?
Ni hao!
In Chinese "Takurama-kan Saboku"
Takurama-san means "If you enter once, you'll never be able to leave"
Hey! Because you drank a strange herbal medicine,
your body is getting heavier and heavier this time!
I-I'm getting heavier again...
Ha ha ha! I knew this would happen!
No need to worry!
I knew it! Do something about it!
Don't worry!
You can drink this and you'll be fine!
The magic weapon used by the Chinese "Sengin" to fly in the sky!
You can chew it, so hurry up and fly, you!
Oh no!
I mixed another medicine with a tea-brewed candy!
What?
What is it?
No need to worry.
Let's see...
Hey! Hurry up and do it!
Hm? This!
Really?
No doubt!
It's a one or two or eight!
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
Somehow, my body is...
Wahhh! It's getting heavier!
Help me!
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
What's this?
What's wrong?
It's just a little, but a strange gravity field has been detected.
What?
Wahhh!
I finally made it.
Shuman! Shuman!
What?
It seems that he gave another medicine.
It seems that the insect reacted and became heavier and heavier.
What's the medicine?
That's a medicine when a thousand people fly.
Ha-ha-ha!
A thousand people will fall from a tree, right?
It's a joke about the year 4,000 in China.
A monkey falls from a tree, right?
Huh?
But your feet are warm.
Wahhh!
Gorilla-kun!
It's a hot spring!
You dug up a hot spring!
I've got it!
I can make a fortune with this!
First, I built a giant hot spring in Cameari.
Then I used the earth's heat and made a jungle paradise and a nether world.
We have to expand our business with the zoo!
But if we keep this up, we'll drown!
Hurry up and give me the medicine!
Oh, right, let's see...
This is it!
Where is it, Mr. Gorilla?
It's here!
Oh, is that where your brother is?
It's okay, hurry up and give me the medicine.
Oh, wait...
It's getting heavier again!
It's getting sucked in!
What's the cause?
I don't know.
But it's true that something huge is forming on the Eurasia Plate.
This is bad!
The gravity is increasing even more!
That's right, it's getting heavier and heavier.
What are you going to do about it?
You know the dolphin, right?
The Eurasian dolphin is a dolphin that lives in the water, and it's in danger of extinction!
Don't lie to me!
What's this?
It's a dinosaur fossil.
Moreover, it hasn't been discovered in Japan yet.
Tyrannosaurus rex!
Really?
I'm the dinosaur doctor, so I'm sure of it!
Since when did you become a dinosaur doctor?
Dinos...
What?
Stop it, you liar!
Hey, there are some more!
Oh, this is Brachiosaurus.
This is Euprochephalus.
This is Tornacromerum.
This is a great discovery!
It'll sell high on the Dinosaur Mania!
No, first, we'll build a dinosaur museum in Kameari.
Furthermore, we'll expand our business with character products and theme parks!
This is a new type of discovery, you know.
Let's call it Ezaki Kameari Zaulus!
You can include my name too!
Well, let's celebrate our success and have a cup of tea.
Oh, right, the tea-making candy...
This is the flying fire!
Hey, you! Don't leave me alone!
Oh, the fishing...
It's getting heavier again!
I got it!
Japanese Kameari!
It's 10,000 meters underground!
Oh, Kameari!
I'll show you the main screen!
The problem is that the X-Men are moving to the underground, while increasing the amount of matter!
At this rate, we'll be able to get through to the Mantle層!
It's getting hotter and hotter!
It's magma!
The X-Men are being pushed back by the Mantle層!
They're being pushed back by magma!
The amount of matter is increasing!
No! At this rate...
What will happen at this rate?
If the amount of X-Men continues to increase, the amount of matter will increase!
The Earth's Earth's axis will tilt!
The Earth's Earth's axis has tilted!
It's Hawaii, as I thought!
Yeah, you're right.
What?
Snow?
It's terrible!
The Earth's entire environment is in danger due to the tilt of the Earth's axis!
The Earth's Earth's Earth is in danger due to the tilt of the Earth's axis!
Ryo-sensei!
Senpai!
Ryo-chan!
What?
As long as we have the X-Men, we can't escape the threat of the Earth's destruction.
Please give your decision, President!
I understand...
As soon as possible!
Execute Project Tornado!
Look! The rocket was launched!
The Earth was destroyed by the Earthquake, but the X-Wing disappeared!
Everyone around the world, the Earth is saved!
It's broken!
Captain!
How long will I live in this place?
The meteorite will become a poop and come out of your body.
Or if you want, you can stay there forever.
No way! I want to make a plastic model and a radio.
What's going to happen to the next game?
Don't worry.
It's okay to be as heavy as it is in the weightless space.
You can go anywhere.
Hey! Professor Tornado! Why are you here?
Thanks to the medicine, I was able to come to the universe.
That's right.
It's all because of your strange herbal medicine.
Wait, it's tea time.
Don't come to this place and have tea.
The oolong tea I drink in the universe is special.
There are still many strange things in the universe.
You should be careful when you eat the bone-in-the-sandwich.
There may be some gifts from the universe.
Episode 2: The Oolong Tea
Komachi and Nakagawa went to the countryside.
They looked so upset.
But I have a photo of the oolong tea that has no movement.
Next time, "The Oolong Tea I Long For."
What are you going to do, Komachi?
This time, we will find out this story at the end.
Let's see its true meaning.
Please help us this time.
The Oolong Teaently
"Bowl's Oolong Tea"
A small jade, isn't it?
A huge jade.
It looks like a painting by a Japanese artist.
What is the meaning of this jade?
Whet, what is this?
-Depedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedepedep
It's on the ground.
But a regardez beckons from grandeur.
Isn't this amazing?
No way we're making that up!