Please turn on the light for the TV to see the room.
The poor are coming to me.
I'm not here but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
It will be somehow.
I have no job.
If you know, just follow me quietly.
The End
In the year 2301,
the life form of the Earth was in danger of extinction
due to the bacteria attack of the Dubidaba Seijin who were aiming for the earth's conquest.
On that day, at the secret base of the Earth Defense Force,
an important meeting was about to be held
to respect the lives of humanity, no, all living things on the earth.
The End
Today, there is no other reason why I have you all here.
Because the countermeasure against the Dubidaba Seijin's killing virus,
Shabadobi 11PM, has been finally discovered.
Really?
Then, Dr. Iidabashi, please explain.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm Iidabashi from Paradise Research Institute.
I have thoroughly researched the antibodies that can fight against Shabadobi 11PM,
including the past database.
As a result, I was able to discover only one of those antibodies with that possibility.
Please look at the screen.
This is the antibody that was found 300 years ago from a certain police officer's lymph node in Japan.
Surprisingly, this was an invincible antibody that could defeat any virus.
However, at that time, it was a very strong attack,
so it was dangerous for anyone other than the person who was infected.
So, the research was cut off.
Wow.
However, it is the 24th century now.
If we use the current medical science, we can control this antibody.
What?
Is it true?
Yes.
And this is the simulation result for Shabadobi 11PM.
Wow.
If we can obtain this antibody and produce a large amount of vaccines,
we can eliminate the threat of Dubidaba Seijin's recent attack.
That's great.
We can defeat the Dubidaba Seijin.
Professor, what is the name of that antibody?
The name of the star that saves humanity is Ryotsu GPX.
The only person who has that antibody is this Ryotsu Kankichi.
Ryotsu!
I recognize Ryotsu Kan-Kichi.
Ryotsu! Ryotsu! Ryotsu!
Let's go!
If you want to play baseball,
You need to be like this!
We'll give you a chance!
One more!
Ten!
No, no, no!
Oh, I won!
Don't worry!
The game is just beginning!
Tamachi!
Don't lose to such a cowardly man!
I know!
Director! Chief!
What's going on?
Ah, I'm sorry.
Reiko.
Actually, the director was sent to a shopping street to get a ticket for a pair ticket to a hot spring trip to Kyoto.
Unfortunately,
That day was Reiko's wedding.
If someone asked me to give it to him,
It would be a rock-paper-scissors competition.
One was decided by Ohara-kun,
But Ryotsu said the other was decided by baseball.
Then all the girls will get off.
It's Ryo-chan's usual cowardly hand.
But Komachi-chan has that personality.
Yo-yo-yo!
Oh, no!
Then Komachi,
Let's take it off!
Take it off?
You can take it off if you want.
Oyama!
We are Budokans!
I was born in this region!
Out!
If you do this,
I'll shake your ass out!
I won!
That's what I called you!
Ah!
Don't put it off!
Cowardly gentleman!
Hey, Ryotsu!
You lose!
I won't forgive you for being so
sissy!
Don't worry!
Here!
How unfair!
You're wearing two pairs of pants!
There's no law that says you're not allowed to wear
any pair of pants!
Now, let's go to the next one!
Yeah!
How many pairs of pants are you wearing?
Now, here I go!
Now, what are you going to do, Komachi?
How frustrating!
I got the Kyoto trip here!
Oh!
Ryotsu Jitchoku, here I come!
Please come in.
Excuse me.
You can go.
I was wondering if the descendants of Ryotsu Kan'kichi
were among the defense force.
I'm sorry.
As the grandson-grandson-grandson-grandson
of Ryotsu Kan'kichi's brother,
you are the most suitable.
Oh, roast staff of Ryotsu.
I have a question.
Your mission is to find Ryoutsu Kankichi in Japan in 2001 and bring back Ryoutsu GPX.
Listen, your life is at stake! Please!
Yes! Even if I die, I'll bring back Ryoutsu GPX!
And this is the man called Ryoutsu Kankichi.
Well done, Miss Termi!
Listen, before the Earth Defense Force contacts us, we must eliminate Ryoutsu Kankichi.
Without Ryoutsu GPX, the Earth will be ours. Go, Miss Termi!
Roger.
Yes, Miss Termi.
I'm sorry, Nagaga.
Please enjoy the trip with the Chief and Kyoto!
Yes, sir!
Hey, wait! Wait!
Ryoutsu, it seems you were too sleepy to make it in time.
Now you can enjoy Kyoto alone.
Chief! Chief! You're mean!
R-Ryotsu, did you make it in time?
I told you I'd give Ryou a call in the morning!
Oh, really?
Well, I've been forgetting things lately.
I was about to be late, and I was in a hurry.
It was hard for me.
You should have been late.
What is it, Chief?
It seems you don't want to go on a trip with me.
Of course I don't!
I've never had anything good after going on a trip with you.
Like the last time we went to Paris...
It was my fault!
It's all right. I didn't have breakfast.
Then go on your own!
I can't believe I'm going to be with you for the next three days!
Oh, really? You're a bad boy!
W-W-Whatever...
Hey, you almost ate it. I'm going to cook him for you!
Well. That's a good day today.
You didn't eat much today, were you?
It seems like a volver to live a life like this, so...
W-What the hell is this?
R-Ryotsu...
Yes.
Where are you coming from?
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
Didn't you go to Kyoto with Oharu?
No, I...
And what's that weird cosplay?
Change into your uniform!
Yes.
I'm glad I can wear something like this.
Does it look like the person named Ryotsu Kankichi?
I wonder if it's similar to someone named Ryotsu Kankichi.
As I thought, it's Ryotsu Kankichi!
No, I'm...
Why are you here?
Why?
I got it!
You bought the travel sword you got with your cheating baseball.
You sold it in a gold sword shop.
What?
That's right.
You're the worst man.
You're also the No. 1 man who doesn't want to marry for 12 years in a row!
No, no.
That's not it.
If you don't, you'll be married for 30 years in a row.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
I'm sorry.
R-Ryotsu Kankichi lowered his head!
Something's wrong with him today.
Let's go.
Is the legend of Ryotsu Kankichi that was told to my house true?
Mr. Ryota!
We found it!
You!
What's the matter with you?
You're a liar!
This is also the legend.
This is what it is!
"A short kamikaze"
"A short kamikaze host"
It... It's... It's foam.
Senpai!
You want to see me?
Ryo-chan?
If you marry me, you won't be able to see me.
I want to see you, Ryo-chan.
Please tell me where you are.
Unfortunately, Senpai is on a trip to Kyoto.
-Kyoto? -Excuse me.
-Ryo-chan? -Ryo-chan?
What's wrong, Senpai?
Didn't you make it on time for the bullet train?
No, it's not that.
It's not that.
I'm...
Ryo-chan is 95% confident that he is the real Ryo-chan.
Ryo-sama!
What are you doing to my Ryo-sama?
N-no way!
W-what's wrong with him?
He's 24 years old.
He's the Terminator, a robot killer from the 24th century.
Terminator?
Why do you know me?
Don't tell me you're...
Exactly!
I've been under the command of the Earth Defense Forces since the 24th century.
My name is Ryo-tsu.
What?
You're not Ryo-tsu Kankichi?
Kankichi is my great-great-great-great-great-great-great-grand-grandfather's brother.
You're not Ryo-chan?
Please stop joking around, senpai.
Whatever.
If you kill me, there won't be any people left who can carry G.P.X. to the 24th century.
Die!
Run!
Ah!
- He's not here! - He's a fast runner!
When the sound of the night-time whistle started,
it seemed like he ran away in a hurry.
Maybe he's weak to the sound of a certain frequency.
Um, I don't know what it is at all!
That's right! Please explain!
Um...
Ryotsu, it's Jitchoku.
Jitchoku!
What do you mean by 24th century or something-ancient?
All right, everyone. I'll explain it to you properly.
What?!
Is that what the Earth will look like 300 years from now?
You wouldn't believe it, but it's true.
What?
I thought you were talking about the world of manga.
But it's a lame name for a Terminator.
Yeah, because he's a flying adult.
Anyway, it's true that Ryo is aiming for his life.
I'll call you, senpai.
What's with the noise?
Use your mobile phone as a deck.
I know.
I'm on a treat trip now.
I can't keep up with you if you keep bothering me.
It's not working.
It's not connecting.
If we wait, Ryo and the manager will be in danger.
We'll go to Kyoto, too!
Yeah!
Eh?!
We'll go to Kyoto, too!
Then we'll go straight to the inn and have a big drink.
What are you thinking?
That's why we don't have to come to Kyoto.
If we were going to come to a temple, we wouldn't have come here.
Of course! A guy like you who got a punishment is a perfect opportunity!
I'll use you to purify that rotten heart!
Chief, let's take a picture here.
With a self timer, the two of us together...
Let's leave it around here.
Chief, a little more right...
Yes, like this.
Hehehe, what are you dressed up for?
Ryo Tsukan Kitsu, 100% Probability of the real person.
Okay, here we go.
Target locked on.
Here we go!
What are you doing?
Hahaha, I'm just playing with the trash.
Just kidding.
Generally, when you go on a trip,
there's no one who can wear something so easy to slip.
Oh well, next up is the Kiyomizu Temple.
Hey, Chief!
The two-shot photo is not ready yet!
Please wait for me, Chief!
Da!
Oh, no!
It's the Koke Temple, the Koke Temple!
Let's do this forever.
Chief...
Here, cheese!
Now, next up is Ryo.
Let's go to the Kiyomizu Temple.
Wait a minute, Chief.
I haven't even taken a single photo yet.
Hmph, it's a waste of film.
Chief, that's too much.
Traveling is a way off, and I'm a pathetic person.
Okay, I'll just take one.
Hehehe, please.
Chief, please take a cool one.
Here, cheese!
Huh...?
Yui!
Yui!!!
R-Ryo!
Yieee!!!
Argh!
I really fell from the Kiyomizu's line.
Idiot!
Huh?
Is there anyone to destroy the Kiyomizu Temple?
That's not true! I didn't break it!
Why don't you worry about me?
It's okay! You won't die that easily!
Hey, you're the chief's bad guy!
So this is the 21st century Kyoto.
So what are you going to do, Kei?
You two must be traveling around Kyoto.
Even if I say that, there are too many famous places in Kyoto.
We have to find them quickly.
Otherwise, Senpai's life will be in danger!
Chief, why do I have to sit in the front?
To purify your rotten heart.
I'll be quiet until I do that.
It can't be helped.
Ah, again.
What?
It's a mole!
This is heavy!
Just a bit...
Oh, no, no!
Now it's here, the idiot mole!
Let's get out of here!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Damn it! That Mogura is so quick to run away!
You idiot!
What are you doing to the national heritage site?
I will definitely kill you!
Ah, hot spring trips are only for this.
However, Ryotsu, it's not good to travel with you.
Yes, yes, it's the 65th time I've talked about it.
Ah, damn it, I have to bow my head to get here.
Yes, yes, I understand.
In general, Ryotsu, do you know how much I'm suffering for you?
Yes, I understand.
It's not good to travel with you.
Yes, yes.
You're bowing your head to get here.
It's the 66th time.
Did you say something?
No, no, no.
I really can't be like Chief Ohara.
I'm here.
Did you finally understand, you idiot?
You can't be like Chief Ohara.
Chief, I'm going back to my room.
I see.
There's a bus that's surprisingly fast if there's a car.
It's the type that's easy to get lost.
I see.
Don't care for thet he care about me.
Ryotsu.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's no police office to do such a challenging thing.
Please stop, chief.
We can see a little further from here.
S-S-Shh.
Uncle, I can't stand these.
Don't do it.
My god.
What?!
I'm sorry!
-Excuse us! -Excuse us!
I will kill Ryotsu Kankichi for sure!
Thanks to you, I was able to become a commander!
The chief will kick the house!
-I will be a commander! -Captain Ryo!
W-what are you doing?
Ryo! Are you okay?
I'm so glad!
Why are you here?
Actually...
What?
Oh...
Why are there two of us?
Since the 24th century...
Hmm...
It's like a dream...
I can't believe it.
Then, the reason why I fell off the stage of Kiyomizu,
and the Mobra Incident in Ryoanji...
Could it be...
It's definitely Terminator's doing!
Come on, Ryotsu!
Ryo!
What's wrong?
You shouldn't bring such a robot!
You're my descendant!
Stop it, Ryotsu!
Ugh...
Really...
My family...
You're just like the legend!
Shut up!
I've been thinking of dying many times!
Don't be ridiculous!
You're so annoying!
Anyway, your body, the Ryotsu GPX,
is destined for the future of the Earth!
I will drink it under any conditions!
So please let me take it back!
Please!
What?
Hey!
I just told you that I will drink it under any conditions!
Y-yes!
I got it!
Then I'll take my body for a million yen!
A-a million yen?
Y-you...
You may be conquered by the aliens 300 years from now!
That's right!
Don't try to make a fortune by putting yourself in the weak spot of people!
Hmm!
Whatever you say,
if you don't give me a million yen,
I won't give you back my body!
Now, what are you going to do?
Okay, I understand.
What?
I've prepared your documents from the future.
I thought there might be something like this,
so I prepared them.
Here you are.
What?
What is this?
As you can see, it's a million-yen bill.
A million-yen bill?
You idiot!
It's meaningless if it's not money that can be used in the 21st century!
Even if you say that...
How about a gold worth a million yen?
A gold?
If it's a gold, I can sell it here!
Okay!
I'm okay!
But, it's hard to collect a gold worth a million yen from now on!
If we go back to the 24th century,
I think we can get it back somehow.
Okay, then get it ready quickly!
Okay.
Then, I'll go back to Tokyo with the time machine.
Can you use the helicopter?
Oh, it's okay because I have this.
At that time!
Wow!
You're a cat-shaped robot!
If I used this from the beginning,
I would have been able to come to Kyoto immediately, right?
I'm sorry.
I had to prepare a helicopter,
so I couldn't say it.
Then, I'll go back.
It seems that the story is true.
Oh, I forgot to wear my shoes.
Well, it's okay.
Here we go.
But, somehow...
I was cut.
I couldn't get help from the Kyoto sub-district.
It's not impossible.
It's like a SF story.
If this happens,
I'll go out directly
and ask for your help.
Okay, then.
I'll ask for your help.
Don't worry.
I just asked them for help.
Eh?
To whom?
More importantly, I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
Monster!
What are you saying
that the fate of future humanity is in your hands?
More than the future for hundreds of years,
I came to Kyoto,
so let's eat something delicious!
Excuse me.
Huh?
I've prepared a meal.
Oh, it's a good timing.
Huh?
Oh, it's a big one.
What about the meal?
Eh?
Ah!
What are you doing to me?
Mariya, are you okay?
Ah!
Captain,
I remember where you were.
You're a growing up.
It's a terrible situation.
We have to do something about it as soon as possible!
Uch…
Ah…
I won't let you get away!
S shameful loser!
Ugh!
I can't run away anymore.
Prepare yourself!
Oh, a firecracker!
That was pretty quick.
I was in a camp in Kurama-yama.
Are you Ushiwakamaru?
Who are you?
I'm not just a skeleton.
When an incident happens on the land,
I solve everything with just one firecracker!
I'm the leader of the Special Investigation Division, Sanbagaras!
Firecracker Deca-sadaima is here!
No analysis. No response data.
Then I'll kill the one who forgets!
Wait!
Terminé-chan, I don't like to fight.
Let's throw away our weapons and talk about this.
You...
Now, you, throw your weapons away!
Oh, no, again.
Don't be in a hurry.
Time to eat.
You must have a surprise for the first time.
I don't get it.
That's meaningless!
Now, the meal is over.
You're going to do it, after all?
What are you doing?
Now, you'll be naked, too.
W-What are you thinking?
Why do I have to be naked?
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
When humans are born, they're all naked.
Why don't we talk to each other in a pure heart like babies?
Idiot! That's a robot!
That's not what we're talking about!
All right, fine.
What? You're kidding!
But I was a little happy.
What?
That's not me!
I got it!
Hey!
I-I-I lost!
Hey, you! Don't try and decide who wins!
It is a loss for me!
Hey, you! I forgot about this!
Uwaaaah!
It's no use running away!
Hai!
Uwaaaah! Stop it, you idiot!
Uwaaaah!
Nyeh!
Ugh!
Uwaaaah!
La la la la la la la!
Love the sea and protect justice!
Who read this, Poseidon?
I'll put it in my tank!
In my tank!
Snikkon!
La la la la la la la!
I am the captain of the Water Police Force, Umino Dodaemon!
The
Dolphin Degga!
I can't analyze it! I can't analyze it!
A-Also...
You came to a good place!
Hahaha!
I'm here, so it's fine!
Dolphin!
Come on!
Come on! Dolphins!
Hehehe!
Well, you know...
It's a promise, after all!
Dolphins!
Hehehe!
Let's go!
Duh!
Yes!
All right!
Next!
Hehehe!
Come on!
That's right!
Duh!
"The Dolphin"
No! My cute dolphins are...
...in a big trouble!
Hey! I'm on board too!
This Dolphin is a one-man ride!
Sorry, Ryotsu!
You didn't come to save me, did you?!
"The Dolphin"
Don't look at me like that!
The moon's energy is in my back!
The stick of justice is in the dark!
If it's a sky incident, I'll take care of it!
The next death, the giant giant!
The same, the giant Venus!
I'm on board!
I don't care about the factory that's long!
Help me quickly!
Sure!
"The Dolphin"
Go!
Bye!
"The Dolphin"
What the...!?
Hey, they're coming this way!
They'll get us!
"The Dolphin"
I'll do it this way!
I'm the giant Venus, Henshinder!
I got it!
I don't have to do that!
Make up!
Let me explain!
When the Moonlight Giant transforms into Q-chan,
he can run 42.195 kilometers with his strong mental strength!
Q-chan, let's start here!
Yes!
I don't understand! I don't understand!
It's impossible!
Director! Where's Director?
Please praise Q-chan.
Ah, Director!
Damn it!
He's always doing those time-out jokes,
and now this is what's happening!
But what am I supposed to do if the Special Giant doesn't work at all?
DRIVE ON!
-Senpai! -Ryo-sama!
Ryo-chan!
Hey, it's you! Get me down!
Ryo-sama, I'm home!
Ryo-sama, are you all right?
Maybe, but...
Ryotsu, we finally got the Kyoto city police to act!
Senpai, where's he?
He's in the basement.
That's what we're talking about!
There they are!
Fire!
The Batow Car that the Kyoto prefecture gave us...
What are you talking about at a time like this?!
Damn it!
Nakagawa, get him!
Yes!
You're not getting away!
Maria, hurry up!
I know, boss!
I did it!
Maybe.
You really did it.
What?
Why did you become me?
And you're so innocent.
I went to the public bath.
It's not up to you, chief Ohara.
This is my weakness.
It's different.
Robots in the 24th century are pretty stupid.
I'll kill you!
I won't let you touch one finger of the
You're getting in the way!
Leave me alone!
Maria!
Great news is coming in from Kyoto.
Today's on-site, Mr. Yamazaki!
erna!
O-Ohara-kun!
Suddenly, a mysterious giant sea monster appeared in Kinkaku City!
Surprisingly, the monster is...
-It's me! -No, that's not me!
-I'm the real one here! -What are you doing?!
We're live-streaming!
That's a robot called "Termine-chan" that can transform into anything!
-Termine-chan? -Believe me!
The real one is...
Kinkaku!
It's terrible! A huge sea monster has started running off!
You idiot!
It's an pesticide that falled from under the sea!
Wait!
Hey, how could you keep clicking up these things earlier?
Well...
But what will be shown if you draw it?
Camera! It's a gold-plated paper pot!
Gold-plated paper pot!
Alright! Camera, change!
How's that?
This is the real gold-plated paper!
Oh no!
Oh no! It's on the front of the gold-plated paper!
It's on the front of the gold-plated paper!
-Ryo-chan! -Ryo-chan!
Die!
I crushed the gold-plated paper pot!
Ryo-chan!
I'll kill you!
Wh-What's that?!
Senpai!
Looks like you made it in time.
Nagagawa! Reiko! What's going on?
Actually, when Mr. Jitchok was being targeted at the emergency room...
...Terminator-chan was really reluctant to hear the sound of the boiling pipe!
Terminator-chan is weak to that sound.
Is that true?
How fast! Pick up the speaker!
Roger! Commence operation!
What was that great noise?
Na-Nagagawa, you're not even going to scare them?
Oh no! That's weird...
Oh, I've got it...
What are you thinking about, Kourin?
Damn it!
It's strange. I was so scared that I was shaking back then.
You said it was a boiling night.
Yeah.
A boiling night, huh.
Maybe...
Ryo!
Senpai!
What are you doing, Giryou-chan?
Ouch!
Oh, no!
With this, I'll take it down!
Ouch.
Oh? The Terminator is...
Wh-Wh-What's wrong?
Sir!
Just as I thought.
Huh?
Good grief! Who was he to be so weak?
Huh? Good grief! Who was he to be so weak?
It wasn't sound, it was fire!
I see!
Nakagawa, gather gas in the whole of Kyoto with a tank lorry!
We're going to get rid of him!
Idiot!
If we do that and Kyoto becomes a disaster, what are we going to do?
Even if we do that, it's a disaster, so there's no way we can do anything about it!
Gozu Tank Team!
Kill them!
Wait!
I'm going to get a bit of a bite!
That's right! It's a tank lorry in the middle of Kyoto!
Eh? Where?
No matter where you say it...
Yes!
Maria!
Maria, are you okay?
Yes. I was thrown off and crashed into the mountain...
So, where are we now?
We're here...
Daimonji Mountain!
Daimonji Mountain?
That Daimonji mountain in Daimonji Yaki?
That's it!
It's the only place in Kyoto that can burn a great fire!
Tank lorry, forward to the tank lorry!
Our destination is Daimonji Mountain!
Let's gather at Daimonji Mountain!
Again!
Our destination is Daimonji Mountain!
Here they come!
Take this!
Gozu's Tank!
Here we go!
We're here!
St grav!
We are here!
Let's get into the tank!
We're here!
They might not want us there!
I'm not waiting for you!
Senpai!
Help me, Nakagawa!
We have gathered the Tankrollies at Daimonji Mountain.
Senpai, please send the Terminators to Daimonji Mountain!
Please do it!
Hey, put on your pen!
Alright! I'm ready!
Senpai, I'm counting on you!
Ryozu, you're not ready yet?
He's here!
He's almost there!
Ryozu!
Ryozu, the Tankrollies are ahead of us!
Okay! Roger that!
Wait for me, Ryozu!
The mountain roads are really tough.
You can't escape anymore.
I'll crush you!
Idiot!
Ryozu!
W-What is this?
Beat!
Hey, Terminator!
Your mother is coming!
Hurray! Hurray!
Idiot!
Ryozu!
Wait for me!
Arghh!
I got you! You're a Terminator!
What did you do?
What do you mean?
Yes!
What does it mean?
W-What is this!?
Uh!
What?
Roar!
Groar!
Gwaaahhh!
Roar!
R-R-R-Roar!
And then...
Alright! I did it!
Ryo-sama!
Oh, Maria! I called you!
If it's for Ryo-sama's sake, even if it's in fire or water!
It's in the water!
It seems that it's settled down in one fell swoop.
But I never thought that we would be able to see Daimonji-yaki without the season.
Alright, we're done.
With this, the future of the Earth will surely be saved.
It's pretty easy, isn't it?
Well then, everyone, thank you for your cooperation.
That was good.
Hey, I wonder if my gold will really arrive.
Yes, I think it will arrive soon.
Oh, it seems that it has arrived.
Well then, I'll take my leave now.
Please be careful.
Take care.
Yes, thank you very much.
Gold! It's my gold!
With this, I'm rich again!
It's a gold!
No, you can't.
All of that gold is confiscated.
Huh? Why?
How much damage do you think you've done to Kyoto in this incident?
That's all Terminator's job, isn't it?
This is my gold!
No, you can't!
I'll use it as a refund fee.
That's right!
Hey, Chichoku!
Get me another trillion yen!
Yes!
Hey!
Wait, Chichoku!
Wait a minute!
Huh?
W-What's going on?
It seems that the time warp entrance has been blocked.
I-I can't believe it!
At one time, in the year 2301,
thanks to the Ryotsu GPX, which was brought back from the 21st century,
the Earth regained its peace once again.
It was a joyous, joyous...
There's no joyous thing!
This is the Honen Horizon's Stabilization Adventure!
Everyone, get ready to participate!
Go for it!
Atrocious!
This is the Honen Horizon!
Go for it!
Uh, I'm bored!
Then, how you're going to survive the rest of the day?
I can feel a miracle.
Hm...
So I kept kicking until I got home
When I was a red stone on the road
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgot
A religious man with a scary face
A girl with a loose heart
A girl with a burning heart
Look at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town