♪What Are You Doing?♪
Let's Play!
♪When you look at the daybreak that floats in the river♪
♪And you hit the stone on the wall, you can even fly on your horses♪
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I used to do
I was laughed at as a child
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are many bad things and bad things
The cityscape that doesn't change even one nightmare
Is strangely kind
From the water fountain of Tongari-boshi
To Taishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
I'm happy again if I win or lose
I realized it after losing
Because I'm stupid
What are you doing?
Chief, you're here?
You're early today
Shut up!
What do you mean you're sleeping while working?
I'm counting on you, Ryotsu!
What?
Even though my subordinates were working during the working hours
Just a little sleep
Will you pour tea on your head?
No, I'm...
I'm really happy to have a good boss
Good job, Ryotsu
You're not tired, are you?
How are you?
Then can I sleep in the back?
Yes
Of course
Chief, can I?
I'm on duty
Hmm
I'm on duty?
You can get paid just by driving a Porsche all night
What?
Is there such a job?
The owner of this car moved to Tokyo by transfer
But I couldn't find a parking lot
Tokyo doesn't have enough parking lots
You can use the company parking lot when you're there
But it costs 350 yen at night
You can't use the parking lot for a paid parking lot
Then if you park it overnight, it won't be a big deal
Yes, it costs close to 10,000 yen
That's why you asked for a part-time job
That's right
If I run around the Tokyo-Kansai line at a limited speed
The gas bill won't cost that much
I see
If you add gas and the speed fee to your part-time job
It's cheaper than the parking fee
You've thought about it, right?
But I'm not sleepy
It's still 4 o'clock
Nakagawa, change the car
Stop the car
Yes
It's a Corvette
The engine is quite modified
It's a beautiful driver
Let's chase Nakagawa
I don't like such words
Let's go
It's a Silver Metallic Corvette
Corvette Spingle 1
Hello, how are you?
It's nice to drive with a beautiful woman at dawn
Can you hear me?
Good morning
You laughed
Good job
Good night
Good morning
Hello
The engine is dead
What?
Good morning
Blast
What's wrong?
I don't feel well
Don't worry
Mr. Akai
I'll drive for a bit
Thank you
Are you hiding the Corvette?
You don't have to
Don't be slow, Nakagawa.
Roger that.
That bastard is finally giving up.
What's that car?
Is it 되는?
Subtitles by Subdiver
I forced him to stop.
This is an unthinkable, bold race.
Get out of the car!
What?
You're a woman? You're doing something unnecessary!
You!
Stop!
Ouch!
Thank you for your help.
It's a '68 Corvette.
It's really cool.
Damn it! Let me go!
Don't be so rude!
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm a member of the Katsushika family.
Hello.
This is a bad traffic violation.
I see.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yes!
Well, that's a great driving technique.
It's not that much.
Do you like American cars?
I'm busy at work, so I can only drive at night.
I see.
I thought you were driving all night because there was no parking lot.
Ha ha.
No way.
It's an interesting man.
He's right next door.
Well, how about having some tea?
Hmm...
What can I do?
He looks really nice, so I'll go with him until the day of the festival.
Hooray!
I-I can't believe it.
I didn't know I'd get caught up in a car accident.
Ladies must be able to see men!
We have a film.
So, I leave the Porsche to you.
Eh?
Sorry for keeping you waiting!
Let's go then.
Eh?
Alright!
Sen-Senpai!
Geez...
Here I come!
You're so mean.
Ah! I did it!
What's your name?
I'm Kyoko.
Ah.
What's your hobby?
I'm a food researcher.
I teach Kado, Sado, and martial arts.
And I love cars so much I even race in them.
You have many hobbies.
I love cars too.
You seem to like it.
Is that so?
What's your hobby?
Eating food.
Eh?
Huh?
Why do you know my name?
Well...
There's no one in Tokyo who doesn't know Ryo Tsu Kankichi from the Kameyari Park Exhibition.
Really?
I was so famous that it's a long time ago.
But you seem like someone you know.
This is the first time I've ever met you.
Huh?
Your ring!
We're married.
I'm married.
I don't care about that at all.
I'm good at taking things from others.
You're a ugly husband, aren't you?
I guess so.
I'm sure you are.
What's your face like?
My eyebrows are sharp and my eyes are sharp.
Oh, your eyebrows are sharp and your eyes are sharp.
I have a beautiful beard.
Beard?
What is it?
It's a hair like a head.
A head...
What happened?
Nothing.
That old man is not my husband.
I'm wondering what's going on.
I can't imagine what's going on.
It's already this late?
I'm sorry, Mr. Ryotsu.
Oh, I see.
I'll pay for it.
Really?
Thank you for the meal.
Well, I hope we can meet again.
That's fine.
I'll invite you next time.
Take care.
All right.
She looks elegant and beautiful, doesn't she?
Isn't she?
She seems to be studying cooking.
Her driving technique is excellent.
She's a super star.
Her style is excellent.
Ah!
I finally see a red thread.
It's spinning.
And on the ceiling.
A red thread?
Yes.
Goodbye to the long solitude.
Wait a minute, Mr. Ishii.
Isn't she married?
Yes.
Ryo, stop it.
You're not married.
Shut up.
The more you have an obstacle, the more you burn.
Maria.
My heart is burning with the fire of envy.
Ryo!
You're too much to be loved!
Calm down, Maria.
So you're giving up?
Listen carefully.
You're a man.
You can't get married with me.
But she's a woman.
If you marry her, you can get married.
Ryo-sama, you're terrible!
I'm so desperate for you!
I hate you, Maria.
What's wrong?
Why is my mother in the picture with Ryo-sama?
What?
Then this beauty is Maria's mother?
I thought I saw her somewhere.
I didn't expect to see Maria's mother.
The world is so big and small.
But Maria's mother is still young.
She's still 36 years old.
Maria's mother?
So that's her father-in-law?
Maria, how old are you?
I'm 20.
So...
You were born when you were 16?
Yes.
You're still in middle school.
You're so stupid.
That stupid father is a coward.
Maria, marry me.
No!
It's a crime to make a mistake.
It's not that my father is stupid.
My mother is more passionate about my father.
What?
Your mother is more...
I can't believe it.
Where on earth is she from?
We met by chance.
My mother was born between
her father, Denyemon Imada,
the son of the hermit,
and my mother, the shaman.
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
She was raised like a doll in a box.
At one point, she left alone out of curiosity
and was involved with the bad guys.
On the spot,
Father, who was training, happened to pass by.
My cute sister, let's play together.
What are you doing? Please stop!
I can't stand that face.
Stop it!
It was a sudden event.
In an instant, I defeated all the Chimpiras.
I'm sure the prince who came to help me on the horseback
remembered my mother.
I was completely mesmerized.
I feel that the girl who grew up in the house
is more likely to fall for the prince.
But, there was also the opposition of your parents, right?
Yes, but my mother's determination was firm.
My father took the plane to New York to go to training,
and we fell into a cliff.
And I was born in New York.
I heard that my parents forgave us because of that.
Well, that's good.
You are dramatic, Senpai.
What is dramatic?
I was just deceived by that Chimpira's father.
I will make you wake up!
Even now, she is still beautiful,
but she was very beautiful at that time.
Damn you, Chimpira!
Oh!
Ai, how are you?
I'm fine.
She is your mother, right?
Yes.
She looks even more beautiful in the daytime.
Ryo-san, thank you for breakfast.
Well, I can't believe I can see you again.
Ah, come on.
Ryo-sama!
Mother, you are terrible.
You know I love Ryo-sama,
but you are dating me.
Ai-chan, you are mistaken.
I just wanted to know what kind of man Ai-chan was in love with.
Oh, I see.
Really?
So, how did Ryo-sama look in your mother's eyes?
He was as unique as my darling,
and he looked good with Ai-chan.
Ah, I'm so happy!
As expected of my mother!
I came here because I was going to invite Ryo-san to my house
and have a dinner with him.
Really?
Yes.
If you don't mind,
please join us.
Ah, I'm so happy!
Don't hesitate.
Hehehe.
I am a much better man than that Chimpira's father.
I have a chance to sell him to a better man than that Chimpira's father.
Welcome, everyone.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Hey!
Yes?
Arrange your clothes properly.
Oh, yes.
I have to draw white lines, too.
It's too detailed.
Your mother's weakness is that she likes to look beautiful.
If she is a beautiful woman,
she will forgive anything.
Ah!
What's wrong, mother?
W-where is she?
A cat has entered my house!
Darling!
Yes, honey!
I'm home!
Ah, Shikigomashi!
Ryo-san!
Darling, you are so annoying.
You are too old.
Why are you here?
I invited you here!
I'm sorry.
There are cat footprints in the hallway.
Please clean it up.
Yes, honey.
I'll do it right away.
Ah!
Hey!
It's my job!
I like to look beautiful,
but when I see you dirty,
I want to look beautiful.
Ah!
There are stains here, too.
And here, too.
Hey!
I told you it's my job!
It's dirty here, too.
Hey, stop it!
Yes, it's clean.
Don't wipe it!
Stop it!
It's dirty!
Ah!
Great!
I didn't know you liked to look beautiful.
Darling, you have to learn from me.
I did it!
I'll show you what a good man I am.
Ryo-chan!
What are you planning to do?
I feel sorry for you, honey.
I feel sorry for you, too.
What?
Darling!
What are you talking about?
Honey, it's nothing.
I won't let you do whatever you want anymore.
Come here, please.
Wow!
It's a huge room!
It's a luxurious room.
What?
All of them are in pairs.
It's like a new house.
Geez!
Don't touch me!
Don't use a pair of cups for your old man!
It's disgusting!
It's a huge house!
Ah!
What's wrong, honey?
Over there!
Is it because of the earthquake?
That garden stone is about a centimeter off to the right.
Can you fix it?
Yes, yes.
Leave it to me.
Yes!
Oh!
I'm going to be a fool with a fire.
I'll go on my way.
Don't be absurd at all.
It's fine.
Okay, I'll go on my way.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Mom!
I love you!
I'm not the one to be expected!
You two are both old enough, so don't be reckless.
Here.
I've prepared a meal for you.
Wow, it looks delicious!
As expected of a cooking researcher.
It's an original dish of Japanese cuisine.
Maria, that's enough. I'll eat it too!
Hey, wait!
I've never seen such delicious food before.
Well, I'm glad you said that.
I can eat it three times a day.
You're jealous, aren't you, Ryotsu?
It's not a big number. Look, I've already eaten this much.
What? Me?
You're a little too much!
Hey, Ryotsu!
Thank you for the meal.
The food with love is the best.
I ate more than you.
Of course, I ate more!
What?
Well, I'm glad you're so happy.
There's still a lot of food to prepare.
There's still more?
I'm already...
What?
I'm already full!
What's wrong, Ai?
I just saw someone sneak into the garden.
Isn't it a thief?
What?
Alright, I'll catch him.
No, I'll catch him.
Leave the thief to the Darlings, and we'll wait for the meal.
Hey, you!
You!
Bastard!
I wanted to show you some good stuff.
But you're not strong enough to take this!
I'll show you some beautiful skills!
I'm Mie-chan of Buffy!
What?
It's an opening!
I'm wearing a protective gear to prevent this.
You're a professional fighter!
It won't work at all!
It's not painful or itchy.
I'll get the money right away.
Oh no! It's coming in!
I can't forgive this!
X!
Where's the safe?
Just a moment.
I-It was just one blow!
I trained him for your sake, but he's stronger than me.
You two!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'll borrow a super strong punch from you!
You've got to clean it up, please.
Okay?
Yes.
You're dead wrong, lady.
It's rare to see you endure this tearful incident.
I-I know that I have been loved.
I will get married for now.
See?
He's still being called.
What do I do?
What should I do?
I'm going to be a monkey!
What's wrong? Why are you looking at me like that?
You're not like the usual Kotone-chan!
Cheer up!
Oh, right!
When the Hanayashiki satellite is complete,
let's go on it together!
We're the best!
We'll definitely do it!
Next time, "Asakusa's First Love Story"!
Don't miss it!
I hear rumors that I'm a woman who can't fall in love
But I have a lot of things I want to do
I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be more free than a bird
With the speed of the full moon,
I change into a lady's dream
My love, I'm sorry, wait for me
The future of the panorama is
pretty bright
You understand, right?
I'm sorry
Wait for me