"The End of the Rain"
♪ When you watch TV ♪
♪ Make the room bright and try to get away ♪
♪ The End of the Rain ♪
♪ Like someone calling ♪
♪ You walk looking back ♪
♪ Your hand is drawn to your mother ♪
♪ The strange feeling I felt at the time ♪
♪ So I tried to walk ♪
♪ Only the black part of the Akegai Tile ♪
♪ The Akegai Tile ♪
♪ I tried to walk ♪
♪ Everyone was a child once ♪
♪ But everyone forgets ♪
♪ A politician with a great face ♪
♪ A blue aunt in the eyes ♪
♪ Turn around and look ♪
♪ At that corner ♪
♪ You can meet everyone ♪
♪ There is a wall over there ♪
♪ Everyone come to our town ♪
Thank you!
"The Trouble is When You Forgot"
Are you sure you forgot all that?
Yes.
I already told you so much!
Ugh! I'm so tired!
Boss, stay still!
You're getting better blood pressure again.
I just said that.
What did you say?
I was kidding!
Boss!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry! Medicine and water.
Here!
Hmm.
Ryo-chan, what did you forget?
-What did you say? -The resident's report.
The resident's report?
In the resident's report, only Ryotsu didn't submit the resident's report.
He said he would bring it a month ago.
A month ago?
What's wrong with you guys?
Chief, I'll bring it tomorrow.
Really?
Yes, I've been forgetting things lately, but I'll bring it tomorrow.
A man, Ryotsu Kankiji, doesn't have a second word.
Not just a second word, but a third or a fourth word.
What are you talking about? I'll definitely bring it tomorrow!
Ryo.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
I bought the pre-sale of the Naitakeba four days ago, but then I had an urgent job and went to the countryside.
I came home last night.
I thought you might know the results.
Oh, I see.
Which race is it?
I'll ask you for the 10th race.
The 10th race is where the number 8 Bakunyu Gal ran away and became Manpa-gen.
Is that so?
Really?
I bought it at the store.
What about the second one?
It's the father gag order that Horiguchi, who came to chase me, took.
It's 82 and it's 18,000 yen.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah, by the way, I took 10,000 yen.
Oh, really?
It's 1.8 million yen.
Well, yeah.
Then, what about the 11th race?
Yeah, the main race is...
Ryo, I remember the result.
I'll ask you for the results of the main race again.
See you.
What a weird guy.
I want to do some work.
Ryotsu, where's the sense of forgetting?
You can forget about me right away.
What does that mean that you remember the result of the race perfectly?
Chief.
Chief, why don't you take a break?
That's right.
Ryo, if you forget the census tomorrow, you'll be fired.
Yes, it's fine.
Look after yourself.
Over there.
Mrs.
I'm glad that I could make a cup ramen with a pachinko.
It's really helpful when you don't have money.
Boss, are you done?
Yeah, it's much better.
Boss, what do you want for lunch?
We're thinking of going to a new restaurant on the third floor.
I think it's better to make soba today, so I'll take it.
How about you, senior?
I want cup ramen.
You're pretty shy.
Thank you very much.
I don't have to ask rich people like you for a meal.
But you got a loan four or five days ago.
Yeah, it's about 1.8 million yen.
Yeah, it's all a bar if you have four days.
Only four days?
Where are the rich people?
But today...
Reiko, I forgot that today is my payday.
I guess so.
Right.
If you tell him, he'll use it all up.
You can keep quiet until you remember for him.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, you're getting married. Congratulations.
Yes, Mr. Ohara.
Mr. Manager.
I'm glad I made it in time.
What can I get you?
Can you give this to Ryotsu?
It's a salary bag.
I was going to deposit Ryotsu's salary, but I couldn't because the account was gone.
It can't be helped.
I see.
I'll give it to him.
By the way, I need proof that he received it.
Please tell him that I'll bring the money tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Oh, Mr. Manager.
Ryo, it's a phone call.
Hello.
I'm already out of time. What's up?
Shut up.
You're always out of time.
Don't talk about the past.
Mr. Manager, if you get too excited, you'll lose your blood vessels.
Shut up.
Tomorrow, bring me a bank note in addition to the resident's card.
A bank note?
Why is it a bank note?
It's important to you.
Don't forget it.
You're such a good boy.
It was a good night.
Father, I'll make you a beer.
Sure.
Here you are.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Thank you.
After all, beer after sunset is delicious.
Father, you really look delicious.
No, the beer I drink at my mother's house is special.
Father, you're just...
What's wrong?
I feel like I've forgotten something important.
Oh, no, father.
Don't you have a lot of things to forget these days?
No, it's not that.
It's not Ryotsu.
Oh, right.
It's probably Ryotsu.
Yay, it's Ryotsu!
Why do I have to remember such a guy until I get home?
The beer is getting worse.
You can't remember it, so it's not a big deal.
Yeah, I remember it well in the bathroom.
Okay.
I'll go to the bathroom again and remember it.
Huh?
Are you okay even though you drank beer?
I'm okay.
You're too serious.
Ryo, that is to say, money, money.
Oh, I remember.
It's a salary bag.
Damn it.
I'm going to make a great feeling.
It's a very small bag.
Is that so?
You can eat ramen well in the morning.
Moreover, I've been eating three meals a day for a week.
Shut up.
It's the day before the holiday, so it can't be helped.
What are you talking about?
Don't come out of there suddenly.
Ouch!
What a man who's been so nosy since morning.
Senior, are you alright?
Ryotsu, did you bring your residence card?
No, I'm sorry. I forgot again.
Then where's your passport?
Passport? It's my first time hearing it.
You called me yesterday afternoon, right?
Was I?
Why do you always forget things like that?
I'm sorry. Tomorrow I'll definitely...
Wait.
I'll write it on paper so don't forget.
But it's about Ryo-chan, so I'm going to lose my hair.
Oh, I see.
It's okay. I'll never lose it.
I can trust you.
No way.
That's right.
What?
Stay still.
What are you doing? Please stop.
Shut up and stay still.
It hurts. It hurts.
Alright, that's enough.
What are you doing?
There's a staircase like this.
But I wonder if there's a mirror in Ryo-chan's room.
Even if there is, I don't think he'll see it.
Oh, is that so?
Alright, I'll write it here too.
This is good.
If you wash it in the bath, it'll fall.
It's okay. I won't go to the bath for about a week.
I see.
Shut up. Leave it alone.
I'm still worried.
That's right. This is the forget-me-not prevention machine.
What machine is this?
My granddaughter made it in kindergarten.
I'll lend it to you. Use it well.
What?
I don't want to use such an important thing.
Don't say that.
Write down things you might forget.
If you check them one by one, you can press them.
If you press all of them, you won't forget anything.
It's easy, right?
It's a perfect machine for you.
I see.
You can change the place where the handkerchief is written into a bank account or a resident's card.
What? I see.
I'm a kindergarten teacher.
Huh? What?
Chief, what's wrong?
I think there's something important today.
Look. You forgot, too.
If you're asking me, I'll lend you this machine.
Shut up! Don't do that with you.
Mine is just a forget-me-not.
I remember when I entered the waste disposal.
Then, we can do the same thing when we entered the waste disposal.
That's right.
It might help you to remember.
Maybe it will bring back memories.
By the way, I remembered that yesterday.
Then let's recreate it.
I think I was putting out a map from the beginning.
I was carrying tea, and Ryo-chan was eating cup ramen.
Hey, do you want to eat again?
You can't do it in the same situation.
I'll make it. Ryo-chan, get on your seat.
Good grief.
Ready.
Then let's start.
Good.
I can eat ramen from the morning.
You said you can eat it.
Ryo-chan, don't forget the play.
I got it.
When I came to this position, Ryo-chan put out ramen.
Senpai, please put it out.
Can you put it out so easily?
Ryo-chan.
Yes.
If you put this much pepper in it, you can put it out.
Remember, Ryo-chan.
Then, once again.
You can eat it if you eat it.
I'm going to be happy.
Wow!
Due to the color, this is wrong.
Why?
Oooh.
Ryo, you can't eat it.
Ryo-chan, just ...
You can only eat soup.
I don't want to eat it.
No!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Congratulations!
That's great, Chief.
So, what is it?
Actually...
You guys are just wasting your time!
Ryo-tsu!
Huh?
Actually, I got your salary from the Manager yesterday.
Salary?
Yes.
It was yesterday!
He's still thinking about it.
What an idiot.
Ryo!
Please give me back my salary, Chief!
Okay!
Don't be so excited.
I'll give it to you now.
Don't be so impatient.
Huh?
N-No!
It was there before I arrived at the office!
Chief, what's wrong?
Please give me my salary!
Oh...
I have a lot of money I want to give you,
but I need a bank account as proof of receiving it.
So you said it was a bank account.
Uh, yeah.
Okay, I'll bring it right away!
Oh no...
What should I do?
Salary! Salary!
Oh, it was in my book.
Oh, right.
It might be my pocket.
I just remembered something.
I'll go to the office, so please take care of it.
Okay.
Chief, what's the matter?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you back.
It's nothing...
Uh...
So I dropped it when I went to the office.
Oh, right.
I'll ask the time check.
Chief!
That was pretty quick.
Would you like to have lunch with me?
More importantly, your salary!
We're not good friends, Ryo!
I'm going to eat eel because I'm angry.
Didn't you eat soba because you were sick?
No, I'm already healed.
I'm suspicious.
When the chief suddenly becomes kind, he always has something in mind.
What are you talking about?
I invited you because I saw you eating ramen every day.
I eat ramen every month before my payday.
Sometimes it was only water.
But the chief once...
What are you talking about?
I'm inviting you because I'm aware of your health.
Let's go.
Have you decided your order?
Eel Nami.
I want to eat special.
What?
If you don't want to, you don't have to pay.
I'll pay from my salary.
Please pay.
I didn't say it because I didn't want to treat you.
I ate ramen so much that it was a mess.
I just thought it would be just right.
What's your order?
One special eel and ramen.
I understand.
It was a big treat.
It's more suspicious.
It's good to be luxurious sometimes.
Did he use my salary?
No, the chief is only serious.
Then, did you forget your salary bag at home?
Did you drop it?
What are you talking about?
Did you see my face?
No, the chief has got wrinkles lately and has gotten old.
If you have a subordinate like you, you can get older by hard work.
I think so.
But if you get old, you'll have many forgotten things and dropped things.
What are you talking about?
It's not like that.
Thank you for waiting.
You're welcome.
Let's eat.
Yeah, let's eat.
It looks like a pot.
Thank you for the meal, sir.
Look, there's a cafe here.
I want to drink coffee.
I don't need it.
Oh, really?
Then I'll drink it by myself.
Please pay me, sir.
Oh, I want to drink coffee, too.
I want to drink coffee.
There's no doubt about it.
Two Blue Mountains, the most expensive.
I'll have a blend.
I'll treat you, sir.
Two Blue Mountains, please.
Yes, sir.
I realized I don't have a salary.
Sir.
Oh, Reiko.
Hey, didn't you have a meal at a new restaurant today?
I was in a hurry, so I gave up.
That's too bad.
Okay, I'll pay you for this.
What?
What are you surprised about?
I'm taking care of them every day, so I have to pay you sometimes as a senior.
It's kind of creepy.
I'm afraid of the consequences, so I'll hold back.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'll accept your kindness.
Then, sir, please pay me for my salary.
I'll pay you for this.
It's too bad.
That's it.
Reiko, Nakagawa, I'll treat you to a Blue Mountain, too.
Don't hold back and enjoy it.
I'll pay you for the pay, but I'll definitely ask for your rent.
You don't have my salary, do you?
What are you saying?
I've got it.
What, what's this confident attitude?
Damn it.
I got it.
I did. Then please give me the pay.
I will. If you want to buy something, write down the price, the reason and the reason in the form.
Then I will give it to you.
What are you talking about?
Why do you have to do that?
From today, I will take care of your pay.
This is not a joke.
Shut up.
It's bad that you lost your account.
If I manage it, the balance of the account will be zero on the payment date of public funds.
That's a good idea.
If the director manages it, we can also save money.
Don't say unnecessary things.
Damn it.
I did it. I'm done.
This is what I want now.
Which one?
The engine of the Radicon plane is 20,000 yen.
The Pachinko is 50,000 yen.
The
No. I can't accept this.
What are you doing?
Buy something that will be useful to you.
Let's start over.
If you write it properly, I will give you all the money.
Then please.
This time, I wrote it properly.
Yes, that's it.
Bentsu, the apartment, the land.
What are you thinking?
You're thinking about something that will be useful for the future.
Where do you get 32 million yen?
It's a pre-paid salary.
Until about 10 years later.
Don't mess with me.
Make it useful for your life.
Damn it.
Okay.
What?
I've rewritten it.
Is it this much?
It's just a stupid thing.
It's a sacred book.
What are you going to do?
Of course, I'm going to read it.
Liar!
You can't read it.
That's a prejudice.
There are no prejudices in Shimura or Takakura prefecture.
Please calm down, director.
It's a pity to judge by appearance.
That's right.
If it's a sacred book, I don't think it will be lost.
You're a smart guy.
What is this Amida Nyorai?
I'm interested in the heart of the Buddha.
Please tell me.
There is no God.
I believe in the Buddha.
Anyway, it's expensive.
What?
8,000 yen for three times?
The contents of the head are about 30 yen.
Isn't it too expensive?
I want to buy it from a charismatic user.
What's charismatic?
Your head is enough for my barricade.
This is no good.
I've seen everything.
Bring it over there.
Everything is okay.
Don't say stupid things.
This is all I can admit.
What?
Take it.
What is this?
This is the amount I've paid.
I can't buy a sacred book with this.
I won't read it anyway.
Look for it in an old bookstore.
It costs about 200,000 yen.
Buy it with your personal plastic model.
There is no plastic model for Amida Nyorai.
You must do it yourself.
That's all.
I'm in school.
What can I do with 1000 yen now?
I'm saying that I'm going to complain.
If you ask me, it's because of this bank.
I'm going to complain.
Recommendation of the general course?
Oh, dear.
Today's the end of the day.
Gyo-tsu!
Mujo!
What's this, Soudou?
Did you buy the Bible?
More importantly, look at this.
Recommendation of the general course?
If you join the general course, you can get a monthly deposit.
And if you don't have a public budget, you can get a refund from the deposit.
That's convenient.
I'm joining the general course.
So you don't have to manage the club.
Oh, I see.
Gyo-tsu, let's have a drink tonight.
That's fine.
Don't say harsh things.
Let's talk slowly.
Gyo-tsu, let's have a drink tonight.
Something happened today.
How about sushi?
Gyo-tsu, let's have a drink tonight.
Don't say harsh things.
Senpai.
Hey, Honda.
What's wrong, Chief Ohara?
I'm asking for your help.
No, I have to be considerate of my subordinates.
You're a good guy.
I'm saying that I'm going to hold back, but you don't listen.
I don't listen.
Senpai, are you going to hold back?
Oh, right.
Senpai, you can't do that.
You'll forget your important pay bag.
What?
My pay bag?
Gyo-tsu, you're wrong.
Why do you have my pay bag?
I was told that I can deliver it to you.
Your staff?
Yes.
I heard that it was on the table in the locker room this morning.
The table in the locker room?
On the table?
Yes.
I took out my pay bag in the locker room this morning, put it next to my bag, and changed it.
Oh, I forgot to put it on the table.
Gyo-tsu.
I used your pay for the research experiment of the rate of recovery of the raw materials in the book.
After all, my staff was honest.
Oh, good.
I think it's just a forgotten item.
Gyo-tsu, what are you talking about?
What?
Gyo-tsu.
It's kind of dangerous.
You two should use this.
Really.
What is this?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Chief!
What happened to Sushi and Sake!
Because the pay is back, live alone!
Until you pay us, we will chase you to the end of the earth!
Are you been waiting for the end of the earth?
Dashi Dashi Dashi
I'm going to get my eyebrows done
and then I'll be on my way to the station
Dashi Dashi Dashi
I'm going to get my eyebrows done
and then I'll be on my way to the station
I'll sleep on my dad's back
It's これからの I'm going to get my eyebrows done
And then I'll be on my way to the station
I'll sleep on my dad's back
I'm sleeping on my dad's back
I love myself like this!
I have no problem every day!
My heart is beating!
Monday!
Monday! Monday!
No problem!
You want me to monitor your new toys?
What's this?
A hero transformation set?
What? What?
You can react to voices and pose?
Oh, this sounds fun!
Hey, everyone!
Let's play with these!
Next time on Hypercop Ryotsu!
Thanks for watching!
♪ Over there is Kameari! ♪
♪ Oh, there's Kameari for sure! ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town! ♪
Thank you!