Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I took off my love stone and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging on a bike ♪
♪
♪ ♪
♪ The sunset falls ♪
♪ It will end tomorrow, too ♪
♪ I lost my happiness ♪
♪ I realized, I'm an idiot ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
"Gekisou Okuno Ozomichi"
"A "
He's so cute.
I'm so excited to recognize him.
Na-Nana-chan.
I don't understand how you feel about me.
What hard work I put into you.
I hate you, Honda-san!
Nana-chan.
The customer's phone is not picking up.
Where it's not too deep.
Hana-chan...
An old pond.
The sound of water jumping into the river.
What are you saying?
You're an adult, but you don't know the Matsuo Basho?
Matsuo Basho?
A great haiku artist from the Edo period.
Over there.
This is the Basho.
The Basho!
He set off on his journey from Kokofukagawa to Okuno Hosomichi.
Okuno Hosomichi?
Yes.
You'll know what life is like if you travel Okuno Hosomichi.
What life is like...
That's a difficult question.
Actually, my grandpa told me this.
He loves the Basho.
That's why you got influenced.
I'm Matsuoku Ichi.
I'm Honda Hayato.
Um, why were you crying earlier?
Uh, I was embarrassed.
Did you have a fight with your friend?
No.
My bad.
Is this really the name of the climax?
Maybe we should change it.
She was worried about her job, so I thought I'd cheer her up.
Um...
What?
I read the manuscript of that manga, and it was really interesting.
I don't know if anyone who's been a fan of the manga for a long time will be surprised.
Mr. Honda.
I know that you worked hard to write the manga, and I want you to have confidence.
Mr. Honda, shut up.
N-Nana?
You don't know how I feel about you.
You don't know how hard it was for me.
I don't know how hard it was for you.
Nana.
I wanted to be a little bit of your strength.
But when I think about it, my advice is a hassle.
What are you talking about?
It's not that bad.
What?
I think so, but somehow...
Thank you.
The voice of cicadas that are quiet and stick to the rocks.
Is that a place?
Yes.
The sound of cicadas and cicadas is interesting.
It's a place that was said to be a place of the ears, and there were a lot of sounds.
Oh, the silence and the voice of cicadas that are sticking to the rocks.
The sound of cicadas is amazing, isn't it?
It's a momentary flight to another world.
The sound of cicadas.
You don't have to be so nervous. You should get along with your friends.
I have to go.
See you.
Thank you.
The statue is moving!
It moves at 5 p.m.
Why does the statue move?
I want to show you the various directions of the Sumida River that traveled on the narrow road in the back.
It's amazing to be treated like that even after you die.
It's amazing.
Sorry, Nana.
Sarah, I am so sorry but how about your work?
"The moon, the day the stars, and its doğal bodies-
cu- cu-
The moon, the day the stars, and its doğal bodies-
"We found the right way to write the name of the moon in the back of the Matsuoba oyun.
"The moon, the day the stars, and its doğal bodies-
and its doğal bodies-
"And the years as it starts to snow.
That's right.
What does it mean?
The moon is a forever traveler and the snow is a traveler again.
That's what it means.
Why is the moon a traveler?
Even if I ask why...
Nakagawa can't explain it well.
Honda doesn't really know.
Because the sun is still low.
Mr. Honda, why are you suddenly interested in the place?
I met a junior high school student who was familiar with the place.
He's a pretty good junior high school student.
My uncle is a fan of the place.
I see.
When I met him at the grave in Sumida River, I was pretty depressed.
He was dumped by Nana Otohime.
No, I just got the wrong idea.
But you can't contact Otohime from then on, right?
That's what the public says.
Originally, the sales were high.
But you're a little cartoonist.
You give up on the moon and the moon.
I give up on a love that can't be fulfilled.
I don't want to!
Did that elementary school student comfort Mr. Honda who was depressed?
The poem of the place he read stuck in my heart.
Somehow I was really healed.
That's why I bought this book.
That's right.
That's a good story.
I know the place.
The frog jumped into the pond and fainted.
Oh, Ryo-chan.
It's completely different.
You sound like that to your seniors.
I can do more interesting things.
Like a pond.
I can predict the frog that comes out of Ryo's pond.
I don't feel like listening.
I don't want to listen.
You guys are making fun of me like that.
I have the talent of a writer.
I'm clear from the fact that I made a hit in a manga.
Frog is a little thing.
If you say so.
Then why don't you apply for this?
Director!
Good morning.
What is it?
The
Ryo-san.
Done!
The
Ryo-san,
the
The
I'll change into a horse and come back.
You have a lot of words to say.
A horse?
I can't believe it's a miracle horse!
Stop it, idiot!
Listen, in haiku, you put a symbol that represents the season.
If it's spring, you put a symbol that represents the summer.
You don't know that, so what are you aiming for?
You're a laughing stock.
I know, Kigo-Grai.
I should put it in, right?
Speaking of spring...
I see.
How about Okashou and Tennoushou?
Recently, I have a stomachache and it hurts again.
That's not good.
Hey, you don't have any ignorance, do you, chief?
Idiot!
Okashou and Tennoushou?
You should apply to the central competition!
I apply to the central competition every week.
I'm not good at it.
Matsuo!
What?
I met you in Sumidagawa.
I'm a junior.
Matsuo Kuiichi, a junior, won last time.
He is the first member of the horse research team to be the chairman of this competition.
He is the grandson of the horse repairman Matsuo.
He is a great candidate for the haiku world.
He won the competition, not the entrance competition.
I've seen this old man on TV.
Life is a journey.
You have to travel the narrow way of life.
You can see what life is like.
I want to tell you young people.
You are not playing games at home.
You should travel the narrow way of life.
Have you seen that program?
Actually, I just read the narrow way of life.
Matsuo was the grandson of a famous person.
The winner last time, the grandson of the chairman?
The son-in-law of the haiku world, a friend of Honda.
3,000,000 yen.
I can do it.
Here it is, sir.
If you climb the stairs in this gate, you will find the statue of the Buddha.
The shrine nearby is the new one.
You're getting better at it.
When you climb that staircase, you will find the Sumida River.
Yes.
Sumida River
The Sumida River
Yes.
Let's go at full speed.
The
I can't even without you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's OK.
*Cough*
I was aware of the place.
Uguisuga, hohohokekyo, hohoke...
No way! You should give up on winning.
I knew it.
No way! I'm wearing my uniform!
Amagaeru! Gero Gero Ge Gero! Gero Gero!
A little bit of a bug.
Well, I'm free to apply.
You're such a little brat.
But you're not in a good mood here.
The water bubble is a big investment.
I'll endure it for three million yen.
Then, why don't you introduce me to your grandpa?
I'll do anything, so please do me a favor.
Just like this, just like this.
You're unreasonable, senpai.
I have a place I want to go.
If you take me, I'll introduce you to your grandpa.
All right, let's go!
Where is it?
Odaiba? Roppongi? Shiodome?
Or is it a amusement park in Chiba?
Matsuo, where do you want to go?
Okuno Hosomichi.
It's 2,400 kilometers from here.
2,400 kilometers?
What a person!
Oh, no, a child of your own taste...
No, no, a child, what is it?
It's cheap. It's a Honda.
Take me there.
Me?
But will the people at home forgive me?
You don't have to worry about that.
I don't care if this old man here
is advertising Okuno Hosomichi.
Are you taking me?
Are you not?
But 2,400 kilometers is a big trip, senpai.
He's a child.
He won't find out if you drive on the road.
You can just go around Kanto Kinko on a bike.
Use this place a little.
Matsuo needs this trip now.
I got it!
Let's travel Okuno Hosomichi together, Matsuo!
Yay!
Matsuo, I'm glad you got your father and mother's permission.
I'm glad, I'm glad.
Now you can introduce me to my grandfather.
Yeah, I'll introduce you to him when we get back.
Well, I'll come pick you up early tomorrow morning.
Okay!
Mr. Ryusenshi.
Miko!
I got a letter, so I came to deliver it.
If you'd just give me your phone number, I'd be able to pick it up.
I have to apologize to Mr. Ryusenshi.
Okay, he sent it.
Miko, do you want to go as it is?
Yes. I'm sorry for being too selfish.
Why are you apologizing? I'm so happy, Miko.
Eh?
This is an adventure for Miko Ai, in a way.
It might be possible that people will leave me and go further.
It was really fun.
It was really interesting.
If you've been a fan for a long time, you might be a little surprised.
If you're ready, I'll be happy to fight with you.
Mr. Ryusenshi.
Let's go this time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Mr. Honda.
How are you feeling?
Matsumoto Shonen.
Yeah, it's great.
It's different from the usual Honda.
Mr. Honda and Matsuo.
How are you feeling now?
Maybe I'm a little better than before.
Okay, I'm done.
When I get back, I'll pay you 3 million yen.
It's a good result.
Is there a detective named Honda?
Oh, it's a teacher who is a teacher of haiku.
What?
Then it's Mr. Matsuokuchi's grandfather.
Mr. Matsuo.
Actually, I've been studying haiku for many years.
I'm in the haiku competition of the "Mai-cho" newspaper.
I'm studying haiku to apply for the "Mai-cho" newspaper.
I heard that your grandson Kuichi went with a detective named Honda.
They went on a trip to the "Oku no Hosomichi" early this morning.
What?
To the "Oku no Hosomichi"?
Mr. Kuichi's parents should know.
I haven't heard anything.
Call them back right now.
Call them back?
Your granddaughter was looking forward to this trip.
First of all, that's just a child.
What if she gets hurt?
Call them back quickly.
Yes, I will call them back right away.
Who are you?
I'm a man who lives in haiku.
I'll call you right away.
If I can't get the grandfather's attention, I don't have any money.
Is the customer's phone in a place where the radio does not reach?
At least keep it loose.
What's wrong? Can't you contact me?
I'm home.
I'll put in some tea.
I'll buy some tea and sweets.
I'll go to the patrol.
You guys!
If anything happens to your granddaughter, I'll call you back.
I understand.
I'll find her right away.
I'm sorry.
I have to catch Honda soon.
I'll lose 300 million yen.
"Ara and the sound"
"Ao and Wakaba's sunlight"
Honda, that's Nikko.
It's a great view.
"Aro and Wakaba"
Then, let's take a rest here.
Yes.
"Aro and Wakaba's sunlight"
Hi, I ate kelp rice ball.
You have a different personality from when you rode a motorbike.
People often say that.
Matso's is Umeboshi.
Matso, do you hate Umeboshi?
Shall I exchange it for you?
You're welcome.
"Aro and Wakaba's sunlight"
I'm glad you came, Matsuo.
Yeah, my grandpa always said on TV,
"You'll know what life is like when you travel on the narrow path."
You're young, but you're really amazing.
I'm not amazing.
You have a lot of respect for your grandpa. You like him, don't you?
I don't like grandpa.
What?
Your grandpa says on TV, "Go on the narrow path."
Yeah.
Then you've been there, haven't you?
Well, I haven't been there, but...
What? Your grandpa is a liar!
Liar!
He's not a liar.
On the narrow path? You're still too young!
But everyone at school...
Instead, think about the haiku you're going to do in the competition.
Grandpa...
Grandpa only thinks about haiku, and he doesn't think about my feelings.
Tell everyone to go on the narrow path.
Why can't I?
Matsuo, do you really hate haiku?
No.
I like haiku because it's fun.
I see. It's hard.
I don't like Umeboshi, but my grandpa says it's good for your health.
You don't have to force yourself. Eat this.
Yeah, thanks. But I'll eat it after I eat Umeboshi.
I see. All right, I'll give you a lot. Eat a lot.
Yeah. It's sold on the side-car and I'm hungry, so I think I can eat it.
All right, let's eat.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Senpai, I haven't contacted Mr. Honda yet.
Does Grandpa want to wait all the time?
Uh?
Nana!
Mr. Honda is here.
Well...
Welcome, Reiko.
Actually...
The narrow path in the back?
Yes. A policeman who said "Honda" brought out a baby who was old enough to be lost.
"Honda" is...
A tabula kasu...
Mr. Honda knows how people feel.
He's a kind person.
Yeah.
I believe in Mr. Honda.
I heard that Mr. Honda was dumped after fighting with her.
Yeah.
It seems that Mr. Honda was a chicken-back slave.
Get on the phone, Mr. Honda!
Hello, senpai!
Mr. Honda, you idiot!
Where are you?
We're in Nikko right now.
It's a nice day and I'm feeling good.
Nikko, you idiot!
Are you all right, Honda?
What?
I can't hear you, senpai.
Are you all right?
I'm angry, so hurry up!
Shut up!
Go on!
Alright, I got it!
I'm on my way.
What?
I'm in trouble!
Mr. Honda, I didn't go to you!
Your phone is somewhere where the radio doesn't reach.
Oh, crap!
Kasane is the name of the "Nanarubeshi" of the Yaenadeshiko.
Sora!
Mr. Honda!
Hey, what's up, you crazy boy?
N-Nothing, I just called you.
Ha, just called you.
We're friends, right?
What did you say?
N-Nothing.
It's a phone.
I'll stop it for a moment.
Alright.
Here it comes.
The voice calling Mr. Honda.
Mr. Honda?
Who is it?
I can't! It's already here!
Hello, Mr. Honda.
Where are you?
Hello.
Mr. Honda?
Hello, the phone has changed because Mr. Honda is crying.
It's factory review.
Please let Mr. Honda know that something he wants to see.
Something he wants to see?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Give me a break!
Kuu-chan, are you Kuuichi?
Huh?
Hello, Nana?
Kuuichi? Who are you?
Are you Mr. Honda?
Well...
If you're Mr. Honda, please take my place.
Bring your grandchild back here.
He'll be back soon.
Matsuo is worried about something.
Please listen to him.
Kuuichi, leave me alone!
Matsuo, the old man wants you to take his place.
Give it back to me.
Hello?
Mr. Honda?
What's wrong?
He's gone.
What?
I was really worried about him.
Nana, I want you to see something.
See something?
That's what I said.
I said, "Go back."
You want to go back, don't you?
Not really.
It's fine if you go back.
Let's continue this journey together someday.
Okay.
Bye.
Amazing.
I'll never get it right again.
Bye.
I'll never run away.
Hey, big brother.
Looks like he's Create a New Alpha.
Stop, Big Brother.
And you'll never be able to break away from this.
And you'll never be able to come to the opposite side of the room.
Bye.
I'm just kidding.
Yes.
Grandpa!
Rui!
Are you all right? Are you hungry?
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
It's okay. Let's go home.
Nono-chan!
I'm gonna cry.
What's wrong, Reiko-san?
This is Nada-chan's comic.
It's always so moving.
There's something in my heart.
Oh! Let me read it next time.
Me too! Me too!
If you don't mind, here you go.
Honda-kun!
Thank you.
These are all the same magazine!
I bought them all the time when I saw them.
Honda-kun, you're able to get back together with her, aren't you?
Yeah.
Thanks to you,
I have the confidence to work hard as the shrine maiden of love.
You'll always watch over me, won't you?
I always watch over you.
I'll always watch over you.
Thank you.
Nana-chan!
You're more loving than ever.
You're more like manga than ever.
Honda-san!
Matsuo-kun!
You talked to your grandpa, didn't you?
Yeah.
And we decided to play soccer as well!
We're playing next week!
Really?
I'm going to cheer you on!
You made up with him, didn't you?
Yeah.
Well, see you later!
You did well, Matsuo-kun.
By the way, where's your senior?
He didn't come.
He didn't come back to Ryo's place, either.
Where could he have gone?
Well, he had gone home.
Only one thing.
I thought you'd told me.
You were all so happy, Ryo!
I'm so happy!
I'd be so happy too, but this is too much for me!
Hey, I'm getting jealous!
Not swipe it!
It's too much for me.
Kouya-kun!
Should I remain quiet for three minutes?
Hey!
I have a question for you!
So?
I was drawn to the world
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk on the black side of the arcade
The dial of the arcade
Everyone was a child once
Everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
A blue lady with blue eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
You can meet everyone
There is a camera
There must be a camera
Everyone come on
Let's go
To our town
There is a camera
There must be a camera
Everyone come on
Let's go to our town
Thank you!
The one who will re-examine the exit is coming?
It's a story that the chief will be burned
Hey, chief!
Chief!
Isn't it a great fever?
Are you okay?
Are you okay with such a flurry
What happens to the exit when the chief does that?
Next time
Chief please sleep
Yoshikura
There is a camera
There must be a camera
Everyone come on
To our town
Thank you!