When you watch TV
Make sure you keep your room light and keep your distance
It's like someone is calling you
After the rain
I walked back and forth
I reached out to my mom
I felt something strange at that time
So I tried walking on the black rail of the arcade
I tried walking on the black rail of the arcade
Everyone was a kid at least once
But everyone has forgotten
A politician with a big face
And a blue aunt in front of their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a wall over there
There's a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Now I have no choice but to defeat you!
It's a mysterious treasure!
The two beauties have started to fight because of their fate!
Marilyn is the most popular actress in Hong Kong
The master of martial arts who can defeat a cow with one blow!
The best female prostitute in the world!
Jody is the leader of the Great War
She defeated a bear with her bare hands
And is the best female prostitute in the world!
The best female prostitute in the world!
The battle is now on the way to Hong Kong!
The best beauty in the world!
B-1 Grand Prix 1998
Hong Kong Grand Final!
First place!
Great! Great!
It's the best!
The rest is currently being filmed
It really is a disaster
It's a big deal that the double date between Volvo and me
Now we can make a big profit
I won!
The prize is a 100,000 per percent win rate
This time it's 200,000 including the risk of death
What!?
Listen to me
This project is only around 15 minutes
Plus, you can get a plus 10% for fighting fans.
Plus, you can get a plus 5% for foreign fans.
You can get a total of 30%.
I'm a man too! I'm waiting for the best frame!
Alright, I'm ready to go.
I'm counting on you, Ryouto-chan!
The End
You really came to Hong Kong?
Yes. From now on, Bobby and I will be living here alone.
Marilin-san!
That blonde lady came.
She said she wanted to see you.
I won't let her touch you.
Right, Bobby?
I can't stand it!
Why me?
Don't think too much. You're just a record holder.
We have about 2 hours left until Hong Kong.
I'm sorry, everyone.
This happened for my sister.
This happened to her for the sake of our marriage.
At least you should be thinking twice before having a double date.
I-I didn't mean that...
That's all right, but it's what you asked for.
Don't make excuses!
It's Jody-san's flight attendant.
Give me back my Volvo!
Volvo is America's pride!
Thanks to everyone!
They even moved the boat for Bobby and me.
For Jody's sake!
If that's the case, we'll go to the ends of space!
Yeah!
This is getting serious.
We have to go to Hong Kong and persuade Marilyn to return Mr.Volvo.
It's not easy to persuade her.
The winning rate is 30%.
It costs 6 million.
Ah! My sister's house is over there!
Wow! It's a big palace!
As expected of the best actress in Hong Kong!
No good. That's too small for a battle.
Senpai, what are you talking about?
Oh, nothing.
Hey, Nakagawa, fly over that house.
Y-yes, sir.
W-what's this?
It's fine. It's fine.
Well then, we'll head over there.
Eh? Head over there?
Ryo-sama!
If you pull the string, the parachute will open!
Don't drop the camera.
As expected of the best actress in Hong Kong.
At times like this, this is it.
One, two, three.
Wow.
It's a real YAMU茶.
Take as much as you want.
I am eating.
It's good.
For sure.
Aichi!
What?
You're selling the fight between Marilin and Jody to the TV station?
Shh! You have a big voice.
That's why I brought you here as a cameraman.
I'm not kidding!
If you two fight, it'll be a big deal again!
I'll do it before we part ways.
No way! I'm going home!
Hey, wait!
Ugh, you idiot...
Ah!
Huh?
What's wrong, Honda?
Hey!
Ah!
What's going on?
You're talking about the table in the yard?
Ah, help me, senpai!
Huh?
I'm busy looking for a cameraman.
The cameraman I brought from Japan ran away.
No way!
Ah, I wonder if he's anywhere.
That great cameraman...
He's here! He's here! He's here!
What?
Really?
Huh?
What did you say?!
I can't believe he ran away so soon.
He already ran away.
That's why I'm asking for your help.
Wah!
Never say such a thing.
Hey, you stupid black kitty.
!
Huh?
it cost 6 million!
I will not allow it!
!
Ah! Where's the sound?
Huh?
Hmm?
Leon!
Leon! What's wrong? Is something wrong?
Listen, if you talk about me, I'll eat your tail.
Leon, it seems like your body is full of scratches.
Over there? I was looking around and I slipped my foot and fell down the cliff.
Then I happened to pass by and fell into the circus lion cage.
We got into a little fight.
Yeah, I don't mind if you're a lion, but if this blonde lady comes, I'll kill her.
You have to beat her thoroughly.
Okay, okay.
Bobby, I'm going to go out to make a reservation for the wedding.
Are you getting married?
Of course. You and I.
Zen, hurry up. I'm going to make a reservation for the best wedding, so look forward to it.
Marilin and I are getting married?
Yes.
I'm getting married.
If we get married, we'll live in this house.
If I have children, we'll play in this garden.
That might be a good life.
You're so naive, Bulbul.
Ryo-ryotsu, why are you here?
Hi.
Jody is heading over here to get you back.
What?
So Jody asked me to come and get me back?
No, I came to show you this.
What?
Ta-da. It's a nude photo book of a popular housewife.
Here.
No way!
No good.
Okay, I'll take you there.
What? You're not going to wait for Jody to come here?
This place is too small for two people to fight.
It's more like Hong Kong.
It's not like Hong Kong.
At least, you'll get 18 percent of the view.
What about...
She'll be taken to a lion-baum garden to feed you.
What?
It's a great place to fight.
You'll get 25 percent of the view at least.
You can eat this dish.
Why?
You'll eat some gourmet food.
The plus is 3 percent.
No way.
No way!
I'm back.
Honda, tie me up with a rope.
Yes, sir.
Like this?
Okay, put your head forward.
This is bad, Marilyn!
Why are you here?
Where's Bobby?
Jody took a friend and took Volvo.
What?
We came here to stop Jody's rampage,
but we didn't make it in time.
That blonde girl...
She said she'd go to the Lion Balm Garden
to celebrate her arrival in Hong Kong.
The Lion Balm Garden?
Hey, Honda, get up!
I'm sorry, Volvo.
I'll take him with me.
So you were wearing underwear.
My precious fiancée was kidnapped by a Yankee woman
from the U.S. Navy.
The enemy must take the Lion Balm Garden back!
Yes, sir!
Hurry, Honda!
Hey, Kurohio!
I need your help.
Honda, get on this.
Don't call me by that nickname!
Don't you wake me up!
I'm sorry.
Her brother's brother,
goodbye,
Let's fly, Mr. Ryosu! Hold on tight!
All right! Go, go!
Rin! Rin!
-Senpai! -Honda!
-Ke-chan! -There's no one inside.
There's not a single car!
Where did everyone go?
Here they come! Johnny's aircraft carrier!
Hey, Johnny!
Hey!
Hey, Mr. Ryosu!
There's someone who's suddenly coming in!
The aircraft carrier won't stop suddenly!
What? Bobby is in the Lionbaum Garden?
Yeah, I've been checking it with my own eyes.
Marilyn is totally alone.
I won't forgive you! Bobby is my fiancé.
I'll definitely get him back!
Be careful! Marilyn's guardmen were surrounding you.
I'm a professional bodyguard.
I'm a soldier.
Hooray!
Honda, take this aircraft carrier!
Yes, sir!
And take the soldier maniacs, too. Plus 2%.
Bobby will be in here for sure.
Search thoroughly!
Yes, ma'am!
All right!
I'll take this camera.
What's your camera position like now?
Huh?
What?
Charge!
Melissa, protect her!
Yeah!
I found you, you slut actress!
Who? This character's just like a nurse.
Don't worry!
Good, good, good. It's finally time.
I guess I need to get a sound effect here.
Alright, let's go!
Give me back my Bobby!
Go, go, Johnny!
Mr. Marilyn, fight!
Yay!
That was really intense!
No, it's not.
The beauty contest is a regular one, but I can't get my head around it.
I can't do that military uniform and the martial arts.
I'm hiding my nice body.
Alright.
W-What are you doing?
Go for it!
What kind of battle is this?
I can't believe my clothes are getting torn just by the casta.
Alright, good.
Now, it's Marilyn's turn.
Go for it!
I'm going for it!
Go for it! Go for it! Go for it!
This is...
This is the painting I've been waiting for!
This is not even a 40% chance of winning!
I-I can't believe that's the Hon-dara-ken.
I called for you.
Why?
To make the battle more flashy.
W-What is this?
I can't believe...
I'm Hon-dara-ken's general,
Asato Bandai!
Father!
I heard you're important.
Who's your enemy?
This woman!
Miss, there's a good Cantonese restaurant nearby.
Do you want to eat with me tonight?
W-What?
I'd be happy if you could tell me your cell phone number.
and tell me your present time.
Father!
That woman is my enemy!
I'm here!
Th-This music...
Papa!
I heard that you're the most important person, so I came running.
I salute Colonel Bokuryu!
Hm.
Yai! Yai! Yai! Yai!
It's cowardly to do a proper appearance!
What?
Get lost!
Who is this?
My enemy's father.
Who is your enemy?
That woman!
Hm.
It's a terrible wound.
Oh, young lady. You've come to the right place.
This is a wound that was shot in Vietnam.
This is a wound from the war in Auckland.
Furthermore, this is a wound from the war in Wangan.
And this is...
The wound that was scratched by my wife.
This is my wife.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Let's go.
I can't let myself start bragging about my family.
Then I'll do the same.
My wife is beautiful, isn't she?
You're lying!
A man like you can't have such a beautiful wife!
Your photo is a fake one!
Hm?
I won't forgive you for insulting a soldier!
You're...
Ah!
This is...
P-P-P-Pineapple!
Ru-ru-ru-ru...
Ruby...
I-I...
C-C-C-C...
Ka-ka-kamakiri...
R-R-Ringo...
What are you doing, damn it, father?
Bu-B-B-Burinin...
Ah, damn it!
You're an idiot.
I won't forgive you, you bastard!
I'll beat you to death.
That's my line.
Let's go, young men!
Huah!
Hahaha, you...
What?
Yeah!
Ah!
I'm sorry!
No!
Alright, enough!
Make it more flashy!
Honda, get it!
Yes!
Alright!
I'll do it too!
Yeah!
So dangerous!
Honda!
Ha-ta!
Are you okay?
Yeah, it was dangerous.
Yeah, thank you.
A swindler like you saved people.
You...
I'm surprised.
Hmm, I never thought a villain like you could save me.
You're a fraud?
A villain?
Who would do that?
Good, good!
Now you have a 50% view!
That's 10 million!
What's 10 million?
Huh?
Argh!
W-Why are we here?
You're not going to notice this much noise, are you?
Huh?
What's in this bag?
Argh! I'm not giving it to him!
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?
Polino?
Ryo-sama?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Get rid of him!
Ah, that's...
Oh, hello?
I did it, Ryochi-chan!
I got the Sunday Golden!
Now I have a 30% view!
I'm waiting for the Jody vs. Marilyn video to be completed!
Ryo-chan, what's going on?
Huh?
I-I think it's a wrong call.
That's not it.
We want to ask you something, too.
Huh?
What happened to the battle between you two?
More importantly, I want to ask why Bobby is here.
W-Well...
You don't have to know that.
You're really lucky for having me.
W-Wait...
I can understand if you tell me.
Don't get your head around the world!
Oops!
You jerk!
Cheers!
I don't know about this but this is the centenar old friend!
You both are...
How can you...
Sheesh...
If you think you can control people in TV...
You're just retarded!
Basically.
Alright, let's get along with each other from now on.
Speaking of which, Bobby!
You're the cause of this!
Hey, I like you.
Me too. I think I can become good friends with you.
Since we're here in Hong Kong, I'll introduce you to some good restaurants.
Oh, fantastic.
Then, let's go.
Let's go.
Hey, wait!
Are you leaving me behind?
Papa, please be more considerate.
You too, dad.
Hey, Jody!
Leave it to me, Rin!
By the way, why did you come to Hong Kong?
Help me!