"I'm sorry!"
"Hey, hey, Mr. Omawari."
"I want to go to Harajuku, but..."
"Can you tell me where?"
"Can you tell me?"
"Oh, then take the train."
"And change trains at Akihabara."
"It's the second station."
"Thank you very much, Mr. Omawari."
"Oh, then I won't go to Harajuku."
"That's fine."
"I'm fine. I'm fine."
"When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away!"
"A man without money."
"Come to me now."
"I'm not here either, but I'm worried."
"Look at the blue sky, See the blue sky,
and the white clouds!"
"We'll somehow make it somehow somehow!"
"Whahaha!"
"Akane"
Come to me, you jobless man.
I'm not here, but don't worry.
Look, the burning Akane is...
...will be fine soon.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
You know what to do, right?
If you know what to do, just shut up and follow me.
"Demaga Dema Yobu Ryotsu Nabe"
Ugh, I'm cold tonight.
If I didn't get a night shift on this day, I'd be dead.
Ugh, I have a cold...
What's this?
I'm sure there's still plenty of gasoline in there.
This stupid Stomach!
"Demaga Dema Yobu Ryotsu Nabe"
Ow!
I'm freezing.
I've got a cold, my hands are cold and I can't train.
"Demaga Dema Yobu Ryotsu Nabe"
Ow!
This is bad!
Why am I getting so hungry?
"Demaga Dema Yobu Ryotsu Nabe"
Why do I have to be alone like this?
I'm just not sure what's wrong with you two!
What did you say?
You want me to pay you the night shift?
Yeah.
My father was hosting a party, and I had to attend it on my own.
I can't afford to go.
If I don't go, it might affect the future of the Japanese economy.
Well, I've been in the middle of it.
I've been in your care.
I'll buy it if I can't help it.
Thank you very much.
I'm coming to you, senpai.
In return,
I know.
I'll make this arrangement someday.
I'd rather have a puffer fish.
Fugu sashimi, fried fish, puffer fish, puffer fish broth.
Uh, senpai.
Well, the time is...
That's right.
After all, sardines, too.
Well, then, I'm sorry.
I'll take it.
Ah, leave it to me.
Yes, yes.
Now that it's decided, the night is long.
I'm bored anyway, so I'll spend a night to finish it.
Ryo-chan, first.
Hey, Reiko.
Are you going home?
There's still time.
No.
Today, I told you that I would go early because I had a drink party with Komachi-chan and the others.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Oh, my, Ryo-chan.
The other day, I brought you a cake to thank you for paying the bill.
Well, I see.
Ryo-chan, you forget it after walking a little bit.
Don't treat me like a bird.
But promise is a promise.
Yes, yes.
I know.
Please come here soon.
I'll go without being told.
See you later, Ryo-chan.
What do you mean, "See you later"?
They're shaking because of the cold.
If you take them out of the warm room,
they'll be full of good alcohol and delicious food.
And the worst thing is the manager.
Ryotsu, is Ryotsu here?
Oh, no. It's the manager.
Yes, I'm coming right now.
Manager, what's wrong?
I asked Nakagawa, but he changed his night shift.
Yes, it's for his cute junior.
It's for the Japanese economy.
It's not for Fugu.
Fugu?
I think he asked Nakagawa for something again.
No, it's just my big feelings as a senior.
Well, it's okay.
Anyway, Ryotsu, I have an urgent business trip.
I have to get on the Shinkansen at 9 o'clock.
I have to get ready as soon as I get home.
Sorry.
But I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Ryotsu, Kankichi, while the manager is away,
I'll do my best to protect this station.
Don't be so overreacted.
I'll do it properly.
See you.
Have a good day.
I can stretch my wings without hesitation.
Don't expect to be a boxer with a red pencil in your ear during your work.
I'm counting on you.
I'm not alone.
It's too pathetic to cry.
Damn it, it's Tearai.
Clap!
Here, a train to Kouenmai.
Ryo-san?
Why Tearai?
I have a cold and have a fever of 39 degrees.
39 degrees?
It's a mild fever.
I'm not like Ryo-san.
When I say 39 degrees, my head is spinning, my nose is spinning, and my legs are shaking.
I'm about to die.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, but please let me rest.
Stop it, you idiot. The wind is coming.
Will the phone come?
Okay, okay, go to sleep.
Ryo-san is so kind.
Damn it, I can't do it.
Even if the wind blows, it's a gap.
Who will be the winner?
What the hell?
I ate all the cup noodles that were left on the floor.
Damn it, this is terrible.
Why am I the only one who sees this?
I'm working for Nagagawa, Reiko, Terai, and the head.
What the hell is this?
Damn it, I can't do it.
I'll be in trouble at the post office.
If it's tomorrow, I'll be found with ice.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Oh, Senpai?
Nagagawa, something terrible happened.
What terrible happened?
Is there meat there?
Meat?
There is, but what is it?
I don't think anyone has eaten it yet.
Yes.
I'm glad I made it in time.
Did you say you made it in time?
Is there a problem with the meat?
No, not now.
Listen, Nagagawa.
Bring the meat to the post office immediately.
To the post office?
Senpai, what do you mean?
Shh, don't make a loud voice.
Yes.
The head just got a very bad message.
Listen, it's raw.
Oh, right.
Don't forget the seasoning for the ponzu.
Seasoning?
Yes, the seasoning.
Not only the meat, but I don't know what else is in the seasoning.
I'm in a big hurry.
I understand.
Yeah, the pot is the best in the cold.
Who is this?
It's a boyfriend of Reiko's.
No, there is no one like her.
Oh, hello?
Oh, it's Reiko.
It's tough.
Ryo-chan, what's wrong?
The manager is...
The manager...
What?
What happened to the manager?
The manager...
He was crying.
Be strong, Ryo-chan.
The chief's life is...
...in a state of emergency!
What did you say?
The doctor said that he's too nervous to use it,
and that he'll be dead in a few days.
No way!
It seems that the lack of vitamins and calcium is the cause.
If we can feed him vegetables, somehow...
Come back soon, Reiko!
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Thank you.
Don't forget the vegetables.
Chinese cabbage, shungiku, and green onion.
What?
And I heard that you can also use shirataki and other seafood.
Especially fugu.
Bring it to the office immediately.
Please, for the chief's sake, Reiko!
Yes, it's me, Terai.
Ryo-san, what's up?
You did it, Terai!
Congratulations!
Congratulations? I'm still cold.
Don't be surprised.
I'm the donabe in your house.
Donabe?
That's right.
You know, I used to make hot pot at your house.
Oh, I see.
The chief brought a person who said that he could buy that donabe for 1 million yen.
1 million yen?
1 million?
That's right.
Bring it to the office right now.
But I bought it at the supermarket for 2,980 yen.
Yeah.
That's not true!
If you see it, you'll understand the difference.
You're mistaken.
It's a work of the Human Declaration.
It's a special edition.
I bought it.
What?
But it's like this.
You have to come out now.
The other person is a foreigner.
A foreigner?
Wait a minute.
I'll call you right now.
It's over.
I'm busy.
If I don't hurry, the plane will leave.
I'll do something about it.
I don't have time anymore.
Will you come or not?
1 million yen will run away.
I'm coming right now.
Please wait for that person.
I'm going to do it.
I forgot to turn it off.
Here you go.
Balbo!
Oh, Ryotsu.
I'm in the middle of a survival game.
I'll cut you.
Help me, Balbo!
What's up, Ryotsu?
Bobby, I won.
Jody!
Balbo!
Do you hear me?
I'm the Cassette Gas Conloader!
Bring me the gas!
I need a gas stove!
Whoa! Stop!
The stove, now!
I don't know, but Ryosu is in danger.
Yeah.
Hello?
What, is that your husband?
What?
What do you think?
Now we can have a fun hot pot party!
Senpai!
I brought the meat!
Senpai?
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-san, I brought the pot!
Ryosu, are you okay?
Senpai,
I brought the ingredients for the tamago-zake.
But isn't it a little too much?
Huh?
Oh, you're here, everyone.
Good job, good job.
Senpai, what the hell are you doing?
Meat, vegetables, seafood,
it's like you're making a hot pot.
Ping-pong!
That's right!
Huh?
No, I was gathered for emergency training,
but I couldn't make it because it was cold,
so I thought I'd make a hot pot.
Emergency training?
That's right!
That's not a joke!
That's right, Ryo-san!
What about one million yen?
Don't make a fuss.
Let's have fun with the hot pot.
What do you mean, "let's have fun"?
You're fooling people,
it's too much of a bad joke!
I'm 39 degrees!
No matter how much it is...
It's too bad.
Ryo-san.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I, I just...
Don't be fooled by such a play.
Oh, I see.
It's a bit saddening, isn't it?
To be told that way by a friend who has been with me for years.
I guess I'll have to say goodbye to this locker.
Huh?
And to this desk.
Did something happen, senpai?
Did the chief hit you often in this west?
Ryo-chan.
Hey, what's wrong?
This night, filled with memories.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Ryo-san.
Senpai?
N, no, it's nothing.
This is my own problem.
What happened?
Actually...
No, I want to talk about this while eating the hot pot.
Did you do something and get a death certificate again?
But, if it's that bad,
Senpai wouldn't be depressed.
Then, maybe...
Super-Sexual Food?
What?
A death certificate?
Is that so, Ryo-chan?
Don't make me say that.
But...
Life is like a hot pot.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Tell me the truth.
Is it a death certificate?
Senpai...
It's fine.
Anyway, let's start the hot pot.
It's the last supper.
The last supper?
That means, after all...
Death certificate?
That's right!
It's this place, as Senpai said.
We can do it even in a hot pot.
That's right.
Since we finally have all the ingredients, we can also do it in a hot pot.
There is also a cassette gas stove.
Yes!
There is also a drink!
Thank you.
It's good for everyone's kindness.
At the same time,
I got a call from someone.
They said something about Nick and left.
Nick?
That wasn't just a coincidence.
It seems like there's a secret.
Secret?
No way! Nick is developing in our company!
Yes, it's me.
What?!
The microchip Nick is developing in Gokuhi is...
Okay, I'll look into it.
Wh-What's going on?! Nick's file is gone!
This is an international conspiracy!
Colonel Buckley.
Yes.
Colonel, the young lady just sent a message.
From Jody?
Yes. She said she'd go deliver the gascon, so she didn't have to come pick it up.
What?! The gascon?! Jody said that?!
The code name gascon is the code name of the emergency emergency system!
I'm sorry.
Colonel Buckley has an important report.
A terrorist with a new weapon in Japan's Katsushika Kameari is going to the presidential election?!
What?! Report it to the president immediately!
Ha ha ha ha!
It seems like Reiko has left the Katsushika Kameari.
I'm sure there was something at the park before the exit.
Ha ha ha!
It's probably aliens invading.
Awesome!
Is something wrong with Sagakashi?
No, but it seems that the area around Kameari has been completely invaded by aliens.
Really?
The plants and tofu work well here!
Yes.
What? From the US Department of Defense?
I've just heard from the Treasury that there is an international conspiracy.
It's a big problem, sir.
What's going on?
A strange incident occurred at the exit in front of the park.
I know! Call Ohara right away!
What? The exit in front of the park?
I'll be there soon. It's a big problem.
Hey, Ryo-chan. Can you talk to me?
Well, that's...
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Leave this to the Department of Defense!
Goofy, you're awesome!
I'm not!
We'll save the evil first.
We'll put the meat in later so that it doesn't get too hard.
That face doesn't look like it.
Well, it's a problem.
Ohara is in charge of this exit.
Is it true that aliens on a Donabe-type UFO were attacked?
Are you kidding me?!
An international pianist has taken a new type of murder phone and has occupied the exit!
A pianist has?
Why did a pianist go to the exit?
The attack is ready.
Where is the brutal monster of肉?
It's the pianist!
Are you an alien?
A carnivore!
I'm a pianist!
I'm an alien!
Pianist?
Alien!
Pianist!
He's attacking me!
W-wait a minute!
My subordinate has become a hostage!
It seems that the amount the culprit is demanding is 2980 yen.
Captain, we have received a call from Colonel Bakuryu.
What?
We'll arrive in 5 minutes.
If you're okay with that, you can launch a missile at any time.
No!
My subordinate, Ryotsu, is here!
I can't do this!
There are 7 people inside.
There's a heat source in the center.
Is that a new weapon?
I'll have to find a way.
What's that?
Leave this to us MIB.
What are you talking about?
Our job is to protect peace in Japan!
No!
We are protecting peace on Earth!
Life is a hot pot!
By the way, Ryo, what really happened?
Take it easy, Ryo.
The night is long.
That's right.
Okay!
You can eat vegetables!
Ah!
The bomb!
I stretched out my hand to the bomb!
Okay!
Get the SWAT unit ready!
Ah!
Don't do that!
I'll tell Ryotsu...
Yes!
I'll call!
I'll ask for the culprit's request on the phone!
Okay!
It's about time to eat meat!
Huh?
Who is it?
Even though it's a good place...
Yes, yes.
What happened?
Ryotsu!
Are you okay?
W-Warship!
Ah!
I can't go!
Ryotsu!
It's dangerous on the plane.
If we get them on the plane,
we don't know what to do!
Yah.
The SWAT unit has arrived on site!
Okay, let's wait for the orders!
We'll arrive at our target in a minute.
Attention, get ready to attack!
Yes!
Isn't it too noisy outside?
Uh?
Terai!
Shut up, Terai!
Yeah.
Ah!
So, Terai became an hostage too.
Maybe Nakagawa and Reiko...
Uh, SWAT mezkin!
Please let us retreat.
There is a danger of being shot by the subordinates by mistake with the culprit.
I'm counting on you.
Hmm.
Alright, let's switch to the rush operation.
B2 unit, ready for attack!
C3 unit, ready for attack!
D4 unit, ready for attack!
Alright, let's go!
Alright, it's finally time for the meat!
Let's eat!
That voice...
It's a rush operation!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Then, I'll try the meat again.
What's happening?
What the hell is that?
That violent face!
That's the culprit!
Catch him!
What the hell?
Stop it!
Ouch!
Don't run away!
Target detected.
Captured!
Captured completed.
We took care of the alien.
What's that?
Captain Buckley, the host has been rescued.
Please return to base.
Roger that.
I'm so glad!
I'm so glad everyone is safe.
Where's Ryo-tsu?
I'm so glad he is safe.
Captain Buckley is in 2019!
To be continued.
Edit 5: The Watchers
So, what happened yesterday?
Hey, make me eat some pot!
A living alien.
Hey, wait.
What are you doing?
Quit it!
I'm not a human being!
Help me!
Mommy!
Little granny!
Let me sing!
RABBIT N broadcast
I don't want to be an idiot to fight with the looks
When I was walking on the road at the bend corner, the moon escaped
I ran away
Because now is not everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat a little
Sometimes you're saving someone
Baby do you know me
I'm heading for tomorrow
Nice breath
Don't be rotten
I'll do what I have to do
A cute breath
What's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than seeing it
Delivery Police
A convenience store near a far-off station
If there is a station in a nearby convenience store
The security effect of the city is also increased
This is Columbus's egg enemy
A great plan of the two birds with one stone
Next time
Here is the convenience store exit
Thank you
There is a wall over there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
To the town of the city
Thank you