Sunset
When you watch TV
Try to look from the corner of your room and stay away
Makin' Up
Crawling by the river
I gaze at the sunset
When I kicked the stone, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if it's going to be a good day to go
I laughed as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I can't help but feel a little bit of pain
The cityscape that doesn't change a single
wail is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of Tongari Boshi
To Kaishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow
Why does it end like this?
Whether it's a win or a lose
I was just happy
I realized
Because I'm an idiot
-Good morning! -Good morning!
What are you doing, chief?
Good morning.
I got a video letter from my daughter to my grandson, Daisuke.
I bought a video camera to reply to it.
But I've been addicted to it since then.
Huh? The chief is shooting a video?
It's the age of AV where anyone can enjoy a video camera.
The age of AV where anyone can enjoy a video camera.
Oh, yeah. You see kids in the park often, don't you?
I don't have any pictures of my childhood, even.
Ryotsu, do you want to see it?
Daisuke's video that I took. It's cute.
No, it's fine.
Huh?
Those things only fun for the family.
It's just boring for others.
When I go home often, there are parents who show their child's video to the end.
No one but pain.
I can't imagine the video the director took.
An amateur's useless long-distance shooting,
hand shake, pin bokeh, and zoom failure.
If you take it while walking, it may fall,
but it only shows your feet.
Just thinking about it makes the screen look good.
Idiot!
You're an amateur, so you can't take it so well from the beginning.
It's a great work if it's full of love for children even with a boring video.
I'll show you.
I won't let you see it.
I'm sorry for the long-distance shooting.
Well, I'll go to patrol.
That's terrible, Ryo-chan.
It's true.
How is it? Do you want to see the video I took?
Of course.
I really want to see it.
Oh, I have to go to patrol with you.
Kei-chan!
That's right.
A patrol is a rule for two people.
Here, Reiko.
Yes.
"A patrol is a rule for two people."
Here, here, here.
Cut.
No, no.
You look so hard.
Listen, Shata.
This is a video library you'll never forget.
A more natural smile.
One more time.
Yes.
Scene 1, cut 3, take 5.
Ready. Start.
Here I go.
Cut cut cut!
You should express your happiness more childishly in your body.
Is it okay?
"Today is a fun sports day! Ran ran ran ran!"
Like this.
Don't put it into words!
Express it in your body!
Then, let's do it again.
Okay.
Next is a scene where she is full of will and goes to school.
She runs lightly to the
"Hey! Don't stand there without permission!"
"But the dog..."
"But I don't!"
"I told you that the ad lib without the script is forbidden!"
"What a dog!"
"You can jump over it without any worries!"
"You can bite it!"
"I won't let you!"
"Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!"
"Let go! Let go!"
"Stop it! Stop it!"
Okay, put your head on the second floor.
"Dad, I'm going to be late for the sports day."
Then, don't say anything and act properly!
"Okay."
Ready, start!
Good, good.
You have a natural look.
Let's go to the sports day!
"Oh, I missed the lane!"
"Oh, the slope!"
"Dad!"
"H-help me!"
"Huh? What?"
"Help me!"
"Nagaga, let's go!"
"Yes!"
"Go!"
"Are you okay?"
"I'm not okay!"
"C-camera! There's no camera!"
"Huh?"
"I'm glad! It's nothing! It was dangerous!"
"The camera is more important than yourself!"
"Mr. Omawari, don't be so rough!"
"If I don't do anything, I won't be able to stop!"
"It's a high-class camera!"
"It's so insensitive!"
"What?"
"Senpai!"
"Dad, I'm really going to be late for the sports day."
"Oh, that's right!"
"I shouldn't have done that!"
"Let's film the rest of the scene later."
"I see. Sports day, huh?"
"That's a lot of heavy equipment."
"The children's sports day is the biggest event for parents with video cameras."
"What's wrong? Why are you carrying such heavy luggage?"
"I'm delivering something I forgot. From my husband."
"There are various things in the video camera, such as batteries."
"What are you doing?"
"I'm carrying something heavy."
"Is it a man with big glasses with a backpack on his back?"
"That's right. There's a sports day today."
"He's a tough guy. I'll deliver it to him."
"It's hard for women to carry heavy things."
"Where is the school? We'll take you there."
"I'm sorry, Mr. Omawari."
"Kameyari's turtle and Kora's latte camera?"
"I see. That's a perfect name!"
"That's all I need to know."
"What?"
"The owner's name is..."
"It's written as 'Pinto' in 'ichi'."
"Pinto'?"
"It is said that you read 'Pinto' as 'ichi'."
"What about your son's name?"
"Yes, it's 'Shutter' in 'Shanyitaro'."
"Hahaha! 'Pinto' and 'Shutter'? That's too much."
"I don't think your wife's name is Zoom or Shibori, is it?"
"No, it's a print child with a bronze head."
"What?!"
"Oh, I'm kidding. His name is Asako."
"That's too much."
"Asako... Asa..."
"Look! Isn't that the feeling of the film?"
"Huh?"
"It's like a family that was born to get into the camera world."
"What are you talking about?"
"What is this?"
"It's a huge number of people!"
"It's like a photo shoot for an idol."
"It's hard to find out from this."
"However, no matter how many sports events there are,
the number of children participating in the competition is too great.
Some parents even monitor and edit the video while children are not participating in the competition.
"How about some videotape?"
"I have a battery now."
"The business is doing well."
"It's much different from the old sports club where I was eating rice balls."
"Ah, over there."
"Huh?"
"What?"
"Hey, you! You forgot something!"
"Ohh, sorry, sorry!"
"Oh, you two are...?"
"My wife looked too heavy. So I helped her carry it."
"I see. Well, thank you."
"However, it's a great camera!"
"Do you understand?"
"A-Ah, I saw it, so..."
"It has a super-wide-angle lens for the commercial camera,
and it's a special camera for the sports event that was modified for."
I'll get rid of all the cheap videos there!
You're really serious.
You're not losing to the camera.
This is the ultimate video game!
The third-year obstacle race is starting now.
The shutter's on!
Mr. Omawari!
Hurry up and connect the cable to the D2 video deck for the business!
Yeah!
Let's go!
8mm is fine, right?
You cheap camera man, move!
6x zoom doesn't work at this distance!
Open the front!
It's in the way!
It's like a war.
Ready!
You look good, shutter.
Look up a little more.
Shutter Chance!
That's a good idea.
Now that's a powerful image!
Stop running around like that!
What am I doing here?
Now that's really no good!
Here we go!
Good shot!
What?
Now we're going to cross the mud!
W-what a great... masterpiece!
That's good!
Thank you so much for everything!
You guys really did a great job!
You've got a lot of scratches everywhere.
Thanks to you, I got a nice picture.
If you like, you can come over to my house.
Maybe I can get something cold...
Oh, no! I forgot the last scene!
I'm taking a picture of going home from the gym in the sunset.
You're not done yet?
What a healthy guy.
Hey, Mr. Omawari.
I'm not going to that place.
What? You're not going to that place?
That's my house.
This is the video.
Isn't that a TV station?
I couldn't find the tape.
I bought it from the used one.
Here you go.
There are so many tapes.
Ever since the shutter was born,
I've been taking pictures of it.
I've put together 5,500 videos every day,
from 5 hours to 8 years old.
That's not a number!
There are still 2,000 unedited videos.
Videos are the asset of the shutter.
When I grow up,
I'll be grateful for the love of my parents
who have made me grow up so much.
But how do you watch them?
It takes more than 15 years to watch a video every day.
That's why you can be moved by the depth of love of your parents.
There is no parent who can do this for you.
Here, have a cold drink.
This is a 6-month shutter.
Did you see that?
This expression, this angle.
It's the best.
Next is the kindergarten entrance ceremony.
Look at this falling cherry blossom.
It's fantastic.
It's idealistic and makes you feel like a poem.
It's a masterpiece.
This tasteful contrast.
A sharp zoom.
A flowing bread.
It's a masterpiece.
Is that so?
That was hard.
It's amazing to be so hard.
But I can't keep up with you.
You two should have watched Chief Ohara's video quietly.
Mr. Omawari.
Something bad happened.
Shota went home.
What?
Shota?
Actually, he went to the gym he missed yesterday afternoon to get a workout.
But he suddenly jumped out of the gym.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Shota.
What?
Shota?
That's a gift from my father.
Hey, Shota.
What?
You said you had never seen a baby before.
That's a beautiful gift.
It's a great video.
The reflection of the water is giving off a beautiful silhouette effect.
You're an otaku, so go now.
Shut up.
It's getting dark soon.
Let's go home.
No.
Why?
Dad prefers videos over me.
Is that true?
Because you always shoot videos.
If you don't shoot videos, you won't talk to me.
Shut up.
How long are you going to shoot?
Hey, this is the best place.
I don't want to go home.
I hate you, dad.
Look at that expression.
I failed to take it.
Let's do it again.
Let's go home.
You don't understand this girl's feelings.
I don't understand.
It's a great performance of the white god.
Then it's fine.
I'll take care of this girl.
She's great when she leaves.
All right.
OK.
This is a masterpiece.
What?
Here you are.
Thank you.
So you took care of Shatta?
If there's no child to take care of him, he'll think about it again.
Your father is always like that.
He shoots videos even if I fall or drown.
Videos are more important than me.
That's not true.
There are no parents whose children are not important.
Shatta is cute when he shoots videos.
But that's too much.
What's wrong, senpai?
I was in the park across the street and something was shining.
I was thinking of something.
That's too much.
Sh-Shatta!
I never imagined that you're so obsessed with this.
You're staying at my place tonight.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Your grandma will make the food.
The bath is huge, too.
Yeah.
Grandma, it's Shatta who'll take care of you.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
That's a good boy.
I don't think he's Ryo's secret son.
Don't say such stupid things.
That's right.
There's no one who can be his mother.
Huh?
What's that? It's suspicious.
How is it? It's a big bath, right?
Yeah. It's the first time I've been in a big bath.
Even if I go to the hot spring, I have a placard with a function.
I see.
Dad, if you have a video, you don't have to worry about me.
That's not true.
By now, I'm sure...
Who is it?
You!
Dad.
Hey, Shatta!
He's definitely a serious patient.
Maybe he needs a rough treatment.
We're here.
Let's go somewhere.
See you.
Bye.
Sh...Shatta...
You're so lively.
A car?
This is... a kidnapping.
Huh? Shatta was kidnapped?
So what did the murderer say?
He said that...
I shot him...
He said he would give me all the 5,500 video tapes...
But why video tapes?
I'm sure there was something on the video you put up.
I see. He was shooting a crime scene or something.
No way!
The tape has memories of me and Shatta...
Honey...
Anyway, I don't have time to waste!
Okay. Let's go.
Okay.
Honey!
Did you bring the promised item?
It's in here.
Show me.
Okay.
Where's Shatta?
Don't worry.
Hey!
Yeah?
Shatta!
Tell me.
How many days, how many hours, how many minutes did I take you?
That video tape...
If you say it's all, it's all!
All?
But all of Shatta's things are in this.
It's his property.
You're still saying that?
Which is more important, the child's life or yours?
Huh?
That's...
What's wrong?
Make it clear!
Yeah.
Senior, isn't Mr. Volvo and Mr. Sakonji overdoing it?
That's right, Ryo.
It's a bit cruel.
No, he won't know unless he does this much.
Tell me.
Which is the video tape and the child?
Uh, that's...
Dad!
What?
Father!
Dad!
Son of a...?
Shitta!
What?
Dad!
Shut up!
Ah!
What's up, Rosen?
Sir, Concenari ...
Dad!
Ouch!
I'm coming!
Shatta!
Ryo!
Step on the brakes!
That's why the model gun is stuck in the middle!
Damn, you're such a pain.
Shatta, I'll take over. Hold on to the handle.
Okay.
There!
Ryo!
It's the ocean!
What?
Dad!
Shatta!
Dad! Dad!
It's okay. It's okay.
Shatta!
Dad's tape is...
Forget it.
You've gotten heavier, Shatta.
Why didn't I hold you like this before?
Honey.
Asako?
Honey, about the next time...
I know you were all just acting.
Sorry.
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
Huh?
Until now, I've been turned around by taking videos.
I couldn't think about your feelings.
I'm awake.
Honey... Honey!
It was dangerous at the end, but now it's easy.
What?
We had a hard time, too.
So we had a hard time.
Seriously...
Even though this villain doesn't suit us...
The two of us are more real than real.
That's right.
Why don't you forget one person?
I didn't realize the shutter was getting this heavy.
Even if I'm a stupid parent who has never seen a child on the video finder.
I was moved by that.
The video...
I don't know what a child's weight is like.
By the way, are you three going out today?
Yes, to the amusement park.
Without the camera, in the palm of your hand.
I'll leave the memories in our hearts.
It's going to be a good memory.
After all, it's better to watch old stories on video than to hear them from your parents.
Natsuki Takahashi
Hatsune Miku
Even if the sun sets at midnight
If it's you, then wake up
Even if it's a boring story, I want to be close to you
I want to be your friend
I want to be loved
I want to be loved, just a little
The more we say it, the more we feel like we're melting
I really want to break it open
For some reason, love is only cowardly
Don't hide everything that you're not strong enough
I want to be loved, just a little