Episode 1: The
I was sleeping here, even though it's a day off.
Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu!
Hey!
Listen, Ryo-tsu.
The pot I put here is a souvenir for the next foreign guests.
Don't break it. Got it?
I'm sorry.
I really can't help it.
Yes?
What's up, mother?
Huh?
The vase?
Why do I have such a thing?
The vase is in the expo...
Huh?
I have something that's convenient.
Okay, okay.
I'll bring it to you right now.
Wait for me.
I'll go get it.
Okay.
When you watch the TV, make the room bright and move away.
Ryo-tsu! Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu!
Come with me if you have no money.
I don't have any, but I'm worried about you.
Look at the blue sky.
The sky, the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, you jobless guy
Come to me
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Do you understand?
I understand, I understand
If you understand, then shut up and follow me
Live broadcast tonight?
A pot?
Yes, it was in the back room.
A pot-shaped one. Ryo, don't you know?
Hmm.
Do you know where this pot is?
Yes, my mother said she wanted a vase.
I thought this dirty pot would be good for a house like ours.
I brought it.
What happened to that pot?
That's the boss's important pot.
The boss came and said, "The pot is gone!"
It was a big fuss.
He gave it to a foreign customer.
It's bad.
Okay, I'll go to Asakusa and get it right away.
If the boss comes, please trick him.
What a mess.
Did you get caught by a thief?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Please let me in.
Hey, Dad.
What happened?
Are you alive?
What's wrong?
What do you mean, what's wrong?
It's obvious.
It's one of us.
What?
What's wrong, Dad?
That's it.
Is it Asukusa Fukada?
No, it's not.
The role of this drama is Shizuka.
What?
Drama?
Director, did you hear this?
What's wrong, Murata?
Murata, a character with this life suddenly came.
What do you mean by this drama?
You idiot!
You don't know the doll drama would put on stage!
No, Director.
This is a special films of Kyoho.
But I still know it is the fan.
What's going on?
Huh?
You used my house for a TV drama shoot?
Yes. It's about Tsukudaniya's father and his daughter.
This drama is great.
It's starring the popular Asuko Fukada and the charming Kazumasa Murata.
Oh! Is that Kiriko Koizumi, the actress?
Kiriko Koizumi?
She's Aoyanari Kiyokazu.
That cat is also in the commercial.
She's very generous when she meets a famous cat.
She's more expensive than our salary.
But still, is it okay to have so many people in this small room?
We're rehearsing right now.
The opening performance will be on the 35th anniversary tonight at 7.
There's a 2-hour live special.
Hmm. So what happened to the parents?
Did they get kicked out of the house?
No, they went to the first-class hotel in the city.
A hotel?
Yes. Asakusa...
Asakusa Beauty Hotel's special suite?
Here it is!
This is amazing!
As expected of a special suite.
Hey, Kankichi.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Why are you standing right in front of the door?
Because it's too big and I can't calm down.
What are you going to do with just the 4th class of the special suite?
You're so poor.
Huh?
You don't have to wash the baby...
You don't have to go to such a place!
Is it okay to leave it to so many people?
It's okay. I'm paying a high price for that.
Huh? What are you doing for lunch?
I'm preparing breakfast, lunch, and dinner at the hotel.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I brought you a snack.
Oh, this luxury meal for lunch.
Enjoy your lunch.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Thank you for your hard work.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
I was so nervous when I saw the other party.
Anyway, can you eat all this luxurious food when you're old?
I'll leave most of it. I'm not good at cooking.
I'll leave most of it.
I don't have to use a knife or a fork.
I'm getting dizzy.
I don't want to eat Japanese food.
Shall we have sushi then?
Sushi?
We have room service.
Really?
It's so expensive.
It's a hotel.
I'll take room service.
10 servings of special sushi.
A big order!
What did you just say?!
Don't do such a disgusting thing!
Don't be so hasty!
Everyone has a TV station.
No matter how much you pay, you don't have to pay a cent.
Really?
Yeah. It doesn't hurt your stomach.
Don't worry.
But three people can't eat it all.
That's right.
Shall we call the next Gen?
Oh, that's good!
The room is big, so it's better to have more people.
Then let's call the women's club.
Let's call the women's club.
Okay.
Then let's add sushi.
And let's get some good sashimi and alcohol.
No.18, I'll sing a song from Katsushika Rhapsody.
I'll sing a song from Katsushika Rhapsody.
You can do that for free.
So you can spend the rest of your life at home.
Nagagawa, Raid!
I brought sushi as a souvenir.
Sushi is just a thing.
Oh, Chief.
You have such a scary face again.
Here is sushi.
Sushi.
What are you doing drinking booze while on duty?
Sorry, Ryo.
I couldn't stop lying.
So, what happened to the pot?
Pot?
I heard you took the pot you left here.
Oh, I see.
That's why I went to my father's house.
Did you forget?
Idiot!
That pot was supposed to be given to a guest from abroad.
I can't believe you.
If Ryo-kun doesn't make it tonight,
he'll take it.
If he doesn't make it by 9:00,
you both won't know what's going to happen.
Hey!
You make it so easy when you shoot.
You just forgot all about it.
You made it so easy when you shoot.
5 seconds before the main event.
4, 2, 1, go.
3, 2, 1
Meow
The 35th Anniversary Special "Bella Vole"
Tonight is broadcast live
It's started, it's started
Mom, it's started
They're doing it, they're doing it
Dad, I'm on TV
It's really a surprise
What?
You made your favorite?
Bella Vole
He's a young man now
His hair is black and his ears are pierced
He's as fluffy as a cotton ball
You can't tell that to him
Dad, you don't have to decide so suddenly
That's right, dad is usually old
Humans can't judge just by appearance
Meow
Shut up, kids and cats are quiet
So, what kind of man are you?
I'm on TV right now
What?
Sis, hurry up, I'm sorry
Dad, you're right
Ryo, Ryo
Well, I'm on TV
He's on TV
Well, I'm a child
What's wrong with the boy's personality?
He is trying to get free
He can't say anything
I went to the hospital
I'm sorry
Well, I have to go
Just like Kan-kichi
I'm here to see it!
I have no choice but to continue with the ad-lib.
Wh-What is it?
That curry is...
I've been waiting for you, Mr. Tadashi!
Now, please come up, Mr. Tadashi!
Ah, Mr. Tadashi!
I-I'm so sorry...!
Don't you think about it!
Look here, as I told you to--
Nope.
I don't have a simple hairstyle...
Today, I'm like a man with a simple personality.
A typical Japanese man!
Ah, that's right...
Let's go, Mr. Tadashi!
Sit down.
Oh!
You're Mr. Omahari, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I've been in charge of the police.
Right, Mr. Tadashi?
No, I've been in charge of the police for all the years.
Again?
Mr. Tadashi?
You're always like this.
You're always joking.
You're a funny person.
I'm on the air.
You can do what it says there.
I'm not serious.
Director, it's my turn.
No way.
This is my drama debut.
You're done.
You're in the middle of a live broadcast.
One more.
One hour and forty minutes.
I have to bring that pot by 9 o'clock.
I have to do something.
What's wrong, Mr. Tadashi?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tadashi.
Thank you, Mr. Tadashi.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
Tadashi, you're here.
I'll call you back.
OK.
Little annoying.
Wait a minute.
Hang on.
She's wearing a high dress.
You're gonna be a nightmare, Lee, for the rest of your life.
Go.
Don't.
You're gonna have to leave.
I don't know. But Ryo-chan is on TV right now.
It's a live broadcast.
What?
Next news.
That one?
Correct!
This one.
Dad.
It's true.
What's going on?
I have to keep acting to get the pot.
Well...
I'll show you how to make a great tsukudaniya.
What do you mean?
Give me that pot!
A pot?
That's what I'm going to do.
Wait a minute!
Mr. Tadashi, don't go!
Don't rush!
Let go of me!
I just want a pot!
Mr. Tadashi, it's me, not the pot!
That's right!
You came to get your dad married, didn't you?
I see.
Damn it.
Do I have to keep acting?
Shizu...
How do you read it?
Oh...
Shizu and Baka.
Baka?
That's not it.
What the hell are you doing to my daughter?
You stupid brat.
You're always so mean.
I'm Yorozuya Shuzo.
You stupid brat.
I'm Yorozuya, my father's last name.
My father's name is Ginji.
Shut up!
I'm Tadashi.
Yes.
It's all right.
You stupid brat.
You two.
You're right.
Calm down!
Please!
Is it a commercial?
Alright, I got a chance!
What?
It's a movie!
I can't see the pot!
I found it!
What would you do in a situation like this?
You'd use a flashlight?
But I'm in trouble.
There's a lot of times where the battery runs out.
Even in those situations, I feel at ease with this Tohdai Jirushi's candle.
It goes well with birthday cake candles and Buddhist altar.
We hope you enjoy Tohdai Jirushi's candle!
This program is brought to you by Tohdai Jirushi's candle which is bright to the foot.
So they have a live show up until the commercial?
This program is brought to you by Tohdai Jirushi's candle.
I'm not going to give you a daughter!
Dad!
You'd better not say that!
Mr. Tadashi...
It's you, Mr. Tadashi!
I see.
What's wrong, Kiriko?
I'm not Kiriko, I'm Matsuko!
Is that right?
Yeah.
No, it's not!
If you're a man, say something!
That's right!
Say something to your dad!
Meow!
I'm not going home until you say you're going to give me something!
Stop it, you idiot!
I won't do it!
I don't care about your daughter!
It's just a candle!
Why don't you just listen to what your father says,
without being so stubborn?
That's right!
If you ask me to be sincere, I'm sure you'll understand!
I can't live without that candle!
The chief will scold me,
and I'll be left with nothing to do!
Please, I'm begging you!
Anyway, I don't need anything else!
I want that candle!
No!
Your daughter won't do it!
That's why I said it's a candle!
Give me the candle!
You're really getting close!
But it's already 8 o'clock!
You idiot!
Hurry up!
I'm going to miss the flight!
If you really want your daughter,
you better take her away from me!
That's too much!
If you're a man, take her away!
I can't stand this!
Dad!
Give it to me!
Shizuko!
Hurry up!
I have to hurry!
Stop it!
Hurry up!
If you do that,
and drop the candle...
Dad!
Hey!
Wait, Kouta!
This way!
Stop it, Takichi!
Don't wait for me!
The egg tower!
You're too clever for a cat!
Ouch!
You!
I did it!
I won't give it to anyone else!
Don't let me get away!
Kouta!
You're not getting away!
You're too honest!
Don't let me get away!
Stop!
Don't go!
Hey!
You can't tie up a bike!
Dad!
Mom!
Help!!!
Gotta get it done fast!
Shut it, you muddy old...
Ah, this is a perfect spot!
It's early to the exit!
We gotta put on our dry-coats.
Not sure about that, but let's get out of here!
You take care, old hen!
Let go!
This is going to be a huge development!
I'm so hungry!
That's right, Kikichi!
I'll bring it!
Mr. Tadashi!
I won't allow you to marry someone like you!
You! Don't say that!
I'm a stubborn father!
Bring it here!
Shut up! I'll show you!
Let me do it!
I won't let you die if you end the live broadcast in the middle of it!
What a stubborn guy!
I'm screwed!
What should I do?
That's right!
Wait!
Mr. Omawari, you're going to be in trouble.
It's already the end of the show.
Oh, I found it!
Dad, give me this!
Yes, yes.
I'll give you this.
Well, then, 2,000 yen.
Chief!
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting!
I did it! We're still in time!
Yes!
What's wrong?
Senior...
You know, Ryo.
I've been watching everything.
The live broadcast...
The place where you dropped the pot,
The place where you bought the fake one,
The place where you bought the fake one, is perfect.
You idiot!
I'm so sorry! Please forgive me!
I'm sorry!
I'll admit my crime and come out on my own!
You're great, Mr. Tadashi!
You're a man!
You should respect me!
I'm going to make better sacrifices, I'll get this marriage ready!
Thank you, Tadashi!
Meow!
I'm not sure what it is, but this really moves me!
Kanna, are you going to make it?
Would you make it?
Would you?
Kanna!
You're going to make better sacrifices!
……………
Augh! What!?
I can't believe this!!
Na na na as it comes,
To the one that's always playing dumb with looks,
I don't want to be someone who just fights for looks
If I make a mistake on the corner, the moon will run away
Because now is not everything, don't worry too much
Even if I lie and cheat a little, I sometimes help someone
Baby do you know me? I have a nice breath heading for tomorrow
Don't get sick, I'll do what I have to do, my cute breath
What's hard to understand is
I want to show you that
It's better than seeing it again
Na na na na na na na na na na na
You came again, Professor Tondemo!
What? Food crisis prevention with biotechnology?
What's this huge shrimp and crab?
If this thing runs away, I'll tell you it's ridiculous!
I'm running away from what I'm saying!
Next time, shrimp, crab, squid, the arrival of a huge biopsy.
Thank you!
There is a wall over there
Ah, there must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!