Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you're watching TV, ♪
♪ make sure to lighten up your room and stay away from it! ♪
♪ Baby! ♪
♪ Hello, goodbye, ♪
♪ if you're just a night away, ♪
♪ you'll be home soon! ♪
♪ Don't panic, ♪
♪ this town is small, ♪
♪ where are you going? ♪
♪ If you're in a hurry, ♪
♪ turn around! ♪
♪ Maybe, ♪
♪ there's someone better than me, ♪
♪ someone, ♪
♪ if you're here, ♪
♪ let me hear it! ♪
♪ Let me hear it all night! ♪
♪ I don't hate waiting, ♪
♪ because I'm a woman on a camel's back! ♪
♪ I don't want to lose, ♪
♪ I'm a woman on a camel's back! ♪
♪ I've loved you for ten thousand years, ♪
♪ I've loved you, ♪
♪ I'm a woman on a camel's back! ♪
The year, 1999.
The sudden outbreak of war seemed to be a long-term situation.
Later, it accelerated to a slowdown.
and then...
Stop!
You can't catch me!
I'll make you turn around from here!
Tensai!
It's a good match.
No way!
I did it!
It's been two hours and fifteen minutes.
I finally won!
Fight, Trump's Dome!
How frustrating!
Even though I'm Trump, I lost to Ryo-chan!
Then, I'll let the loser get a penalty.
A penalty?
What's this?
Reiko-san!
Yeah!
What are you doing, senpai?
I lost to Trump, so I'll get a penalty.
Trump?
I'll definitely pay you back.
Hey, the war will take time, so let's make it a faster match next time.
Then, how about speed?
Speed?
I want speed.
Speed.
It's a game about speed.
You have to take out a card from your hand, and you have to take out the rest of it regardless of the mark.
The one who loses the fastest wins.
If it's speed, I've never lost before.
You're stupid.
You think I can win with speed?
Ready, go!
3 and 9.
So it's 4 and 10.
You're too naive, Reiko!
It's so fast!
What are you? A speed patrol!
This is...
The speed of Senpai is so fast that I can see many of your hand solar plexus.
The game of soldier mode.
Ouch!
Ryosan is so strange.
It turns out even Reiko didn't play any.
The balance is too much.
You know how hard it is?
It's ten years faster than winning with speed.
Then, let's play a penalty game.
One more.
Let's play it together next time.
How about Indian Poker?
Indian Poker?
You put a trump card on your forehead and the one with the most numbers wins.
Thirteen is the strongest.
I can't see mine.
That's different from the normal poker.
If you think the opponent is stronger, you'll get off.
I see.
Match ball is the tip.
Let's go.
One, two, three!
They are so strong.
I can't beat them.
I can't beat them at all.
Then, it's a tip.
First, five.
I'll get off.
Was it this?
I'm so frustrated. I shouldn't have got off.
Now I don't know how to play.
Nakagawa, what are you going to do?
Me?
Get off or play with me?
Which one?
That's...
Ten!
What are you going to do, Nakagawa?
Wait a minute.
Senpai.
I have three cards.
Normally, I have a low chance of losing.
But Senpai's confidence...
Could it be that I have one or two?
Twenty.
You're going to play a game, aren't you?
Don't regret it.
Thirty.
It's okay to play a game.
But don't regret it later.
It's a game, Nakagawa.
I'm going to get off.
Good.
I'm the winner.
I've got five.
Three.
Two.
Benz price, this time.
That's right.
Ten.
I won't do that.
I will win.
Three.
O!
Ten!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
You can't watch it!
Ryo-chan, why don't you just do a no-fault game?
No way! I don't have the fun of playing games then!
Huh? I have an idea. A game that's no-fault but still fun.
Huh?
The winner sits on the chair, and the loser is kneeling on the ground.
An ultimate game.
An ultimate?
Game?
The game is called...
"The Wind of the Wind".
"The Wind of the Wind"?
I don't know.
What kind of game is it?
I've brought it, Ryo-tsu!
Hey, Sakonji Okuda!
Senpai, what is this chair?
It's a no-fault chair that you use when playing Daito.
The winner is the only one to sit on this chair.
Huh? This is...
Hey! I told you this is a no-fault chair!
Don't touch it!
I can't afford to lose today's game.
Why not?
Huh?
Ah!
A Doki-Memo cushion!
I've never been able to become a no-fault.
But I have the will to win.
I can't let you take this chair away from me!
It's over!
"The Wind of the Wind" is a game where you get a bigger number of cards than the previous players, and the one who dies first wins.
Three is the weakest, and two is the strongest.
If you get two or more cards in the same number, you can get them all at once.
Then I'll go first.
Three...
Then I'll go with eleven.
Wait a minute!
I'm going to throw away the cards that are smaller than four!
No, eleven is the smallest.
What?
One.
Hey, what's with Reiko?
Because the only cards in the picture are one and two.
What?
Me too!
Then, are these two the only ones with strong cards?
I can't win.
I can't give up. Saori's chair is on it.
Thirteen, double.
One, double.
Eleven.
Twelve.
One.
Eleven, double.
Twelve, double.
Two, double.
Pass.
Two.
Thirteen.
I'm number one!
Two.
Twelve.
I'm number two!
No! Saori!
Then I'll go next.
Three and...
Four.
Five.
All I have now is one card.
I know you'll say, "No, 4, no, 14."
I know.
But I never really remember the number.
If Saori was number one,
that would mean she knew it.
Really?
I'm so sorry for him.
I don't know what to do.
I'm at my limit.
Three and...
Five.
Your game is useless.
"You're useless."
This bloke.
-The last one! -That's so dirty, Terai!
Why don't you take out one?
I'm not trying to be a traitor.
I don't want to be the last one.
That's right, Senpai.
You remember Ryo-chan, don't you?
What will happen to the last one?
What?
Damn it! I didn't expect to sit here.
Terai-san doesn't have a seat, Sakonji-san has one,
I have three, and Kei-chan is the top.
Then I'll take a seat.
What... what is it?
Nothing.
It's a natural right of a great man to sit there.
I-I see.
Then...
What is it?
You can sit.
I don't mind.
Then...
Then let's sit on the back.
That's good, right?
If you want to do that, then it can't be helped.
Then...
Hey you, Biri, hand over the trump!
I understand, mess!
I'll go off the wall holdin' it right then and there!
My two luckys has come, that'll give me another shot!
Ryo-san, you give it up!
Huh?
I have to be the last one to hand out the two best numbers in my wallet to Daifugo.
There are two groups of Buffy here, so you should share both of them.
We're starting to run out of space.
Yes, senpai.
Damn, I came all the way here.
Oh, my goodness. I've become a terrible person.
Then, I'll start with Ryo Iri.
You're the boss.
Huh?
I'm sorry. That's exactly right.
See? I knew it.
Damn it. Don't think you can live like this.
"Diamond Five-Round"
Impact! Diamond Five-Round!
I didn't think you would have such a hand.
Can you do this, senpai?
Yes, you can put the same number of lines on the same table.
Ryo always uses this rule.
So, there are various local rules.
So, don't complain that the rules are different.
Everyone, give up.
Okay, this is the end.
I did it, Saori!
But, Kei-chan has already gone up, so it's three.
Oh, when will I reach your place, Saori?
Damn, I only have one more.
Is it a rematch between the Terai and me again?
Ryo, pass?
Yes, you.
Can I give it up?
Hey, let's start the game.
Then, I'll give it up.
I'm going to do a rematch.
In fact...
Oh, it's a draw...
Wait a minute.
Eh, can you give it up, Ryo-san?
I don't think so...
Pass.
Then, let's start the "Double Five-Round."
Ah, I got it!
It's a non-civilian-competitive pair attack.
Ryo-san, you said "Pass."
Pass.
Double Seven.
Double Nine.
Pass.
Three, please.
I lost.
Ryo-chan, you're getting the best of it...
It fits perfectly in your seat.
Shut up!
I had a F and a 2 at first.
If I had that, I could have won.
You're a loser.
I should have avoided my first card.
Saori!
I can't get up because I'm going to take the card.
Even if you say that, that's the rule.
The odds are falling and the big bad is more and more against.
That's the rule.
This is Japan.
It should be capitalistic.
It's unfair.
This game is capitalism.
Eh?
Those with power will win.
That's unfair.
Those who stop the poor will be equal.
That's the world of capitalism.
Isn't that socialism?
You seem to be fundamentally mistaken.
Eh?
You think you're poor and make a fool of yourself.
No, Ryo. Don't say that.
Is there any big bad that is big bad?
It's the same.
That's what you said.
You're right.
The real poor are Billy and Booby.
It's the poor's fault.
Ryo, calm down. It's a game.
Don't you want to become a big bad?
Don't you want to be the best in the game world?
But I don't want to become a big bad.
You're so naive.
It's a man's way of life to get up with any hand.
Ryo is the only one who does that.
Any hand?
Yes.
Right.
I was just curious.
These guys were all amateurs.
There was nothing fanciful about the game.
This game is fun.
It is.
Even the amount of Nico-nico is popular here.
I'll use it.
The ultimate hidden trick, the picture card.
You collect cards when you have one or two good cards, and they come up.
When you cut it, the good part will not move.
You only cut the upper part.
When you hand them out, just take out your own cards from the bottom.
Like this...
I did it! It's perfect!
Here, Senpai.
Nakagawa, you gave him a third one.
It's from Ryo-chan.
I'll show you how I do a great miracle!
It's a King's Three-card!
What's this card all of a sudden?
It's a long-term card.
Hey, are you going to hand them out or not?
Pass.
Then it's my turn.
Ace's Four-card!
-It's amazing! -It's amazing!
Double Two!
-It smells good! -It smells good!
And finally, Nakagawa gets the third pair.
Kei-chan, did you really exchange them?
Yes. It's true that Senpai gave me two of them.
Then... then all the good cards went to Ryo-chan.
How could this happen?
Then I'll apply the rule of the country.
The rule of the country?
The rule of the country.
If the best one gets the top,
the worst one gets the bottom.
If the best one gets the bottom,
the worst one gets the top.
Then I'll be the bad one!
Then I'll get closer to Saori.
Sakonji-san is in the middle,
so you can't change your position.
That's not true.
That's...
I haven't even put out one card yet!
Shut up!
Come on, move!
That's my seat!
Sigh...
What a mess.
The rules are rules.
Even if it's a mess, the rules are rules.
Well, let me get closer.
This is good.
Saori!
The big bad guy's seat is comfortable to sit on.
Ryo-chan, what are you doing?
You won't forgive my Saori!
You won't forgive me?
What are you talking about?
Who are you talking to?
If you're upset,
come here yourself.
I'll take care of Saori until then.
Hehehe.
S-sorry, Saori.
Please hold on a little longer.
Then I'll give you the card.
It's a good job for a big bad guy.
Hohohoho...
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute!
W-what?
I'll give it to you.
Eh?
But...
It's the best man's job to give the card.
Why? You're a big bad guy.
I told you it's good for the best man.
Shut up!
What?
I'm not like you.
I know the suffering of the poor.
Even if you're a big bad guy,
you're doing the work you don't like.
That's dangerous.
If I don't pack it properly,
I'll be in trouble.
This is the best hand for a big bad guy.
Senpai.
Yes?
Hmm...
Oh, this is the best.
It's a good card.
Then,
I'll take care of this.
Oh!
A better card than the one I gave you has returned!
What?
Hohohoho...
Maro is a kind man.
But is it really good?
It doesn't matter.
Start early.
Then I'll start.
Yes.
From 3 to 13,
it's a series of cards.
No!
I can't believe it.
I've never seen this before.
Ryo-chan, it's a joke.
No, it's not a joke.
I can't stand such stupid things.
It's a pile of cards.
Senpai gave it to me.
What?
What do you mean by a pile of cards?
It's a game of picking a good card for yourself.
Come to think of it,
Ryo-chan's hand was too good.
That's right.
And it's a big failure.
but it's strange that I don't have the duty to hand out cards.
Senpai, no way.
Well, Boku-chan,
let's go back to the meeting room.
Because Boku-chan is the one who will cut the trump card.
So, Nagagawa-chan,
you go there.
I don't like it.
Everyone is so suspicious.
I don't blame you.
Damn it.
I can't put it in anymore.
Are you not going to leave now, Ryo-chan?
Fine.
But why are you just standing there?
I'm sure you're thinking like that.
The others here are also MIKE.
You two have to get out of here as soon as possible.
introductions
I just said nothing.
Let's go back to our meeting room.
It's been a long time.
Another double?
Gah!
Come on! Pick it up, you poor things!
Here, a double for eleven.
So you had it.
Hey, here's your favorite, a shot.
Shut up!
This is an important moment, so stay quiet.
Hi, my sweet honey. How are you?
Sorry for making you lonely.
Now, drive my Porsche to the tavern.
Sorry, but I'm getting a little sick, so go over there.
Here, ten!
Why aren't you going to take Reiko?
I'm begging you, everyone, mind your own business!
Pass, pass, pass.
Why don't you join us, Shiratori-san?
The Grand Fugou.
The Grand Fugou?
It's a game that's good for me.
No, it's not an exaggeration to say it's a game for me.
Okay, I'll be happy to join you.
Shiratori's in, so let's start over.
That's unfair.
This is...
There are two "Ni"s, right?
It's a chance to become a Grand Fugou!
Hey, Shiratori, you're a beginner, so I'll let you do it first.
You're foolish. I'll make you regret it right away.
Look at me!
This is the true power of the Grand Fugou.
N-no way!
Two "Ni"s all of a sudden.
How's that? Did I scare you?
You're an idiot!
What did you say?
What are you going to do after this?
Oh no! The rest is just "Kasu"!
Pass.
But if you don't play, it won't be a game.
I-it can't be helped.
Here.
Yes.
Pass.
So Shiratori is the best.
It's too late to be alive. I'll be a Grand Fugou right away!
I'm not forgetting anything about Billy's Shiratori,
but I have to give you a card.
I know!
Lucky!
This time, two cards are four.
Here, Shiratori-san.
Yeah.
But there are still two cards, so it's okay.
Hey, it's your turn. Hurry up and give it to me.
Hmph.
Look at this.
My card!
Here it is!
What?
No one can cut this card.
I-I can't cut it, but...
So, what are you going to do after this?
What did you say?
Oh no!
It seems to be going to be the same as before.
What?
Let's see.
Hmm...
This will make Shiratori-san Billy 20 times in a row.
It's not like he's just bad at cards.
He only sends out big cards.
Well, in other words, he's a weakling.
I've never seen someone so weak.
From here on, I'll call you Billy-kun.
See, Shiratori-Billy-kun?
See, Billy-Billy-Shiratori-Billy.
You're as like a game as you really are.
Huh?
Even if the game is Billy, I'm a big loser in reality!
Take this!
That's what happened yesterday.
Just like the game, I became a poor person in the real world.
You must be satisfied too.
I really thought I'd be a loser...
Sorry, I wasn't mean, Billy-kun.
I won't be a loser again!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Subs by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Check out the description for the
I will make something like this
Next time "Departure Robot Police"
Thank you for watching