Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you're watching TV, ♪
♪ make the room brighter and look away! ♪
Baby!
♪ Hello, goodbye. ♪
♪ If you live just for a night, you'll be home soon. ♪
♪ Don't panic. ♪
♪ Where are you going in this small town? ♪
♪ Hurry up and turn around. ♪
♪ Maybe, there's someone better than me. ♪
♪ If you're here, ♪
♪ let me hear you. ♪
♪ Let me hear you all night. ♪
♪ I don't hate waiting. ♪
♪ Because I'm a woman on a camel's back. ♪
♪ I don't want to lose. ♪
♪ I'm a woman on a camel's back. ♪
♪ I've loved you for a thousand years. ♪
What?
Marry me!
Kan-chan, don't make such a big voice.
How can I not make a big voice?
Why can I marry you even though I'm single?
Even if you say that...
Did you say Shiori-san?
Yes.
You're still in your 20s.
Why did you marry a single man from Tonchin Kankon?
Tonchin Kankon?
When we were kids, we were friends.
Tonpei-kun and Chin-kichi-kun
called Kan-chan and my four friends
Tonchin Kankon, with the name in their minds.
♪
...Ton bei, Ton.
Chin-kichi, Chin.
Kan-kichi, Kan.
♪
What are you doing, Kanta?
Kanta, let's go!
The four of us,
Without the K
Kanta, you are going too slowly.
You're too much! You have to go to the store early!
But... I'm embarrassed, Kan-chan...
You're just a plain person in Tonchin Kankon.
I'll take a picture of you.
Ready?
Yeah!
Even if you go in a hurry...
Is everyone ready? Is there anyone who's not around?
No one's around!
Then, please.
Okay.
I feel like I've forgotten something.
I feel the same way.
But I remember...
Wait!
Kon-tan!
W-wait!
You can't forget me!
Sensei! I forgot Kon-tan! Please stop the bus!
What?!
In such a state,
Tonchin Kankon was eventually turned into Tonchin Kankon.
The reason we got together was because of a bus tour planned by a travel agency.
G-Guide?
The person next to you isn't on the bus!
Hey!
It's terrible to leave me behind!
If you hadn't noticed, I'd have been left behind.
Thank you so much.
Um, if you don't mind...
How about one?
Well, I'll have one.
That's how we started dating.
And then, I've had similar experiences.
So, you've been stimulated by your female instincts.
Uh, well...
Kon-tan, you did a good job.
You're pretty and you're nice.
K-Kan-chan!
Anyway, you're so smart.
I'll be the one to give you the wedding ceremony.
So, when is the ceremony?
Uh...
What's wrong?
Kan-chan, I've decided not to give you the wedding ceremony.
Why?
Actually, the company I work for is still in red.
There's no bonus and the salary is 20% off.
I don't have the time to give you the ceremony.
That's because you're impolite.
But is that okay, Shiori-san?
I'm happy just to be with you even if I don't give you the ceremony.
You're making me cry.
I really did find a good wife!
Alright!
I'll give you the wedding ceremony!
Eh? K-Kan-chan...
Don't worry about the money!
But...
It's okay! Leave it to me!
That Conta, right?
So, lend me the venue where the master is.
I understand the situation. But I can't just say it's free.
Yeah!
It's only for friends and relatives to attend.
It's 50 people, but how much does it cost?
I can give you the wedding ceremony for free.
But the charity...
Well, it's only 20,000 yen for one.
50 for 20,000 yen?
It costs 1 million yen?
I'm not joking.
I can't afford to pay for it.
I'm so tired of it.
It's because you don't know the common sense of the world and treat it cheap.
Shut up, you idiot!
Even if it's a new year or a new year's party, you can't afford to drink alone if you have 5,000 yen.
You're such a jerk.
You're running to make money even if you have 5,000 yen.
You idiot!
Don't make the wedding ceremony a new year's party or a new year's party!
Well, it's true.
There are some souvenirs and photos of the anniversary.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Hmm...
The 13th of next month will be a big disaster on Friday.
Kankichi, the wedding ceremony is not scheduled for this day.
It's okay for half the price.
That's okay.
Really?
It's a big disaster on Friday the 13th.
In short, you should have a wedding ceremony.
Okay, it's decided on that day.
You can meet up with me later.
See you.
You idiot!
Why aren't you coming?
Damn it!
How bad of you!
Why don't you ask if Kansai will get married?
Isn't this place setup?
No, it's...
It's too much!
Practice makes perfect!
Master, you really are a genius!
That's how the master hired me to be the butler's servant.
Master, this is the episode that we promised.
Please take a look.
Th-This is it!
Hello!
Ryo-san, you really think you can win?
If I lose, I'll return half of my share!
But there are three former professional baseball players in the enemy team.
Are you sure you're okay?
Even if there are a Maguire and a Saucer in the big leagues,
I'll never lose as long as I'm a skid!
Volleyball!
Now you're a professional.
But to earn 500,000, you can't lose!
What?
What about the ball?
I can't take that kind of hit!
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I... I got it!
Out!
He's got a great spirit.
Ryo-san is different when it comes to money.
Two outs, two or three draws.
I'll finish you off in one shot!
He's the only one who's tough.
There's one draw open here, so I'll let him walk.
Hmph.
That's right!
Oh, my God!
What the...
Yay!
If you want to win, call my physical strength company anytime!
Hello?
Physical strength company?
No, it's not.
It's me!
It's Kasane.
Hello?
I got a call.
Yes, yes.
It's a baseball pitcher.
When is the game?
The 12th.
Wait a minute.
It's open from 9:30 a.m. to 11:00 a.m.
Is that okay?
Where is it?
Yes, yes.
I got it.
The bonus is cash, so you can deposit it in the bank.
Or you can prepare cash before the game.
Well, then...
Here you go.
From 9:30 a.m. to 11 o'clock.
All right, I've got the target amount.
You'll get my pocket money after 13 days.
You've started your business again?
Yeah, that's a little different.
I need to earn 500,000 by the 13th.
So I started a physical strength company.
Physical strength company?
It's for baseball, gateball, mahjong, moving, and hunting grass.
It's a company that attracts for a number of sports and jobs.
The company is a company that takes care of the staff.
That's a great schedule.
It's true.
During the day, there are also gate ball matches.
Look at this!
You've been wearing that shirt for more than 10 days.
No, it's the inside.
Body!
Look at this well-trained body.
Superficial physical strength and quick-release power.
A man is the main thing to earn money by taking care of his own body.
He's a very stingy person who loves to earn money.
It's strange.
You're always stingy.
I can't say anything.
But I've thought about it.
It's a perfect business for my senior.
Right?
I started working and earned 250,000 yen in just a week.
What's the 250,000 yen?
Oh, manager!
It's nothing.
More importantly, the manager.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Are you okay with the meeting with the manager?
Oh, I'll leave it to you.
Yes.
That's right, Ryo.
I'm counting on you for the judo tournament on the 12th.
I forgot about it.
Idiot!
The president said he was looking forward to it and going to support it.
You know what?
Win it, even if it's a small amount.
Got it?
Hey, it's free to win.
Did you say something?
Nothing.
Have a good day.
Good.
Nakagawa, when are the judo tournaments starting?
The start is at 12 o'clock.
If we win, I think the finals will be at around 5 o'clock.
Oh, no.
On the 12th, we have four games of grass baseball from 5 a.m. to 11 a.m.
From noon, we have a rugby game and a swimming tournament in the town.
And we have a ballet presentation and a golf caddy.
What?
It's true.
No matter how much you lose, it's impossible.
No.
I'm going to do it because I've been told to.
That's the motto of Ryo-tsu Stereo Co., Ltd.
I'll definitely do it!
The end.
I don't have time to be angry. Ryo-chan, change your clothes quickly.
The last match was an extension.
So, did you win all four matches from the morning?
Of course. If I lose, the price will be halved.
I didn't come out of such a simple match.
Don't say that, hurry up.
Then, we will start the first round of the fifth match.
Ryotsu, who is the winner of the Katsushika match, and Yamada, who is the loser of the Aoto match.
Let's finish this match quickly.
Start!
Clear!
One point!
That was fast.
One second was decided.
Senpai, you did a great job.
You did it, Ryo-chan.
I'll be back in 30 minutes.
Yes, sir.
Ryo-chan.
You did it.
No, it's already started.
Ryo-san, you are late.
You have already forgotten.
It's a precious thing to do a job that takes money.
Ryo-chan, you are in the 50m freestyle of the men's youth club.
Are you there?
You will be disqualified if you are not here.
Yes, I'm going back in 30 minutes.
Don't scare me, Ryo-san.
I'm sorry. My schedule is a bit different.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Wow, this is great!
I've become a fish!
"The strength of the strong is overwhelming. This is amazing!"
"You're amazing, Ryo."
"The next 100m freeway was at 1:30."
"Oh, is that so?"
"I'm a little tired today. I'll be back at 1:30. See you!"
"Ryo!"
"Ryo, aren't you here yet?"
"I told you I would definitely come."
"Hey! Sorry to keep you waiting."
"You're here. Hurry up and listen. We're about to kick off."
"Ryo!"
"Leave it to me!"
"Don't push me!"
"You're in my way!"
"Ryo!"
"I'm going to kick your ass!"
"I'm gonna kick your ass!"
"Ryo!"
"We did it! As expected of the human-based Ryo-tsu!"
"I want you to join our rugby team instead of being a spy!"
"Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!"
"Hey, what's wrong, Ryo-tsu?"
"Are you hurt?"
"What? I'm fine. Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!"
"I'm fine. I'm your dear friend."
"You should rest on the bench for a while!"
"Referee! We're moving the players out of their place!"
"That team is strong, so we'll win if we show up!"
"Let's go! Golf is starting!"
"Caddy, is that your belt?"
"T-that's the safe one. Then, how about you, sir?"
"I'll hold this and do my best!"
"What? You're not going to carry it?"
"I'm not going to let you take it!"
"O-okay!"
"Then, everyone, you can drive the cart yourselves."
"Then, I'll see you in the next hall!"
"Wait!"
"Ryo-tsu from Kazushika!"
"Is Ryo-tsu from Kazushika here?"
"What? You mean the caddies for rugby, swimming, and golf?"
"And he's also going to be a volunteer for the 3:00 ballet performance!"
"He's going to be a runner, too?"
"That idiot..."
"He's not here, so he's in danger!"
"I'm here!"
"Ryo-chan!"
"W-what's with that outfit?"
"It's all because the road is crowded, so it's a pain in the ass!"
"Here I go!"
"One! That's it!"
"Wow, that's strong!"
"But that outfit is too creepy..."
"It's so bad..."
"What's that?!"
"Although it's for money, it's embarrassing to look like this!"
"Hey, Mr. Takemoto. How long are you going to look at me?"
"Well, well... Here."
"Sorry I'm late!"
"No problem."
"Wh-what? What's with that outfit?"
"Whoaa-!"
I'm getting a little nervous.
Are you okay, Senpai?
You look pale.
I think I'm having a hard time with my schedule.
You've made it to the finals.
You'll win for sure!
Leave it to me!
The final round will begin soon!
I can't believe I'm facing someone like him.
Damn it!
Hajime!
I have to keep my stamina!
Rear!
Ryo-san, you're the champion!
I did it!
You're too big.
Senpai!
What's wrong, Senpai?
I think my back is flat.
You'd better not skate today and just take a rest.
Don't say that!
Your money is the biggest problem if you cancel the race!
You're not going to be able to swim if you don't get 500,000.
You have to win in the last round.
Nakagawa, bring something strong!
O-okay!
Ouch...
R-Ryo-tsu, what about the award ceremony?
Please come out on behalf of the leader.
Ouch...
You're already at your limit.
I know that.
But a man's promise to say something once is something you can protect no matter what.
I'll participate as long as I can move!
Rather than helping the pro, you're helping the money.
The 200m free-fall is finally over.
Who will win?
Damn it!
My back hurts, I can't get any strength!
Oh, yeah!
He passed it to the fish!
He won't come out again!
The second-place player is chasing him!
Oh!
He got away!
No good!
I'm losing consciousness!
Gonta...
You'll definitely get a wedding ring!
Oh, Ryo-tsu!
What a great start!
Who will win?
What?
Ryo-tsu!
He won the 200m free-fall after the 50m and 100m free-fall!
Yes!
I won the first place!
Ryo-san, you're so lucky!
Ryo-san!
Oh!
He's sinking!
We have to help him!
I'll do my best, Gonta!
Ready...
Don't touch him!
Where did Ryo-san go?
He paid for the free-fall in the morning, but he's still clean!
J-j-just hold on.
We're heading to the hospital now.
He had a rough day yesterday, and he's had a bad back.
Now that you mention it...
It was my promise!
Um...
I came back today to get some words of thanks for Kan-chan at his wedding...
Is Mr. Ryochi here?
I see.
Kankichi, is your back okay?
If you had me give you a painkiller, it would be better than last night.
Even so, you're just a little kid, aren't you?
One ten thousand yen for one is a good deal.
Kankichi, how can I thank you?
You worked hard until you were a little kid.
Don't say that.
You're the most beautiful woman in the whole of the world.
You'll be happy.
Thank you.
Hey, Mr. Ryo, are you there?
Damn it, you came all the way here to complain.
Mr. Ryo, we didn't come to attack you.
Huh?
You're so mean, Mr. Ryo.
If you're working hard for this day,
you should've just told us.
Mr. Ryo, I'll get you fired up.
Hey, come on in.
Even the Samba Team from the shopping district.
Ryo, I've been looking around.
Let's dance together.
Oh, you're happy.
Kanta, Shiori, come on in.
Okay, let's go.
My back hurts.
To be continued
I loved you with tears in my eyes
I wonder how much people can get
With such irreplaceable things in their lives
You are me, I am you
That alone was enough to fill me up
Just laughing at you
I felt that I was healed from all the pain
Next time on Laugh Family, Ebisu-kun!
Thanks for watching!