By statistical european
When you watch the tv, please bright up the room and look away!
Don't have money? Come to where I am!
I also don't have money, and I worry
Don't worry
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
Sooner or later it will be somehow
I know! I know! I know!
If you understand, shut up and follow me!
Ryo-tsu's Prank!
Here it comes! Make it more intense!
Yes!
A policeman with thick eyebrows tied up with sandalwood!
It's definitely the person I heard from the viewers!
It's Mr. Omari, Ryo-tsu!
Are the traps okay?
Perfect!
I brought the fake
I saw it!
Good! Keep it as it is!
Huh?
I went too far
That's strange
Why didn't you pick up the fake?
There's no fake!
When did you...
No way!
Here it is!
Stop!
There's nothing suspicious
I'll play it slowly this time
I can't see anything unusual
Next, I'll try to send it in pieces
I'll try to send it in pieces
What?!
I can only see this one piece!
How fast!
It's not the time to be impressed!
Hurry up and follow me!
Bring out the placard and take the final picture!
Hey!
I found something good!
I got a reward from the God of the Placard!
That's right!
What a pain in the ass!
There's something good about living as a human
Thank you, God!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
What is it, Terai-kun?
It looks fun
Did something good happen?
What are you talking about?
What a strange Terai-kun
Is that so?
Oh, that's right
Ryo-san, do you want to eat this?
What is this?
It's a small-sized fried pork
What?
It's a small-sized fried pork!
It's a bite-sized fried pork
So it's a small-sized fried pork
How about one?
What is this strange development?
I can't believe he knows about the small-sized fried pork
I'm sure the Terai still has the reward
I know it!
Give me the small-sized fried pork!
It doesn't fit in your hand!
Even if you change it, it won't fit in your hand!
What?
Ryo-san, you are so strange
That was close
Although I'm his colleague, I'm not talking about money
I have to be careful
Who is looking at me?
Is it my imagination?
No, I feel it
I bet I'm a small-sized fried pork!
Small-sized?
Yes, a small-sized fried pork!
Small-sized!
Small-sized is a big job!
Small-sized?
I want to do it!
Small-sized fried pork for a cat?
Don't tell me they are...
I can't believe it
I'm rich anyway
Ouch!
Alright, let's go to the Kimegose River!
Yes!
Too bad!
It was a surprise camera!
We made such a decisive moment
If we don't show this, the show will not end
Damn it!
We'll catch it no matter what!
Hurry up!
There it is!
I'll protect the small-sized fried pork!
Too bad!
Was it a surprise?
Oh no!
Damn it! Where did it go?
Over there!
Too bad!
Wait for me!
Where did it go?
Over there!
Alright, we can do this this time!
Then, let's go!
Too bad!
It was a surprise camera!
Go away!
OMG!
I can make it count!
Wait for me alright?
I'll give you this fried pork no matter what!!
We will give you a little something!
What?
So, you made a surprise film for Ryo-chan?
Yes
I received a note from the audience
that said that there is a crazy...
No, no, no, a very unique police officer
I was wondering what would happen if I found a fake koban.
I thought I'd film it, but Ryotsu-san took it away in a flash.
If I don't show this, the show won't end. Please catch him somehow.
But did Ryotsu really take away the koban?
Certainly he is an idiot, a mess, and a poor and poor police officer.
But he was a cat, so he would have fallen.
Or maybe...
There's a definitive evidence.
This is it.
I expected it, but...
I can't believe he was really a cat.
Damn it, Ryotsu!
I'll make my heart empty, which I tried to believe just a little bit.
Let's go!
Where are you going?
I'm looking forward to seeing where Ryotsu, who got the koban, is going.
He looks like he has given up on the people.
Well, let's see if I can change the koban into money.
I have no choice.
Wait!
Hey, Ryotsu!
What are you doing here?
Nothing serious...
What do you need it for?
There was a kottouhin-ya here.
I didn't know about it.
I heard that there are some people who sell the food they picked up in the army.
Especially, there are those who pick up the bowls and try to sell them.
That's right. The chief is right.
Are you hiding something from me?
No, nothing at all.
If you apologize now, I won't forgive you.
What are you talking about? I don't mind.
Really? You really don't do anything.
Of course. I'm the one who is the most powerful and most wise.
Don't be stupid. I've already checked the bowls you picked up.
What?
Look.
That's too bad.
It's a surprise camera.
So, what are these bowls?
They are all fake.
Fake?
Yes.
What? You're so mean.
You did a good job of making me fall for you.
You idiot.
You're the one who tried to make me fall for you.
And you were the one who was beaten to the end.
You won't forgive me today.
Ouch.
Shit. I'll run away as soon as I can.
Thank you.
I'll definitely get my score.
But...
I don't think we should broadcast this.
What?
If this is broadcasted, the whole country will be ashamed of the book.
But we'll definitely get your score.
I'll put a mosaic on your face. It'll be fine.
Excuse me.
Hello?
What?
No way.
What's wrong?
The bowls you brought are real.
What?
I was going to check them next week at the treasure inspection program.
But my phone just...
What?
Are these all fake?
If they're real, I'll...
Ryo.
Oh, it's you guys.
Hey, what's that?
This is...
Well, it's a fake of the bowl.
A fake of the bowl?
I'll do it because I want to.
Yay!
There you go.
Wow!
Awesome!
That's great.
All right, me too.
Wow, that's Ryo!
If you're going to do this, leave it to me.
See?
All right.
Come on.
Hey!
Where did Ryo-tsu go?
I'm not kidding! If we lose the real one, we're done for!
I don't want that! I still have my car loan!
I still have my house loan for 32 years!
Ouch! Ryo-tsu! Where's the one from before?!
Yaaah!
This is good. The old one is scraped and the gold powder comes out.
Ryo-tsu, that's...
Hey, it's a fake old one!
You can play with it even if it's fake!
If you give it to the kids, they'll be so happy!
N-no way! The old one you picked was the real one!
I don't want that, chief! Are you going to use the camera again?
I can't use it anymore!
No!
That's not real! It's genuine!
What? It's real? It's true!
The real one is worth $11,000,000!
Hold it!
What did he do?!
Good grief!
Stop it!
You idiot! You should reflect on yourself for a while!
No way! I'm not in the wrong!
The TV station people are the ones who made a mistake with the real thing!
Idiot! It's your fault that you got caught in the camera!
The fact that you made a mistake with the little board and the children...
It's all your fault!
No way!
I'm so embarrassed because of you today!
I never thought you would do something like that!
But I don't think there's anyone who would make a mistake with the little board!
So I thought it was a gift from God!
Idiot! You should rest!
I can't believe you got caught in the TV show!
You're the idiot who got caught in that kind of thing!
So you're saying that the director is not caught in the camera?
Of course!
A man who is always calm like me...
He's not like that!
He's not caught in such a obvious trick!
Unlike you!
Huh?
If you had acted with pride as a police officer like me...
You wouldn't have been so caught!
You'd better be careful!
I see. I understand, sir.
Welcome!
Hmm?
Huh?
Hey, is this pot also 500 yen?
This one?
Well...
I'm in trouble.
Grandpa hasn't come home yet.
Well, whatever.
Then, I'll take 500 yen.
Okay, here.
This is good.
Please wait, sir.
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning!
Ryo-chan hasn't come yet?
He's in trouble.
Good morning.
Thank you, sir.
I'm sorry.
Please pass the bill.
Here you go.
What's that?
It's a pot I got from my grandpa in Tsukuda Island.
Here you go.
Hmm...
It's a strange pot.
Huh?
I knew you wouldn't take it seriously.
This pot is made in the Ming Dynasty.
It's a Chinese-style pot.
Oh, I see.
It doesn't look like it, though.
But why did you take it?
I was worried that I might be stolen if I leave it at home.
But if I leave it at home, I'm afraid I'll break it.
I see.
So, sir, would you like to take it?
What?
You mean me?
Anyway, you're a gentleman.
If you're as sharp-eyed as the chief, you know how valuable this pot is, right?
If you break a precious asset, both historically and culturally, I'm sorry, sir.
And this pot is as sharp-eyed as the chief.
I think it would be better if you were by my side.
I'm leaving it to you, sir!
I'll leave it to you!
Oh...
Ah...
It can't be helped to be told that.
I'll keep it at home.
Really?
Thank you!
The first step was successful.
Well then, everyone.
Thank you.
Thank you very much!
Oh?
Who is it?
No matter how many times I look at it, it doesn't look like such an expensive pot.
Could it be that Ryotsu is trying to trick me?
What a surprise! This pot costs 1 billion yen!
It's a wonderful pot!
It's the same as this pot!
This pot was made in the Ming Dynasty in China,
and it is said to be the only pot that the emperor used at that time.
Therefore, if it is in existence, it will cost 1 billion yen for sure.
1 billion yen?
1 billion yen.
This pot is 1 billion yen.
You!
You idiot!
Don't talk to me before you get in!
I'm sorry.
It's because a professional inspector said so, so there's no doubt.
This pot is real.
The second stage has succeeded.
Well then, I'm going.
Yes, have a good trip.
No way.
It's 1 billion yen.
N-no way.
What's wrong with you?
You!
Well then, I'm going.
Yes, have a good trip.
This is good.
No way.
I feel like everyone is aiming at this pot.
And so, my pot is...
Pot?
Ah, pot, pot!
Two buttons?
Pot!
Isn't it one button?
Pot.
Pot!
I thought that you would put it in a pot, so I took it out.
Why are you all looking at me?
Why!
Ryo-tsu, Ryo-tsu, are you there?
What's wrong, my daddy?
What's wrong or do you have to do this?
I couldn't hear the line "1 billion yen?
There are some suspicious people wandering around from the house, and I don't want
to be in touch with such ugly things.
I'll give it back, right now.
Give it back now.
No way.
I have no one to count on than the chief.
I believe that the chief will protect the pot no matter what happens.
I know that the chief is not a person who betrays his subordinates.
I know very well that he is not a person who breaks the promise of taking over once.
That's right. I will always keep my promise.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
As expected of the chief. No, the best in Japan, no, the best in the world.
Ah, ah, ah, ah ...
Ah, stupid!
Oh! Ah, ah!
Emergency! Who put a banana peel in such a place?
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm a little hungry.
Ryotsu, you ...
No, no, no, I don't think I did it on purpose.
I can't do that.
If you get caught, you can't get a pension even if you pay one life.
Ah, ah ...
I know.
The chief is taking good care of the old man on Tsukuda Island,
so I told him to rest assured.
Please take good care of him.
Yeah, you're so loud.
What's going on, Cheshirikun?
The pot! What's going on?
Alright, let's get out of here!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm asking you what you're doing!
You can tell by looking at me.
I'm building a road.
That's why I'm asking you why you're building in front of the station.
Hey, there's a pot! A pot!
We're not allowed to build!
Move quickly!
You don't have to say that...
Hey, there's a pot again!
Anyway, don't build here!
Hey!
Hey, stop!
Hey, hello?
What?
I made a mistake?
Yes, I understand.
I'm sorry.
I think I made a mistake.
Look at that.
If you understand, go away!
Yes, sir.
You've been chased quite a bit.
Now, it's time to finish.
Today was a rough day.
I'm in a bad mood these days.
Well, I guess you are still in a good mood.
I heard you were not able to beat it.
And I don't see what kind of world he has steps up his sleeve.
Okay, okay, bye, bye.
Siyu, what are you doing?
Hurry up!
This is too much for me.
If it's a glue, then...
This should be the original.
Why are there some parts left?
I'm back! I'm back from the patrol!
Chief Oya, what are you doing here?
Oh, no, it's nothing...
Chief, what did you use the glue for?
Why is there glue here?
It seems that there are more adults who can't apologize for their mistakes these days.
Is that so? That's a good thing.
Especially the worst thing to do is to break things that people have taken from you and give them away.
That's right.
I hope everyone is as honest and honest as the chief.
Chief, did you hide something from me?
No, I didn't.
If you want to apologize, you can do it now.
You can forgive me in private.
What are you talking about? I don't have to do it.
Really? You really didn't do anything?
Oh, no! The jar is broken!
I can't do this anymore!
My life is over!
Chief.
What?
Ta-da!
It's a great success!
It's a surprise camera!
What?
That's why it's a surprise camera!
The jar is all messy!
What? Then what is this jar?
It's a 500-yen jar that I bought for free.
So you're talking about 10 billion yen?
Yes! It's a video I made for that TV show.
The shadow around the house...
That's me, too.
The jar suddenly broke.
I broke it in advance and after a while I put it together with a detachable adhesive.
I see.
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
Ryozu!
You're a...
Hey, hey, hey!
Why are you getting angry?
The chief said it's worse to get caught.
That's why you're doing too much!
No way!
Senior!
Hey, Nagagawa Reiko!
You sold me a jar, didn't you?
Yes, Ryo-chan.
It's a big deal.
The jar you bought was a big deal!
I'm sorry.
What?
When I asked my grandpa, that jar wasn't for sale.
I bought it by mistake.
What? Is that so?
That's not all.
Actually, that jar...
What?
China has an illusionary jar from the Song Dynasty.
Apparently it will make 500 billion.
Huh?
500 billion?
That's right!
It's not just 100 billion, but 500 billion!
It's a high-class jar!
So where's the jar?
Where is that jar now?
Huh?
The illusionary jar is 500 billion...
Please be patient!
Wait!
Hey!
Th-This is 500 billion?
Does that mean I've broken 500 billion by myself?
No way!
Nagagawa Reiko!
Unfortunately...
It's all true!
You're so selfish!
N-No way!
Somebody, tell me this is also a surprise camera!
To be continued
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt on top of his eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is Kameari
There must be Kameari
Come to our town
Thank you!
Bonus season has come again this year!
After being chased by a group of shoppers, I escaped from Kameari before the deadline!
I can get money anywhere!
However, the village deep in the mountains was a terrible village where poor livestock rampaged!
Next time, Bonus Soudatsu 7!
Thank you!
There is Kameari
There must be Kameari
Come to our town
Thank you!