Translated by Vortex
I look up at the sunset floating in the river
When I kick the love stone, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I was saving on
I was laughed at that I was just a kid
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only get a slap
It's a city that doesn't change a single time
It's strangely kind
From the water source of the Tungari-boshi
To the taishakuten, the sun sets
Tomorrow is already over like this
I lost my happiness because of the Katsushika Shiba
I realized
I'm such a fool
But isn't that fair?
I like all day being stupid
I aim for the top of the list
of the top of the list
I'm so stupid
But at the same time
I want to get her
and do it
I love what Katsushika Shiba does
I'd be so happy
Because I'm aparadise
Yes.
Well, that wraps up the new SOKAI store.
Everyone, please enjoy yourself until the end!
- Azuma, have you see the bodyguard from before? - I think he has a car accident.
Thank you for visiting my store every time.
Ah, it stinks!
I'm hungry!
I'm so busy!
I have to go to the store!
Why are you still here?
The typhoon is coming, so I have to go to the store.
I'm sorry, sir.
The typhoon is not coming.
These two are former soccer and basketball champions.
They are professional defenders.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry.
It's a million dollars sale.
What?
Sir.
It's off-side, sir.
Give me a ball.
I don't sell roses.
This is the only money.
Please sell it somehow.
But...
Don't say it's impossible.
You can buy an egg from a single one.
You can buy 1 liter of milk, 500ml, 250ml of milk.
You can buy 50ml of milk.
You can buy a pachinko shop according to the consumer's needs.
No way.
Any famous man can't do it with one shot.
All right.
I understand.
After one shot, you can go home.
Of course.
You can't pick up and shoot a falling ball.
I understand.
It's a promise.
If it's no good with just one shot, you must go home.
I'm a man, too. I will keep my promise.
Hurry up and shoot this guy and hand it over.
Yes, sir.
It will be a big fight.
What the hell is this?
I don't know what I can do.
That's a raccoon.
It's a raccoon.
Good.
That was too cruel a raccoon.
I've taken too many.
I guess I'll go with this one.
Seriously, I can't believe my eyes. I'm going to faint.
Wait, I think the other one's coming out.
I can't forget that one.
1, 2, 3, 4...
This one?
This one, I knew it.
But this one...
No, stop it!
If you're the manager, you should practice your poker face.
Go!
I can't believe it!
Yeah!
I've won!
Hurry up and hide the money!
I'm going to take it all!
Hide it, hurry!
It's 52,725...
I'll put the biscuits in a 5-case juice,
Then, 20 cans of yakiniku, crab cans, corned beef each.
A year's worth of toilet paper, 100 sheets of underwear,
1 rice, miso, soy sauce, and 1 bottle of sake.
Just in case, I'll also take 30 watches.
If I take them at night, they'll be enough to live.
After that, deliver them all to Niconico.
How many are left?
There are still 300,000 left.
Please forgive me.
If the prize is empty, the business will be...
Shut up.
You don't have any other money?
Huh?
What about that?
Yes, I'm doing a pet shop for a second job.
If you don't mind, I'll give you 300,000 left for your favorite pet.
Pet, huh?
Ryo-tsu's late again.
He's late for the next day.
I wonder if he'll be able to get a job.
Oh, he's here.
Hey, Ryo-tsu, what time do you think it is?
Good morning.
Ryo-tsu, what's that?
Does this look like a surfboard, chief?
It's a crocodile.
Isn't it cute?
It's a very quiet crocodile.
It doesn't even tickle.
Don't scare me.
Chief, please don't do this.
Well, that was a nice idea.
*你好,四面相*
Ryo-tsu, it's a crocodile.
*もつもちママ*
The pet shop isn't open yet, so it'll be dangerous if they come by tomorrow.
U-u-u-u-u 같아요
It's delicious potato.
You can bite it often.
I love you!
If you're eating with them, they'll be quiet.
They won't bother you.
Good boy.
You're so cute.
Hey, you're not going to buy the crocodile, are you?
Of course I will, Chief Ohara.
Because I've been dreaming of buying a crocodile since I was a child.
I've never heard of that.
Why do you call it a crocodile, not a dog or a cat?
It's hard to believe that it's so easy to misunderstand.
Look at its big eyes shining in the depths of its shell.
You're too good.
No, Ryosuke! You're going to get eaten!
No!
You're going to get eaten!
When you use sharp fangs, you can protect yourself from the outside enemy and kill the prey.
You can even attack people.
Senior!
What? I was just kidding.
You're so cute.
I'll do it!
Chu! Chu! Chu!
Don't be so naughty!
What'd you say?
Su! Su! Su!
I don't forgive you for hurting me.
Let's clean up, Wani-chan.
Be careful so you don't break your back.
Keep it inside!
Don't leave anything behind!
And now you have that sharp fr Virtual Face!
You're so great at taking care of animals.
I hand-me-downed a lasso, to the top of the net.
I'll just have a few bites.
What's up? Are you hungry already?
I see, I see.
You'll get hungry as you grow up.
Okay, okay.
Eat a lot and grow up soon.
Hey, the crocodile is shining.
If you're so spoiled,
you can't raise a good crocodile, Ryo-tsu.
It's okay.
From today, I'm going to be a crocodile
and fight against paranormal phenomena
and evils with the spirit of animal protection.
I'm aiming to reform.
Reform?
There must be a reason.
Eat a lot and grow up soon.
Six? Okay, okay.
It's a crocodile!
What?
You're so smart.
The crocodile's handbag
will cost more than 500,000 yen.
Is it that expensive to have a crocodile?
Yes.
It's a real problem.
If you buy this crocodile for 5 years,
it will grow 5 meters and
sell for about 4 million yen.
It will definitely sell well.
If you buy it for 5 years,
it will grow 4 million yen.
Is that so?
What?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you, Nakagawa?
I'm going to raise a crocodile
and sell it for 4 million yen.
No, no.
I knew it.
I'm not in trouble
with the crocodile.
The manager is.
I knew it.
What money, huh?
I thought you woke up
your mind of animal-loving.
Do you buy chickens, cows, and pigs
as pets, manager?
You buy them for the sake of your life,
don't you?
But...
It's fine to buy a crocodile for your life,
but I buy this as a moving bank.
There's no crocodile here!
If it's a crocodile,
let's go to the kitchen.
What happened?
Look! What?
He's standing with two legs!
Hey, that!
If you buy it for dinner, it's not everyone's meat!
Don't eat it!
Hey, stop it, Reiko!
But, the crocodile is everyone's meat!
If it's meat, I'll give you a treat!
Instead, don't be violent to my precious crocodile!
Got it?
That crocodile is laughing at us!
Don't make fun of him!
Now, let's go for a walk!
You're so violent!
How far are you going?
Hey, hey!
Welcome!
Hey, this is a famous and expensive meat shop!
What do you want?
No, I'm fine today!
Hey, 4,000 yen per kilo!
Don't be so luxurious!
It's cheap!
Hey, you're not eating it!
It's a large portion!
3 of this is for you!
Ouch!
It's meat or meat!
4,000 yen for a handbag!
I have to be careful with my luxury!
This is for you!
100 grams...
Ouch!
One kilo, please!
4,000 yen for a handbag!
I'm a rich man!
I'm a little selfish!
I can't help it!
It was 4 million yen five years later!
Ryo, how much is the meat you fed the crocodile during the day?
Huh?
It was 2,940 yen for 3 kilos of thigh meat.
7,000 yen in total.
What about the amount you ate?
100 grams, 200 yen for a loaf.
That's 1,000 yen.
If you calculate it roughly, it's 240,000 yen per kilo.
Then we'll lose it!
Huh?
What did you say?
The crocodile's sales are 4 million yen.
Stop eating the thigh meat and keep the food cheap.
If you keep it cheap, it'll be 100,000 yen a month.
1 year, 1.2 million yen.
5 years, 6 million yen.
The transaction is minus 2 million yen!
Senpai...
It's not about the savings!
It's about the money!
Shut up!
You tricked that pachinko guy!
Senpai!
Shut up!
I don't care about the money!
I didn't calculate it because it was about the savings!
Damn it!
I can't believe I'm getting so much more money!
I don't need your consolation!
Now that I know you're the boss, there's no reason for me to buy you!
Get out of my sight!
I will not Nuke you!
Now who I am to judge a man like you?
If the crocodile hombres a problem, then Senpai will get fired too!
Why would I get fired?
The problem's with this abacus!
You decided to buy it once.
Now you must take care of the pets, Ryo?
I cannot do this?
I'm not able to take care of my pets?
I don't have the right to be your pet!
You're so stupid!
This is a very soft crocodile.
It wouldn't be good for us if it was a bridge.
But I've never seen a crocodile like this.
It's so cute!
What?
Can you do anything else?
I think I can do it.
You!
You can only feed the birds if you don't make money!
And now, the winner of this week's best work is...
The genius crocodile!
- He won 100,000 yen for winning! - You did it, crocodile!
100,000 yen!
All right, all right, I get it.
I'll make a dog food from tomorrow.
This will be a better deal than selling it.
For the video of the crocodile riding a bicycle,
you'll get 100,000 yen for winning!
Crocodile!
Today, I'll feed you real meat.
But I'll give you the cheapest meat.
If you want to eat good meat,
you'll have to make more money.
You'll have to make your own living expenses.
You understand?
Hey, you old man!
10 more calories for each person!
The crocodile won again!
He won four weeks in a row!
Dad!
Give me all the plums in this basket!
I have money.
It's about time I get bored of bicycle jokes.
Find me another one.
It's amazing.
The crocodile won't get bored.
Let's ride it again!
Okay!
Everyone, please give me an applause!
It's been a long time since I rode a bicycle,
and I hope that I can keep it up.
Let's get back to our safety.
I won't.
It's all he got.
All right.
Hey, Riko.
Did you get any calls from the TV station?
No.
Why?
The amateur TV program was also in a bad situation.
It's about time to get some attention from the entertainment world.
I wonder if it's going to work out that well.
There it is!
Here it is!
Oh, it's that brother.
Who are you guys?
Oh, excuse me.
I'm the TV station's producer.
Actually, I'd like to ask you to appear on the show.
Of course, I'll prepare a lot of meat.
Oh!
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Then I'll ask you, the manager of the TV station.
Especially about the character.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Are you the worst?
Huh?
Why?
Well, if you get 90% of the attention, even the crocodile will get angry, Ryo-san.
Huh?
Damn it.
You're so nice.
But he's a precious money thief.
Now, I can't let him go.
I can't let him go.
How can he do that?
Sir, crocodile.
No, please don't.
Please...
This week's 1st place is the popular explosion crocodile.
My outfit is perfect!
All right.
It's a little rush, isn't it?
It's been a long time to see you.
It's been a long time.
Thank you for being so good to me!
You're such a liar, manager!
Nice shot!
Next time, please come on my show and play a guest, Ani-san!
Look at this!
She was on the stage!
I saw her!
She's so popular.
Hey, you!
Don't look!
I'm tired of you!
Here's your coffee.
If you come with a high school girl again...
I'm sorry!
Please say hi!
I'm going back right now.
Damn!
Remember this, monk.
You hung in there, huh?
You think you have me, I don't care what you say.
That's Handsome Monk!
It seems he's been on TV quite a lot lately.
But you know what?
I don't see any point
I think it's too early to get bored.
Please come to our new show!
I've decided on another cast.
No, I'll take care of it.
Hey, ah, ah, I cut it.
Damn it, I can't do this either.
Yes!
Ah, ah, that's right.
Ah, canceling the crocodile?
Are you tired of it?
Please don't say that.
Look, the schedule is completely blank.
There's no work from now on.
You don't have to be rich.
I'm going to quit my job as a manager today.
See you later.
Your show is boring the world.
Think about how you're going to make a living.
I'm sorry if I'm involving you anymore.
The End
Boss! You're late!
I think I've done enough.
What are you doing, man?
Thanks, crocodile.
Boss, what's this guy doing?
You're late again.
Ryozu. You've done well.
Thank you for helping.
You're all so helpful.
You made it out real quick.
He's a good boy, and he's been doing his first job for a while.
He's better than you.
That's right, Chief. Let's massage his shoulders.
The crocodile massaged his shoulders earlier.
It's a shame that he's not allowed to go to the festival.
Which station is Kameari?
I don't need you if you're here, Ryo.
Please do something about it.
Let go of me. I don't need you.
The only one who can get the money is the one who has no brain.
They're going to have a baseball match outside the store.
But I'm going to be a spy.
I'll beat you no matter what kind of cowardly hand you use.
You won't forget your promise.
Next time on the baseball competition
♪ It's said to be a woman who can't love. ♪
♪ There are so many things I want to do. ♪
♪ Look, I'm here. ♪
I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be free more than a bird
The lady's dream changes with the speed of a full moon
I'm sorry, wait for me
The bright future of the panorama
You know it, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me
Translated by Releska