When you watch TV,
make sure to keep your room bright and keep away from all eyes.
I look up at the fooled sun that floats in the sky,
The cityscape that never changes is strangely gentle
From the main street of Tongari Boshi
To Kaishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
Weaboo of Katsushika will forget the happiness
And realize that I am stupid
Kameyon's night is gentle
Wh... what is that?
Eh? What about you?
Let me out!
Isn't this a bento?
That's right.
I said I don't need it, but I made it.
Yes, honey.
Wow!
It's like a Japanese food life.
I didn't know it was still in this world.
Ryo, what about dinner?
I have decided that I will have a cup ramen for dinner.
Look, these are the three dishes I prepared for today's dinner.
Is cup ramen a smart dinner?
Of course.
It's been almost 30 years since cup ramen appeared as a revolutionary emergency food that produces a small amount of high energy.
Various menus that are in the middle of the world.
The progress of cup noodles in recent years, which have been able to reproduce the taste of the professional until the last minute, and the noodles that have been boiled.
It's exactly what the heavens gave.
It's a miracle.
It is even awarded the Nobel Prize.
I don't know if I'm going to eat such a noble food.
I see.
My wife made another one for Ryo.
You don't eat it, do you?
I'll eat both of them, so it's okay.
Well, ramen, yakisoba, fox udon.
Well, where should I start?
I wonder if I can eat it.
Before that, I'll pour the water.
Add the powder and the soup base.
Now I'm ready.
Aren't you going to eat?
You don't do your best for the rice lunch.
When the water boils, I'll put in the tea and eat it.
I'll tell you.
That's the water I'm boiling for my cup noodles.
There's enough water for the tea, right?
Sorry.
I'm only boiling water for a cup of ramen.
I'll consider the amount of evaporation.
455cc.
So there's no more.
Oh, really?
Then it's fine.
I'll add the powder and the soup base.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Before that, I'll add the ramen soup base.
Add the powder.
Now the soup base.
While waiting for this, I'll add the powder.
It's almost over.
I'm back.
It's hot.
This is so hot.
What are you doing?
I'm not going to do that!
You're going to do that!
That's great.
That's awesome!
Sorry.
Is this an ice cream bento too?
What kind of ice cream bento is this?
That face is a loner.
What a poor guy.
Don't make up your face.
Find your wife.
And get her some ice cream bento to make.
It's not my job.
As soon as I marry her,
It's not like I'll get a bento for free.
In other words, you're a fraud.
Congratulations!
Why don't you get married soon?
Oh no!
The hot water evaporated while I was drunk!
Maybe it's too little water.
Shut up!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Hey, don't just lie there, Terai.
Pour the hot water into the line inside.
Wait four minutes.
You don't need to wait four minutes.
Help!
Oh, it's your wife.
No, no!
Hurry up!
Wait, what's wrong? Tell me!
You're here!
I'm here!
I'm in my room!
What? You're a newcomer to a room for young women?
Ryo-san!
Chief!
So, are you a thief or a cop?
I'm a cockroach.
Ugh!
You idiot!
Don't come to the station for that!
I mean, there's no one else to ask for it.
The police's job is to protect the lives of the citizens, right?
That's not what the police do.
It's the security office and the police station.
That's what they do.
There's no one else to look after the health insurance.
Ryo-san, if you're going to look after him, I'll go.
Huh?
I'm feeling a little sick.
Are you okay?
I'm scared to go home.
Well, I'll go.
Thanks, Omari-san.
I'll be back soon.
I'll be waiting for you.
So, is the house near?
Yes, it's in that apartment.
Where is it?
It's about five centimeters black.
It went into the back of the stereo.
Is it here?
There's no shadow or shape.
That can't be true.
It must be clinging to something.
Look for it.
It's okay.
It won't come out anymore.
How can you say that?
What if it comes out again?
I wouldn't die if a cockroach came out.
And it's about three minutes.
No!
Get rid of it and come back!
I hate people who are half-hearted!
I don't care if you don't like it.
I'm not your husband or lover.
Please, I'll put in some coffee.
Don't go home.
Sit here.
I'll be right there.
I can give you a bit.
Good?
Huh, you can't give me some coffee.
There must be something wrong.
I'm thinking.
Oh, no.
Are you begging me to open the door?
Okay, fine.
I can't seem to open the door.
And you're worried about the sound of a cockroach.
Hey.
Don't tape me.
What about you, Mr. Sato?
Huh?
He's here!
Thank you very much, sir.
Good luck with your work.
Good luck with your work, you idiot!
It's so good, and so cold!
Hey, you!
Welcome back, Mr. Ryo!
Welcome back?
I didn't drink!
No, I'm really happy!
I have something to tell you!
Your wife is a very good cook and beautiful!
She's a very good cook and beautiful!
You're a fool to take someone's words!
You're a selfish man!
Do it yourself!
Pour it all the way in.
In three minutes...
Blur!
Blur...
I'm having a hard time.
I'm going out for a bit.
In three minutes, throw away the yaki-soba.
Okay, I'll throw it away.
Don't throw it away!
Don't forget! It's only three minutes!
Are you guys fighting?
You're so noisy that I can't sleep.
Do something, Mr. Omari.
I can't help it.
Hey, get away! Get away!
Ouch!
Stay still, Mr. Omari.
You bastard! I won't forgive you!
Where did he go?
What a suspicious guy.
To be continued
What are you doing there?
Hey, don't run away!
What's your name and address?
I'm Matsu-fuji.
My address is here.
What?
This is my house.
Why were you peeking in your own house?
I drank and got home late.
I was locked in the door chain, and I think my wife is asleep.
What should I do?
Wake up your wife.
If you don't want to, you can do it here.
That's a little...
I don't care. Do whatever you want.
Wait, Mr. Omari!
Please apologize to your wife.
Why do I have to apologize to your god?
Please!
If you're with me, will you forgive me?
Are you really that strict?
You worked all day and got home late.
You drank and got home late.
What's wrong with you?
You're right.
Hang in there.
What are you going to do if your god gets scared?
If you're a man, show him your manliness.
Alright.
Okay.
Where did you think you were going?
I mean the shop.
I brought you here because I became a drunken master.
It makes no sense to do things that are not your business.
Please do something about it, Mr. Omari.
No! It doesn't make any sense!
Oops!
You're drunk again!
Stop it!
You can drink as much as you want!
A man should be able to have a manly relationship!
Don't you dare talk to my family!
You!
I won't forgive you for being a woman!
Damn you!
Please don't resist!
My wife is a former world champion of women's wrestling!
What?
Idiot!
Say that to your wife!
What are you doing to my wife?
I'm praying that she will come home soon without drinking.
Ouch!
You're praying to my wife?
Drinking is bad for your health.
Drlessness is good for you.
You're still into this, right?
Red Corner 320 lbs former world champion of TOTOWC!
Blue Kong!
Now, let's see who we hit first.
I'm the killer of the second, Bullkong!
How many seconds do I have to get rid of him today?
What are you doing?
It's time to start the match.
Hey!
Wow! A series of moves that can be moved!
What do you think?
Mr. Miru Tabigara!
I don't feel any trouble since the Gen'eki era!
How did you become a wife of a woman like this?
I was a big fan!
How big of a fan are you?
That person said,
"If you marry me, I'll listen to anything you say!
I don't care if I die!"
Can you see it?
The special Death Valley Bomb!
It's a one-shot!
Hey!
Champion! Defend!
Hunter!
You!
I love you!
Why am I so...
This is mine.
This is my yakisoba.
Welcome home.
What are you doing?
Ryo-san, I'm sorry.
You can't hold the lid properly, so it will spill.
You made a big mistake.
You're such a bad person.
In addition, why are you throwing away the hot water now?
It's been three minutes already.
I talked to Sasaki-san and finally ...
Finally?
Do you know how I got away from the yakisoba that I just poured hot water with?
You will be cut off.
You will be devoured.
It was a painful and sad feeling.
Ryo-san, I'm sorry.
That's enough.
I was an idiot who trusted a monk.
I've met you like this.
Forgive me.
I can taste the taste of tears.
I'm really hungry.
This time, I'll be honest for the third time.
It's hot.
I'm not getting there.
What is this hose?
It stinks.
Sasaki!
Please don't stop it.
Why?
There are two idiots who commit suicide at night!
I was chased by my work and I came home.
Three months early, my beloved wife escaped.
I ran away three months earlier.
Run away, run away!
You're running away from your wife!
Ryo-san!
Since then, I've been jobless.
My life has been ruined.
I'm already at the limit of being a man.
It's hard to go home alone.
I finally got rid of it.
I feel like there's nothing good about living as it is.
So...
It's hard to live, but...
There must be something more fun than that.
Sasaki-san!
As long as I have this guy, I don't need a troublesome wife.
This time, I won't leave you no matter what happens.
Pnyu~
This is my wife.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
There are things to be proud of.
Reiko Ohara, Yuyuko Asano, and Norika Fujiwara.
They were popular in the neighborhood.
I like cleaning and washing the most.
I'm good at cooking.
I'm bright and honest.
I'm loved by everyone.
I'm a waste of a good wife.
Let's have hope, Sasaki-san.
Maybe your wife is regretting leaving the house somewhere now.
She might come back one day.
That's right.
No.
Your wife is a beautiful woman now.
She's living happily.
She must be drinking champagne while living a luxurious life.
Ryo-san!
If I were this beautiful, I would never marry her.
I would be forced to pay her taxes.
Sasaki-san's wife is not like that.
In the first place, this beautiful woman is not a rich girl.
She married you.
It's like an accident.
If you are an adult with a certain gender,
you should have noticed before you got married.
You should have given up because you thought it was a good dream.
That's Ryo-san's prejudice.
Does Ryo-san, who has never married,
know anything about a married couple?
I don't want to know.
The night guard is calling me.
My wife is not coming back.
I will die!
Don't worry about what Ryo-san said.
Please don't worry about what happened.
Please don't stop me.
I'm sorry, Sasaki-san, who didn't solve the problem.
Ryo-san, don't say anything that stimulates me.
I'll eat you now.
Damn it!
Goodbye!
Please stop!
If you're going to die, you have to die!
Sasaki-san!
Ryo-san, stop it!
Don't worry, Terai.
If you really want to die, you will die.
You can't come to a restaurant like this.
All right! Time's up!
Please don't die!
I'm serious!
Ryo-san...
My fox udon...
Damn it!
I won't forgive you!
I'll die!
Please stop!
Sasaki!
Please don't stop me!
Who's going to stop you?
I'll help you!
Help me!
Please stop!
No!
You're killing me!
Please stop!
No!
Stop it, you fox!
Idiot!
You want to die?
S-s-save me!
I can't swim!
I want to die!
Isn't that perfect?
I don't want to die!
Sasaki!
Please wait!
I'll save you!
Help me!
Help me, Ryota!
Ryota!
I can't help it.
Here, hurry up and get him!
Ryota!
Come on, hurry up and get him!
One by one!
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey!
Good morning.
Ah, sir. Good morning.
Oh, I thought it was Ryo-tsu and Terai-kun's shift until noon.
That's right. Terai-san called to say he wanted to switch shifts because he was cold.
I see. So, what's up with Ryo-tsu?
Senpai, well...
Hm?
He's such a pathetic guy.
He hasn't woken up since he started talking.
He must be tired.
That's impossible.
His face is all white.
He must be playing around with the others.
Ramen...
He's not married, so he's always playing around.
He can't be conscious of himself as a person.
Hey, Ryo-tsu!
Can you make me some yakisoba?
You idiot!
How long are you going to dream about others?
Wake up, Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu's Dream
♪ I want to beat you up with my feelings ♩
♪ For some reason, love is just cowardly ♩
♪ Don't hide all your strong wills ♩
♪ Don't hide ♩
Captain! Why am I playing golf?!
Don't worry, Ryo-tsu! The chief is Dai's coach!
You can't make mistakes and do well!
Even if you say that, I'm...
What are they?!
Next time, "The final battle! Golf-jou yaburi!"
I'm counting on you, Ryo-tsu!