Room"
When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away!
The
poor
guy
come to
me!
I'm
not here
but I'm
worried
about
you!
Look!
The
blue
sky
and
the
white
clouds
will
be
a
while!
I'm
unemployed
but
come to
me!
I'm
not here
but I'm
worried
about
you!
I'm
not here
worried
about
you!
I'm
not here
but
I'm
worried
about
you!
You
know
it, right?
You
know it,
don't
If
you
know,
then
come to
me!
Hmm...
There are fewer and fewer bathhouses in Tokyo.
That's right, if you say so.
I feel a little lonely.
Ryo-chan loves bathhouses.
I like them too.
That open-air bathhouse.
It's a commonplace and I like it.
If you say that to Nakagawa, I'll get into trouble.
Well, a bathhouse is a car park for adults and a playground for children.
In the past, there were many bathhouses in the same town.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
That's right, this is a picture from that time.
Eh? Senpai, that time?
Yeah, there were bathhouses all over our childhood.
There aren't many expensive buildings yet.
That's why there were many high-altitude chimney in the first floor.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
We're going to be overtaken by the first class.
You're going to hand over the third Nakashima's bathhouse, aren't you?
I can't throw away the first one.
Yay! I got on the first class!
Huh?
What?
The first class is the first class?
It can't be helped.
They haven't gone to school or work.
It's because they're in the dormitory.
Even so, they're going to the second class in the order of Matsu-no-yu, Take-no-yu, Ume-no-yu and Shochiku-ba.
It's really strange.
The first class is the owner of the first class.
He was called "the president" by the owner of the co-op.
What kind of president was he?
He was the one in charge of the crew.
Well, this is...
This is great.
Drink more "seiken-."
All right, I'm ready.
Well, the first is the high-altitude chimney.
Don't lose, Chinkichi!
Furukawa's "Seisui Eiho!"
Are you ready?
That's how it is!
T broth
Ohishimasen kachi!
Yay!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!!
That was a sąro!
Me too.
Kairou is so stiff, it's hurting my body.
You two, you have been late.
If you put situación in this way, will you no problem?
I see!
Me too!
Alright!
I don't care if you win or lose!
Okay! I won't lose!
The second round! Masao vs. Kankichi!
Ready!
Mach 15 speed!
Fire!
Awesome!
There was a problem with Chin-Chin's upskill.
The brakes didn't work because he couldn't see ahead.
You guys are in danger too, so stop.
No one will do it.
Ouch!
You guys again!
We'll ban you from getting out of the car if you do this again!
Hey!
I used to go to the battle every day.
I used to go in for 5 hours a day.
5 hours?
Yeah, I felt uncomfortable and looked like I was dirty.
It was just then.
I went to the Shinovazu's pond with Zenko.
Hm?
Are you sure?
Yeah,that's for sure!
Do you wanna fight me?
Of course!
Akira,Arya and Kazuhara will be fighting you.
Really?
What are you doing?
Are you joking?
Imagine if you were me.
All right!
Ah,I didn't even know what you were talking about!
Huh?
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
Yaaah!
Ahhh!
Ahh...
Y-yabai!
I'm so glad.
Ah!
Ah, um...
I'm sorry...
It's fine.
Huh?
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Ah, it's true!
I've never seen a painting this beautiful!
The painting is beautiful, but so is your sister...
Idiot!
I'm talking about impressions.
I like paintings like Monet, Manet, Goffo, and Cezanne.
I-Imitation? Go-Go-Cezanne?
A comedian?
Is she in Rock?
I don't know.
I know the rest, but...
Ah, um...
My sister...
Her name is Miki.
Miki Orihara.
I'm Kankichi.
I'm Chinkichi!
I'm Tompei!
Nice to meet you.
Y-Yes!
Um...
Can we sketch together?
Tell me about the painting!
Sure.
I don't care if you can tell me.
Let's draw together!
Yeah!
Yes!
Let's draw together!
I can't draw well!
Me neither!
How can you draw well like my sister?
I'm trying to draw well.
Really?
Yes.
For example...
Don't try to reflect the tree over there...
What do you think of that tree?
What do you feel about it?
It's Kankichi's painting!
Cool!
It's a bronze!
Yay!
Oh!
It's mine!
Yay!
Chinkichi!
You guys don't draw what you see,
but what you think of it.
I'll draw a picture of you.
From now on,
call me Kankichi Gahaku.
Hahaha!
Kya!
I'm glad I did what my sister said.
Yeah!
But, you know,
I haven't seen you lately,
but what's wrong?
Yeah...
Today's the best day!
Eh...
Ah...
Huh?
It's 5:00 today.
5:00?
Why?
I'm repainting the drawing on the bathroom.
The drawing on Mt. Fuji?
The pen is wet and the color will fade,
so I repaint it every year.
So I repaint it every year.
Huh?
Show me!
I'll give you some advice.
Kankichi Gahaku?
Ah...
You're late!
Bring it here quickly!
Huh?
Don't be so nervous!
The pen will dry out!
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Ah...
Well...
Don't show it to me!
It's in the way!
Get in!
...
Tch...
It's fine.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Huh?
Kankichi-kun!
Sis...
Why are you...
Miki, the brush!
Ah...
Yes.
Miki?
Dad?
I don't know!
"Hand and foot are examples of the tools of craftsmen."
For a craftsman, the tools are the same as his hands and feet.
Hurry up and find it!
"Hand and foot are examples of the tools of craftsmen."
Sis, I'll help you look for it, too.
Thank you!
Where's that eye ball-pad?
It's my father's!
It's a real craftsman's treasure!
"Food"
"Milk"
Oh, I found it!
This one, right?
Oh, that's it! I'm so glad I found it!
But it's weird to think you can't draw without this kind of thing.
That's true.
Don't you draw at the bathhouse?
What?
My father thinks my drawing is just for fun.
Rather than oil paintings that make rich people happy,
I think it's more important to make the guests at the bathhouse and the movie theater happy.
I'm proud of my current job.
That's why my drawing is...
That's not true!
Anyone can see your drawing!
Not yet.
That's why I want to study oil painting seriously.
I want to study in France.
France?
My father is absolutely against it,
but he won't let me live there if I do oil painting.
You don't have to listen to that stubborn old man!
Your sister is a very good painter, so go to France!
Thank you!
I'll be more brave if Kankichi says so.
With that, what happened?
Well, here's the story.
Huh?
Ah, it's about winter this year.
That year, she finally decided to go to France and told her father.
I'm taking the plane together again in the evening,
and I'm very grateful for everything.
Just like my father said,
I may not be able to live in the oil field for the rest of my life.
But I want to try my best.
Have a job.
My father told me that and I lived my life.
I thought so too.
What's the point of drawing a picture that doesn't make money?
Don't think you can eat oil fields.
I'm ready.
Do whatever you want.
Sorry!
What?
My sister is going to France tomorrow evening?
Really?
What about my sister?
She's going to help that old man in the fish pond.
Fish pond?
My sister!
Kankichi!
Jinkichi!
Tonpei!
You again!
I'm going to get in your way, so go home!
We have to say goodbye to my sister.
Ouch!
Kankichi!
We'll continue.
Damn it.
Father!
Damn it. I only have one day off today.
I have to run all day long. I can't do business.
I'll do it.
What?
Leave it to me.
You can do it?
I can do it.
You're really good at painting.
Besides, I've been helping you for a long time, so I can do it.
Yeah, we'll help you.
Let me do it, Father.
Father.
Do it yourself.
Father!
Thank you, Father.
Huh?
It's so big when you look at it up close.
It's overwhelming.
How many times bigger than a 100-carat canvas?
You have plenty of time to get lost.
You don't have time to get lost.
I'm gonna draw my own picture.
All right!
Please grind up more paint on the blue and green.
Okay!
It doesn't get stretched no matter how much I paint it.
It is completely different from the canvas.
The brush is dry too quickly, and it's completely different from the oil.
Hey, here it is.
Get off.
Get off my face.
I forgot about them.
Wake up, Kankichi.
Tonpei and Jinkichi, too.
It's too late. You have to go home.
Thank you for helping me.
No!
You're welcome.
I'll help you until the end.
But...
Please help me. I want to help you.
Okay.
But, please get permission from your family.
I'll bring you something to eat.
Okay!
Done!
What?
I did it!
It's a women's bath.
It's a men's bath next.
What?
I see.
There's still a men's bath.
What's a good man's bath picture?
What picture do you want to draw?
Mt. Fuji.
Me, too.
Me, too. Mt. Fuji.
Mt. Fuji.
Okay.
Mm!
Well done.
Do it.
I understand.
Good.
Shoo!
Good boy.
Yes.
I'm going now.
Shoo!
Good boy.
Eh? Red? I don't have any.
Eh? I'm in trouble. I need red.
I'll get it.
Yeah, leave it to us.
Thank you. Please.
Mister, red pen!
Red?
I'm trying, but I'm running out of red.
Where is the red pen?
Mister, where is the red pen?
Hey, bring me the two reds on the shelf.
And the empty can too.
I made the red.
I'm the only one who can make the same thing.
Not yet.
Now! Mix it quickly!
Okay.
The red pen...
Kankichi, hurry up.
What time is it now?
About 2:30.
We'll make it in time.
There's no one who comes at 3:00 anyway.
Old Man Ichibanbu!
I was in Matsunoye the other day.
So I'm in Umedoi today.
That old man gets really angry if he can't go to the bath on time.
You guys go to your sister.
I'll do something about Old Man Ichibanbu.
The
We're in Umedoi today, right?
Yes.
Get there just on time.
Yes, sir.
...We've run out of time.
Okay! Hit it and crack it!
...
Uwaaaaaah!
I can't feel my arm.
My legs are like a stick.
Hang in there, big sis!
Just a little more...
Ah...
It's done!
Complete!
I did it!
3 o'clock.
Oh, perfect.
Now, let's have a drink!
Oh, it's the red flag.
This is wonderful.
Huh?
Dad...
It's so bright.
Old man, look at the woman's face.
From Japan, the city of Mt. Fuji, to France.
This is how you feel, big sis.
Both are wonderful.
It's a good omen.
Dad, I...
Ah, it's time for the plane.
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
Let me go before I get there.
Ah, let go!
Sis, hurry!
Be careful with your health.
You're going to be late.
Go.
Dad!
Well then, I'm going.
Sis!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, sis!
Thanks, everyone!
Ha...
One year has passed since then.
I did it!
I found you, Ichiban!
You're Ichiban's old man!
But above that...
What?
The picture has changed!
I was a bit shocked.
There was only a little bit of red paint left under the painted picture.
I felt like my precious memories had disappeared.
I thought it was only natural.
I realized how important it was when it disappeared.
The painted picture of the centaur is wet and discolored, so it can be repainted once a year.
That is the fate of the painted picture.
Then this picture is valuable.
Well, yes.
At that time, I regretted why I didn't leave it in my memory even more.
I tasted it and that was the end of the video.
Every time I wore it, it felt like I Hanae this time because it was so cute.
I walked looking back at the light
I was drawn to the gacha
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black side of the Akedogai Tile
I was drawn to the black side of the Akedogai Tile
Everyone was a child at one time
But they all forget
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt in the eyes
Look up at that corner
I want to meet everyone
Let's go!
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
I did it! I picked up a small number on the street!
This must be a gift from God!
I thought so!
It's really a surprise camera!
Even the president has come with me!
Then, if I'm the president, won't I be deceived?
Next time, "Ryotsu Dokkiri Maruhi Report"
Please watch it!
There is a turtle there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!