When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and try to look away
It's after the rain that someone is calling
I walked looking back
My mom was holding my hand
I felt that strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black tile of the Akegogai
I tried to walk on the black tile of the Akegogai
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
The politician with a great face
And the blue lady above her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall there
Come, everyone
To our town
Thank you
The day of strike at Hita Town
Deadly by a미
The whole body is covered in blood.
He looks like a wild animal.
Is he really a police officer?
He's the chief of the police, Kanagawa Ryotsu.
He comes to our station for temporary work.
So the chief came to pick you up?
I met him at the east exit at 3:00, but he hasn't come yet.
Then he might be waiting at the upper exit.
There are two exits at the east exit.
Can I take a look?
What's wrong with you?
Watch out! Stop him!
Run up the stairs!
Stop him, Taro!
Midori!
Shut up!
The police stopped him!
Watch out! Run up the stairs!
Sir, could it be...
He's an outsider, a wild animal, and a fool.
Then he's Ryotsu!
Ouch!
What a heavy cow!
Are you okay?
Ryotsu, let me treat your wound.
It'll heal if you look at it.
Huh?
Who do you know my name?
Who?
The chief of the 5th exit of the lower house, Ban Isoroku.
I'm glad to see you. I'm Ryotsu. Nice to meet you.
I was a good man as soon as I got here.
If you're okay with the wound, I'll go now.
Huh? Isn't this the exit?
Yeah. I'll show you around, so follow me.
Okay.
It seems that the land around here is bright.
Yeah, because my house is close.
It used to be a playground.
By the way, what's that cow?
Tarou, who lives in a dry- béchic-terrain area.
He lives in a dry- béchic-terrain area?
He's usually peaceful.
No, I'm not talking about that.
It's Ryo-san!
It's been a while.
That's your father. He looks healthy.
Only his health is important.
Are you his acquaintance?
My friend from junior high school.
I heard that Dagashiya was a great success in the hit-and-match boom.
That's not true.
No problem. There are not many dagashi shops in Tokyo.
My neighbor stopped selling last year.
When I was in my early 30s, I used to come all the way from Tokyo to buy snacks in Nippori.
There were over 60 dagashi shops at that time. Now there are less than 10 of them.
I'm going to work hard and do business.
Cheer up, old man. I'll buy two bags of snacks.
I'll buy them all at the next book fair.
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
Is this the 5th and 8th store?
Yes. It's like a museum.
What are you doing?
Stop, Ryo-san. I asked for a towel.
For the dog?
Good job, Kanikichi.
You call that dog Kanikichi?
You're Kanikichi, too. Don't mind me. It's a coincidence.
Good job, everyone.
Are there more?
Yes. From the end. Reiko, Keiichi and Daijiro.
They're the same as the kameyari.
Do you like animals?
Yes. As I picked up stray dogs, they grew up.
What? You picked them all up?
It's like a zoo.
Chief, did you pick up the children?
Idiot. The children in the neighborhood came to play.
Then, Ryo-san will be in charge of feeding.
I knew it.
Who will feed us?
Don't worry about that.
Good evening, old man.
Tonight we'll have oden.
Please, if you like.
Mr. Tanaka, you're always so kind.
The children are always taking care of us.
With the Japanese sweets from the rabbit shop.
I'm sorry.
Hey, let's go home. Ichiro, Jiro.
Yes.
We always have a lot of things from the neighborhood.
I see.
Well, then, take care.
Bye-bye.
See you.
I used to be afraid of the court.
But now I'm not afraid of it.
In the court, the parents and children are safe.
Oh, no.
Mr. Gin and Mr. Segare.
The old lady from the shop in the middle.
Did you become Ueno's maid?
No. I'm here for a temporary job.
I see. I have to inform Mr. Gin immediately.
Hey, don't do unnecessary things.
I'll leave some for Monaka.
This is really delicious.
I'm not good at sweets.
I'm in trouble.
If you think about it, you have a lot of acquaintances.
In this area,
If you have a lot of acquaintances, you can't act poorly.
I was born the same way, and I have only acquaintances.
It feels like I'm working at home.
It's hard to do something.
Let's eat!
Why are they together?
It's better to have many meals.
That's not the problem.
Hey, that's mine.
Ryotsu, don't bully animals.
I took my snack!
Then you should share Kankichi's dog food.
I'm a human!
You're so stubborn.
There's no human who likes dog food!
This may be a bit awkward, but please bear with it.
It's fine if you can sleep in a good bed like this.
That's Kankichi's bed.
Sorry, but yours is this way.
You sleep in the same room as these guys?
Of course!
I'll wake you up when it's time to change.
What kind of station is this?
What?
Are you going to the station under Ueno to be hospitalized?
That's right.
Five of the six staff were hospitalized due to a cold.
They were hospitalized due to a cold.
The police officer who never gets cold,
who knows the details of the Ueno area,
found out that you're the only one who can be hospitalized.
He's the selected dispatch officer.
He's amazing!
He's meeting with the head of the Daigo Expressway at the east exit of Nippori Station at 3:00 today.
What? Now?
That's right.
They say that a cute child should be knocked down by the former.
Let him travel!
What?
What's going on?
Ryotsu, it's time.
It's still dark.
It's time for the birds to eat at 5:00 in the morning.
I think I know why the officers were hospitalized.
What are you making, Ryotsu?
This is a hut for them.
A hut?
Do you want to lock them up in a place like this?
This is normal in the world.
The chief is too sweet for animals.
They can't survive through the 21st century.
I'm going to take care of them.
What if the chief is hospitalized due to illness or injury?
What if he gets a stroke?
Nobody will take care of them.
That's...
On that day, I'm going to tell them
what it's like to be a normal pet.
I'm going to tell them what it's like to be a normal pet.
What about the way you've been walking?
I'm going to let the animals do it on their own.
That's why...
Look at the belly of the big bird.
It's a complete middle age.
You don't know what it's like to be a diabetes.
I will train them thoroughly from today.
The middle age, huh?
It's been a long time.
When I was a kid, I used to have a lot of competition here.
What?
Hey!
Don't be so weak for a dog.
Chief!
It's not easy.
You guys.
I can't talk to you.
I'm so weak.
I don't have much stamina.
When we patrol,
I'll take you with me for a walk.
Here's your meal.
From today on,
that's your bed.
Take your time.
I'll eat it.
How about I feed you a little more?
I've exercised today.
No!
They're just fat.
I'll have to go on a diet.
Liu Zifeng,
it's time for their discharge.
What time is it? How long are you going to sleep?
Wake up!
Hey, you guys!
Ryotsu!
Hey, Ryotsu!
What the...
Why are you here?
You should have slept in the futon!
To be continued
Well, how ridiculous they are.
Speed has decrease.
Get more energy!
Hey!
Hey! Where are you going?
Damn. They are so disaster.
*panting*
I'm back.
Hey, I've been waiting.
Do you know the escape route under the Yushima Tenshin?
Yeah, the one that stands at the intersection.
Yeah, sorry for coming back so late, but can you go return the gun to me?
You're like a servant to a child.
You two go with me. I'm going to lose weight.
*slurp*
There are many temples in Yanaka.
After all, the mountains of Ueno are not for the rich.
Oh, Ryo!
Huh?
Hey, Ichiro, Jiro!
I was going to go to the escape route, but I couldn't clear this game.
I'm just going to use it for a while, so wait at the escape route.
Yeah!
You're Ryo, huh?
I thought you were.
Are you that famous?
I'm a three-faced man walking.
I'm not a police officer.
There's no one I don't know here.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, I got it.
It's just a little.
I'll gain some weight again.
*slurp*
This place is close to Shinobazu Lake.
It's a good environment.
I used to come here often as a child.
I came here many times at Yushima Tenshin.
It's a long slope when you go to Hongo.
There's a making shop near here.
I think it was around the beginning of the Showa era.
It was a time when cars were scarce and people carried luggage in the eighth car.
I picked up a sake bottle at this place in Sakashita and climbed up this Kirido Shizaka at once.
The eighth car's luggage is heavy, so I'm trying to show off my strength so I don't stop on the way.
I'm not sure if you know, but where were you born?
It's a prefectural clan.
It's right next to Yoshihara Daimon.
Kanda Myojin is close, so it's good here.
Didn't you wear a miko-shi at the Kanda Festival?
I go to the Kanda Festival every time, but I feel like a man who always causes trouble.
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
Aren't you the police officer who always tries to catch me?
Yeah, that's a misunderstanding.
You sound like one.
I'm from Asakusa, so I only wear miko-shi when it's cold.
Well, I'm going home soon.
Wait a minute!
What?
What is it?
Can you deliver this pot to the Hongo Toadai-mae Exhibition Room?
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
I have a job to go to Hongo.
I'll go up with you.
What's the matter with you guys?
You still don't have enough training.
Huh?
Don't be so hard on yourself, Kankichi.
As expected of someone with the same name as me.
You're the one who's calling me the Toadai-mae of the Katsushika Office, aren't you?
I've heard a lot of rumors.
What kind of rumors?
A lot.
Like beating up the chief, or destroying the 20-car train.
That's what people say after all.
Are you home?
Huh?
He came to deliver the pot.
He's the toadai-mae of the Toadai-mae Exhibition Room.
Huh?
That famous...
The guy who set fire to the Exhibition Room.
You know him well.
No, I don't.
He was famous for destroying the main office.
That's the issue of the Katsushika Office.
He destroyed the main office...
Well, the main office.
We'll leave it at that.
Oh, right.
You seem to know a lot about the Chiri area.
It's like a garden.
When I was a kid, I used to fish in the Sanjiro Pond in the Toadai.
I used to run around the Yasuda Highland.
My employees are very fond of Chiri.
I have to learn it myself.
Do you know that there is an Exhibition Room on the slope of the Yayoi Crossroad?
Of course.
Go there to return the Sukiyaki pot.
We're going home anyway.
That's right.
The TV we borrowed from the southern Exhibition Room in Dangozaka, Sendagi...
Oh, that's right.
It's a little far, but it's a bicycle, so it's OK.
You mistook me for a delivery.
I'll give you four souvenirs.
All right, Machido.
You have to chill yourself and eat.
I know.
Thank you.
It's a little late, so I'm going to give them souvenirs.
You're going.
What can I do?
Maybe they're in here.
Drink this.
You'll feel better.
This is your first time at Lamune, isn't it?
I got it. I'll give you a drink.
When you're done, we'll leave.
You're late, Ryotsu.
We have to go to the meeting soon.
I can't help it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
The suspect is heading to the upper side of the road.
Damn it!
What? Why is there a cow?
What's with this sound?
It's a cow!
It's over here!
The identity card is here.
Yes.
The suspect is heading to the 5th exhaust of Kitaya.
That's your exhaust.
...
W-Wait, what should we do? What's the situation?
The culprit is asking for a helicopter for escape.
If he doesn't obey, he'll get the children injured.
This is bad. We should have returned the children to our house first.
What's with this fuss?
Senpai!
Ryo!
Why are you here?
The culprit who attacked the bank with a turtle is running away.
He's holding the children hostage in the exit.
What? Then Ichiro and Jiro are...
They're being taken hostage.
What's going on?
Are you ready?
We're ready. Just wait a little longer.
If we don't hurry, the kids won't know what's going on.
Ichiro! Jiro! Someone, save them!
Okay, I'll hurry.
They were waiting for me.
Huh?
Tabards?
Where?
This is terrible.
There's a monitor!
You can't run away.
This is where...
I didn't know there was such a place.
This is the area.
Take the car up to the exit.
Don't stop the engine.
No matter what, the host's life is the most important thing.
I can't let them escape like this.
Don't tell me you guys...
I got it.
Hey, stand up!
Who's there?!
What is it? A dog?
Don't make me laugh!
Oh no!
Are you alright, Ichiro, Jiro?
Ryo!
Don't let them escape!
Yes!
Oh no!
Hey!
Who's there?!
Taro, it's Nakagawa.
Thank you, Kankichi.
Hey.
1 hour later
It was a short time, but...
Thank you very much.
I had a lot of fun.
You guys should join us.
Senpai, it's about time.
Yeah.
Well then, excuse me.
How was your work in your hometown, senpai?
Yeah.
I've been going to many places now.
I'll try to go home now.
You can call me here.
Thanks, senpai.
Do you still think about my mother?
I'm aware of that.
I'm sure she'll be happy to get a son.
I wish I could have a wonderful son.
But, it's my fault.
Even if we are separated
Didn't it hurt a little more?
I'm sorry for that smelly animal.
Kankichi!
Take care! I'll come back again!
Senpai...
Let's go back! Kami-Ani is waiting for me!
Yes!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
We have the final say in the Katsushika-sha!
What?
You're going to battle at Ganryu-yama?
Interesting!
Let's take it!
Next time, "Kendo一直線"!
See you next time!
♪ Kameari by Kendo ♪
Thank you!
I'm saved!