Opening닝
Te, te TV wo miru toki wo
Hey, a wa karukku shitte hanarette mite ne
Nakakawa ni ukabu
Noru hi wo megakete
I kicked the pebble and it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I was working out
I laughed at the fact that I was just a child
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I'm just a child
The cityscape that doesn't change is strangely gentle
From the water tank of a pointed hat
The sun goes down to the sea
tomorrow
This is how it ends
I realized that I lost happiness
Because I'm a fool
Oh, there's something unusual
Is it a shield?
It's called a recorder now
I fell into the abyss before this
I used to play with this a lot
I imitated Charmela
When I was a kid, I played with a flute
You did too, didn't you?
I was a flute when I was a kid
A flute is a string
Back in the days, when you were a whiz
I had a gold-plated flute
I'm sorry
It's too old for us
I see
Why was Reiko learning that?
Even if you tell me why
The first piano I got was a flute
I was a fruit at first.
I was a special student in the middle school.
Why do you guys always have good quality things?
When it comes to elementary school, it's all about the Tatebue!
Even if you say that ...
Senpai, you have a lot of memories.
I'm so frustrated! I can't talk about Tatebue!
You won't cry, will you?
Oh? There's a meaning to it.
What?
It's true.
Maybe it's an initials of the owner.
I think so.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
I just remembered.
I once had an initials.
It's a Tatebue memory of Senpai.
Let me hear it.
I want to hear it too.
I think it was when I was in the fifth grade of elementary school.
I remember that.
I remember it.
A girl named Himeno has transferred to this class.
I am Yukiko Himeno.
Nice to meet you.
That girl is so cute.
She's an idol.
She came to me a few days later.
Um ...
Kankichi-kun ...
There's something I want to ask of you.
Oh, me?
"A beautiful girl in Class 1 is asking for Kankichi?"
What's going on?
What do you mean, "Kankichi is asking for me"?
That's...
What's wrong? Tell me.
No way...
Kankichi, please go out with me.
Oh, no.
Actually, it's about the flute.
Flute?
Yes, the one we use for music.
What's wrong with the flute?
A classmate of mine is exchanging his flute with mine.
What?
I noticed something was wrong, so I bought a new one.
I see.
So you're exchanging your flute for an indirect kiss.
I don't feel good.
I thought Kankichi would do something for me.
Himeno...
Okay, don't cry. I'll do something for you.
I'll do something.
Really?
Yes, leave it to me.
Listen, put my flute in Himeno's flute bag until the music starts.
Wait.
If you do this, you'll know who exchanged it.
I don't feel good.
That's too much.
The flute was exchanged for a good one.
Let's dig up the letter K.
He's exchanging it again.
Two or three months.
So that's why most of the class boys...
use the flute with the letter K on it.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You exchanged your flute with your own.
The evidence is the K mark on your flute.
Really?
It's a mark I left on my flute for Himeno's flute.
I'll beat you up!
Of course! I won't do it again.
Thank you, Kankichi.
So we solved the case safely.
I see.
That's good.
Good!
Hey!
Hey, is the stolen thing delivered?
Stolen thing?
Yes! It's Sonori-ko!
What? Is this Junpei's?
Yes! It says Junpei's J here.
It's definitely mine.
That's great.
Don't drop it again.
Yes! Thank you very much!
Well then.
Hey, Senpai, it's patrol time.
I have a lot to do even though I look like this.
I have to keep an eye on the social movements.
Ryo-chan, you're going to skip again?
Then I'll go instead.
Nagaya! I'm going after all!
Senpai!
I'm going after you, Ryo-chan.
I'm really in a hurry.
It's certainly getting old.
Hey!
Idiot!
You got caught, Kankichi!
What?
I'm not Kankichi!
You too?
I saw you in the newspaper this morning.
I was going to watch it again before I was taken away.
Me too.
No.
You got yelled at earlier and my body reacted.
That thrill is nostalgic now.
Yes, indeed.
Our classroom is here.
It's small.
Our desk has grown.
You've grown up.
What? 10 people in one class?
It's like a city.
We had about 50 people back in the day.
There were so many people,
that we couldn't find anyone in the next class who would eat.
You did it!
You always didn't have enough food,
so you became one of the seven mysteries of school!
Speaking of the seven mysteries,
it's the one where ghosts appear in the big mirror in the hallway.
The one where ghosts appear in the big mirror in the hallway.
But the real one was...
Kankichi.
You did it!
And the one where Beethoven's eyes move in the music room.
That was also Kankichi.
He was peeking from behind the wall.
He was usually playing with a ball and deceiving us.
The seven mysteries of school are like the ones we made!
Speaking of the music room,
there's also the one where the piano plays.
Huh?
Oh, I know!
Is this good enough?
It looks like there's really no one here.
Hey, it looks like someone's coming.
Okay.
Huh?
Stop it!
Tompei and Chinkichi!
So, the one who played the piano was...
Kankichi, didn't you?
So it was him?
No one would be scared of such a little freak.
Even ghosts.
Do you like this one?
First time, we went for a walk!
Amazing!
You are very talented, Himeno.
I love playing Piano.
It's my dream to be a pianist.
Himeno, are you ready?
I am ready!
Alright.
Grrr, okay.
Huh?
What's taking you so long?
I getغatome~
I getgotome~
Hey, Kankichi! You again!
Run!
Himeno!
Hey! Wait!
Himeno went to Europe to study piano right after graduating from elementary school.
What's he doing now?
You don't know?
Huh?
Himeno died in a car accident last year.
What?
He had a dream and became a pianist. He was trying his best.
I see. I didn't know that.
Kankichi...
Hey! I heard the piano!
You can't hear it?
I can hear it!
There's no one here!
No way...
I can hear it from here.
Let's go!
What's that? A bell?
It's automatic.
Oh...
Let's go.
Are we going to the music room?
That's the only place to play the piano.
I knew it.
Kankichi, open the door.
Open the door.
Me?
Donbei, you do it.
Why me?
Kankichi, open the door.
I don't know what to do.
Let's do it together.
Okay.
Let's go.
A student is playing the piano.
What?
Himeno!
I'm sorry!
What?
The piano...
I used it without permission.
What?
You?
Was it Himeno's daughter?
It's true. It's similar.
Her name is Megumi.
Maybe...
It's the three members of the Tonshin family, right?
Why do you know that?
I often heard from my mother.
Himeno told us about us?
Yes.
It's exactly what I imagined.
All three of them.
I used gold-colored pens and made a golden golden pen,
and a dehumidifier used alcohol lamps to grill and eat.
My mother said she had so much fun in school,
I probably wasn't good at this.
At the time,
I knew that my school would be detained,
so I decided to check the newspaper one by one.
When I entered the music room,
I bumped into the piano,
so I just...
So that's where we came by chance.
I feel like that's fate.
Megumi is good at piano, but is it a dream to be a pianist like me?
Yes! But I'm not sure if I can be like you.
You don't have confidence? You were playing so well.
Compared to you, I've been aiming for you all this time.
But you're no longer there.
I thought you played better while you were playing.
That's not true. I was the same age as you.
You?
What's wrong?
See? I filled in the time capsule.
Time capsule?
I was at the school when you graduated.
Oh, so you're in it too.
I'll make you the same age as Megumi.
I thought it was around here.
It was more than 20 years ago.
Hey, Ryozu.
Yes?
When I said I wasn't confident, you said you were the same age as your mother.
Yes.
Can you tell me about that time?
We were the same age when we graduated.
Are you going abroad?
Yes.
Are you sure? You can't understand Japanese if you go abroad.
You're going to eat with a knife and fork instead of chopsticks.
Are you worried about me?
Yes.
No, it's nothing.
It's a little sad to part with everyone at this school, but I've already decided.
I see. You're really good at playing the piano.
It's better to study abroad than in Japan.
Kankichi.
Do your best. I'm supporting you.
But I have a test before that.
You'll pass it for sure.
But good students come to take the test from all the schools.
If it's okay, I'll take it.
I guarantee it.
Thank you, Kankichi.
No, I can't play well.
I have only one week left until the test.
What's wrong?
You were playing so well until recently.
I heard it.
It's the first time I've ever seen Kankichi.
He's not even bad.
You're really good at playing.
Good luck.
Really.
Hey, Momo.
What are you talking about?
Why are you so serious?
We mean it, right?
I know you're going to try.
I didn't know.
The bat didn't come out smoothly, but I tried my best to hit it, and when I hit the shirimochi, the strength of my shoulders came out.
I think it was good to relax and swing the bat without getting tired.
Yes, this is it.
This is the second one.
There's a simpler way to do it without showing your face.
What is it?
If you do this,
Look!
Look, the strength of my shoulders came out.
Don't interrupt me!
Hey, Himeno!
This was a big failure.
Of course, Chuno!
Shut up! I thought it was a good idea at that time.
I tried a lot to make Himeno relax, but it didn't work out.
I can't do it.
Hehehe, Himeno. Don't make such a difficult face. Relax your shoulders.
I told you to stay away from me! I hate you, Kankichi!
Himeno! Please open the door! I can't go up alone!
Finally, he stopped listening to me.
I couldn't help but notice that he was in a bad mood.
I can't do this. I can't do this at all.
Hang in there. You can do it.
Himeno...
Yes.
What are you worried about, little girl?
Huh?
It's me! It's me!
It's me!
You don't know that I'm right in front of you?
No way.
Look at me.
Do you understand? I'm Beethoven.
I've been here all along, listening to your performance.
Again?
Don't worry. You have enough talent.
All you have to do is relax.
Relax?
I know you love playing the piano.
You used to play it more happily.
If you play it with fun and relaxation, you'll get good results.
Yes, Mr. Beethoven.
Relax your shoulders.
He's praised his exhibition.
Nice. You're doing fine.
So you've all been doing this to ease me, haven't you?
Thank you, Kankichi.
I did it!
"He told us he doesn't like the school."
"He said he will go to school anytime."
Congratulations, Mr. Himeno!
Congratulations!!
Congratulations!
You did it, Himeno!
That's it.
Mom, you didn't tell me that...
Hey, did you find it?
No.
I didn't.
Where did you bury it?
Kankichi!
Himeno.
Thank you, Beethoven.
What? You found out?
Even if I go abroad, I won't forget about you.
Because you are my Beethoven.
You'll do your best.
Yes.
Did you find it, Kankichi?
No, not at all.
Did you really bury it?
It's getting more and more suspicious.
It's dark and we can't go any further.
But...
What?
But the demolition will start tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
But if it gets dark like this, it'll be...
If I really wait, I won't be able to play for the rest of my life.
Megumi...
Tompei! Chinkichi!
Turn on all the lights in the school!
Oh, it's surprisingly bright.
We'll find it tonight.
It should be there.
I'll get it back!
Don't worry, Megumi.
We'll find it for sure.
Kankichi, the system will change!
It won't!
More importantly, don't you guys stop!
Found it!
This is it!
Did you find it?
No doubt!
Himeno's is...
Found it!
This is Mama's.
Try to open it.
There should be a 6th grade Mama like Megumi.
Yes!
Hey, we have one too!
What did you write?
I don't remember at all.
"I'm the future jet pilot?"
"I'm the future Prime Minister?"
And "B-Ball"?
Those are the ones who write stupid things!
What? Show us Kankichi's!
I'm not as childish as you guys!
I'm the captain of the Earth Defense Force!
You're the most childish!
There's still the mud ball.
That's right.
What about Himeno?
"I'm the future captain of the Earth Defense Force."
I'm not as childish as you guys.
That's right!
Do you remember me?
Here's a picture.
That's me.
I'm the future captain, Himeno Yukiko.
They keep having fun.
"Oh, Jin иメレも一緇だ。
What? Mama was the same as me, right?
Thank you, everyone. I've finally made up my mind.
I'll walk the path that Mama walked.
I love playing the piano too, Bono.
I see. You'll be happy too, right, Himeno?
Yeah.
Now, let's send them off, Megumi-chan.
Yes!
I'm so glad I came to this school today.
We're glad we could meet our old selves again.
The school called everyone.
They made us make our last memory.
We'll be out at 5:00 tomorrow.
We'll have it set.
Bye, everyone.
Yeah.
بعد
I want to be with you
I want to be loved
Just a little
The more everyone says
I feel like we're melting
I want to shoot you
For some reason, love is just cowardice
Don't hide all the strong feelings