When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and stay away
Like someone is calling
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
I'll return it to you!
What does it mean to return it without looking at it?
In the past, the manager's meeting story
There was no good woman at all
I'm fine!
Idiot!
I can't do that!
Listen
I don't want to see you
A bad woman may not appear again
I will refuse
I have no intention of marriage for the time being
Besides, marriage is love marriage
I have decided it in my heart
Do you think there are people who want to marry a man like you?
Of course
The manager doesn't know at all
Even if it looks like this, I'm popular
Are you popular?
Stop joking around.
You're dating a woman or something.
I've never heard of this before.
What are you saying?
I've finally calmed down recently.
About ten years ago, women were so noisy.
"Ryo-chan, you have to get married to die."
"I want to have a child like you."
Who are they?
Akemi of the Kinshicho.
Naomi of Shinkoiwa.
You're the older sister of a bar.
If you're a customer, you should say that to everyone.
I came with you.
Excuse me, sir.
May I?
What is it?
I have a customer.
Me?
Dad!
I missed you.
Dad...
Dad?
I'm not joking.
I don't know you.
Dad!
Don't stick to me.
I'm leaving.
Are you okay?
Ryo-chan, what are you doing to my child?
Poor thing.
What are you doing?
First 94's F-Cup.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let me go.
It hurts.
What a dirty thing.
You are dirty.
Let me go.
I won't let you go.
Let go of me.
You're just like Ryo-chan.
You said that he is a cheat.
That he is a coward.
He has two eyebrows.
And your name is Kankichiro, right?
What?
Kankichiro?
My mother said that my name comes from my father.
Kankichi?
Kankichiro?
He may be Ryo's son.
Be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be.
Kankichiro.
Would you like to hear the details?
Can you tell me something?
My mom told me that my dad died when he was a baby.
But my mom died in a car accident a week ago.
Before my mom died, she took my hand and said,
"I have to tell you something.
Actually, my dad is still alive."
Was that your father?
"Your dad is a local named Kan-Kichi Ryotsu,
who ran the Kameyari Park Exhibition."
But my mom fell in love with him and gave birth to you.
She said, "He doesn't know anything about you,
so you shouldn't bother him."
So I didn't want to come to the beginning.
But I wanted to see your dad's face at least once.
So...
So that's why you came to see him.
Where do you live now?
Is it your relative's house or somewhere else?
I don't have any relatives.
I live alone.
You live alone?
Yes.
But I'm not lonely.
I know that my dad is there even if we live apart.
I don't agree.
Shut up.
Kan-Kichiro,
your mother's name is Akemi, right?
Or Naomi?
Naomi.
Now it's decided.
What do you mean?
Kan-Kichiro is your son.
No way!
It's not like that.
Ten years ago,
you said, "I can die if I marry you."
Or "I want to have your baby."
That's what you said.
No, that's a lie.
Don't talk nonsense.
Listen, Ryotsu.
Now that you know who your parents are,
you can't leave your child alone.
From now on,
you're going to raise Kan-Kichiro.
You're kidding.
I don't want to.
Now, Kan-Kichiro,
you're going to live with your father.
Really?
Yes.
Dad!
You little brat!
Senpai, don't do that!
Dad!
You're so mean.
You're so naive.
Dad!
I'm going to go!
I'm going to get you!
Dad is dead!
Dad!
-I'm not you kid! -I see.
I'm very angry, too!
-Are you not going to go? -No, I won't.
Kan-Kichi,
maybe you should understand.
Mom.
You're amazing.
You're so really cute!
Miguel is a wicked, evil man!
Please cooperate with us!
Don't make me a criminal!
Get out of my way!
Damn you!
Dad...
It's okay, Kankichiro.
I'll help you.
I can't get out of here!
What?
You're not good at pachinko!
Why are you here?
Reiko said she would be here.
Reiko, stop it.
What?
Get out of my way!
I don't want to.
It's my turn.
You think a little kid can play pachinko?
If you're going to stop me, I have to think about it.
What?
I got it.
I'll stop you for a night, so change!
It's 6 o'clock.
Let's go home, everyone.
Everyone.
I didn't think you'd come out like that.
I'm sorry.
Don't forget that it's all thanks to me, Dad.
Stop calling me Dad.
Call me Ryo.
Okay, Dad.
So don't call me Dad.
Ryo!
Maria...
Ryo...
You made me a criminal while I'm still alive!
Maria...
I'm sorry.
Ryo's evil...
Stop it, Maria.
You're not a good mom.
Maria, are you Ryo's girlfriend?
Then what?
So will you be my mom in the future?
Mom?
Mom...
What a pleasant sound.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Ryo's wife is Ryo's wife.
Ryo, who's your daughter?
In that case, my child is the same.
What's your name?
Kanchiro!
Mr. Kanchiro?
I'll be your mother from today!
Really?
I'm so happy to have such a beautiful mother.
I'm so happy too.
We're going to make it work, right?
Yes.
This is because Ryo has a secret word.
I'm sorry.
Wow! It's amazing!
Then, let's eat!
Let's eat!
Kankichiro, is my dish delicious?
Why are you pushing Maria to eat?
Because we are family from today.
Right?
Father, you should eat with us.
Father, let's go somewhere together tomorrow.
That's right.
Let's tell your father about Asakusa.
Kankichiro, let's go somewhere together.
What are you talking about?
I can't go.
And stop calling me father.
Kankichiro, have you been to Asakusa?
There is a amusement park called Hanayashiki.
Let's take father there.
Yes.
I said I can't go.
The roller coaster over there is very scary.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you, Kankichiro.
It's this time of the year.
Let's show your children's faces at your parents' house.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to go.
Wow.
The lantern is big.
Right?
Father, hurry up.
So, stop calling me father.
Don't pull me.
Father, let's buy this.
Let's buy this.
So, don't call me father.
Hurry up.
Don't pull me.
Don't let me fall.
Wow.
I don't want to go.
Father.
I'm persistent.
I don't want to go.
Try it.
Great.
I see.
Next, next.
Next.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yes.
I don't want to.
First of all, I can't ride a bike.
What? You can't even ride a bike?
You're so generous!
I'll make sure I can ride it.
Really?
Yes. But my teaching is very strict.
Ryo, you can take as much as you want.
Maria, who the hell are you?
You'll know when you take a bath with me.
Maria, Kandichiro wants to take a bath with you tonight.
Sure!
Hey!
Kandichiro, how's the water temperature?
It's just right.
My dear daughter,
I'll give you a share if you don't want to go to bed.
I don't want to go to bed at night.
Dad is...
You can do anything. You know I'm going to fall in love with you, right?
Alright! This should do it.
Wow! It's like a new product!
Then let's do some special training.
Listen. The pedals are fine, so balance with the steering wheel.
Don't let it fall and run all the way down.
No way!
Don't be like that! Normally, you would hold your back in a park and ride more and more.
Don't be so cheeky!
What you need to be able to ride a bike is balance and courage!
That's it!
I knew it!
Do it!
Do it again!
I did it!
Now! Burn the pedals!
Y-Yes!
I did it!
Are you okay?
Dad, look! I did it!
Yeah.
Here.
Well, let's go home.
Yeah, let's go.
Yeah.
It's going to take a while.
We're all hungry!
Yeah.
How much were you tired?
Ryo-sama.
Kids are cute, aren't they?
Mm?
Huh?
It might not be so bad to have a child.
I'm just kidding. Good night.
No. You do it like this.
Oh, I see. Like this.
Yeah.
Ryo-chan, you're a pretty good father, aren't you?
Yes.
I guess so.
Hey!
Isn't this a request for search?
What's wrong with this?
He was lying.
Your parents will be coming soon.
I've already fought with Ryo-sama.
What should I tell Ryo-sama?
I've brought Hayato's parents.
What do you think about this trip?
Thank you for helping me.
No, that's...
Hold on tight.
Hayato!
Hey, Hayato! You're worrying me!
Hayato?
No, I'm not Hayato!
Hey, don't lie to me anymore!
No, no, no, no!
Huh?
What are you doing?
What?
Oh!
Ryo-sama, this isn't Kankichiro.
You...
Huh?
What happened?
Y-Yes?
We were in trouble.
The other day, we went to a restaurant that we wanted to go to.
They said Yasuraoka-san would come at 3.
But we're not there yet.
We might not be able to get there by 3.
I'll be right back.
Mom!
I'm making a mess!
I can't let go of your hand!
Look at me, Hayato!
See?
It feels better now, right?
Did you hit me?
It doesn't hurt!
I can't help you, Kasen-chan!
It's not my fault!
You're an older brother.
You need to take care of her properly, right?
You want a bicycle?
Everyone has friends!
The only one who doesn't have a bicycle is me!
I'll buy it soon.
It's in the way of work.
Go ahead.
Didn't you say that the other day?
Hey, Mom, buy me a bicycle!
I don't have time for that.
I'm going to be patient.
I'll fix it.
It's useless!
You're so stubborn.
If you can't do it, you can't do it.
What?
You always make me do all the housework!
It's boring!
You can buy me a bicycle!
Hey!
How dare you talk to your parents!
I'll beat you up, you bastards!
You!
Dad and Mom,
I hate you!
You're so annoying!
Hayato!
Get out of here!
I'm so busy that I don't have time to think about her feelings.
I see.
But why did you call Ryotsu your father again?
I'm glad I came home, but I have nowhere to go.
Listen,
I'm not just going to beat you up.
You're not going to beat me up.
You're going to have to calculate the wind direction and put it on the current.
Hmm...
The wind from the north and the west...
I saw Ryo playing with the children.
You're lying!
Did you find out?
My dad is just like Ryo.
I see.
Dad,
I'm sorry for shouting at you.
Hayato.
Let's go home, Hayato.
No!
I'm going to live with Ryo!
Hayato!
If I go home, I'll be alone again!
Ryo will go to the amusement park with me,
and he'll teach me how to ride a bicycle!
Hey, Ryo.
Please put me in your room.
Let's live happily with Maria again!
Don't be so nosy!
Who lives with you?
Ryo...
I hate liars and bald people!
Ryo, I'm sorry!
I won't lie to you anymore!
Shut up!
Ryo...
I don't want to see your face ever again!
Go home!
Ryo...
Thank you for taking care of me.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well, take care, Hayato.
Come again sometime.
Come anytime.
Don't lie to me anymore, Kankichiro.
Well, let's go, Hayato.
Kankichiro!
Take the bicycle to the front.
What?
Are you sure?
If you leave it here, it'll be in the way.
This is the full order I made.
You'll be fine.
Take care of yourself.
Don't lie to me!
Ryo!
I'll make you ride a bicycle like Ryo!
♪ Awaken, clock, throw it away, little finger, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ I'll draw my eyebrows and I'll go to the station, ah, ah ♪
♪ Every train goes, a single person sleeps on Dad's back ♪
♪ Safety, good law and good Nein, even a quack ♪
♪ The racquet is down to one hand ♪
♪ The beef bowl is a stew ♪
♪ The remaining work is annoying ♪
♪ Annoy and unpleasant, clean up, too ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ If you take a hot shower ♪
♪ Get well with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ Monday ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ There is Kameari ♪
♪ There must be Kameari ♪
♪ Come to our town ♪
Thank you!