Summer Has Come
Ah, the summer has come again, this year
the summer has come, this year
it has come, it has come
with mah, I have come to Okinawa
after drinking, it is the night sky
The wind blows south
A big chest, a small chest
A guy with a big chest
A big chest
Ah, this year too
The month has come
It's come, it's come, it's come, it's come, it's come
Ah, this year too
The month has come
It's come, it's come, it's come, it's come, it's come
A big wave, a small wave
A guy with a big chest
The wind blows south
A big butt, a small butt
A guy with a big chest
Ah, this year too
The wind blows south
This year too
Episode 1: The Big Bang
The Big Bang: The Big Bang
This time, there are traffic accidents in the city of Tonai, especially in our district.
So, next week, a traffic safety guidance training session will be held in this district.
On that day, the students of this training center will participate as instructors,
so I want to give the students an idea of a training that is easy to understand…
There are too many accidents, Ryotsu.
That's right.
Like the one where you break the speed on a bicycle.
I don't like it.
Or the one where you ignore the traffic lights because you're on a bicycle.
I don't like it either.
Or the one where you get into a house and destroy the shop.
You're so stupid.
Or the one who makes plastic models and doesn't listen to people.
That's ridiculous.
You idiot!
It's about you!
I'm listening!
I'm making plastic models for mental health!
Don't mess with me!
Do you think that's a Helix?
It's just like tea!
Don't make plastic models and tea together!
What will happen to the traffic safety?
I don't know.
Anyway, think of a plan for a traffic accident before the training session!
I'm not kidding.
I have a good idea for a traffic accident.
It's simple.
You all have to get in the car.
I'm busy making plastic models.
Damn it.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Yes.
Do you need anything?
Is Ryotsu here?
Wow, it's you!
Long time no see.
Is he your junior?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Honda from the Traffic Traffic Team.
Actually, I'm going to join the same group as him.
So, I came to say hello.
Wow, it looks delicious.
I baked this chocolate cake.
Look at this.
Isn't Surara's face cute?
Surara?
She's the main character in an anime.
She's the girl from the park.
She's quite popular now.
I heard that.
She's a good actress, too.
She's cute.
Stop it.
I mean...
Damn it!
I'm so sorry about this!
Stop!
Stop, you idiot!
Don't!
Stop!
K creditor!
I can't believe it's a modified motorcycle!
Get it!
It's time!
Someone stop the motorcycle!
Honda!
Hey, you came here by motorcycle today, right?
Yes. I'm always on the same bike.
Okay, Honda, you go!
I'm scared. I'm a little...
Don't worry. Get on the motorcycle!
Why?
I can't do it without you.
You can't do it without Honda!
No! I can't!
Stop it!
Get on the motorcycle!
Stop it, Ryo!
I feel sorry for Honda.
You can't get on the motorcycle!
I knew it!
You can do it!
Okay, I'm going to get on the motorcycle today!
What's wrong with him?
I'm the great Honda!
It's great. The motorcycle technique is amazing.
Are you ready, Mr. Ryotsu?
Yes, go ahead!
What's wrong with him?
He looks like someone else.
Wait!
Hey!
I can't see anything.
What was that?
It looked like a white horse.
A capulet of observer silver.
Exosong that handler the soul.
His heart is always pressing out.
I'll push you to your loser hole!
Come on, we've got it!
Huh?
This is terrible!
Do you think you'll get away from this, stinking raccoons!
Uwaaahhh!
Uwaahhh!
Huh!?
What the heck is that?
What happened to you?
Are you two late?
Mr. Honda took out the whole scene.
I'm so cool!
W-what is this?
I-I can't believe Mr. Honda has...
Yes, that's right!
He's a former hound of the Honda gang.
He's a traffic patrol officer now.
But when he rides a motorcycle, his personality changes.
He's a man who's feared as a double-decker devil who cries a lot in the countryside.
Double-decker...
Devil?
The engine is getting warmer.
You two, let's go for another run!
Yeah! Let's go!
Double-decker devil...
No way...
What's going on?
Wasn't the traffic light red just now?
You know what?
If you can't find it, it's not a violation.
If you can't find it...
I found it!
The traffic light is on in front of Honda.
It's a fake one.
Hey, run, baby!
Can't you just stop for a moment?
I have to stop! I have to stop!
What are you going to do?
I'll shoot you!
Here's your license!
What are you doing?
I'm sure you don't mind me ignoring the signal.
I do.
They've come this far?
Move the car in a hurry!
But, the engine...
What? Is it my fault?
No...
There's something wrong with you!
Move the car!
No way!
He destroyed 3 bikes, one passenger and caused a big traffic jam.
What kind of personality is this?
I'm sorry.
It's a big deal.
Well, well, well, Chief.
Honda is reflecting on itself and today was a big day.
You destroyed Honda, didn't you?
No, not at all.
I just wanted to take it.
I think Ryotsu-senpai told you to go.
I don't like it, Honda.
When did I do that?
Well, you're the one who died.
Well, well, well.
I don't care!
Ryotsu!
I'll give you 100 books of traffic safety books!
I'm sorry.
Destroy all of them before the meeting!
It's complete.
With 1750 horsepower, two-speed, three-speed, and a low-break engine,
it was a masterpiece produced by Germany,
Junkers Jumo 2131.
The name is Tank 152.
Ryo, are you studying traffic safety?
If you don't study, you'll get in trouble again.
You don't inform me!
And you're not the one playing with that doll!
I'm not!
It was the chief's request.
I'll take it to tomorrow's meeting.
I'm going to hit a toy like Ryo that looks exactly like her and do traffic accidents.
A-a toy that looks exactly like me?
The one that looks exactly like me?
Stupid!
Don't let him do that!
That wretched chief is really trying something!
He's turning his grudge into a puppet!
Wretched who?
Wretched Chief, no.
It's Джirta's fault that he wanted to eat it.
He seems healthy and that's good.
Tomorrow's lecture is to read a hundred of theaszle+scripts, right?
Th-that's right.
He'll come tomorrow for sure.
Byouzu.
Of course. I'm looking forward to tomorrow. I'll sleep tonight.
I'm going to ask you to do a lot of things.
What's with that funny laugh?
Are you still here? I hope you didn't run away.
I'm not going to run away.
I'll be there.
I've been complaining for days.
But the chief can't go against me.
It's about him.
He's been walking around in a daze even after I've been late.
Maybe he skipped.
While I was saying hello, he was smiling at me.
No way.
I don't like the way he is.
Why are you so serious?
Sorry I'm late, chief!
What are you doing, Ryotsu?
What time do you think it is?
No, it's a water...
It's not my fault that the alarm suddenly stopped.
And the bike is punctured, and the bus never comes.
I ran all the way here by myself.
It's true!
You idiot!
Don't blame it on people!
Chief, the people are watching.
I see, it can't be helped.
The alarm broke and the bus was delayed.
You've studied the traffic law, haven't you, Ryotsu?
Of course!
From head to toe, the traffic is safe.
I'm getting it, I'm getting it.
Don't mess with me!
Chief, look at the people.
Well, it's a good idea to tell everyone about the difficult traffic rules by gags.
Well, you have your role.
You're up to something, Chief.
This is the first time I've seen you.
I'll help you.
It's scary.
It's going to be a week of traffic safety.
Will it be okay?
We work every day to protect the people of Kubin from traffic accidents and crimes.
However, the traffic safety is...
Did you fail the strategy that you thought would be over if you were late?
Shall we start the next strategy?
Hey, Honda!
Can you hear me?
Huh?
I can't do that.
Besides, I'm on patrol, so...
I'm a little lost.
What I'm saying is dangerous!
Okay, I'm going.
All right, all right.
I can't help it.
What?
Uh, hold on, you two!
Wait for it, dear!
transp illegally
I don't know who you're talking to.
But it's not a karaoke, grandpa.
I didn't think you'd learn that.
What do you want?
Wh-what do you want?
Get in line, girls.
I'll give you a break.
Hehe!
Now what?
The End
Hello, kids.
You're all small, so it's hard to see from the driver's point of view.
So be careful.
Yes, sir!
Chief, you're so angry that you're going to make fun of me?
When crossing the Odan River, raise your hands and cross them.
Yes, sir!
Kaki-chan, you're in danger!
As you can see, cars don't know when to jump out.
So be careful.
You bastard!
Next is a bicycle accident that happens often among elementary school students.
A bicycle accident is often caused by a truck.
Let's try to reproduce that scene.
I want to see it!
Damn it.
You idiot!
Why are you so sad that I have to dress like this?
Hey, don't call me "I" when you're an elementary school student.
Kankichi-kun!
Oh, I'm sorry.
All right, all right.
In the case of the accident,
please be especially careful of large trucks.
At such crossroads, when a large truck turns,
this boy and this boy will be hit by the inner wheel.
This boy and this boy will be hit by the inner wheel.
I have been hit with a large truck before.
Please take a look nicely.
Chief!
It is not a chief to hit otherwise.
The driver of the large truck.
laptops?
You are an elementary school student who plays hard!
It's all right, everyone.
Please pay attention to this one.
Then I will play it.
Car accidents occur when a car turns,
and the rear tire bends to the inside.
and the one that comes out from the other side,
in this case, I will definitely pull that boy out.
Go!
Damn it! I can't stand being stuck in the chief's trap!
Look! Here comes the Nailin-san, and the boy...
Ouch!
-Get out! -I don't know!
He dodged it on purpose, didn't he?
At this rate, my position...
-Return! -You two!
You're so tough!
Well, that was a good example of how to escape like this.
But I thought I'd be able to escape every time.
Next! Next is the main event.
Stay here, Ryotsu.
I won't let you get away this time.
This is the end of your play.
I'll escape as many times as you want!
I won't let you do as the chief wants!
Here I go!
When you're running parallel to the truck like this,
you need to be careful!
Hey!
Don't run faster than the truck!
I'm trying to survive the traffic war!
-You're going to die! -You're going to die!
You're going to die!
Like this,
you can't expect the truck to come and get close to you.
Everyone, be careful!
-You're going to die! -You're going to die!
Damn it!
The truck jumped, and it was spinning,
and it came and got close to me!
Damn it!
It's like a child's fight.
I don't think it's a very safe negotiation.
You don't know what's going to happen.
You'll survive the traffic war by following the rules!
You don't know what's going to happen?
You're going to die.
I'll let you taste the meaning of that word, chief!
Next is an accident of a 50cc motorcycle that often happens to women.
It's a 50cc scooter, but it's quite fast,
so please be careful how you ride it.
Thank you for waiting.
-Huh? -Huh?
Chief, please show us the safety standards.
I got it.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Now, get in.
Get in.
You're planning something, aren't you?
First, you'll be riding with the stand on.
Of course, don't forget to wear a helmet.
And before you start the engine, make sure you check the surroundings...
What?
I started the engine on my own.
I can't even brake or handle the handle.
Everyone, this is a bad example of a scooter.
This scooter is modified to be able to control this Radiconder.
Please stop it!
What's wrong with this scooter?
Now, Honda!
Get in!
Roger!
Hey!
I'm a safe rider today, too!
What?
What's going on here?
Check the way!
Ryo, Ryo!
This is your fault.
No!
Hey, hey...
Please don't do this kind of driving.
So scary!
Nobody's been listening.
We're driving this Honda...
You idiot!
Honda, get your safety gear back, please!
Now, let's test the dangerous car with this ugly doll.
Damn it, chief.
You're going to make fun of me, aren't you?
This is awesome!
This is amazing!
As you can see, even though it's only 20 kilometers away,
it's still pretty damaged.
Now, let's speed up and see how much longer it can withstand.
Oh, my poor Ryo-chan doll.
It's like a real me is being tortured.
Mr. Ryo,
What?
Can you just keep quiet?
No, Ryo Tsukankichi is not a man who will be ashamed of his silence.
Next, let's test it at 60 kilometers per hour.
Let's see how much longer it can withstand.
Well, will that doll be able to withstand?
It's a doll, but I can feel it a little.
I don't mind.
Take this.
Wait a minute!
Hey, the motorcycle is coming from the sky!
You don't know what's going to happen.
It's a traffic war, chief.
Damn you!
You're going to get in the way of the meeting.
Go!
Nakagawa!
Yes, sir.
Go!
What are you doing?
Can't you catch up?
No, I can't.
If I keep going like this, the motorcycle will be more advantageous.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and go!
No, I can't.
The road is covered with oil.
I can't go forward or turn.
What?
Look at this.
It's scary to be in a traffic war.
Suddenly, there is oil on the road.
Damn you, Ryo-tsu!
All right, I'll put on my armor at once.
Are you sure, Mr. Ryo-tsu?
Why are you so scared?
If you're going to do it, do it thoroughly.
Okay, I'll do it.
Let's dance!
It's a double lock!
Let's do it!
OK!
It's a double lock!
What are they doing?
Mr. Ryo!
What's wrong with you?
I can't see anything.
Go!
It's cool!
It's effecting!
All right!
It's a double lock!
Go!
Fantastic!
You see!
It fits you
this is the basics of this world
Not this world!!!
Noooooooooo!
Come here!
The meeting isn't over yet!
What the hell are you doing!
Please stop, Yamcha!
Everyone
What's this?
Everyone, thank you for your hard work in this long session.
Now, we'll do the final demonstration.
The two policemen are ready to die, and will be doing a car crash test.
Please don't imitate us.
Bye.
Do it, Nakano!
Get in the car and go all out!
Are you sure?
Carver, do it!
Manager!
Help me!
Manager, I'm sorry!
Stop it!
We're not dummy dolls!
We did it!
Tomorrow, we're having a party at Nakagawa's house!
It's the birthday party of the prince of the Hondara Kingdom!
It's about Nakagawa's house!
We'll have a feast like a feast in the mountains!
Alright!
Let's start today!
Let's make him hungry without eating anything from now!
Next time, we'll have Nakagawa's house meeting!
Next Episode
Sakンド
Kaldare
♪ Let's smile anytime ♪
♪ Even if there's something awful happened ♪
♪ Please smile cutely ♪
Smile to me
You can go out with nothing on your face
Hey, smile to me
You're not bad
With the same attitude as before
Smile to me
The girl who made a serious effort is not beautiful
So you should smile right away
If you're not a child
Smile to me