ild" "W
ild" I'm
watching the sunset floating on the river If I
kick the love stone, I can fly to the shoes
I wonder if I'll go to the gym where I was saving money
I was laughed at as I was a
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi
The sunset falls to the Kaishakuten
Tomorrow is already over
I lost my happiness again because of the Katsushika Shiba
I realized that I was stupid
So
Run,
Father!
I'm full!
Yes, I'm home.
Here you are.
Honda Hayato
I don't need it.
I have you!
Yes, go!
Honda!
Go!
Yes, go!
Yes.
It was all right.
You can forget about Yoko
Yoko
Why?
Don't be so nervous.
If you're a man, you should forget about the woman who was dumped.
Yes!
Honda Hayato
Forget about it!
OK!
Boss.
.
Well...
It's 13,000 yen, but thanks to Mr. Honda who took out Mr. Ryo's past years of experience,
we'll accept 10,000 yen each.
I see. Then I beg your pardon!
W-wait,
are there more times where you let me down than my seniors do?
Well, yeah.
I can't take it anymore...
I don't have the confidence to live as a human being.
Look at him, he's talking nonsense.
I'm sorry, Ryo.
Don't be sad.
My number of times I've been in trouble is the number of times I've been in the police.
If you count the number of times I've been in trouble since I was a kid, it's more than that.
You're still a kid.
-Really? -Yeah.
That's great.
I'm getting more and more brave.
Yeah?
Okay, let's go one more time.
Yes!
Let's go to Tokoton today!
Tokoton!
Hey, you came on board, didn't you?
Look!
Isn't that Mr. Honda?
He's amazing!
He's saying that he's working so hard.
Well...
I guess it's better to comfort him.
Shut up!
I've been drinking three cups of beer since that day.
Besides, I was accompanied by the chief yesterday and he said a lot of bad things about me.
Why don't you learn from Mr. Honda?
He's a good friend of mine,
so he's working so hard for me.
How naive.
Huh?
When Honda is on fire, it's the time to fall in love.
He's quick to be depressed, but he'll recover faster.
Then...
Yeah, he's definitely in love.
"I'm in love with you."
I'm in love with him.
He hurts me!
Yeah, you're in love!
I'm going to make you come to my home!
My feelings for you!
Your feelings for me?
I love you!
Stop!
I can't!
My heart hurts!
Oh, my knees!
I'll make you come today!
With me!
The next day
What the hell is this?
Run away!
I thought I could run away, but I've done too much!
Honza-senpai!
Hey, Kokoro!
We've received a message from the rescue team!
Oh, I see.
I'll leave the rest to you!
Yes!
Damn that bastard!
He did it so hard!
I'll write it in the newspaper!
Did something happen?
No, nothing. I'm sorry!
You'd better be investigated!
It's more scary than a bird's nest!
So, what did you say?
What's the matter, Senpai?
You?
Are we in love again?
Daiya, darling!
Good boy.
You are scared to confess like that.
I'm afraid that your job will be more difficult for you.
Truth be told, I'm scared to confess, too.
So, who's your sister this time?
Actually, there's a shop in Azabu to maintain white voracely.
A lady working there has a man
I'm so tired.
Alright, let's go.
What?
You should get your scars on before it's too late.
I-It's obvious that I'm going to get hurt.
Don't be so stubborn. Just hit it and smash it.
I don't want to smash it!
Honda, be brave.
That's right.
Ego, I'm counting on you.
It's a big shop.
It's a motorcycle import company.
Motoguchi Motors is famous.
It's the second largest import company in Japan.
I see.
I guess I'm going to have to...
Honda!
Wait!
No, no, no! I'm going home!
Let me go!
Don't come near me!
Let's decide!
Right, Honda?
Wow, they're all famous in the world.
Recently, they started selling a motorcycle with the name Motoguchi.
It's the fifth largest motorcycle in Japan.
They're aiming to become a motorcycle manufacturer.
I'm looking forward to the future.
Is she the woman who was at the Shiroba inspection?
Yeah.
Then, I think she's the president's daughter.
What?
President's daughter?
Yes.
You're in love with something great again.
The president's daughter and the bike repairman's daughter are the same.
No, I'm going home.
I'm going home!
Senpai!
Yes?
Are you with that lady now?
Yes, I am.
This way, please.
No!
I'm going home!
I'm definitely going home!
That lady is running now.
She's a good runner.
Right, Honda?
Yes.
Yeah, I'm really going home.
I'm Motoguchi Rika.
Can I help you?
This girl is so pretty!
Well, yeah.
I'm Ryotsu Kakuchi.
I'm Nagagawa.
Nice to meet you.
But this guy...
Oh, the Shirobai team that came the other day.
You remember me? I'm impressed!
I'm Honda Hayato of the 4th Mobile Team!
You're the famous Honda-san?
What? You know me?
There's no rider in Tokyo who doesn't know the late Honda.
You have a completely different image.
I thought you were a more scary person.
When I get off the bike, I become like this.
I'm like Jekyll and Hyde.
You seem to have a lot of veins.
No, that's not true.
By the way, Rika-san, he likes you.
Will you go out with him?
Senior!
Yeah.
Sure. Let's go out.
What?!
That's great, Honda!
As a friend, I'm very welcome.
As a friend?
Yes.
Friendship is a habit.
You can also say that it's a good thing.
But it's not completely a denial.
It's all up to your skills.
Naka, let's go.
Yes.
Wait a moment, Senior.
What should I do with my skills?
Think about it yourself.
Even if you say that...
There's nothing like that.
I have to go in this case.
But...
But there's no strike.
Mr. Honda!
Are you alright, Mr. Honda?
No, I'm fine about this.
Senior...
No need to worry.
He's a good man at fixing women's instincts.
Well done, Honda!
-Honda! -That's amazing!
Congratulations, Mr. Honda!
Oh, thank you very much!
-Honda, this is a reverse-sacrifice. -Versus-sacrifice?
It's a reverse-sacrifice.
-She's single, right? -Yes.
That means if you proposed to her and got married,
you're the president of Motoguchi Motors.
N-No way!
I just invited her to a date.
You're the president of Motoguchi Motors.
50% of the people will get married.
50%?
-Really? -Yes.
If that's the case, I'll have to thank you.
What?
If you become president, you'll get a Dohgatti or a Harley bike.
But I can't ride a bike.
I'll pay you.
No way.
You can at least get one every month.
Don't be ridiculous.
You should mind your language.
If I didn't join, things wouldn't have gone this well.
Well, of course you wouldn't.
Alright, one for your next month.
You can see I'll be heading on with a full time position
as vice president as a colleague of mine.
Okay.
You can say I'm going to be the "big president" of the future.
Subtitle by Subdivers
You idiot!
You can't date a girl who rides a manual!
Oh, I've been looking into it...
You can't be a city girl like that!
You have to show your personality more!
My... My personality?
Umm...
You look great on a motorbike!
He's a pro rider too. That's not acceptable!
If you can show your personality to others...
Nice!
I'm worried.
Actually, I am! Don't worry!
What?
Really?
There is a weapon that Rika Motoguchi doesn't have in Honda...
That is...
The birth of a city girl!
A city girl?
Yes!
As the killer of a city girl, I summoned a city girl!
Then, what I can't do?
To a nearby town in a town I know, I can't run away!
Seems like Americans do.
I first saw a town in a town where the Edo culture begins.
She encountered a culture shock, I got shocked.
That's why Honda-san is so wonderful.
I see.
So, I'll do your hand-to-hand and...
I won't!
I will be a big shot in Asakusa!
No matter how much I own a town or a city, I'll attend!
Then, I can't do anything you ask of me.
I can't help it. I'll set up the whole date course.
Senpai...
If you do as I say, everything will be fine.
Yes, thank you.
I'll make you the president no matter what.
I'm going to be on a big ship.
I count on you, senpai.
Namidabashi?
That's not a bad place.
Idiot!
Namidabashi is the place where Jyo and Tanke met for the first time.
But I don't think there's actually such a bridge.
I'll explain it to you.
"I'm crossing Namidabashi, Jyo!"
And I'll make Tanke and Tanpei laugh by imitating their voices.
As expected of you, senpai. You're so detailed.
"Jyo!"
"I'm crossing Namidabashi, Jyo!"
Mama, what's that?
Don't look at me.
Will this really be okay?
Hi, this is Honda.
Oh, Rika?
Mr. Honda?
Excuse me, but can you change the address to the intersection of Matsuyama and Sukiyabashi?
Ah, that...
Is that okay?
No, I'll be there soon.
I can't imitate Sukiyabashi and Tanke and Tanpei!
Um, um...
Next is...
Next is to Motoguchi by tandem.
You two will make Rika feel excited.
"Feel excited"?
Motoguchi's original bike.
Rika will be happy to ride it.
That's great.
The exhaust note that will sway your heart is...
I can only say my original words.
Oh, Honda-san!
I'm so nervous!
How is it?
Senpai, I'm a man!
I'm so nervous!
Then I'll write you a note!
Yes.
Ah, I can only say my original words
I'm sorry, Honda-san.
I'm late.
Riku-san,
no, I wasn't waiting at all.
That's good.
Hey,
how about I drive?
Oh, what a cool car!
I'm so excited.
Where should we go?
That's right.
Next,
let's eat.
Oh,
Monjayaki?
You're so naive!
Monjayaki is too representative and has no freshness.
If you want to give her a culture shock,
you can have a gift of a Japanese-style sushi.
You can have a Japanese-style sushi.
A Japanese-style sushi?
What's that?
Don't you know what a Japanese-style sushi is?
It's a whale's cutlet.
It was served at a school lunch.
Hmm...
It wasn't served.
Is that so?
It's because we're from different generations.
It's been 12 years since it was banned from eating.
Isn't that impossible?
I'm sorry.
Don't be ridiculous.
If you were younger than you,
you wouldn't even know that you can eat whale meat.
You'll be shocked for sure.
I see.
A meal is a whale's cutlet.
A meal is a whale's cutlet?
Hey, Rika,
we're having a meal.
Huh?
Oh,
what?
What?
Is it your first time having a Thai meal?
Oh,
yes.
It's my first time being born.
It's spicy but delicious.
I'm so happy.
That's good.
A whale's cutlet wasn't good either.
I can't get sick.
Berth?
This is my last meal.
See you later.
And after that,
it's an excursion to Riki Island.
Riki Island.
on a small boat.
You can never go on theüty boat tour too.
We didn't quite get it.
This is an ice rink.
Don't do that.
growth losers.
Do and don't put on aDrone on an ice rink.
I don't really understand.
Just wave to the beach.
Haha....
Hahaha....
Hahaha.....
Hahahaha...
Hahahaha....
It was fun.
Yes.
This is not going to continue like this.
We need to decide only for the last time.
On your way back from your date,
I'll send her to your house.
I will show the man's worth.
I'll show you the true power of the Ichi-Gisa!
Understood?
Um, Ms. Rika...
Well then, Ms. Rika.
I had a lot of fun today.
I'm glad you're happy.
Well then, good night.
Good night.
Oh my!
Well, I was surprised to hear that.
I was surprised to hear that.
What are you going to do after being shocked by the culture shock?
Well, I was really nervous
when I was taken to Ms. Rika's house.
You're completely at the other side of the spectrum.
I'm sorry.
Well, did you confess your love?
What?
You idiot!
Then why did you go on a date?
But,
Ms. Rika introduced me to your parents.
What?
Parents?
You were introduced to your parents on your first date?
Yes.
So, how was it?
Well, Mr. Honda, here's a cup.
Thank you.
When I said I was a white-collar employee,
my father liked me.
You did well!
It seems that 80% of your father liked you.
Really?
That's right.
I think you should give it to your daughter's boyfriend.
Mr. Honda, you did well.
You can't forget the president's sword.
I'll leave it to you.
If you want to be a good husband and daughter-in-law,
you should first be a good son-in-law and a good son-in-law.
You should attack your father as much as possible.
Yes, I will.
Actually,
I was invited to my father's company for the next vacation.
I see.
90% is not bad!
Good luck, Mr. Honda!
Yes!
I found a good girlfriend.
But she hasn't been around lately.
Don't be so annoying, Nakagawa.
I'm off work.
No, I was wondering about Mr. Honda too.
He hasn't gone out for a week since then.
Miss, please be careful.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, I'll be going.
Mr. Ryotsu, Mr. Nakagawa!
Where are you going?
I'm going to Europe.
Europe?
What?
Then, what about your marriage with Mr. Honda?
Marriage? I don't like it.
But that's fine with me.
If you have a girlfriend, you can marry.
But do you know his name?
Mr. Honda is not my father.
He's my father.
Excuse me, I have to talk to him.
Bye.
Let's go on a date when yoru will be back.
Lots of excuses.
I'll be waiting for you.
Boss, we've reduced Rika's course record by 2 seconds.
What?
This is amazing data, Boss.
Tonira, you're back.
You're still doing well.
I see. You're very reliable.
Then, I'll take care of the test run of this bike.
Before that, please let me see Rika.
Rika?
This is bad. If Honda finds out, the development will be delayed again.
Rika is taking a shower right now.
Shall we go to see it together?
No, no...
By the way, Rika said that the Honda on the bike is the coolest.
Rika?
Honda!
I'll go to the test run!
What is it?
It's just a test driver.
By the way, Honda said that he liked your skills.
Hey!
Rika's boss!
Isn't Honda pitiful?
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'm a friend of Honda.
Why is Rika keeping it a secret that you started in Europe?
But,
Rika is a test driver for me.
I think that he can be my son.
What?
Then, marry Rika?
It has nothing to do with you.
What?
Please choose one.
But then, Rika and Honda can be brothers, right?
That's right, but...
there is a problem, I suppose.
Or, is it?
No! No! No!
No problem at all!
Boss, the course record again!
What?
Wait!
Boss!
It's alright.
At least we got a good landing.
No way!
You're really good at this, Honda.
Get the next machine.
Yes!
Boss, wait a minute.
I know.
Your wife always said she wanted to see you on a motorcycle.
I'll go, dad.
Well, Honda.
You're my son now.
You can do it.
Boss, I can't tell you the truth.
Poor guy.
I'll go out with you again sometime.
You're really good, Mini Pato girls!
You're all over the place!
Watch me now.
I'll teach you a lesson.
I'll blow up different newspapers like Koshin that're not about to be published.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Be sure to pay attention next episode!
The纹社新聞大戦争!
Subtitle by Subdiver
♪ I heard the rumors that a girl who can't fall in love will fall in love. ♪
♪ There are many things I want to do. ♪
I am as much as a mountain
I want to ride through the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be freer than birds
The lady's dream changes with the speed of a telescope
My love, I'm sorry, wait
The bright future of the panorama
You know it, right?
I'm sorry, wait