Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new age ♪
♪ Diving to the city with a hero ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Instead of just wearing trendy clothes ♪
♪ I'll be more handsome ♪
♪ Let it rain ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Let's start running ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Let me run ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if it's a little dark ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt ♪
♪ Don't be excited ♪
♪ Be strong and high ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
Let's go to the city tomorrow
♪ Diving to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ The world is a city of dreams ♪
♪ With everybody we can ♪
♪ Let's set off ♪
♪ Omnibus ♪
Ryo-chan?
Wait!
Please, Reiko-chan!
If I eat a lot of katsu-don, I'll be able to drink water until the end of the month!
No way!
How about you try putting this on your wallet from next month?
Yeah!
You can lend me a little!
I'm hungry...
I don't have anything to eat.
I'll watch TV though...
It's juicy meat.
It's delicious!
It's so good!
I ate meat before the end of the month!
It's the best!
Don't make me watch this show!
I love you.
I really love you.
I really, really...
I really, really love you.
I can only win 3% because I'm making a drama like this!
I love you.
I really love you.
The viewership rate at this time is common common sense!
Mimi takes a dog tail every week and will shampoo!
The clothes are Chanel.
Thepede is special products of Geragamo.
Kobe bureau is a popular item...
Ahahaha!
Ahhh! The color of the moon!
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
I'm hungry, so I'm watching a horror movie.
Let's eat it!
Ugh!
I don't know how the viewers feel on TV these days.
I don't understand anything!
It's so unpleasant!
Oh! This is the Katsudon of Tsurukame Prefecture!
What's up, Reiko?
You took my share, didn't you?
This is Kei's.
Well, you don't have to say that.
Ugh!
I told you it was Kei's!
By the way, you're late, Nakagawa.
Oh, really.
It's about time to return from the patrol.
When the Katsudon of Tsurukame Prefecture cools down, the taste is halved.
I knew it!
Ryo-chan!
If you eat someone's food without permission, it's a theft!
Huh?
I-I-I don't care!
Ryo-chan!
You're a good cook.
I'll give you some.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
I'm going to sell it to Nakagawa.
Hey, be careful!
Hey!
Nakagawa!
What's that?
Please help me!
I'm sorry, I'm on a strike.
Please open the road.
Nakagawa!
Please look this way.
Nakagawa?
Hey, stop!
Sen-Senpai!
Oh, Nakagawa.
What are you doing here?
Senpai, please help me!
What's going on?
I don't know.
Are you okay, Senpai?
Nakagawa!
Please do something!
I can't go any further!
You can help me if you break the katsudon.
Please!
Okay!
Move!
Move, Move Move!
Move, Move!
Move,
Move!
Musset mantener!
Move,
Move!
Da-da-da!
Hurrah!!!
Oh my god! Are you OK?
Well...
Tell me you're going to stop!
Sorry to interrupt, but we're waiting for the bus...
Uh...
I'm, the producer of Kanto TV, Sugihara.
Kanto TV?
I'm Yamanoto. I'm also the director.
Well, what's Kanto TV?
That's...
In other words,
a full-fledged interview with Detective Nakagawa!
Okay?
A 24-hour interview!
Um, why me?
Here you go.
Oh, it's Nakagawa!
Nakagawa is the winner of the Nice Guy contest
This is the cause of all the commotion.
Oh, hello?
Nakagawa, have you been to Kanto TV?
Yes, but Chief, what's this all about?
If you appear on TV,
it'll improve the image of the Katushika office.
Please help me.
No, Chief!
Look, they're here again!
Nakagawa, do something!
You just have to take my day.
Okay, let's do it!
Yay!
Then, follow me!
Oh!
Oboki-chama, it's morning.
Oh, good morning.
It's time to go to work.
A uniform I ordered from Barbary
has been delivered from England.
Yeah, let's try it when we get back.
Oboki-chama, have a good day.
The end!
Okay! Good job, Nakagawa-chan!
I tried to recreate the atmosphere of this morning as it is.
See?
The ratings will be 20% harder.
I don't understand the audience's feeling.
Huh?
The 24 hours of close contact has already been compared with the ratings of the worst section.
1.2, 1.0, 1.3%.
If this continues, the show will be cut off.
What?
You're an amateur. What do you know about this?
An amateur watches the show!
Huh?
A few years ago, the old man's stall was closed for 24 hours.
That should have hit 20% of the high ratings.
The excitement at that time.
The smile of the old man at that time.
It still burns in my brain and never leaves me.
Oh, oh, oh!
It's all over.
The show is called "24 hours of close contact".
It's a show that goes through the attitude that comes with living in the common people,
and at one time, it was even said to be the parents of Kanto TV.
How about that?
You can show Nakagawa's rich side and say, "Yes, it's okay."
I can't do the same thing forever.
Yeah, but you're a professional.
Hey, ramen and dumplings.
Welcome.
You know what?
You're trying to make the guests who came to the ramen restaurant eat spaghetti.
What?
That's right.
It's true.
Sui- Sui-Hara-chan.
What kind of program do you want the viewers to watch now?
Hey, hey.
Well, for example, the five-man show that takes away the tears of the viewers.
That's it.
It's a show where you can see the misfortune of the people you've met.
What do you mean?
Listen.
The viewers want the misfortune of the people.
You have to fulfill that desire.
The concept of the project is...
poverty!
I see.
Depending on the consultation, this high viewing rate will be accepted,
and Director Ryoichi Binwan will be able to get rid of it.
One or two of these.
However...
Please lend me your wisdom, Director Ryoichi.
Let's go with a low-paying rate of 100,000 yen per percent.
100,000 yen per percent?
Senpai, what are you thinking?
The great plan to completely convert Nagagawa-chan into a citizen.
Cut!
Producer
We'll set it up as to how much will be taken in this condition.
Nakagawa-kun who lives an upright, bright country by his own lamps.
Listen, Ryoichi-chan.
I don't think that's sound good.
Sound good?
Hey!
This isn't something like that.
What exactly is it?
Production, sir.
Production, huh.
The End
Hey, old lady. I just got home.
Oh, Mr. Ryo. You're home early.
Yeah.
Inruna-kun's in.
Oh, a guest?
I'll put you on TV.
What? TV?
Thank you. Thank you. Good evening.
Oh.
This is awful.
I-I know.
This place might give the viewers a sense of comfort, but...
Do you really live here every day?
Of course.
Come on in, Mr. Ryo.
I'll get you some tea.
No, thanks.
First, you need to wake up.
You need to lay down on the floor.
Then, you need to get up.
You need to twist your head.
And then, you need to face the screen.
I'm a rookie, so I'm in trouble.
Such unnatural camera marks are not good.
Right, Mr. Sugihara?
Y-Yes, you're right.
The director of the TV show is silent!
What?
Even the most lively fish can't be eaten by a bad fish.
Ugh, it's a disaster.
So, let's see what I can do.
Uh, will you sleep in this futon?
You can't sleep in uniform.
Hurry up and take off your jacket.
That...
What about your pajamas?
Pajamas?
That kind of thing?
Hey, by the way, this chair is...
Well, in that case, the citizen's safety guard will be on standby with his own shirt.
Stand by in T-shirt.
Is it like this?
Hmm, it's not like this.
Hey, Eddie!
It's you, you!
Me? What did you say?
Yamamoto-chan, hold on tight here.
What? What?
Put that over there, put it over there.
Try to make this and that a telecon.
All right.
It's not like that!
No, no, it's not like that!
You just have to line them up!
Hey, Nakagawa, stretch your hand.
Yes, sir.
Everything is within reach.
And then, a picture of the beautiful lady.
Well, this is what realism is.
By the way, Yamamoto-san,
you and Eddie?
Yes, sir!
Do you think something is missing?
Huh?
You're a pathetic guy.
Do you not understand this?
No!
It's a chicken.
A chicken?
Go buy a chicken! Hurry!
I should buy it, right?
A chicken in winter, Senpai?
Nakagawa doesn't know.
A summer windmill on the window of winter.
A winter kotatsu on the window of winter.
A dinner table in the middle of summer.
That's the love of a single man.
Now, the husband's tears are squeezed tightly.
Um, what should I do?
I think the viewing rate is 3% up.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
The love is bleeding.
Standby, okay!
Ah, I slept well.
The weather is good today.
Cut!
Huh? Why?
There is no commoner who has such a well-prepared face when he wakes up!
Ah!
There is no one who has such a well-prepared face when he wakes up!
I don't have any set lotion.
I'll use the remaining oil from the frying pan to make you sleep like this.
I'll blow on your sleep and make your eyes red and clean.
I'll make you sleep like this.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I don't have enough swelling!
Ah, um, Ryo-chan, that's enough.
Don't interfere with the production!
The finishing touches are the sleeping fashion.
But in terms of budget...
Oh, this is worse!
This is also part of the job.
Nakagawa!
Alright!
The reality has come out!
Listen!
You have to do it only once.
So watch carefully!
Yes, sir!
Shut up!
Good morning.
The wake-up kiss!
Did you see that?
This is what we call human sleeping!
Try it!
Yes, sir!
You know this is not for everybody, right?
Got it?
And this is for the people.
Isn't this too much?
Break!
your second job,
and now the second one!
Just get rid of everything and become naked!
You're dangerous.
I..I lost.
Morningナ
Don't make me cold...
NO!
SHIT!
SHIT!!!
Oh, it stinks!
What? Why is there a mold?
Oh, this is bad!
I see. I thought you'd eat the ramen and then blow it out like this.
And then you're going to be aged as it is!
Well, I guess I'll have to wait another week or two.
Why isn't this thing working?
I'm sorry, Senior. I can't get my fart out.
Cut!
Okay. Well, your episode is different.
You've improved a lot, Nakagawa.
Your ratings are now 5% for sure.
Now all that's left is to decide how many things the viewers like to see.
Nakagawa, a poor police officer, has a garbage bag to store food.
Hey, you!
What?
Nakagawa, a nice boy, gives his dog a fried bento he picked up for dinner.
Now he can grab the heart of the other person and get a 1% rating.
Yay!
Nakagawa, a nice boy, also has a heart of a child.
He's a good police officer.
Now he can grab the hearts of his husband and children and get a 1% rating.
"A little help from the police"
There's a great boss named Junsa Ryoutsu at the Kameari Park branch.
He sometimes serves ramen to the hungry Nakagawa.
"A little help from the police"
With the appearance of ramen, the ratings are now 10% up.
What the hell is going on, Ryou-chan?
No!
The camera's too high.
I'll take it.
"A little help from the police"
Alright, Reiko.
Just walk straight ahead.
I don't want to.
I've been doing too much, so don't aim.
"A little help from the police"
Nakagawa is in the frame.
Ame!
"Ame"
A sexy beauty and a second person.
What are you talking about? I don't remember you being born!
Ryo, what are you doing there?
Director, maybe...
Grandma is a mischief.
An amateur's reaction is life.
Grandma's lines are overflowing.
How many percent of the heart of the eyelid is recovered?
18% of the national tears and emotions.
18% of the reaction.
Then, the total number of views is 40% x 100,000.
4 million!
Well, Nagagawa, who is wet with tears,
will enter the battle.
Sometimes, Nagagawa, who accidentally enters the real world,
Um, soap, soap, and...
There it is.
Shampoo.
Lucky, it's still there.
The civilian police officer collects and uses both soap and shampoo.
Finally, he closes it with maniacal fruit milk.
Alright! It's the climax!
The civilian police officer, Nagagawa, will be doing this for a day.
Mom!
Keiichi! Keiichi!
Keiichi, what are you doing?
I wanted to see you!
Reiko-san!
Well done, Nagagawa!
You've made it this far.
It was nothing, poor Kei-chan.
This is another person.
Not me!
Nagagawa-chan!
Ryou-chan!
Hello!
So...
Right after the show started,
Nakagawa-chan received letters, faxes,
and a whole staff room full of gifts from all over the country.
Nakagawa is really good at acting.
I... I fooled the government.
How can I apologize?
Oh, yes.
By the way, what is the viewer rating?
It's 30%.
Oh, I see.
Which means...
My money is 3 million yen.
But...
Ryosu-chan was the director of the ballet club.
I don't need someone less capable than an amateur.
You two are...
Nonsense.
So...
I don't have any money!
W-what?
Ryosu...
W-Wjong!
That fake show is your doing after all!
That's mine!
It's the final of Nakagawa's sweat and tears!
Right?
Because...
My senior forced me to do it.
Chief, it was good, wasn't it?
You are...
You idiot!
Who is this guy who is like a catalog of walking brand products?
It's super rich Shiratori Reiji!
Did he follow Reiko to the press office?
Hey, Reiko!
Do something about this dangerous guy!
Next time on "Super Rich Shiratori Reiji"!
Thank you for watching!
"Shiratori Reiji"
♪ Even if I try to stop the clock, ♪
♪ time will pass away. ♪
♪ Don't stare blankly, ♪
♪ don't look back, ♪
♪ laugh and live on. ♪
♪ Even if it rains today, ♪
♪ even if it rains today, ♪
♪ tomorrow will be sunny. ♪
♪ Bye bye, ♪
♪ let's wash our hands. ♪
♪ Don't say ♪
♪ goodbye ♪
♪ to the past. ♪
♪ Oh yeah. ♪
♪ Let's live ♪
♪ as we like. ♪
♪ There's a good thing. ♪
♪ Outside the door, ♪
♪ the sun is calling. ♪
♪ Let's talk ♪
♪ to the future together, ♪
♪ without love. ♪
♪ Even if it's in the future, ♪
"The