Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle ♪
♪ I kicked the love stone ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ in the middle of the taiko ♪
♪ I wondered if you really did ♪
♪ But I was laughing ♪
♪ at the greater good ♪
♪ Someone from somewhere ♪
♪ Piss off or something ♪
♪ There's a reason to be hard to find ♪
♪ Which means I'm ranting ♪
♪ The streets are unchanged ♪
♪ It's so kind ♪
♪ The glass breaks ♪
♪ And the poultice just experiences a dead end ♪
♪ Are the guys ♪
♪ being stuffed with chicken boiling? ♪
♪ Wearing a Matsubo hat ♪
♪ The nine-tailed bat ♪
♪ From the east to the west ♩
♪ The sunset falls ♩
♪ It's going to end tomorrow, too ♩
♪ But I'm happy again ♩
♪ I'm happy because I'm happy and relaxed ♩
♪ Yeah! ♩
Ryo Tetsuan!
Genki Bakusi
Who is this guy??
What's wrong with everyone?
Idiot! Why is he leaning his head like that?
A new invention, developed from the nations, has been announced by the chief.
New invention? What is it?
What about Reiko?
What's wrong with Reiko?
Come to think of it, I haven't seen her for a while.
Did she miss out on something?
Not you! It's Reiko!
There must be a reason for it.
It's starting!
Listen, don't make a fuss!
Yes, yes, I understand.
Today, we have a new invention
developed by the Katsushika office.
It's to show off the new Super Power Assist Suit, Otasuke-kun.
Otasuke-kun?
What a simple name.
What's a Power Assist Suit?
It's a machine that can easily move heavy objects
even for women and people with weak strength.
When you move a patient from bed to the wheelchair,
it's easy for anyone who has been doing it for two to do it.
I see.
It's something we need in the future.
Then, Professor Korosuke Ezaki,
please.
What?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What's going on?
Ladies and gentlemen!
One, two, three, come out here!
Please welcome the Super Illusion of Professor Korosuke Ezaki!
A-Reiko!
You weren't in the room because of me?
I'm afraid this is what you've been asked for.
This is what I think it is.
This genius magician,
another legendary scientist,
The science scientist, Ezaghi Korosuke, developed it.
Reiko, who helped him, has now become an invincible superwoman!
If you run, you can run faster than a ball!
If you have power, you can be stronger than a machine!
And you can build tall buildings!
I've heard of something like that before.
It's suspicious of Ezaghi's invention.
Oh, so that's Gorilla-kun.
I guess he's suspicious of my ability.
Good.
I'll go out and have a match!
It's a match!
It's arm wrestling, finger wrestling, mangle wrestling, anything!
All right, that's interesting!
Ryo-tsu, don't use your stupid strength to break it!
All right, let's have a match with arm wrestling!
Be gentle, Ryo-chan.
You know, it's Ryo-tsu Gorilla-kun vs. Super Beauty F-cup, Reiko-kun's match.
Watch carefully!
If I win, I'll have everyone here have lunch!
Then I'll go!
Ready, go!
That's a great power combo!
Oh, so that's why you're putting in the effort, Ryo-chan.
What?
Damn it! Then I'll do it seriously!
Oh, no!
It's all right.
Then I'll put in a little effort.
I can't believe you lost.
I just put in a little effort.
Are you okay, Ryo-chan?
If it wasn't for me, my bones would've been broken.
But still, it's a great power.
How's that, Gorilla-kun?
Do you accept Ota-suke-kun's ability?
Yeah, I do.
It's a great power.
In a week, we'll have to show it to the general.
With this much power, it'll be useful.
Now I can make a profit.
Ryo-tsu became Ota-suke-kun's monitor?
Yes.
That's right.
Professor Ezaki sold him to him.
He says he'll live off of Ota-suke-kun for a week.
I'm sure he's up to something.
Hello, this is Ryo-san's Zenigami moving van.
The study desk is on the second floor of the children's room.
The TV and the toilet set is in the living room.
The table is in the dining room.
Yes, I understand.
I'll finish it in five minutes.
In five minutes?
But only one person can do it.
Leave it to me.
Move, move!
No matter how much you move, it's like a powerless house.
Hey, Gojyujin!
Huh?
Whoa!
I'm in the way, so I'll stand here for a while.
Hello!
I'm here to deliver the Africa's first-class.
This is Ryo-san's Zenigami moving van.
Yes, it's here, it's here!
Please leave the moving van to the Zenigami moving van.
That's good.
If you go like this, you'll be rich in no time.
What?
The elevator is broken?
The moving destination is the top 10th floor.
It's not efficient to use the stairs.
Tomorrow is the day of the public display at the police station.
I want to make as much money as possible by today.
Hmm.
Hmm?
The distance is roughly 30 meters.
That's a good distance.
All right!
Ta!
Dorya!
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it anymore.
It doesn't feel good.
Oh!
I'm sorry!
It's warped.
It's warped!
You're sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not.
I'm saved!
What the hell happened?
Oh no! The control computer is broken!
No! I can't fix it!
I'm screwed. If I say I broke it, I'll get a penalty.
I think I'm getting a lot of money.
Besides, it's about Ezaki. I can't just pay for it.
I have no choice but to cheat.
Oh, here it is!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was a little sleepy.
Hey, Ryo-chan. Show the general officer the power of your help.
Be careful, Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan, I'll be careful. Okay?
I know.
I don't need to be here.
Did you say something?
No, it's nothing.
Battery charging is OK.
Professor Ezaki.
Then please bring the example.
Yes.
Please carry all this iron skeleton 50 meters away.
The time limit is 30 seconds.
You're going to carry it there in 30 seconds?
I'm not ready, Gorilla-kun.
Ryo-chan's power plus the help's power will be reduced.
Let's start! Ready, go!
What a weight!
Ouch!
You seem to be a little lost.
Gorilla-kun's joke is a joke.
See ya, Gorilla-kun!
Even if you do this, you're OK with the help.
Stop!
I'll bother you with each one.
Ouch!
Gyaaaaaa!
*Gasps*
*Groans*
30 seconds, just!
Are you tired?
Not at all!
Next is the speed test.
*Groans*
10 kg of iron array
on both hands and legs, just like this!
Oh, wonderful!
*Groans*
Alright, Gorilla-kun!
Let's add one more iron array.
*Groans*
If you have the power,
you can pull this big trailer
and run 100 meters in 10 seconds!
Impossible.
No matter how hard I try,
I'm at my limit!
*Groans*
I can't reach the chain yet!
Senpai, you're too fast!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?!
I'm just helping you!
*Groans*
I can't stop! I can't turn!
Senpai! Ryo-chan!
*Groans*
Somebody stop me!
*Groans again*
*Groans one more time*
*Groans*
* Expansion*
*Music stops*
I must finish my work!
I can only hear the music.
You're right, Papa. It's like music.
My daughter is like a terrible poet.
I don't like it, Papa.
Oh, my God. What's so fun?
Well, well, this girl is...
It's okay. Let's have tea.
Oh, that's unfair. You want to have a snack with me?
You're a child forever.
No! It's not my fault!
Senpai is now moving to Nerima at a speed of 60 kilometers per hour.
He's moving straight from the start point.
What's going on?
I didn't know you had such a defect.
This is not a defect.
You can work even when you're asleep.
Your learning mode is now in line with Gorilla's behavior pattern!
I see. So that's what it is.
Then how do you stop it?
You can't stop it?
If I just keep going straight, I'll be able to cross the Kanjou Line 8.
Are you going to Mejiro Street?
Wait, if you say you're going to Mejiro Street...
Oh, no! If I keep going straight, Ryo-chan will get stuck in that gas tank!
What?
I knew it.
If I keep going straight, it's going to be a big deal.
I have to stop Gorilla-kun's rush somehow.
Is there a good way?
Alright, let's go with this strategy.
What strategy?
Give me a name.
A big trap!
Alright! Do it! Hurry!
Make a huge trap and drop Gorilla-kun here.
Since I'm helping you, Gorilla-kun can only go straight.
This is a success, no doubt about it!
The digging is over!
Alright, put on your seat belts.
Yes, sir!
It's only about three minutes until the senior arrives at the scene.
Hurry! Hurry up!
The big trap is done!
Alright!
Here he comes!
All right!
Thanks for the hard work, Ryo-kun.
I'm usted.
I did it!
It went well!
That's just what I envisioned.
I guess I'm old. But it's finally stopped now.
No, no, stop! Stop this!
Ow, ow, ow!
It's Ryo!
What the heck!
The trap is a failure! Senpai is still heading for the gas tank!
What?!
I-I can't hold on to the gas!
I have to do something!
Damn it! I can't even move my hands or feet!
Oh, I see. I can move my neck freely.
Alright!
I'll take it myself!
No, no, no, no, no! Stop it!
I only got extra speed with my centrifugal force!
Senpai and the gas tank are only a kilometer apart!
Oh...
Professor Ezaki, anything else you want to say?
You're so good, Gorilla. But this is just a matter of time.
The next step will be...
A great strategy to blow away the starboard at once!
I'm going to blow Gorilla-kun away with that iron ball and change its direction!
There's no doubt that this will be a success!
I'm ready!
Senpai is coming!
Alright!
Begin attack!
What the hell is this! What a hell!
What! What the hell is this!
It was so good!
I can't get away from this! Damn it!
I'm done for!
Damn it! I'm running again!
You did well! The direction has changed!
I'm glad!
So good!
Right?
Let's go!
The plan is a success!
We did it!
Wait a minute.
This direction is bad!
There's a gas station!
What? Is that true, Nakagawa?
Professor Eizaki!
I'm not sure about that.
Next is...
Super strong electromagnetic magnet stop!
Ota-suke-kun, great plan!
Start!
I'm going to suck up Gorilla-kun with the super strong electromagnetic magnet.
This time, it will be a success for sure.
Are you ready?
Alright, let's start the plan.
Alright! Super strong electromagnetic magnet, get ready!
Super strong electromagnetic magnet, switch on!
Switch on!
What is this?
Good!
Now, power up!
Power up!
Yes!
It's annoying!
Oh, I'm back!
Good!
Everything is as I expected!
I'm back!
Ah, ugh!
The magnet is going to suck up other cars, not just Ryo-chan!
Oh, still, Cinderella!
What?
Oh...
Uwaaah!
I won't be broken!
I can't make it!
What?
Uwaaah!
Please do something!
Huh?
I slipped on the banana peel.
Hoho, this is also a matter of calculation.
Liar!
Senpai!
Natchan!
When will it stop? Stop it.
It seems that the battery can be used for five consecutive days.
Five days is nothing.
Damn it!
Uwaaah!
Wait!
What?
Who stopped this?
Who?
What should I do?
Uwaaah!
It hurts!
Stop!
Uwaaah!
Hey!
Stop it!
I'm sleepy!
10 games, 10 games, 5 times택
With a slipper and a water fish
Always sandals, always scandals
Don't worry about it
"I don't have one"
Play with your own nails
Everyday
I've put my boredom in a
"I don't have one"
"I am very excited!"
"Amazing"
"The lightning in the Sheep Hunt is like a smoke"
"If I run and run, I will be a educación"
"But I'm in a good Canvas"
"With a big dose of carbon monoxide " "I
don't know who to watch out for" "I
don't have one" Play with
your own nails "I
don't have one" "I
don't have one"
Where I sleep
Ya, Murakoji, Murakoji, Paiko, Paiko, Paiko
Shurinkan, Shurinkan's Kururindai
Kururindai's Ponpoko, Ponpoko's Tiro, Ponpoko's Na
The super-sounding Chosuke!
The Olympics?
I wonder if I'll wake that guy up soon
Higurashi, wake up!
Huh? He's not here
Hey, don't you know the Higurashi I left here?
Hey, did someone move it on their own?
Next time, "Higurashi, 3000 Ryo"
See you next time!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Oh, it must be a turtle ♪
♪ Come on everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!