They Count on you
Make the room a little brighter for watching TV.
Please, stay away from me.
There are no rich people here, so come to my house!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, just shut up and follow me
Hana-chan?
It's not Hana-chan!
Jun-kun?
Nonsense!
What are you doing?
It said the commercial will continue!
It's a trailer for next week!
Is it the love bird that's being talked about right now?
I've never seen it before.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Boring!
That can't be true!
Now is the best time!
The best!
What's the drama with high ratings?
I'm getting 30% every week!
It's not only interesting because the ratings are high.
Welcome back to the Yukata Brothers!
Who decides the ratings?
It must be a survey or something.
I've never been asked to do a survey.
Do you?
I've been asked to do a survey.
I've never been asked to do a survey.
There's a device that checks the ratings on TV.
I've never seen or heard of such a TV.
Don't you think the media is the one who decides the ratings?
No way!
It's just a love song.
You're the only one who's watching it.
I've been watching it because it's a high ratings drama.
I thought I wouldn't be late for the trip.
It's a Japanese style that is easy to be swept away by the boom.
Yes, it is.
Ryūtsu, why don't you play a game as a free-iary?
I've played a lot of games earlier.
Why don't you watch a video instead of that?
In fact, I got a video about enough goods.
A video about enough goods!
It's an educational video about the US Marine Corps of the camp set up in theлер Germany,
and this is a nice move.
Which part of the video is interesting?
What about this one?
It's a video about theumpinance of thejeRockầun
It's a video to warn you against the war.
Bring me a better video!
Oh, right.
I have a lot of video of Hojo.
Hojo? Who is that?
He lives in Niconico.
Don't you know him?
I don't remember him at all.
He's like a senpai.
Yes.
Hojo is an university graduate.
He is a man who volunteers and works as a fireman.
Oh, because he's an university graduate,
he has a very smart face.
Hojo, are you there?
Yes.
What's wrong, Hojo? Are you sleeping?
If this is Hojo,
he doesn't look like an elite of the university.
What do you need, Ryo-tsu?
What?
Do you know me?
Yes.
I'm Junsa-cho Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I'm a first-time officer in the park.
I'm from Tokyo.
I'm from Ryo and Taito.
I'm the eldest son of Ryo-tsu Ginji,
who runs the Tsukudani store in Yorozea.
My brother, Kinjiro, is a lawyer.
Kinjiro's wife, Keiko's family,
Kirigayake, is a member of Nakagawa Group.
Wait.
Why are you so familiar with me?
Oh?
I know about all the people who live in this dorm.
All of them?
Yes.
First of all, I'm Junsa Muranaka Makoto,
a first-time officer in the 1st floor room.
I'm a member of the Kasushika-cho Traffic Division.
You don't have to say it.
I've heard about him before.
He seems to have a great memory.
No, I just remember what I've seen and heard once.
As expected of Todai.
Do you have a video?
I have about 512 videos.
That's a lot.
But they're all serious videos.
Isn't there anything more fun?
Even if you say so,
I'm not sure.
No, wait.
It's not like it's really recorded.
I see.
The label looks hard,
but it contains something different.
The more serious you are,
the more you collect dirty videos.
I see.
All right, check it out.
20 years.
That was the era of war.
That's a lot of content.
That's what it is.
I'll just clean up.
That's it.
I'll go through the video in three episodes from today.
Next.
Oh, my God!
What's that?
I got it!
the lens is in front of me.
But it's a without a word,
the one next to it.
Wow.
What is the difference?
Next time.
Ah, that's...
That's? What's that, Hojo?
N-No, it's nothing.
It's not nothing, is it? What machine is it?
No, I mean...
Hmm? A machine that can't be told by people...
Ah! Now then, it's a machine that erases mosaics!
What did you say?!
M-Mosaics disappear?!
N-No, it's not! It's not such a machine!
Then what?
Wh-What's that?!
Hojo-kun, if you're saying you won't tell us how to do it,
then we have something we can do.
W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W!
T-T-Please stop!
M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M...
Hahahaha!
What-what is this!
Hahahaha, stop it!
Th-this is the only story we can talk about.
This is definitely a secret.
Actually, this is a meter system that relative ratings are examined.
What?!
We can loo- 잡ä-á receipt ratings like this?
Just the other day, some BTS personnel from a rating research company came...
??
What's that?
Here's the thing.
You were chosen as a sample of the target group of the rating survey, so could you help us with the survey?
But why are you the one who's the target?
Are you being fooled by the fraudulent method?
It's ridiculous!
Instead of taking the money, they gave us the license!
The channel was recorded by this device, and the radio waves were captured by this machine and sent to the survey company via a telephone line.
I see. That's how it was planned.
What I just said is a secret.
They were very careful to keep the meter device a secret.
Why?
It's because if someone finds out, they'll use it.
First, they'll know.
Second, they'll know that the person in charge of the media is excluded from the sample.
So, it means that the person in charge of the media wants this device so badly.
Fuji, can you help us a little?
No way...
I won't say that you don't want to help us.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Maybe it's because we are a little too eager...
That's right!
Manai-chan, how are you doing?
I'm good!
Let's go drink some more next time!
Hey, Ryotsu-chan. Long time no see.
Hello. I'm...
This is the producer I know.
Oh, hey. What are you doing today?
You brought some interesting project, right?
The one that can earn a lot of viewership ratings!
You're a guy who can earn a lot of money.
Yeah.
I actually came to sell the viewing rate.
What? Sell the viewing rate?
I think he's very interested in this guy.
This is not good. Send it to me.
Why do you have this?
It's a meter device that checks the viewing rate.
You're very knowledgeable.
Actually, this guy was selected as one of the target generations for the viewing rate survey.
So?
No, I've never seen anything like this before.
It's precious, right?
Yeah.
Even we businessmen...
No, it's because we're businessmen that we can't see it often.
About 6,000 generations nationwide are target for viewing rate surveys.
Even in the Kanto region,
there are 15,59 million TV generations.
Out of them, there are 600 generations.
What?
Out of 15,59 million, there are only 600?
It's 25,983 generations per generation.
So can you get accurate numbers?
It seems that there is no problem with statistics.
Even so, if you're getting a viewing rate of only 600,
this is one...
About 0.17%.
It's surprisingly small.
What?
Ouch!
Even if it's only 0.17%,
it's precious for the TV station.
Right?
That's...
By the way,
the program I was in charge of before
was cut off because the viewing rate didn't go to 10%.
Right?
It went up to 9.9%.
0.1% left...
If someone in the sample world watched it,
it would be 10%.
But...
Look!
This guy will help you at that time.
How about that?
10,000 per floor.
What?
No, no, no!
No matter how much you do,
don't use this kind of trick!
You don't want a viewing rate?
Well, I want a viewing rate.
I want it so much that it comes out of my throat.
But I don't want it!
I don't want that!
I can't sell my soul as a TV man!
We're trying hard every day
to increase the viewing rate.
If you do such a trick,
you can't face the staff who are working hard.
Effort every day?
Yeah.
For example,
evening news.
In the past,
the market was decided from 6pm
when evening news was said.
But the content of the news
is similar to any other news.
So,
I thought it would be better
to start a little earlier
to increase the viewing rate.
Then,
one song
made the time of the program
to start earlier.
Other songs
that saw this
raised the time of the program.
The time of the news
was getting earlier and earlier.
To increase the viewing rate
even a little.
I see.
That's why.
You're going to combine
the news of the day
with the news of the day,
aren't you?
In the program,
efforts are being made
to increase the viewing rate.
Recently,
the subtitles are often
released in the variety show.
Subtitles?
See,
they're coming out
This is a role
that tells the viewer
that this is the laughing place.
If you watch the subtitles,
the viewer can laugh
with peace of mind.
This will
increase the viewing rate.
I see.
And,
to always attract the interest
of the viewer,
I'll put the subtitles
here as well.
Huh?
Do I have to do something?
At the end,
wait until the end.
I think
Well,
that's it for the subtitles.
Next time,
wait a minute.
Let's do the black cat.
The last time
it was going to be
a lot of black cat.
Ah,
who are you?
If you watch the subtitles, the viewers can relax and laugh.
That leads to an increase in the viewing rate.
I see.
Huh?
Didn't we have the same conversation just now?
It's exactly the same as before the commercial.
The difference is about the subtitles here.
As you can see from the middle,
I'll put in a little bit of the first half.
Because the viewers of the recent videos change the channel immediately.
You're having a hard time with a lot of things.
I'm having a hard time.
What do you mean?
You're just doing such a silly thing and pulling the viewers.
It's a new thing.
The only number that can evaluate the program is the viewing rate.
It's a natural act of the TV man to try to raise that.
But is that really reflecting the viewing rate?
Of course.
But if the other programs imitate it at once,
The effect of the viewing rate increase should also be reduced.
Then it's another different thing.
Even if you don't use such a trick,
There is a chance that the viewing rate will be increased by 0.17%.
No, no.
Even if I want the viewing rate,
Can't I just do that?
Do you know about the viewing rate survey company that left this device?
Yes.
I got the name.
It's a company called Nakagawa Research.
Nakagawa?
Then maybe...
Yes.
It is one of the companies run by Nakagawa Keiichi-junsa, who was a first-time employee before the performance.
It's more convenient.
What?
Did you break the viewing rate meter?
I'm sorry.
I don't have a reason.
No, I don't know what kind of device this guy is.
I just cut it.
I'm sorry.
But I can't believe it.
Is this guy really selected by the target audience?
It's true.
Is there any evidence?
The name of the target audience?
I can't show it to outsiders.
I don't need to worry about that.
The president of this company is Keiichi Nakagawa, right?
I'm his boss and a relative.
I'm not a company.
What?
Is that so?
I'm not trying to abuse you.
I'm just looking at it.
Wait a minute.
Well...
Kanto, Kanto...
Listen, Hojo.
When the name comes, remember the address and name of the audience.
What?
Use your memory.
Okay?
Yes.
This is it.
I'm sorry.
Here, Hojo.
What do you think?
Do you have your name?
Well...
Well, next is the Tokyo-Kokubunji City, Nishikokubunji 2-36-6, Zenomidori.
Okay, that's 600.
So the one with this pin is the house with the ratings meter.
That's right.
So what are you going to do with it?
From now on, we will freely control the ratings.
We will become the god of ratings.
What?
Yes!
Um, is your grandmother living in this land all the time?
Over 80 years.
I found it.
The ratings meter.
This angle...
at that position...
Konji!
Press the "ha" button.
Okay.
The sales position!
Alright.
Alright, it's a success.
Alright, let's move on to the next one.
This is the SWA producer calling.
Yo, what's up Ryosu-chan?
If you're talking about the initial rate, I'm sorry.
But if you're going to make 30%, then we're talking about something else.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's the GATEBALL GO GO rating for tonight's broadcast.
Look forward to it.
"GATEBALL GO GO"
However, I have the final winner in my hands now.
GATEBALL GO GO will start soon.
GATEBALL GO GO!
Alright! I'm running on all channels!
Take it out!
Oh, zero!
'Sugisaki-san's right!
Oh, Mr. Lucky! You're so good!
I can't do anything!
Ah, Mr. Tane is leaving here!
Currently, the rate of "Go! Go!" in the GATEBALL is 100%!
Yay!
So, I won't do it!
Ah, the channel is being returned!
That's right!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Wheeeeee!
18 minutes and 40 seconds until the end of the broadcast!
"256" has been returned!
Next is "413"!
"218"!
"13"!
"109"!
"215"!
"444"!
"329"!
Next week on "Go! Go!" in the GATEBALL!
"Go! Go!" in the GATEBALL is...
65.3%!?
Mr. Tsubasa, it's a call for you.
Huh? Hello?
Did you see that?
The GATEBALL 55% ratings.
Oh, so that's your trick.
Now you know my abilities, right?
If you're interested, I can make you get higher ratings.
How about 100,000 yen per percent?
Eh? But that's the TV man's duty.
I'm sure you were the main producer of the GATEBALL TV man.
Oh, yeah?
I'll give you a higher rating for your behind-the-scenes show.
What!?
Look forward to the next show.
Yeah.
GATEBALL TV MAN
Good evening, I'm Rodríguez Ito.
I'm Nancy Shimazaki.
All right, we'll be back on all channels except Hachi.
We're back to Hachi!
You're back to Hachi!
If you watch the same channel for four seconds, you'll be on the record.
If you don't, you'll be on a different channel.
The ratings are 0%!
I'll show the stupid TV crew how scary I am!
Mr. Tsubasa, it's a call for you.
Hello?
The TV man is on a break, isn't he?
You're...
He's in charge of the after-show, right?
I hope we get a high rating for our next show.
Mr. Ryo, you can't be...
If we have a low rating for the next show, what will you do?
You'll be on the wrong side.
But...
So, what are you going to do, Tsubasa?
Oh, I see.
I'll buy the ratings.
200,000 for the ratings of 1%.
What!?
100,000 for the ratings of this time!?
If you don't like it, it's fine.
Instead, the ratings of the behind-the-scenes show...
Oh, I see.
200,000 for the ratings of the behind-the-scenes show...
Alright, I'll get you the highest ratings in Japan.
Look forward to it.
Listen up!
The highest ratings of Japan so far is 82.4% in the 14th Kouhaku Song Contest.
We're going to change that record with the TV man who's going to start today!
Yeah!
The TV man who's going to start soon!
TV Man:
Alright, all channels have reached eight!
It's getting more and more getting back to normal!
Once again, it's getting back to another channel!
TV Man:
"The
It seems there's some terrible news in here.
Sit down on the spot!
Yes, this is the spot.
This is the room of the man who caused the world to tremble by increasing the number of viewers.
"The man who caused the world to tremble"
This is the man!
Everyone, please look!
"The man who caused the world to tremble"
The TV guy who attacked yesterday!
He recorded the highest viewing rate on the TV so far!
It seems that the people who were the samples wanted to see the criminal who was changing their channels.
Ryo-chan is satisfied with the fact that he is the highest viewer.
He's a really nice person.
Well, the people in the TV department were happy that they could get the number.
Huh?
"The man who caused the world to tremble"
Damn it!
That's him!
He betrayed me!
"The man who caused the world to tremble"
Wait a minute!
So the public bath there was not in the latter half!
What do you mean?
Damn it!
You're fooled!
"The man who caused the world to tremble"
After the rain, I walked back and forth
I was drawn to my mom
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black road
I was drawn to my mom
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt in front of you
Turn up and see that corner
To everyone
I can see you
There's a turtle there
I'm sure there's a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
It's forbidden, that's too much, chief!
Indeed, I went to the building
I was drunk and broke my house
It's bad, but
If I drink, what will remain?
Next time, mass production is prohibited!
Thank you!
There's a turtle there
I'm sure there's a turtle there
Everyone come to our town
Ah, it feels good
Look forward to the next time!