There's a courier on the river bank
If you pick up the pebble
You can fly into the water
From the tapestry of a cap,
to the taishakuten,
the sunset falls.
Tomorrow will end like this.
Katsushika and Shiba are happy again.
I realized a stupid habit.
The Same-Sense Age of Volvo
Oh, now I'm in peace.
It's really peaceful, isn't it?
It's not a big deal. Here, tea.
Now that I think about it, I can still remember that day when the Eight-Minute Island was spinning.
Is that so? You said it was already a mess.
What's wrong?
A strange man is approaching us.
A strange man?
That's...
What? Isn't that Volvo?
What?
Hey, Volvo!
You're still as arrogant as ever.
I don't know when I'll be attacked from behind.
Japan is not such a dangerous place.
When? In Japan?
And that uniform...
Volvo Saigo. From today, I will be working as a instructor at the Katsushika-cho Shooting Training Institute.
I see.
So you two are friends.
Yes. Please take care of me from now on.
Kakushiju.
You still wear that kind of armor in Japan.
No, that's all I have.
Really?
Yes, that's true.
Then I'll investigate.
See? There's so much of it.
But, as a policeman, this amount of equipment...
This is...
This is not a New York or some other place.
Look, look. This is a sniper rifle.
It's like a Zatoichi.
It really feels like a weapon department.
No, it's just a small piece of equipment.
What are you talking about? I'm here to protect the citizens as a policeman.
No, they're all weapons to protect yourself.
There's a policeman who has a full-auto model in every corner of the world.
But...
What are you talking about?
No, what are you talking about?
Stop getting close to my back!
Your guns are all here.
Ah, that's right. When the people were coming from behind, it was just...
That's why you're so narrow-minded.
Anyway, this evening is your welcome party, right, Volvo-san?
I agree! I agree!
I have to teach you Japanese common sense.
I'll have to teach you something about the rules.
Ryo-chan?
Nya!
Well, thank you for coming.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, where's Ryo-chan?
She's gone to sleep.
Oh, well.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Good night.
The End
Time's up.
What's going on?
Who's there?
He's gone!
Where are you going?
What's with that helicopter?
It took 20 seconds to defend.
Mr. Bakuryuta!
If you attack at this time, you're dead.
Don't attack at this time of night!
What are you doing in Japan?
My daughter, Jody, likes Saigo.
What? Me?
Really?
I heard that Saigo doesn't like women
because she lost to her daughter in the Aramco candidate battle.
Oh my!
No!
Chance!
I won!
She says she really wants to fight again.
That's impossible.
We'll lose again.
That's why you should stay with your daughter so you can get used to her.
Then you will have to fight again.
To fight...
As Jody and Bulborou?
Hey, Jody!
Hi, long time no see.
While Carl Vinson is staying in Yokosuka,
I'm going to live with my wonderful roommate, Mr. Volvo.
Wonderful?
Oh, I'll carry the luggage.
Thank you.
Are you really going to make us live together?
We're roommates. We're just living together.
You're just a roommate, Volvo.
Don't think of weird things.
I know, you're a bad boy.
I don't want to marry a man who loses to a girl, Daddy.
So let's fight under the condition that you're a thug.
I-I'm getting married.
Hey, Volvo, shut up.
I'll give you a shower.
A shower?
The shower's next door.
Right, thanks.
Hey hey, don't take off your clothes.
Oh, it's nothing, you know?
Of course not. Just get changed there.
scolded
I see.
You're too bold, your daughter.
Because of her open-mindedness,
she sometimes passes in front of me naked.
Butter! My nose!
Balbo, be strong!
My daughter has 100% mother's blood.
By the way, this is her wife.
Isn't she beautiful?
Her cooking is the best in the world.
She's a great cook.
She's the best in the world.
Don't brag about your family like that.
Japan and America have completely different cultures.
It's even worse when you live together.
I got married to my wife, so I know.
What if Saigo and my daughter get married?
I don't know about that.
You're saying it's not supposed to be like this?
It's too late to tell each other.
So, the best way to know each other is to be roommates.
Even if you live with a man,
you can be his father.
Is that okay?
It's my daughter's decision.
Jody has been independent since she was 15.
She lives alone.
Even college students don't have parents in Japan.
That's why the culture is different.
They're independent.
That's why.
Do you understand?
I finally got it.
Can I borrow your bath towel?
Take this towel with you.
Thank you.
I'm...
I'm going home.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
This is really cold.
It's so cold.
Please take it easy.
It's terribly disturbing to the father at 3:30 in the morning.
Are you okay, Borubo?
It appears that he is curvatureally anxious.
That was a great bath.
Hey, Borubo.
Go out by changing clothes!
I don't really care.
I can't stop talking!
So, you came back in the morning?
I can't keep up with you.
A man who never held a woman's hand suddenly lives with a woman.
And he's got a lot of money.
That's a big gap.
Isn't it?
I wonder if your father is worried.
It's perfect legalism.
And Jody is a flight attendant for Carbinson.
He lives in a soldier's room like a wrestler.
So he's got a more manly character than a man.
You're right.
When they're awake, let's go see what's going on.
Is he going to be all right?
He's got a lot of blood in his nose and he's dead.
It's scary that there's no possibility.
You're right.
Oh, is that Mr.Volvo?
Yeah, that's right. It's Mr.Volvo.
He's sleeping outside, being careful of Jody.
He's like an insect.
I'm going to have to take care of him.
You're awake?
Nakagawa and Reiko have been worried about you.
What do you mean?
Don't you dare lie down there.
Hurry up and put him in.
All right.
Oh no.
Mr. Jody.
Something's wrong.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you're naked.
No, it's not.
I got hot in the middle of the night and took it off.
It's the same thing.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Because if you're going to put on women's immunity,
You'd better show them your usual life.
Mr.Volvo's immunity is like a junior high school student.
Think about it a little and act.
Oh, it's really troublesome.
Mr.Volvo, are you okay?
Mr.Volvo!
Oh, I almost looked at you.
You must have been in a lot of trouble.
What a bad couple.
.
What's going on?
The next morning
I told you to come to the morning meal.
These are all canned food for the army.
As I thought. It's very delicious.
Bobby will be happy to eat.
No...
Bobby? You're going to show off your newly married life soon.
No, it's not that...
It's like a late-night meal. Let's eat.
I'm not good at cooking other than canned food.
Oh, you can.
Really?
It's a dish made by wild boars and bears.
What?
I was the best at survival training.
Hang what you want to catch with a rope.
First, peel the skin.
Then pull out the organs and eat it from the bones.
It's delicious.
Oh, the brain is delicious, too.
It's like chicken.
Especially the thighs.
It looks delicious.
If you have a chance next time, please try it.
Well, it's time to go home.
That's right. I'm sorry to bother you.
Well, Paul. You have to do it well.
See you.
Good night.
Are you really going home?
Please stay until morning.
I'm going to see the Drift Grand Final in the All Night.
No way.
Bye-bye.
You have to live with Jody.
That's right. I'm a roommate.
That's right, Bobby.
Only 5 days until the flight of the aircraft carrier.
You have to overcome Bobby's female phobia.
I will do my best.
See you.
Thank you for coming.
Bye-bye.
Oh, he left.
Hey, I have to go.
I have to do something about you, Volvo.
That's right.
I love you so much.
Oh, I'm alone with two people.
I know.
Jody.
Bobby, you don't have to push yourself too much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I said you only had 5 days.
But if you think about it, you have 5 days left.
So, let's go to bed.
I'll go to bed.
Of course, separately.
I see.
This is good.
I agree.
Good night, Bobby.
Good night.
Let's go to bed.
Okay.
And my key is in the mental health room.
Good night.
Jessie.
You called me.
Huh?
The sound of sleep...
The sleeping face is beautiful...
Bobby...
I love you...
Be a man...
Okay...
I'll do my best...
I'll overcome the fear of women...
I'll win against Jody...
I almost died...
But I won't lose!
What? You want to do special training?
I knew something happened last night.
At this rate, I won't be able to hold my body.
Don't worry. I'll think of a way.
I'll definitely modify the Volvo.
Please.
This woman and judo...
They're the bad guys from the Yudansha.
And this!
What is this?
It's a machine that can tell the Volvo's balance and strength at a glance.
What do you think, Kagawa?
Yes. It's almost done.
Good!
It's done.
Good! Everyone, don't hold back and come to the Volvo!
Yes!
Now!
There!
My balance is getting disturbed.
What?
That!
It feels like one force is enough.
Don't be so naive, Volvo!
There's no difference between men and women in this game!
Do you think you can beat Jyonei with that?
Boss!
Oh! He's recovered!
Jyonei!
I... I feel...
I can't wait for this!
I'm going to come back from the basics!
Everyone, today, this man is going to be good friends with everyone.
Yes!
Basically from our kindergarten?
You can complain after you get the results.
Uncle! Let's dance! Let's dance!
Your level of peace has been halved!
Don't let your heart be disturbed by the fact that your child held your hand!
O-Okay!
You've improved, haven't you?
Not yet!
Barbarian, dance more passionately!
More passionately?
I can't! I can't!
He's not here!
He's 100% recovered!
Of course! He's a kindergarten kid!
Okay, Barbarian! You've leveled up in elementary school!
Ranked!
He's amazing!
Uncle, you're so cool!
Hang in there, Barbarian!
Alright! Now, it's time to battle with the girls' high school students!
So, you're going to use the cross key to set the frame, right?
Y-Yes!
How is it?
The balance between 50% and 80% is shaking violently!
You're quite upset, aren't you?
Well, you have to come closer, right?
Yes!
Okay, pose!
No way! Really?!
Whoa!
What?!
What's going on?!
That's a shame!
As expected, the girls' high school students have lost...
As expected, this kind of manly space is calming.
What?!
Barbarian, you're making the wrong impression.
Anyway, let's go to the last training today.
Let's go!
Hang in there, Barbarian!
I'm a man this time.
I'm back!
Woman!
Man!
The match begins!
Don't give up, Bobby!
I hope so!
They're fighting!
How's Palmo doing?
He's in good shape, and his stamina is at 100%.
Alright, here I go, Palmo!
He's in good shape!
Hang in there, Palmo!
Palmo, you can't hold your breath!
Focus on the next move!
Don't give up!
3 seconds of wall-ins and you win.
The şimdi-stressing level is decreasing.
Keys?
Palmo, do your best!
Oh no.
Huh?
Maruma!
Oh, yeah!
Huh?
Oh!
My body and mind are at zero!
Huh?
Maruma!
One, two, three!
Yeah!
You idiot!
You can't get married.
Your daughter is too much of a pain in the ass!
It's today!
You can't do anything bad!
What was that hellish five days?
This is making me sick!
I guess so.
You look happy.
What?
I'm sorry, Bobby.
I won again.
Bobby!
Be strong!
Huh?
Boss, what's with this car?
Is this a robot car made of human brain?
And it's a better class than me.
Why do you make me work for you as your boss?
I don't understand!
See you later, Kamikaze.
I'll let you have your way.
And then they all come together and fly away
They have the most amazing power
Everyone, gather around
Come here
It's like a dream
The final energy
Look at tomorrow, yesterday, Shinjuku, and the universe
If you stand on the ground, the planet Kameari will turn into a circle
I drew a circle
Isn't this good?
There's no reason to be good!