Unlucky
"When you watch TV, please light up your room and look away."
"The Unlucky
Come to me, the unlucky
I'm not here, but I'm worried
"Look at the blue sky and the white clouds."
"You'll manage somehow."
"Don't you have any work?"
Come to me!
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look! A red cloud is burning
It'll be all right somehow
You know it, right?
You know it, you know it!
If you know it, then keep quiet and follow me!
The Day of Electronics
The Day of Electronics?
Why is November 11 the Day of Electronics?
If you write November 11 in Kanji, it becomes plus, minus, plus, minus, right?
It's the day that was made to let you know the importance of electrical energy.
Hmm...
At Nakagawa Housing, we'll hold an event to commemorate that day.
Will that event be awarded?
Awarded? Well, how do you say...
Nakagawa!
Yes?
Take me to that event venue!
I don't like it!
I get it!
I've been waiting for you, President.
President!
This is Mr. Shoei, the owner of our Ecology Housing.
Hello, hello, hello.
I'm Shoei Netaro.
Nice to meet you.
Shoei Netaro now?
My father used to come here.
Please take care of the limited resources.
That's my motto.
Please take a look.
This is our latest work, "Sun House: Sunflower".
It's an ordinary house, isn't it?
No, no. This house actually rotates towards the sun.
The house is rotating?
With this, the sun's light is always shining on the inside of the house.
It doesn't rotate?
It rotates once a day, so it hardly gets noticed.
But it's not shining as far from the house, right?
In that case...
The mirror opens!
What are you doing?
You're a robot that can transform.
He's a robot that can transform.
By adjusting the angle of the mirror,
I can get natural light to every corner of the room.
This way, I can stay at home for a month.
You can go outside, right?
Some people don't like the way they work.
They are using natural light.
Recording and animation are often recorded underground.
Why can't we do that?
We can record anything we want
in the sun.
This is love.
It's like dreams,
working and tanning in summer.
It's like dreams, working and tanning in summer.
I don't like it in winter.
Is that so?
However,
This is our best idea, the ultimate energy-saving house
Self-electric power generation, "Energy-saving Jiro-kun"
The roof is made of solar panels
It also uses wind power to generate electricity
What if it's cloudy, rainy and the wind doesn't blow?
Don't worry
There's a bicycle in the house
Why?
What's this?
It's a charging system
When you can't use solar or wind power
You can easily generate electricity
So this house alone can save energy
We'll use this Jiro-kun to do the "Energy-saving house"
"Energy-saving house"
Look at this
We'll show you how to live in the energy-saving house for a week
The winning team will get
What?
That luxurious, golden "Shoyne House"
Wow!
It's a product you can't tell if it's "ecology" or "waste"
I'm good at saving
I won the prize
Why do we have to participate?
That's right
Nakagawa is the host, so we can't participate
And each team has to include a female member
We have to include a female member
What?
Why? Are you going to join us?
Sakonji, Borubo, Jody
Hi, long time no see
Sorry, but I'll get the prize
And we'll make that house the "Sweet Home of Me and Bobby"
We'll talk about that later
Where are you going, Bobby?
I wonder if we can live together there
But the tough one became a rival
Hey, Ryo, Kanchi
Komachi, Naoko, Maria, are you all going to join us?
Yes, we're going to be enemies with Reiko
I won't lose to you
What?
Ryo
Let's live together in that house, no matter who wins
Why do you say that?
It's useless
I guess I'm in the wrong place
Now you will have to live according to your schedule
First of all, each team will get 3,000 yen
Gas, water, and food items will be calculated and displayed on the roof
The electricity generated will also be added to the money
The team with the most money left will win the game
If you break the schedule, you will be disqualified.
Let's start the show!
The participants enter the house.
The first hour is free.
How will each team spend it?
Naoko, turn off all the lights in the room.
I got it.
Maria, open the curtain.
Yes.
The car must not use unnecessary electricity.
I turned off all the lights.
I opened the curtain.
Thank you.
No way!
Why?
The light is still on.
Check again if you forgot to turn it off.
I got it.
Everything is off.
I forgot to turn it off.
What?
Why?
What's going on?
This machine is broken.
You fools!
Most home appliances have a high-voltage power.
You don't have to use electricity.
I took out the power of the refrigerator, microwave and washing machine.
I also took out the power of the computer.
Good.
It's working.
That's how you save money.
What?
It's still working.
I'll pump electricity in no time.
Okay.
Oh, good job team.
The electricère remains increasing at an intense rate.
It looks like theост power went into the starts.
I'm going to make the same mistake, Ren.
Are you ready?
Honda, hurry up.
Does that mean I'm going to start?
Of course.
Look, I made all the necessary modifications for you.
Am I a bike?
Get on the bike.
I understand.
I don't want to be in trouble.
You're doing great.
Don't be lazy.
I got it.
Both teams haven't lost.
The other teams are doing their best.
I'm tired.
I'm thirsty.
Wait!
What?
Look closely.
I'm saving up one drop at a time.
Why one drop at a time?
The water meter doesn't work.
I can drink it for free.
But it takes time.
That's right.
One cup is cheap.
Too sweet!
That one cup is the source of the collapse.
It's the same as a diet.
Food and drink.
Everything.
I'll take care of it.
Great!
I'm going to go and get some water.
He's serious.
It's going to be a hard life.
It's time for lunch.
Please buy what you need at the supermarket.
The money will be withdrawn from the electricity bill.
Oh!
The Terai team went shopping here.
There are so many children.
The time is too short.
I bought it.
My card is filled.
You're барbeque here.
Here.
Take everything.
All are yours.
You live in an uninhabited island.
Not saving.
More survival.
I'm thirsty.
I'm hungry.
Is there enough water?
Not yet.
Thank you.
What are you going to do? I can't take it anymore.
Me too.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to melt the river water.
Are you really going to drink that?
Well, just watch.
Here.
It looks like brown.
Don't worry. I drank it too, but it's nothing.
Don't do it with Ryo-chan's human-torn stomach.
Don't do it with Ryo-chan's stomach.
Senpai, please.
Please give me a glass of water.
I can't help it.
Just one glass.
Here, a glass of water.
It's night.
The meter is running to turn on the lights.
It's dark.
Just one light bulb is fine.
It's calmer when it's dark.
It's time for the bath.
Please get ready.
I put the water in a place with good sunlight.
As expected.
It won't take the electricity.
I don't like this kind of thing.
But it can't be helped.
It's only a small body.
That's right.
Do you know what?
"When could I find it?"
"I couldn't find it."
"Can it be vegetables?"
"Yes."
"What's with him?"
"I see him too."
"Walking".
I can't.
I'm exhausted.
She's done, haven't she?
This is not a bath.
And it's almost water, so it'll get cold.
Be patient.
The heat is used the most by electricity.
If you don't get into the mold, you're out.
I'm about to get in.
See, it's in the mold.
But the temperature of the hot water is quite low.
But it's not like that.
He likes warm water.
What about me?
You like it, don't you?
Good.
Good, isn't it?
You don't have any complaints?
The top is Sakonji Team.
The second place is Ryoto Team.
The match is in the early stages.
I'm looking forward to the future.
Where did Ryo-chan go?
Oh.
There was a water bottle.
Where is it?
I hid it somewhere.
I said, "If it's just us, I can't stand it. I'll drink it."
You're right.
I bought some food.
I'm going to eat it today.
It's a fish sausage.
Is it just one?
I bought it for you.
Do you have any complaints?
No, I think I overdo it.
Look at them.
They have more electricity than us.
They don't turn on the lights at night.
They live in the dark.
And they get food by hunting.
So they don't have to pay for food.
They just do it.
What is the hunt?
But that doesn't mean we have to win.
I don't need to worry about it.
I'll read it tonight.
Calm down.
What?
I don't want to do it anymore.
Wait, Konji.
I don't want to eat that anymore.
One more night.
Be patient.
Let me play a TV game.
It's no good.
The TV is too hard.
It's too hard.
Now, un desperate.
After all,
I can handle both Volvo and Jodi.
But I can't handle Sakonji.
I'll surpass them.
I'll quiet them down.
Will you still do it?
Then you should let me take a shower.
The bath is boiling,
but you can't get in.
Come on,
You can't go to such a mud dumper's bath.
Why can't I get in?
Defeating someone can't kill a human.
I don't think so.
You are growing wealthier.
It's starting to get exciting.
The tournament has finally begun.
It's time for the event.
All representatives of each team, please come to the stage.
It's time for the event?
Please draw a card one by one.
Oh, what's this?
What?
Komachi Team drew a card for the children to play.
What are you talking about?
Harui?
What's going on?
Show me the TV.
I think it's a game show.
If you do that, I'll turn on the light.
Stop it!
It's not fun to just play a game.
It's a game show.
I've added a little bit of fun to it.
It's like a life game.
Next team, please draw a card.
Huh?
Yeah.
What?
What's this?
Sakonji Team has drawn a check for the electricity store.
I'm sorry.
I came to check the electricity products.
Stop it!
Nothing is broken.
Katarin will check all the electrical products.
I'll check the electrical products.
I ate a lot of electricity.
In this event, the Sakonji team will drop the ranking at once.
If I can even find out what's in that card.
Huh?
What's wrong with that?
Is it a power cut?
Someone is looking for it.
...
Let's play it.
Hmm, I'll try it.
Damn it . . .
there is no work card . . .
Huh?
it's a lucky card?
I'm clout cheap.
I'll take this one.
Excuse us.
Then let's continue.
Let's continue. The card that Terai team drew is...
The card that the young group of Smobias is playing!
No, it's not!
It's a monster!
They made a lot of food in a hurry. This is a big damage.
No way...
Then, the next team...
Wait!
I'm...
This!
Finally, this card came out!
The card that the Ryotsu team drew is...
The Unlucky Card!
This is bad luck!
What? Unlucky?
It's true.
This is the worst card.
The Ryotsu team will be reduced to 100 yen for electricity.
What?
It was no big deal!
The cards are now back at the last minute!
This gives me a lot of effort.
Well, here I go.
Now for number 9.
What's up?
What are you doing?
Why is the power so low?
The power cable is being bitten by the mouse.
It's dead.
No way, are you sure a mouse will come out?
This has never happened before.
Why are you all safe?
It's suspicious.
I'm sure the mouse will come out.
I've been taking care of it.
Besides, I'm not the only one who's safe.
That's...
Even so, the top team is all in damage.
What are you going to do, president?
There's no evidence that you did it.
I have no choice but to continue.
I see.
I'll turn it over to myself.
Each team entered the final chase.
However, there is still time left.
No, it's useless.
The winner is mine.
I got the Golden Shoei House.
I'm at my limit.
What's wrong, Reiko?
I'm going to take a bath.
What?
Wait, Reiko!
Open the door, Reiko!
Oh, it feels good.
Stop!
The most electrical energy you can use is the heat energy.
What are you doing, Reiko?
I feel refreshed.
This is human life.
The fourth team, the electricity suddenly began to decline.
What is happening in the house now?
Damn, Honda~~~
No way, I'll handle you guys though.
The last race!
Both teams are going down in rank and have the highest score so far!
Who's going to win?
Damn, I can't lose like thisò
Five more seconds!
Power...
God, give me the power...
Senior!
This is my victory!
It's my victory!
It's terrifying to be called to the thunder.
What a great obsession.
Now, I will announce the winning team of the first SHOEI NE HOUSE tournament.
The winner is...
The Terai Team!
That's impossible!
I can't believe it.
It's my victory. I saw it.
All the counters were turned.
It's not a momentary victory. It's a failure.
No way!
I was just living a normal life.
You're usually so sad.
Damn it! What was my effort?
I can't believe I lost so easily.
I almost became Mihiroku!
But I lost too easily.
I might lose aettihnt in this match.
I won't lose.
I'm a dragon.
What's wrong?
I can't believe it.
You really want to lose?
I walked through the dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark
dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark,
I'm sure this is a wrong way of living!
If I become a dog, I'll enjoy my life as a goblack pet!
Next time, Ryo-san's dog life!
Don't miss it!
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!