As of now, Takumi is sleeping in front of the TV.
Where Is He Going?
When you watch TV, make the room more bright and stand away from the television.
Come over here, you poor fellow.
You're worried about me, though I'm not around.
I'm worried about you
Look at the blue sky
and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen
in the meantime
Come to me if you have no work
I'm worried about you
Look at the red clouds
and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen
in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, just be quiet
and follow me!
Super Kindergarten Lemon
It's just opened, but it's very popular
Even when it's not lunch time,
there's a line
Thank you for the food
It's our turn
What are you going to do?
I just got paid
It's been a while since I've been luxurious
It's Char Siu noodles
I will do the same
Two Char Siu noodles, please
Are you blind?
What?
Can't you see the wall?
Wall?
I only do ramen
Char Siu noodles are just a neck
Go away
What?
There's only ramen in the menu
You're pretty confident about the taste, aren't you?
Well, I guess so
What kind of taste?
I'm looking forward to it
Two ramen, please
Please
Wait a minute
We're guests
You should say that you're welcome
We're not selling service
We're selling taste
If you don't like it, you can leave
What?
Senpai, we're lined up
Please be patient until you eat
If it's bad, I'll pay for it for free
You're going to pay for it
Hey, you're risking your life for ramen
I have to do something
Don't hit me
You're a lame customer like me
Do you want to go home?
Hey, I'm full of hair
I'm full of cats
I'm going to quit the shop
What?
I'm going home
Senpai
Hey, roll the salt
Salt
This is the last one
I won't lose
I've worked hard to make it today
I woke up at 5 a.m. for this day
What?
What's wrong, Komachi?
You don't look good
No,it's nothing like that
I'm sure you didn't make it
No way
The roof is perfect
Ote
Shatori
Senpai, stop
You're making the ramen today
Thanks to you, I'm in a bad mood. I've been waiting.
Shut on down.
Let the king escape.
Hey, move.
Why do I have to move?
The one who takes this seat wins.
That's a reservation seat.
What? A reservation?
There's no restaurant here, so I'm not going to move.
Sorry for being late.
Reiko, I was booking this table, but Ryo's staff is in the way.
Don't call it a day.
We made a hand-made lunch.
Hand-made lunch?
I'm busy with work these days and can't cook well.
So we're going to make lunch once a month.
Today is the first time.
We were going to have a feast together.
It's a good idea for you.
Well, if that's the case, it can't be helped.
Sorry.
Come on, everyone.
Yes.
What's wrong, Matoi?
I forgot.
What?
I said something.
I don't have confidence, so I didn't forget on purpose.
Senior?
Don't say that.
As expected of Matoi.
Mr. Giboshi, a kindergarten teacher is visiting.
A kindergarten teacher?
Matoi, you.
What?
Are you okay, Senior?
I'm okay, too.
Lemon!
Matoi, do you know him?
He's my sister's lemon.
He's my sister?
Cute.
What's wrong, Lemon?
Oh, he came to deliver lunch.
Thank you, Lemon.
What's with that small thing?
It's my sister.
You didn't know?
No, I didn't say anything when I was training at Gepard.
Oh, he was studying abroad in France at that time.
What?
Studying abroad at this age?
Lemon is a taste genius.
He's a ten-year, no, a hundred-year-old taste owner.
That's amazing.
He was studying abroad to make her eat French food at Mito's restaurant.
What?
He went to France just for that?
What's he thinking?
Is he the worst Ryotsu Kankichi in the Ryotsu family you were talking about?
What?
Amazing.
He's not just a taste, but he's a genius at looking at people.
Shut up!
His face and way of speaking are vulgar.
Don't bother me.
How do you know how to use your mouth?
Is it the way of Gepard?
Do you think kindergarten children know my good points?
He was very shocked.
It's true.
Senpai, he's a kindergarten child.
Shut up!
I hate this kind of naughty kid the most.
Hey, Lemon, do you really know how to cook?
Interesting.
I was just about to have a cooking lunch.
Why don't you be my judge?
No, thanks.
Okay.
It's a game.
What's this?
Do you know how to cook?
A little.
You're a child who touches the can every day.
Hmm.
This is me.
Which is your turn this time?
Yes, it's me.
My victory is not moving.
It's your victory.
What?
You're a child after all.
I'm prepared to be a Honda driver.
How can I lose?
It's a simple crime of 33 steps.
33 steps?
Don't be stupid.
You're a professional if you can read that far.
I'm sorry.
You're surprisingly honest to admit it as a lie.
Children should be like that.
There was a simpler crime of 25 steps.
What?
Let's have this brat do it with 25 steps.
If you don't do it, I'll cut your ass 100 times.
Sekuhara.
Hmm.
What a naughty brat.
If you do it, what will Kankichi do?
Don't call me.
I'm a brat who's not in your mind.
What will you do?
I'll stand up and go around the library.
I'll do it.
But you can't call me that way.
It's okay if you say that again.
You won't do it.
And I won't call you anymore.
It's okay.
If you say I won't do it, I'll do it.
You guys are too annoying.
I'll tell you something.
There's no need to lie when you say this to me.
I don't want to die.
I can do it.
Come to think of it, my lunch box has the same contents.
Hey, Komachi, you just transferred it to the lunch box!
Really?
I didn't have time to sleep to make it.
It's so awkward.
Lemon, try my lunch box.
I'm hungry.
What's with this heavy feeling of tension?
It's just a play.
How was it?
It's a season for the
"Sayori" .
In this season, the "Mebaru" and "Kanpachi" are delicious.
What's with that old-fashioned way of talking?
I don't use such words.
That's it! That's it!
I'm using it!
Ryo-chan, you always watch old-fashioned dramas with your grandma.
Sometimes, you say strange things.
That's because of that old lady.
You're a child, but you know a lot.
Really?
How about the "Takenoko" stew?
I made it carefully using the best dashi of Oi-Gatsuo.
But it lacks the flavor of the sauce.
What's with that arrogant way of talking?
Well, well.
It's a "Shokado bento" of "Yadaman".
What?
I got caught!
What? You're a child, too?
That's a "Bento" of the top class.
I'll get caught if I do something bad.
Lemon, eat mine, too.
No, I know the winnings even if I don't eat.
What?
The appearance, the aroma, the nutrients and the calories that are needed.
The winnings are based on the overall balance.
Hehe.
I'm a child, after all.
I can't help but think that I'm the winner of my sister's bento.
I know.
I think Reiko's bento is the best no matter how you look at it.
What? Did Reiko also make it?
Well, it's better to have a lot of people like this.
Which one?
This is the "Bento" of the world!
It's true!
Foie gras and caviar truffles!
It's the most luxurious!
It's true that the ingredients alone are the best.
But it's not well-cooked.
If it's too well-cooked, you can't get the original flavor.
Even with caviar, you can't take it out of the can directly, so it's too salty.
You should add a little more.
You're a taste genius just by looking at it and tasting it!
You're amazing, Lemon-chan!
I-I'm a kindergarten child, but I'm not that amazing.
Oh, I've got a good idea!
Hey, Matoi!
Lend me an hour's worth of lemon!
What? Where are you taking me?
Well, whatever.
I'm sorry, but I'm going home.
I'm waiting for Sanpei.
Okay, I'll go talk to her!
Oh, there she is.
Oh, Ichiro-san!
Oh, no!
She's going back to kindergarten, so I have to contact her.
Okay, I'll talk to her!
Hey, Gepard!
What? You have a cold?
Shut up, don't make me a nuisance!
I'm going to get you a big piece of money!
I haven't got my ears yet!
What do you want?
I'll lend you an hour's worth of lemon.
Nice to meet you.
What?
What are you going to do with a big egg?
Well, see you.
You're still a rebellious old lady.
You can go home by the second floor.
Oh, ah...
Okay, here I go!
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll show you the taste of the ramen here.
Do you know the taste of ramen?
Of course, in the north, Asahikawa, Sapporo, in the south, Hakata, and Kumamoto,
ramen is also common.
So, stop talking like that.
You're a child, so you have to talk cuter.
"Grandpa is wonderful."
"I'll put ramen in it."
It's creepy.
It's not cute.
You again.
You came without a clue.
Don't get excited.
I don't have ramen to eat with you.
Get out of here.
This time I'll eat it.
So, please, stop being so cute.
I'm going to get out of here.
This is a present for you.
This lemon is not just a kindergarten nenji.
It's a kind of super kindergarten nenji, called " spear", so to speak.
It's shiny, so don't take it.
Don't talk so fast.
Rather, do you know the taste of ramen in your taste bud?
Just say so.
Hmm...
What's that?
Tonkotsu-sake.
It's made with long onions and ginger.
It's a secret ingredient.
What?
Right!
That's why I told you, right?
The lemon is the best.
If you know, make ramen right away.
Half ramen is fine.
Here you go.
Wait.
I'm so nervous.
I'm a child.
Oh, he's done the soup.
He's doing a good job.
Hmm...
How about the noodles?
The noodles are well-cooked.
Yeah, it's well-soaked in the soup.
You know the recipe, miss!
Is the chashu black pork from Kagoshima?
Yeah!
Both the cooking and the cooking are perfect.
You're so silly!
Our ramen is the best in Japan!
So, how's the lemon?
It's not bad.
Not bad?
It's a good taste, but it's not the best when you say it's the best in Japan.
What?
When I think that, the taste of this ramen has stopped.
The taste is something that you work hard every day and improve it.
If you think this is good, it's over.
Don't beat me like a kid!
To be specific,
The key point of this ramen is soy sauce.
Soy sauce?
Sorry, miss.
I used the soy sauce I made in Noda's factory.
It's not bad!
The soy sauce is good.
That's right.
But you can tell just by drinking the soup.
The president changed last year.
Until then, the soy sauce was 100% domestic.
Now, he uses 20% of foreign soy sauce.
There is no fresh soy sauce here.
The reason is that seasonings are not enough for all changes,
Is that true?
What a coincidence.
I can't do it yet.
Thank you for your help.
Yeah!
Lemon, you did a good job!
I've never been so depressed.
Lemon, you're the best.
Kankichi, you're too much of an adult.
When I'm happy and sad, I'm neither an adult nor a child.
The End
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Kankichi, welcome.
It's been a while, young lady.
Grandma was really worried about you.
Don't worry about her.
I'll take responsibility and return the lemon.
I'll take this.
What's wrong, Lemon?
Mom, I put it in here.
I don't have any lemon shoes.
Lemon shoes?
It's the shoes that the witch Remifanoe wrote.
Yeah, it was dirty.
I can't wear it anymore because it's too small.
So I threw it away.
It's terrible.
I've been taking care of it.
I was wearing those shoes when I went to the police.
I bought them for the first time with my salary.
Lemon...
You don't have to cry.
Oh, right. I'll buy you the same one.
I don't want to wear those shoes.
Don't say that.
Come here, Lemon.
Kankichi...
Kankichi?
Hey, don't bother me.
Lemon...
Where's the garbage dump?
Over there.
All right.
There's nothing here.
The garbage collector from earlier.
I'm sure it's him.
Kankichi...
It's okay. I'll definitely get it back.
There's a bike in this place.
Lemon, get on the back.
Put this on and hold on tight.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hey, Ichiro.
You have to hurry for the garbage dump to be easy to remove.
You need to stop.
Stop.
There's a lot of garbage.
Come on, Lemon! Don't cry!
We'll make it!
Hey!
Where is the Super-Squad's trash?
Oh, there it is.
Kankichi...
It's dangerous, so stay there!
What color are your shoes?
Pink. It's pink!
I got it! It's pink!
Here I go!
Pink! Pink!
Let go of me!
Pink!
Thank you, Kankichi.
Huh? What for?
Lemon's shoes.
What are you talking about?
You found them yourself, didn't you?
I just picked them up.
Hey, Gepard! What's that sword?
What's that?
I don't care!
Hey, Kankichi!
I'm going to pull your precious Lemon this far...
It's a misunderstanding!
What happened to my bicycle?
Oh, it's broken, so I left it at the garbage dump.
It might be in ruins by now.
What?
Hang in there.
Kankichi, the bicycle is a waste of garbage.
Is that so?
Thank you for the lemon.
No problem.
You didn't even talk to me!
It's a misunderstanding!
I'm going to pull your precious Lemon this far...
Hey, you're so annoying!
You're going to make me the sword of the Kaho's eyes and the hands of the Seki's grandson!
Grandma, you're wrong.
It's okay, Lemon.
It's dirty.
It's like a sport for them.
Grandma! Stop it!
Stop it!
You were so precious to me.
No, no, no, no!
Thank you.
Stop it!
I'm a healthy old woman!
Wait, Kankichi!
Bye, Lemon!
It was fun!
Thank you, Kankichi!
Bye-bye!
I've never seen Lemon laugh so brightly.
No, no, no!
Lemon, you can't fall in love with a man who's mistakenly married!
But it was fun with Kankichi.
Fun? Really?
Yeah.
Well, I'll forgive you for today.
Thanks, Grandma!
♪ I felt a strange feeling at that time ♪
♪ So I tried walking on the black tile of the arcade ♪
♪ I tried walking on the black tile of the arcade ♪
♪ Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgot ♪
♪ A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above his eyes ♪
♪ Turn around and see that corner ♪
♪ You can meet everyone ♪
♪ There is a turtle over there ♪
♪ There must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, come here ♪
♪ To our town ♪
Thank you!
Huh? Did the old man in Volvo open a ninja school?
Who is learning ninja now?
Wait a minute! If that will help the criminal arrest,
you should let him adopt it as one of the police's martial arts.
Next time, I will teach you ninja!
Thank you for watching!
Nin-nin!
♪ There is a wall over there ♪
♪ There must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!