Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea
and fly to the place where I left my love stone.
I was laughed at by the head of the gym who was jogging.
I'm so happy that I can't help but laugh at the sound of the sound.
Hey, are you eating yakitori?
From a
stormy downpour in a club that's hot,
the sunset on the extent of the sun sets.
I'm also LEDs tomorrow and it will end.
I lost happiness at the last minute.
The silly me who fell into my own trap.
Hey~
♪♪♪
Ryou Chikan Kichi
Yay! It took a month to finish!
The ship Nagata's original hand made plastic model is a very nice product!
It's like a war.
I worked for three days to finish it.
I'm at my limit.
Master, please be strong.
The time has finally come.
I have a long life.
One week left.
I have to decide who will be the successor of the Hondara sword.
Originally, my eldest son, Asato Ai, should be the successor.
But Ai was so sad that he betrayed Ryozu Kankichi.
And he lost the desire to be the successor of the Hondara sword.
But when I saw him,
I thought,
Ryozu Kankichi is quite good.
He might be the successor of the Hiden no Shio of the Hondara sword.
I want to confirm it with my own eyes.
Call back the Hondara Shitenno who is training.
Why Shitenno?
Is he the successor of the Hondara sword?
I will make Shitenno fight against Ryozu Kankichi.
But how?
I have a plan.
Listen to me.
What kind of...
Hondara sword?
Yes, sir.
Move.
I...
I have to hurry...
I just have to hurry...
Move!
What the...
I said...
What's this?
This is better than I thought.
22:25
Ryo-tsu Krankichi,
This Asato Ban willzeug your important life for the next plan.
If you want to return it, come to Hondarayama, my sacred land in Hondara prefecture, by 9:59 am.
His Excellency, the Emperor of the文在天кра, is there waiting to see you.
You may as well make your path!
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! G
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah!
I'll blow you up.
No!
Or I'll be modified in a strange way.
You idiot!
I won't let you do that!
Maria!
Lord Ryo!
Maria, help me!
Where?
Where's that mountain of Hon-daro?
Could it be that in Ryo-sama's innocent eyes, there's love for me?
Please, Maria!
Yes?
But why would you challenge the Four Heavenly Kings again?
I want to know!
Of course, it's a test.
A test?
What do you mean by a test?
My father is trying to challenge the Four Heavenly Kings to see if Lord Ryo is suitable for my husband.
But Maria, you look like a woman, but in reality you're a man!
No, whether you're a man or a woman, love is not enough!
Ouch!
Lord Ryo, please win for Maria's sake!
Please!
But they're all Maria-class athletes, right?
No enemy can train them.
There's a place called "Hikou".
If you go there, you'll win.
Hikou?
Senior, if this happens, we won't be able to play anymore!
That's right!
If you're a man, you have to be able to deal with Maria's love!
He's a man too!
It's too much!
Lord Ryo, please, give me your life!
Ouch! Ouch!
Oh!
Lord Ryo!
You idiot!
I was about to throw my life out here!
I'm sorry.
It was too much.
Anyway, let's go, Maria!
Yes, Lord Ryo!
Now, it's a holy land!
Now, it's dangerous!!
Yes, Lord Ryo!
I won't be able to live here anymore!
I can't go down on my own!
Guess I'll stay here.
Well, what do you think I'm talking about?
You were already named Lord Ryo this day.
But you're really the one who is the Lord of the Arche 대통령s.
Lord Ryo, you're my Lord?
Yes, you're my Lord.
I'm one of the Honjirashi Emperor, Chaplin the Traitor!
Chaplin is the Traitor, you know!
Ryo-sama, I'm here to--
Shut up! Maria, you stay back!
You're the one who took my plum!
I'm happy to hear that, Ryo-sama!
You're going to stand in front of me in my place, aren't you?
Come on, Traitor!
Let's go, Ryuu-tsu!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
What was that?
Is he really that strong?
Don't underestimate him. His special move is...
Here I go!
Goukyuu-ken!
Goukyuu-ken?
That was when I was in kindergarten.
I went out with the knot my mother held for me.
But... but that... that...
I...
I dropped it under my hand, like a knot.
That was when I was in elementary school.
I... I...
I stopped going to school because of the rain.
I left my backpack at school.
I spilled milk on my breakfast, and my mother made me a soda.
Sometimes, I wet my face with it.
I was in a dance school.
Sometimes, I didn't even have anyone hold my hand.
Sometimes, I even told people about what happened
when I heard the other person's phone number.
I... I...
What a sad thing I am.
I've been born to this unfortunate planet.
Amazing.
You were crying.
I wasn't crying!
I... I wasn't crying!
You're crying, aren't you?
Be careful, Ryo-sama! The Gou-Qun sword is coming!
My tears are on my face!
Let's go, Gou-Qun sword! The attack of the tears!
What a stone head!
If you take that one blow, even iron won't work!
I'm crying!
I'm scared!
Damn it! What should I do?
That's right! If you're going to cry and get stronger, you should make me laugh!
Gou-Qun sword, defeat!
Now, Ryo-sama! The Gou-Qun sword is coming!
Gou-Qun sword?
The Gou-Qun sword of the part that no human can train!
I see! That's it!
Impact! Gou-Qun sword!
What should I do?
This is my plan!
You did well, Ryo-sama!
I have to hurry! Otherwise, my Pramo will be...
My Pramo will be torn apart!
He's fighting for me, but he's hiding his shyness.
Pramo, Pramo, Pramo.
How cute, Ryo-sama!
The tragedy king has been defeated.
As expected of Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I've been waiting for you, Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
What is this? It's like a special unit.
One of the Hon-Darashi Emperor, the King of the Sword, Kankichi!
There used to be a manga with such a name.
No, no!
Mine is "The Sword of the Fist!"
Even though I'm a swordsman, I'm not good at using a hammer, a candle, or any other weapon!
No, Ryo-sama.
That hammer and the candle are used for different purposes.
No way!
Ouch!
Not yet!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
No problem!
It's dangerous to say that it's wrong!
By the way, what is his special move?
The sword of the sword is the skill of the sword of the sword.
After you hurt yourself and put up with it,
I'll explode your power at once.
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
It's coming! It's coming!
The power is overflowing!
See it! It's the Fist!
Oita Sword! A Sword of Love!
It's an amazing power!
That high-heel is made of metal, and weighs 100 km.
And if you increase the speed at which the waterfall falls,
any kind of metal will puncture the hole with one blow.
I can't believe this is happening.
Moreover, it has disappeared in the water of the waterfall.
I can't predict where it will come from.
It's so scary!
I think it's better to take it seriously.
I can't wait!
Ryo, now is the chance!
Make a飛行 that humans can never train!
Yeah!
Take this!
The captain's sword!
I'm trapped in the deepest part of the waterfall!
As expected of Ryo!
He read it all the way to the end!
If he wore a 100kg high heel,
he might never be able to come back up again!
The adventurer is also dead.
Yes.
The next morning.
If we get out of this grassland,
we'll only have to climb up the Ahondara Hill.
I've been waiting for you, Ryo Tsukankichi.
Don't be surprised to hear my name.
I'm pretty good at swords, though.
The one and only,
the third emperor, Dokaben!
As I thought!
Come on, come on!
My special move!
The baseball!
Let's try it!
Let's go, the thousand-sword sword!
You're pretty good.
But it's getting even worse!
Ryo-sama!
How is it?
Ryo-sama, stand up.
Please, stand up for Maria.
Damn you!
That was so good!
There isn't much left.
When it's over, that's when we win!
Damn you!
And there it is!
I won't forgive you for bullying Ryo anymore!
Ryo-sama, now is the time!
Don't make a habit of not being able to train humans!
I'm sorry, Maria!
Take this!
Emotion source!
Ai won again!
This is the true way to win!
We can become the ideal couple!
Let's hurry up, Maria!
At last, the last person remaining in the ground...
Promo! My Promo!
Ryo-sama, you've worked hard.
No, it's for Promo's sake!
You're hiding your shyness again and saying it's for Promo's sake.
Ryo-sama, I want to live in a house made of bricks with green grass when we get married.
Do you have any wishes, Ryo-sama?
If Promo and I are safe, anything is fine!
Of course, we'll prepare a room for you, Ryo-sama.
I'll be your good wife!
My Promo!
Maria!
I've been waiting for you, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I am the strongest of the Hondarashi Tensho!
The Hundred Beast King, Lion-maru!
This is the real thing!
That's right.
Maria, are you okay?
No, Maria has the power of Ryo-sama's love!
What's wrong, Ryo-tsu Kankichi? Come on!
Let's go, the Impact Tentacle!
What?
Huh? What's that?
Let's go, my Impact Killing Skill, Burning Serpent Sword!
W-W-W-What?
Oh, no!
Let's go!
Nooooooo-!
Lord Ryo!
Next is the last one, can you do what you want?
Ryan, the flight...
...that parts of human beings are not allowed to work can be a flight.
This will be the end, Ryotsu.
Impact!
"Roundeloo Sword"
"Zondara Sword láwardre"
"Shiriketsu Shiragatori"
I can't break out from that damsel blood wire!
Hmph.
Here I go.
"Burning ICS Sword"
- Master Ryo!
Lord Ryoma!
Good one, Mario!
Imitation Blast!
I-I won.
I did it!
It's the power of love!
I'm glad you came all the way here, Ryotsu Kankichi.
The last opponent is me.
Hey, you're carrying a plastic bag behind you!
Father?
Hey, my plastic bag!
Wait, Ryotsu. I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
I want you to give me the Hon-Dara sword.
No!
Don't worry about it.
What are you doing here?
Maria, my life is not long anymore.
What?
No way!
Don't be sad. This is fate.
Hey, give me the plastic bag!
I can't help it.
Alright, alright.
Ryotsu Kankichi, I acknowledge you as my Hon-Dara sword's true successor.
I'll give you this hidden sword.
Hey, give me the plastic bag!
What's wrong?
Ouch!
Father!
As expected of the man I've been waiting for.
I'll give you the Hon-Dara sword.
Father!
I will be happy with you!
Please watch over me in heaven!
What is this?
A needle?
What?
Huh?
The pain which I felt while sawing
Oh, yeah.
I'm great!
I'm super great!
What do you mean "great"?
No!
I'm premium...
I'm Pramon!
You're fine!
With the power of our love, this is a happy ending!
I'm fine!
You're my Pramon!
Let's go!
You always wear sandals, always have scandals, don't worry about it!
Don't worry about it!
You play with your toenails, everyday!
Everyday!
You throw away your boredom in the cleaning room!
You have a round-out instinct, a round-out instinct, you're an idiot!
I'm an idiot!
You're innocent, you're poor, you're not good!
You're not?
I try to do what I want to do, and that's a good way!
The lightning of the leader of the catapults, smoke from the head!
When I run and run, there's asole!
If that's the case, I'm happy!
I have a flower port!
"Good job!"
Soililled medium土!
"Good luck!"
I can breathe freely!
I'm a F xiäl!
Juge! Juge!
Your mind is run out, just like the Atlas of the Sea!
Before the sea!
Lao Miao
Piglet
Damm
I got a tuna!
And it's a 1,500,000 yen tuna!
If you keep fishing like this, you can catch a lot of fish.
Come on, tuna.
Let's fight with the man of the sea, Ryo Tsukanrishi.
Next time, "The Police on the Tuna".
Thank you for watching.
There is a turtle there.
There must be a turtle there.
Everyone, come to our town.
Thank you.
Next time, "The Police on the Tuna".