назыв Brian
When you're watching TV
Try to look in the room, and make it look like you're separated
So I walked around the Akegogai's dial only in black
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle, there must be a turtle
Come on everyone
Let's go to our town
Thank you!
Chase the turtle!
I'm sorry to make a fuss in the world this time
I'm not making a fuss
I am the person who will take responsibility for this injustice and resign
Let me do it
I will do it
But it's not a big deal
I will take the responsibility of the injustice caused by my subordinates and resign
If something happens, I have to take responsibility
Especially I am worried about one person
Drift car!
Bad bad! It's an accident!
Accident!
I'm worried about it
But I don't have to be so
Well, I am sorry
Please forgive me
You guys are so funny
You are at a loss
So he's a good doctor
You have to return this to me
No
It was just a turtle
I see
Hey, if you are in charge, stop then
Yes, recently my hair is getting thinner and my legs are getting swollen.
I'm not asking about your worries.
I'm asking about my subordinates' worries.
Ah, that's...
It's too late to cause a problem.
Also, people who cause problems are often in debt or are busy with money.
Debt?
Or they are obsessed with gambling.
Gambling?
You know, Ohara?
Hehehehehehe...
If your subordinates have such a mind,
then they will definitely start everything, no matter what.
You know that, Ohara?
Ah, yes.
General Ohara, I'll do whatever you want.
Your old school design is going to be a big hit.
Ah, yes!
Ah, good morning, director.
Good morning.
Oh, isn't Ryo-tsu here?
Ryo-san is patrolling.
I see.
By the way, have you changed anything about Ryo-tsu recently?
Changed?
I don't know.
Anything is fine!
Any little thing is fine!
Just tell me!
Hmm, I see.
That's right.
If it's you, then...
What's wrong?
What happened?
They said I'm in debt.
I'm in trouble with my money.
What about Ryo-chan?
Ah...
I was really frustrated to lose the game again.
A gamble?
Hmm, Ryo-san...
He was running around from the plastic shop with a cane.
Even the money...
Ah, no!
The police pattern that causes irreversible problems, as the director said, has already begun!
But that's the usual Ryo-chan.
That's right.
That's why I can't be at ease!
What's wrong, director?
You're in a lot of trouble today.
Shut up!
Do you understand how I feel?
Have you noticed anything else?
Anything else?
Ah!
What?
By the way, yesterday, Ryo-chan...
Ah!
Damn, my head hurts!
Sen...
Senpai's head hurts?
I've never heard of it.
Ryo-tsu's head hurts?
I've never heard of it in ten years.
Yesterday, huh?
Come to think of it, he looked so depressed...
I told him, "Alright, I'll do it."
We have no choice but to do it.
I heard that, too.
Ah!
Ah, good morning, director.
Huh?
Ah...
Ryo-chan, where's your bicycle?
Ah, it's broken, so I had to repair it.
Ah, it hurts, hurts, hurts.
Ah...
Ryo-tsu...
Ah, it's true, director.
I didn't take it to Chia.
You're being so impulsive.
You're hiding something.
No, that's fine.
Anyway, Ryo-tsu...
Ryo-tsu?
Don't you have something to tell me?
You're not here, are you?
Huh?
I-I don't have anything.
I knew you had something.
But I'm not angry here...
Yeah, I have to go on patrol.
Then, I'll patrol a bit.
Hey, Nakagawa.
I'll be waiting for Ryo-tsu.
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll...
I'll just go to the station...
And then you'll be waiting for Ryo-tsu?
Well, this is a difficult mission.
I'll be waiting for you.
Now I'm going to the station.
I'm going.
OK, I'm going.
Don't worry.
Stop.
"Is it anyone?"
Why does he change the engine at this point"
"He got in somewhere"
"He was loaded in a plate"
"He's about to borrow the money"
"He's out of the car!"
Huh?
I couldn't borrow it at that time
But now I know he's in trouble
Damn it
Oh no, hide in the back
Hide in the back
So that car is the Mazda R360
I miss it
It's the Countach
This is the tubular space structure
Amazing
It's a 12 cylinder DOHC 48 valve
You have a nice car
Thank you
Drive safely
Why are they two men
in the car all naked
Don't get involved
Nakagawa, you're an idiot
You too, chief
Oh no, I haven't paid the debt
I haven't paid it yet
It was like Ryo
They ran into the alley
Let's chase them
What?
They're chasing us in the Countach?
They're trying to lure us in
I see
Running
So fast
"Takoyaki"
Are you there?
Yes.
I found you.
If you go forward, you won't be found.
I'm fine.
I'm a guard.
That's true.
I'll tell Takoyaki's brother.
What the hell is this!
Oh my god!
What's wrong?
He's making money.
What a guy!
Don't tell me he's really that...
I can't hold my hands anymore.
I should have called him.
I feel sorry for him.
I can see his future.
I'll be back.
Hey!
What's that car?
Is it a car?
Are you throwing it away?
It's dirty.
You have to call the police station.
Chief, what's this building?
It's a junkyard with a problem.
I didn't know you were here.
What's that?
No.
There's a restaurant named "Ohara" over there.
It's a coincidence.
It's called "Ohara."
The restaurant is on the way.
I know.
There's a restaurant called "Ohara" over there too.
No.
I know it.
I know.
It's a place called "Ohara."
This place is called "Ohara."
This restaurant is called "Ohara."
It's "Ohara."
This place is called "Ohara."
I don't know.
The End
Ryozu!!
Chief!!
What's wrong in this place!?
Ryozu!!
Don't tell me that you have something to tell me!?
What!?
Oh, dear.
I went to my previous manager's house and I broke the dining table,
And I got caught!
I-It's no big deal!
You're hiding something, after all.
But I can't get angry here.
Well, let's not talk about it here.
Let's go somewhere quiet.
You know, Ryotsu,
humans have something they can't tell others.
I knew it.
And if you're regretting your actions,
it's even worse.
Worse?
But no matter how well you try to fool me,
you'll find out eventually.
I see, I'm in trouble.
I knew it.
At first, you were just a little curious.
That's right.
I started to get curious,
and then I started to escalate...
It's too late when you thought you were done.
I thought I was done, too!
Why didn't you tell me?
I thought you'd get scolded by the chief.
Is that so?
Even if I did scold you,
I think about you,
and I'm scolding you with my heart.
Then you'll forgive me?
I won't forgive you,
because I'm responsible for what I did.
I'm glad.
I'm relieved if the chief says so.
In this situation,
it seems that you were able to stop yourself
from stepping into the path of evil.
All right,
let's go.
Let's think about it.
Huh?
Ryo-tsu.
I've always been thinking about you.
Chief!
So let's talk a little more
about each other's future.
Future? Chief?
Ryo-tsu!
Wait a minute, chief.
What a beautiful sky, Ryo-tsu.
Huh?
Ryo-tsu.
I have a family.
What do you want to say?
I can't say that's enough,
but I'll do as much as I can.
I'm responsible for you being alone.
What?
If you think about it,
we're destined to be together for a long time.
It's a natural relationship between a married couple.
There's nothing to hide from now on.
Wait a minute.
We're not that kind of relationship.
No, I can tell from your eyes.
Even if you're silent,
your feelings will be conveyed to me.
Excuse me.
Ryo-tsu.
I'm not kidding.
I didn't know the chief had such a hobby.
You can't throw away your car here.
I didn't throw it away.
It's parked.
I don't like Maria.
I don't like the chief.
Why do I always get attacked by men?
Why can't I be popular with women?
Even though he's such a good man.
You're such a bad man.
You can't be too hasty.
Ryo-tsu, listen to me.
I'm done talking to the chief.
Where are you going?
The bank.
What does the bank have to do with it?
It's just a coin.
What else do you have?
The bank.
That's why I told you to stop.
I told you to consult with me about anything.
I'm an adult, too.
It seems that the relationship between adults and men is...
I can't keep up with the chief anymore.
Ryo-tsu.
Chief.
Hurry up.
Ryo-tsu is going to attack the bank.
Ryo-tsu.
If you don't hurry up, the bank will close.
Chief.
I'm begging you. Let me go, Chief.
Think about it, Ryo-tsu.
It's not your fault.
I was the one who couldn't go.
It has nothing to do with the chief.
You don't have to listen to me.
Of course.
I don't want to say no.
Okay.
Then I'm prepared.
If you have to, you have to defeat me.
Chief.
Ryo-tsu.
Jump into my chest.
It was a close call.
Ryo-tsu.
Chief.
I'm sorry, chief.
I'm sorry.
It's a big deal.
Why are you so late.
I've been investigating the ground.
Please let me talk to him.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Ryo-tsu, can you hear me?
-I'm Ohara. -Nigiri.
It's the chief again. You're too persistent.
Ryo-tsu, do you remember when you first met me?
You were still in high school.
You just got out of the school.
When you became a police officer and your mother said hello to you,
I remember it clearly as if it was yesterday.
What is this?
You can still make it in time.
With the power of my love, I will make you a great man.
Your mother must be crying when she sees you now.
Mother made a hot pot and a glove.
Why?
Why did you sing your mother's song?
It's cold when the wind blows.
It's cold and cold.
The home's message is coming.
I can smell the scent of the fire.
Ryo-tsu, come back to me.
I don't know what's going on.
But I can't answer the chief's love.
It's over, Ohara.
I have no choice.
Let's get in.
What?
I've been arrested.
I've been robbed of 300,000 yen monthly.
No, that's mine.
Shut up, it's the bank.
The bank?
Ryo-tsu.
Ryo-chan.
I'm sorry, senior.
Ryo-san, I'll buy you a rice ball.
Hey, wait a minute.
What do I have to do?
Hey, let me go.
Ryo-san.
Thank you, Ryo-san.
Ryo-san talked to the real estate agent.
That child's playground has become what it is now.
Now we can play soccer again.
By the way, Ryo-san, what's wrong?
It's not like that.
He was robbed by the bank before he could understand.
What?
The child's playground?
He was about to be robbed?
Well, what does the Katsuage real estate company mean?
What's going on, Ohara-kun?
Well, he's not a bank robber.
That's why I'm telling you he's not.
I've checked the cash handling function record.
What's the problem?
I found that the 300,000 yen he had was the one that took out his salary.
Hey, look!
Ohara-kun...
That was yesterday.
As usual, he was taking a nap in the public bathhouse on the way to the patrol.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
That's why his head hurt.
Yeah.
What did you think it was?
Well, I heard the children would have no playground, so I was in trouble.
So I decided to get rid of it.
On the way, I got a part-time job from the takoyaki place where I did the show last time.
You got a part-time job?
What did you think?
No.
Then I took the shortcut and passed through the Sarakin building and went to the house of the landowner.
The shortcut?
Is that so?
And then I made a promise to the landowner to let the children go as usual.
No, he was a father who knew what he was talking about, so he was very kind to me.
Then I took the shortcut again,
and I went to the town to talk to him.
K-Kuroi Kousai...
What?
No...
Then it was easy.
I went to the bank in a light mood.
Well, the line is clear.
That's right.
Oh, Hanako, my apologies.
Well, well, well, well.
Everything was done quickly by the headmaster.
Nakagawa, you...
Hey, it's Sussi-sen!
Cheers, as usual, the three of you!
Hey, good work, good work!
You were in charge of the subject.
Good work!
Come on!
Experiment 1.5 million yen, violation!
With treatment!
I hate it if the criminal is mistaken, my heart is beating fast.
It's a problem.
I'm stuck on the table.
How can I heal this wound?
I got it.
I should pay for it.
But I think there's something wrong.
By the way, Ryotsu.
When I first called out,
why were you nervous?
Yes, this is the exit before the park.
Director, it's from your wife.
It's me.
What?
Imari's plate is broken.
After sticking it with adhesive.
By the way, last time, Ryotsu came to my house.
Ryotsu!
After all, it's your fault.
I'm sorry.
It's because your usual behavior is bad.
Be more serious.
I'm sorry.
Awakening Watch
My little finger is a heart.
Drawing eyebrows for now.
Dash to the station.
Main train
One eye on my father's back.
This week as well.
Work hard.
Till the farewell.
I'm holding a racket in one hand.
♪ I'm holding it in my hands, but it's a hot and cold day ♪
♪ I hate the continued annoyance of working overtime ♪
♪ I love to solve it ♪
♪ Every day is a no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is flying on Monday ♪
Good evening, I'm Shoji Murakami.
Stop it, right hand, left hand, both hands!
Welcome, where are you?
You pervert! Stop!
Stop calling me dad!
What are you saying?
Hayami!
What's that?
Boom!
Next time, Ryo will be in the election!
Please look forward to it!
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ There must be a wall ♪
♪ Everyone come to our town ♪
Thank you!