Hinoji prefecture
What's That low-quality kid doing?
Low-quality kid?
When you're watching TV,
Make the room a bit lighter and look away
Zebra
B occasion
Zeg
Those who are worth nothing, come to me
Come!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen
Tomorrow I know it will be alright
People without jobs, come to my place
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look, everything's on fire
The first welcome party in Tokyo
♪ Akanegumo ♪
♪ Sono uchi nantokanaru darou ♪
♪ Wakatteru ne? Wakatteru wakatteru? ♪
♪ Wakattara damatte ore ni suite koi! ♪
Today's Doggy
Yes, today's report is from a doggy-only sauna!
Wow, they seem to be relaxed and comfortable!
Well then, let's hear their impressions.
Buddy-chan, how do you feel?
It seems very good!
Even though it's a dog, it's a sauna?
After this, this Buddy-chan will be
cleaning up with this dog-only estee,
then having a luxurious meal at a dog-only restaurant,
and then staying at a dog-only hotel for the night!
What did you say?
How is it? Aren't you jealous?
Of course I am!
Senpai, don't get too excited!
Well, can I be this luxurious just because I'm a dog?
I'm not a dog, I'm a family!
As the owner of a pet, I'm a family!
I'm going to Hawaii with my Seara tomorrow!
You're going to Hawaii, even though you're a dog?
Yes, I'm going to participate in the dog contest held there!
Seara is the winning candidate!
Can a dog take an airplane?
The number of services that invite customers is increasing!
Our airline company also has a pet!
Oh, me too!
Ryo's bathtub is broken,
and in this cold weather the dog has to stay in his yard a lot!
Oww! So cold!
The dog had already made a ferocious outing.
And he hasn't eaten with the dog for years!
Dogs do have a better life!
I pity my dog!
That's because Ryo-chan is bad.
Senpai can't argue with that.
What a cold word.
She said she's better off living with a dog than me.
Hm? I see.
Then...
That's right, Reiko.
Bring Seara with you before you go out tomorrow.
Sure.
I'm going to meet Komachi-chan and the others here anyway.
What?
Are you going with that noisy girl?
Yes. What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Ryo-san's Dog Life
Good morning.
Hey, you're getting bigger again.
Good, good.
You're really good to Senpai.
That's right.
Ryo-chan is a face that animals like.
You're right.
Let's go for a walk.
All right.
Have a good day.
Okay, Seara.
Let's go.
It's about time.
Oh, here he is.
Hey!
Hi, Ryo-san.
I'm sorry, Borubo and Jody.
All right, Seara.
I'll be back in two weeks.
Take care of Jody.
LAUREN
What are you doing with a dog?
I just wanted to surprise Reiko.
But it's only been a couple of weeks.
Jody, it's bad for you if Americans pay attention to the details.
Now I'm gonna change my clothes.
Come on, get change.
Tch, tch, tch!
Hmm...
Ryotsu, are you really going to do it?
Of course! The dogs are living a better life than me.
I want to live like a dog!
I'll eat some high-quality food and relax in Hawaii.
Okay!
Good! You really look like a dog!
I wonder if I can trick them well.
Don't worry! My acting skills are like an academician.
Ah, but your eyes are weird.
I'll borrow some.
Okay, this is fine.
Well, I'm counting on you.
Okay!
Reiko-san, sorry to keep you waiting!
Hey, welcome.
Huh? Where's Seara?
Ryo-chan's taking her for a walk.
Mwah! Mwah!
Oh, she's back.
Huh? Morubo-san, where's Senpai?
I-I'm just meeting with Ryotsu over there.
I was asked to take care of this dog because I got a job.
What? You're irresponsible.
I don't have any sense of responsibility.
I'm the king of irresponsibility.
Well, you're Senpai after all.
Hey, you guys, remember this later, okay?
Seara, what happened to your sunglasses?
That's because...
Ryo-chan said that the weather in Hawaii is pretty bad, so I have to wear them.
Ryo-chan did?
Oh, Ryo-chan and Kanchi have a lot of good things.
Ah, Seara seems to like them, too.
Okay, nice follow, Morubo.
Ah, ah...
You look good in sunglasses.
You're cute.
Amazing.
It's my first time in the first class.
I finally got sucked in as a dog.
It's a complicated feeling.
I'm not sure if it's my mood, but the stewardess is pretty.
But...
Look, look! The ship looks so small.
It really looks like a toy.
It's a scratch sometimes when the two are noisy.
Yes.
Are you surprised? That dog can shed blood.
No way.
It's true.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes.
It's true.
Oh, it's a ship.
It's a ship.
What are you doing?
It's kind of a It's kind of an
don't you think so?
Yeah, that probably is.
I can't wait till I get there.
Y saburjya
y saburjya
Wow!
This is our room.
Amazing!
Gorgeous!
I did it! I should do it like this.
Are you tired?
I'm not!
I want to swim!
Okay, let's change!
Let's change!
This is an unexpected showtime.
'Spring Day ' It
's the ocean! You
look near happy. It
's your 5th visit in Hawaii and you want to see it for the first time? Absolutely
awesome! I
never imagined that I would still be able to visit Hawaii for free. Enjoy
your home life! It
's great. There
's a sea.
He's back swimming!
That's your dog, Reiko!
When did he learn how to back swim?
Huh? Is that a dog surfing?
You bastard! You can't stand up!
Leave it to me!
This is surfing, right?
Yeah! It's surfing!
Look! It's a pipeline!
Seara, he's surfing!
You're kidding, right?
Don't be surprised by his surfing skills.
I'm better at it.
Go! Go!
Come on! First spin in space!
This is how you ride a jet!
Seara is so active!
He's like someone's partner.
There are so many interviews coming in!
It's rare to see a jet ski.
What! What! What are you doing?
You're taking a lot of interviews!
I can't believe it!
What? What?
What is this?
What?
Are you looking for food, Lainu?
I'm not like you guys.
It's not the same as the other one.
Golf is also a great skill.
I've never taught it.
This is the life of a rich dog.
This is the rich life I wanted.
The sun is full.
I'm tired of eating steak.
I want to eat something refreshing.
Do you want to eat Japanese food?
I did it!
Japanese food.
It's delicious.
Japanese food is Japanese food.
Yakitori and sashimi are delicious.
Natto and stew are delicious.
Beer at the end.
It works.
I fell asleep.
It looks like my dad.
I want to pee in the beer.
I was wearing a costume.
*Sigh*
Let's go to the bathroom and pee properly.
W-what?
What's wrong, Reiko?
Seara's acting weird!
Seara?
Her hair's all messy!
Oh no!
What's going to happen to the contest?
Seara!
What? It's not working at all!
It's true.
I'm so glad.
Don't scare me, Reiko.
I'm sorry. I think I got it wrong.
That was close. I was careless.
Anyway, good night, Seara.
Good night.
Grrr!
So heavy!
Gah!
Seara, did you get fat?
Yes, I did.
I only ate after I came here.
It was a contest after all.
Seara, you're on a diet starting tomorrow.
You can't be spoiled.
You can't even cry.
Hey, hey, what's wrong with you?
Your legs are heavy.
You just started running again.
If you say that, it's hard to run in this school.
Get out of that place.
That's right, that's right.
I can't do it.
What's wrong with you?
It seems impossible to win this.
If you win, you can get 100,000 dollars.
If I win, I get 100,000 dollars?
If I win, I get 100,000 dollars.
Sarah suddenly got excited.
When I asked her for 100,000 dollars, she changed her dog.
No way.
Sarah.
Come here.
Master wants to see you.
Sarah was good at standing on the slope.
Standing on the slope.
Come on, hurry up.
It's that easy.
If you get caught here, you'll get 100,000 dollars.
And then, the moon came in.
That's right, don't worry.
How I am very excited.
I'll show you.
You surprised yourself like this.
That will be the瞬間.
I was excited to beat you.
I want to run.
I'm not scared.
I want to win.
The next morning
Reiko-san, I'm so sorry. I was just about to ask Bobby.
I'm keeping the Seara at my place so don't worry.
See you later.
How was it, Reiko-san?
I knew it. The Seara was at Jody-san's place.
So that gorilla man really was trying to get rid of the Seara?
Unforgivable!
I'll get rid of it for you.
How?
Actually, tomorrow.
Huh? It's not here?
Is there anyone in there?
I think so.
That guy is such a tough guy...
I've been waiting for you for so long.
It's time for the century-long dog contest.
The true heroes of Kano-ku,
Who will win?
It's finally starting!
Ready, go!
The first round is
Super Tokumori Dog Food's
Fast Food Competition!
Dog food, cat food
It's like an egg!
100,000 dollars!
He's eating dog food!
And it looks delicious!
The top is
22nd Seara
18th Liger
50th Thunder Devil
What's the next event?
Sit on a chair
and spin!
Go!
He's trying to balance
Can he cross the bridge?
Next is
360 degree spin
It's like a rain shower
Tommy's trap
He's slow
But he's fast
Punching Glove
He's fast
22nd Seara
He's finished
And he's
facing off
Amazing
He's moving more than dogs
He believes he'll win
100,000 dollars
Ryo's desire is his motivation
Next is
Diving from a cliff
300 meters high
Climbing a cliff
And getting a treasure box
It's super difficult
He's going to lose
His pride
He's a true
The other dogs are also following!
I wonder if they can keep breathing at 300 meters.
Dogs other than Seara failed to land.
They are falling out of the water here!
My breath is getting harder.
Oh, there it is.
I have to hurry.
I can't do this anymore.
What's wrong, Seara?
They are not coming out.
I wonder if they were unable to land at 300 meters or 600 meters.
It's Seara!
This dog is different!
It seems that the diver who was close to her stole the regulator.
I don't know.
In that sense, it's a great dog!
Can dogs do this?
Oh, I can see it!
The last hero who has overcome numerous trials and is running towards the glory of glory!
Now, please give your warm applause and go!
I won!
I can't believe it!
Now, Seara, the winner is waiting for a wonderful gift!
Seara, are you ready?
Yes!
I got 100,000 dollars!
You are amazing, Ryo-chan!
Stronger than a dog!
As expected of Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
How was it?
Did you know about me?
Congratulations!
Congratulations on winning!
You were chosen as the world's first famous dog.
Please go
By, by, by, by...
Ah, I can walk!
Ryo-chan, stay healthy!
See you next time!
Bye-bye!
ute
You're home
Good boy
Yeah, she's a very good girl.
She's better than my Bobby.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
By the way, I don't think you can see Ryo-san.
Ahaha, Ryo-chan is currently on vacation on the Meiyo Line.
Eh?
But, is Ryo-chan okay?
She's okay, if she's a gorilla man.
That's right. Ryo-chan is okay, isn't she?
Is it okay, if she's a gorilla man?
Hurry and return her to Earth!
♪ After the rain, like someone calling me ♩
♪ I walked, looking back ♩
♪ I held my mother's hand ♩
♪ That's when I felt that strange feeling ♩
♪ That's why, I walked on the Ake-dogai's dial ♩
♪ Just a black spot ♩
♪ Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten ♩
♪ But ♩
♪ A politician with a strange face ♩
♪ And an old lady with a blue eye ♩
♪ Turn around and look at that corner ♩
♪ You'll meet everyone ♩
♪ There's a turtle over there ♩
♪ There must be a turtle ♩
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♩
♪ To that town ♩
♪ Thank you! ♩
When I was a child, there weren't many tall buildings,
and the chimney of the town was very high.
But this is a story of how I met the artist's sister and the memory we have.
Next time, "Sentou Emaki in the Down Town"
Thanks for watching!
Subtitles by: Tanya Duarte www.tanyaduarte.com