"When watching TV"
When watching TV
Make the room brighter and look away
"When watching TV"
Looking at the sunset floating in the river
If you kick the love stone, you'll fly to the shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym where I was saving money
I was laughed at as it was
From the fountain of the Tungari hat to the taishakuten
The sunset falls
And it ends like this
I was happy again
Because I'm an idiot
"Ryotsu"
He has no motor nerve, so it won't work even if he's coached.
Then only Ryotsu is left, right?
But...
Ryotsu has a better motor nerve than others.
If he's coached and improved, the head coach will be happy.
Oh...
Anyway, be careful not to lose your ability on the day.
What?
He's been worse than us since he was coached.
Oh...
Don't let him beat you, even if you make a mistake.
Tell Ryotsu to be careful.
Oh, okay.
I'm already in pain.
What? He took a golf with the boss?
He took a golf with the boss?
You're kidding, Ryo.
There's no reason to refuse.
Ryo, who hated golf in the book, said that he was more of a jester than a jester.
He came to pick me up by car.
He was a bonus.
He said he'd feed me.
This is a chance to get some nutrition.
But, senpai, you've never played golf, have you?
Don't underestimate me.
The other day, I had a par 72 course and a hole in one twice.
I was 24 under.
24 under?
I've never heard of a pro golfer who scored such a high score.
St. Andrews in the All-Star Open and Augusta in the Masters.
I did only a few courses.
18 under was the best score.
However, even if I had played, I'd have been an upstart.
When did you go to England or the United States?
Oh! I've got it, senpai!
That's a video game, right?
Yes.
That's our golf software.
What? You make me feel a bit nervous.
Ryo just has a different style to playing games and real golf.
You wouldn't think that.
I've got the power to be Tiger Woods.
Golf is the smallest sport in my life.
Rather than a tiger, you've got the power to be a gorilla.
What?
Who said "Gorilla"?
Huh? I heard a lot of bad gossip.
Oh, what about the club? You don't have one, do you?
Oh, right. I was thinking of lending it to you.
I have a lot of them.
Of course. I'll bring them tomorrow.
No! You can't have them!
Oh, good morning, chief!
Oh, why can't I go to my club?
How much is your golf set?
Well, they're all premium, so I think it's about 10 million yen.
10 million yen?
That's why you can't have them!
It's not good to use a club that's more expensive than the chief's.
I'll lend you a set I bought for 30,000 yen 15 years ago.
Use it.
What?
And as I said yesterday, I don't want the chief to tell you, so listen to me.
Don't buy it by mistake.
If you're in trouble, I'll send you to the end of the world.
What?
I don't want to play golf with you,
but I want to play golf with you.
I have 99% of the time on my mind.
Ryo, you're in trouble.
It's good that you don't have me.
Hey, how long are you going to sleep?
I'm here. Take your luggage.
I've never woke up this early since the school festival.
Why does he wake up so early?
Good morning.
Head of Kobashi.
I've been waiting for you.
I thought that the meeting will be at 7 o'clock.
I thought it was a little late.
No, I woke up early when I thought it was golf.
I got here at 3:00 in the morning.
It's the same as the time when I was a child.
Hey, do you want to say hello?
Thank you.
I'm Ryotsu, a subordinate.
Golf is the first time today.
Please take care of me.
Oh, is it your debut match?
Well, don't get stiff.
I'll give you advice, so don't worry.
Yeah.
Please take care of me.
Okay, I want one minute.
Let's get started.
Nice shot!
It didn't fly a little.
No, no, it's wonderful.
It's in the middle of the field.
It's a beautiful shot that flies straight.
I'm sorry.
The ball is the head of the club.
The ball is beautiful.
It's artistic.
I see.
You're not going to fly if you dress up.
Well, I'll fly next.
I hope I can fly well.
I know.
Oh, no.
I'm not good at this.
You look too down.
I need to look at the ball well.
Hmm, I see, I see.
Well, as expected of the director, his advice will be useful.
Well, you can really use a great trainer like that.
Hey, ¿ précédente, what are you doing?
It's your turn.
Yes, yes.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're doing worse than the director.
Try to recalculate yourself.
Yes, yes, I know the end of the story.
I know.
This is the first time I've played golf.
You're not playing golf.
This is how you grip.
Is that so?
You're putting too much effort into it.
You need to grip it more lightly.
Lightly, lightly, lightly.
That's right.
Good job, Ryouchi.
Look, twist your hips more.
Stretch your left elbow.
Don't put your feet on your back.
Swing here.
Imagine you're making a wall on the left side.
A wall, right?
Then practice the swing again.
A wall on the left side.
What are you doing?
I'm making a wall on the left side.
What do you think?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm telling you to make a wall on the left side.
Then you should say it more clearly.
This is bad.
Ryouchi, you're being rude to the head of the club.
No.
The head of the club's advice is great,
but he can't understand it because it's a simple thing.
I see.
I'm telling you.
Finish it quickly, eat something good and go home.
Ready?
That's why I told you.
Swing more.
Pull your hips.
Swing down as if you're drawing a circle.
You're so noisy.
Do it like this.
Like a circle.
How was that?
You're not flying at all.
I'm not doing it like you say.
Good job.
You're doing great, Ryouchi.
I did it as the head of the club told me to,
but I can't fly at all.
You idiot.
You can hear me, right?
You have to do it like that.
I got it.
It's a bit of a hassle to put it on the green from here.
I'll give you some advice.
I'm going to shoot it in here.
Here, from the gap in the tree.
Don't tell me you're trying to get out of the way.
You have to put it on the fairway from the side.
No, but this is...
Damn it.
If I don't get the head of the club's advice,
my score will get worse.
But I have to get out of the way here.
Isn't that Norika Fujiwara?
What?
Damn it.
Damn it!
Head of the club!
Ryouchi!
I did it as the head of the club told me to,
but I'm not good at it.
Horrible.
You're not getting any better this time.
Yes.
The banker is here this time.
Head of the club,
how can we shoot like this?
You're right.
That's right. Watch me do it.
Hey, Chief! I've been waiting for you!
I'd like to see your hand.
You have to set the right foot for this.
That was a bad shot.
Chief, this is a bad situation.
Chief, I forgot that I wasn't good at bunkers.
What's going on?
I'll show you what I can do.
Chief, you're bleeding.
You can't do anything.
Take a deep breath.
Shut up!
Do you want to give me advice?
Chief, don't mind him.
Do it at your own pace.
Damn it.
You idiot.
What should I say?
He said he'd lose if he got blood.
How cheeky.
Oh, nice out.
Chief, you're really good.
I see.
In short, you just need to pull the sand as hard as you can.
All right.
I got on.
What?
Isn't it easy?
Hehehe.
Hmph.
You're pretty good.
I'm just trying.
You're right.
It's called beginner's luck.
Hey, hey.
Don't dress up like a beginner.
Hurry up and hit it.
All right.
But this is similar to the eight green that comes out of our golf.
Right.
So, is this the one?
Okay?
Right.
The last thing you must do is get out of the blue.
Why don't you shower with water?
Yeah.
Excellent.
Now, I'm going to fight around the middle.
Let's have some fun.
Good service.
Ready to have a game?
Yes, sir.
The game has begun.
Now, please.
The lights are on.
The white noise is coming from the bottom.
Coaxing me, huh?
We're good.
I can't believe you.
You hit that long putt with one shot.
You're a beginner but you said it's a beginner's luck twice.
No, it's all thanks to the head coach's advice.
I didn't give you advice on the putt.
Huh?
I feel bad. Get in.
Ah!
Head coach, please! That's enough!
You're the one who's always been like that, but you're not as good as you are today!
No way!
This is bad!
Huh?
We lost the golf course!
We lost the golf course?
You're lying!
Come on!
Hurry up!
If there are no professionals who can beat us, the Murasame 4 Brothers,
I'll take the golf course's sign.
The Murasame 4 Brothers?
Who are they?
The Murasame 4 Brothers' parents, to be exact.
Mr. Murah 정치
Mr. Pilpibur
Mr. Poitain
Mr. Orochi
Mr. P DIO
Mr. Marubou
Mr. Pio
Mr. Fukuda
Mr. Hiromitsu
Mr. Pio
So, you can't beat us, too?
Idiot!
You can't say that right now!
Get out of here!
I'm in a good mood.
Hey, you guys!
You can't cheat!
Who are you?
You're a cop!
A cop?
You must be mistaken.
We don't cheat.
Yes, we just want to compete.
I didn't say I wanted money.
I didn't say I wanted money at all.
Thank you very much.
Are you the manager?
Yes.
Please accept my condolences.
I'll take your money.
What?
What should we do?
We didn't say we wanted money.
If there's no one to compete with,
why don't you just take it?
Wait!
What?
I'll compete with you!
You're going to accept our challenge?
I'm going to win with my dirty hands.
But I can't do as you think.
So I'll give you this money as a deposit.
All right.
But no one has ever tried to win against us.
I don't care.
Don't underestimate me.
It's getting interesting.
By the way,
if I win,
you'll get this money, right?
What?
You don't have to carry the sign.
No, no.
Of course, I won't.
Ryotsu,
is it all right to say that?
You can't even play golf.
It's all right.
I'll give you a big one.
It's the best.
I'm glad you brought your medicine.
Give it to me.
The rules are only one hole.
There are no penalties such as OB.
Anyway,
the one with the least number of hits will win.
You're so generous.
You can get away with anything.
I'll be the first.
I'm the second.
How was that?
Did you see that?
It's amazing.
I can fly 300 yards.
So they weren't just a bunch of fools.
The second is Iain Kiyoshiro.
Here I go.
The second one is the problem here.
I can't see the swing.
It's amazing.
This one will stretch, too.
You're so cool.
You can shoot normally.
I'll be the next.
Next is me.
I'm Chin Ranran.
Why are you like a Chinese magician?
Weren't you the four brothers of Murasame?
Why Chin?
My surname is Murasame.
I'm Chin Ranran.
Don't give me a random name.
Amazing.
All three of them have exceeded 300 yards.
This is not a match for Ryotsu.
I'm not the kind of person who can shoot.
That's right.
If you have that much power, you'll lose.
I was a little reluctant to go before the head of the headquarters.
This time, I'll do it seriously.
What?
So you've never been serious before?
I mean, he's a fool.
Don't be surprised to see that.
Oh, my God.
What?
Amazing.
But the form is different.
That's right.
No matter how much you fly, the form is different.
But 350 yards is...
What?
Be careful.
Sasuke, I understand.
Ryotsu.
Well, my ball...
It came around here, didn't it?
Sasuke did a good job.
There it is.
Ryotsu, it was there.
Why is it in that place?
I should have stopped at the fairway.
He should have stopped at the fairway.
He must have hit a stone and fallen.
He was unlucky.
You want to give up?
Shut up! You can't afford to lose!
I'll make him ring the bell.
No, Ryozu.
We have to get him back to the fairway.
If you do that, you'll lose the game.
Even so,
there's a tree in the green direction.
Oh, there it is.
Look.
Good!
Nice defense!
What are you going to do?
There!
How's that?
It's a two-on.
What's that technique?
Ryozu doesn't know the rules.
What do you think of that shot?
It's great.
Huh?
It's a crazy way to do it,
but it's not a good match.
A good match is a good match.
As expected of the chief.
We're telling the officers
to watch out for his match.
Right, Ohara-kun?
Yes, sir.
You're pretty good.
But you're still too early to be happy.
Watch this.
A full-blown attack.
My ball was fired from the green.
Stop it.
All I see is my ball.
Then, a great magic skill will crush you.
No way.
I can't believe I could do that!
What?
Can we say we two did a two-on?
Huh?
Hey, where's your ball?
How's that? Do you admit defeat?
Damn it! Give me all the clubs!
What are you going to do?
I don't care what you do.
If you do that, you'll burn more and more.
I'll definitely buy it!
I did it! This is a song, and this is a super long club!
All right! I did it!
Nice! You did it well, Ryo-tsu!
Damn it! What kind of person is he?
Now it's your turn. I'll do it first, because it's the farthest.
Ryo-tsu, it's not a billiard.
I'll return the change in the change.
Ryo-san's打法:逆転ビリヤード
I'm not good at playing the table tennis, so I'll use the bunker.
I fell into the pond!
Oh no!
You're in my way.
Mido, I'll do the cup.
No!
Don't worry. Sasuke is here.
Stop!
Damn it!
Why is he there?
I see. He was the one who prevented Ryo-tsu from hitting the ball.
I'll go in.
Let's go!
Here we go, Osagi!
I'm in the 4th place!
What are you going to do?
Murasame 4 brothers, will you give up?
Or will you still use your dirty hands to win?
Oh, no!
It's our defeat.
If you want to win, don't ever do this again.
I'll watch you more this time.
Get out of here!
You're so quiet.
The money is mine.
Ryo-tsu!
What?
It was a great game.
Thank you.
I think I've misunderstood you.
I hope we can play again some time.
Unfortunately, I can't make it to the next round.
Actually, I'm going to be fired today.
What are you talking about?
You're a talented subordinate.
Keep up the good work.
It's wonderful to make a fighter like him.
I have to teach him a lesson.
I'm afraid.
Ryo-tsu is my pride.
I don't know what it is, but I think I'm fired.
Thank you.
You really saved me.
As promised, I'll give you this.
Idiot!
Do you have a guy to bring me at such a time?
What?
What is that?
Do you want to do it for money?
No, it's not like that.
Ryo-tsu!
You're fired today.
No way!
I hate golf so much!
Next time
I feel like we're all melting together
I really want to push you away
For some reason, love is just cowardice
Don't hide everything that makes you strong
Translated by Releska