The End
When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and try to look away
It's like someone is calling
At the end of the rain
I walked with a look back
"Mom, give me your hand"
I felt that strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black tile of the Ake-dogai
I tried to walk on the black tile of the Ake-dogai
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a proud face
And a blue aunt on top of her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can see everyone
There is a wall there
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
1st Family of Honda Family
Eve's Treasure
Ryo-chan?
Ryo-chan!
Oh!
You sleep so soon
I'm glad you came to see me
It's okay
I was a little close to the patrol
Oh no
We are in the middle of working hours
Ryo-chan .what?
Olympia
Surprisingly
I love you
Good-bye
Kindergarten
I also have a golden eyelid
I'm gonna eat it.
Reiko-san, there's a Gakuten-san!
I slept well.
What are you guys gathering here for?
Oh, you're awake, Honda.
Yes.
What's wrong? Why are you looking so weird?
I thought the chief was coming.
No, no, no. It's not like that.
Then, what's that face?
Well, this face...
Brother, are you there?
This voice...
Monkey, why are you here?
I called the station, and I was told it was here.
Who is that?
It's my brother, Monkey.
That scary-looking face...
What?
When you ride a bicycle, you change your personality.
It's definitely Mr. Honda's brother.
Did something happen, Monkey?
Th-That's...
My sister fell down!
Reiko-san!
Reiko-san is your sister, right?
Yeah.
She's not in a good shape.
I didn't think she would fall.
Don't get in my way!
How dare you!
What!?
Let's go somewhere near the pass now, you two!
You two!
Get out of here!
I-I got it.
Eve!
Father!
Hayato, you came at the right time.
How do you feel, Eve?
I asked the doctor not to be so harsh on you, but...
Just a moment ago, the doctor did this to you, though.
I was so tired that I caught a cold.
Tired?
Dad, I'm so worried.
I can't stand up.
I'm so worried.
You're the one who's worried.
I think Honda's owner is.
Here it is.
Wear this.
Eve is sick.
I don't have a store.
You don't have to.
Hayato!
What's wrong with your work?
Eve fell down.
People fall down when they're alive.
Don't come back to me.
I'll heal you.
Don't worry.
It's work.
It's a big difference from before.
As expected of the owner of Honda.
Brother.
You said you caught a cold because you were tired, Eve.
I'm sorry to worry you.
It's been a long time.
I'm your senior, Ryochi.
Have you met before?
I have seen you before.
You're still so fire.
I'm the one.
Have you forgotten my face?
Senior.
Don't say that.
What?
Your face?
What happened to my face?
What?
Are you crazy?
It's not me.
Ryochi did it.
What?
-Wait! -Shut up!
-Shut up! -Shut up!
-We're home!
-You finally got out. -It seems like Eve finally fell asleep.
-Your sister went to college? -Yes. She's in her first year at college.
-Perhaps she had a problem with her college admission. -Not a university in the city?
-It's in the city, but it's a little far. It takes three hours to get to college. -What?
-It's in the city of Bakao. -Oh.
-From Minami-Senju, you take the Jouban Line, the Yamanote Line and the Chuo Line.
-You take the bus for an hour from the station.
-You take the bus for six hours? You're like a manager in a restaurant.
-You didn't go to college?
-It's a little far from my home, but I don't want to go far from home.
-You're so indifferent.
-We're home! -It's Mom.
-You're Ryo? -She heard a lot of rumors from Hayato.
-What kind of rumors? Honda? -I don't like it.
-Ryo, you're going to eat dinner, right? -Yes.
-If you don't let the guests eat, you're a man.
-I'll cook it right away.
-Hey, how does your mother change her personality? -My mother is a very ordinary mother.
-Your family changes their personality when they ride a bike or wear a pair of clothes.
-Your mother will definitely be a violent mother when she wears a kappogi.
-That's right.
-I thought the same thing.
-She cut her finger with a knife.
-I can't make it often because I always leave it to Eve.
-Your mother is very noisy.
-I told you it was normal.
-Wait a minute.
-I'm sorry. It's my fault.
-It's okay. I like to cook.
-I'm sorry for the face.
-You should have apologized earlier.
-Well, let's get along with each other when we eat.
-That's right.
-Let's eat!
-This is delicious. You can be a good wife.
-Thank you very much.
-But your mother is lively.
-She has a foreign personality.
-She is active in the family office.
-I didn't know that a daughter who is so shy from her mother was born.
-Eve was not so shy when she was a child.
-That was the beginning of an incident when she was a child.
-What happened?
-I went to the Arakawa amusement park with Eve and Monkey.
-Arakawa amusement park. I miss it.
-That's what Ryo-chan often said.
-I said that a lot before.
-At that time, I'm in trouble with Eve, and I get on a Ferris wheel.
-Then all of a sudden...
-What?
-Abut four minutes ago, the Ferris wheel was taken off.
-About four minutes ago, the Ferris wheel was taken off.
There are people who do terrible things.
Ah, I remember it too.
Eve got scared and since then she has become extremely reluctant to go outside.
Thanks to it, her personality has become introverted and her body has become weak.
I will never forgive that guy who dropped the 2B bullet!
If he wasn't there, Eve would have become a bright and strong girl!
Hmm, I understand your feelings.
Senpai!
Hmm...
What you just said...
I heard it somewhere.
Ryo-chan, didn't you say that before?
That he threw the 2B bullet from the Ferris wheel.
What?
No, I mean, there were a lot of people who did that back then.
I think he dropped it at a boy who was wearing a Nippon Ham hat.
What?
That day, I was wearing a Nippon Ham hat!
Then,
Was the 2B bullet...
Senpai?
That's...
All because of Senpai.
What should we do, Senpai?
Well,
Oh, right, let's see what Eve-chan looks like.
I'm worried about her.
I'm more worried about her being alone with Senpai!
Eve, are you okay?
She seems to be having a fever.
She has a weak body.
Who do you think that caused her to become like this?
E-E, you...
It's hot.
Did you say it's hot? Eve?
Wait! I'll get you ice right away!
Ice, ice!
What else do you want?
Water...
Okay, water!
It's water.
What a naughty boy.
It's for my sister.
Is there anything else you want?
A ring.
A ring?
When I was a kid, a ring...
When you were a kid...
You're asleep.
It's like you're asleep.
Eve...
You've got a lot of precious things.
Everything I had when I was a kid is all here.
Eve's childhood toys should be here too.
I'm hungry.
This is a supercar eraser.
You're going to do all kinds of things with it, aren't you?
There's a rider snack inside.
Ryo, you're not here to play.
Look for your ring.
Whose fault is it, Eve?
I know.
Did you find it?
It's this.
The hat that my senior hit me with a 2D bullet.
You don't have to show me that.
You even have a diary.
I met Megumi-chan three times today.
I was very happy.
Please don't.
It's not easy to read people's diaries.
What?
I went to the festival today and bought a ring.
And I gave it to my sister.
Isn't this the ring?
I remember now.
I bought this ring because I wanted to give it to my favorite girl.
But...
I don't need it.
I was easily rejected.
I had no choice but to take it home.
Eve looked very happy.
So I gave it to Eve.
By the way, I've been taking care of it for a while like a treasure.
Do you know where it is now?
Hmm...
Oh, maybe...
Oh, I found it.
After a while, the three brothers filled the time capsule.
I put everyone's treasures in it.
Where is it?
It's written here.
Behind the Toei house...
Beside the forest...
Harappa...
Well, it's certainly here.
In the past, this was the playground.
It's perfectly covered with concrete.
I have no choice but to give up.
No...
No way.
Eve...
I can't give up!
Eve is waiting for me!
Let's go there and borrow the tools!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Well...
It's not here, is it?
It's not here...
No, there's no doubt.
It should be buried here.
Senpai, don't touch it!
Huh, I got it...
Senpai!
Honda!
I got it.
Hmm?
When making the parking lot, this ground was dug up, and it seems to have been transported to another site.
Another site...
Where?
That's the Tamas.
Tamas?
It's a huge, far away thing again.
Tamas...
Hey.
Hey, is that Tama?
Of course! I'm going to find her!
I can't go with you. I'm going home.
Who did this to you, Eve?!
I know, I know.
You look so close, Takao-san.
Eve's university is over there, right?
It's 50 kilometers from Kameari.
I thought I'd come a long way.
I came here.
There's a lot of dirt in the parking lot here.
Yeah.
I don't know exactly where it is,
but it's probably used for some kind of building.
It's not very good to end up like this, but I can't help it.
It's a poison for the body.
It's a shame, but I'll give up.
Then let's get started.
Hey, didn't you hear what I just said?
It's used for a building around here, right?
Then I'll go back!
This is the first one.
You have to dig it all back.
I'm thinking it'll take a few days.
Eve's waiting!
I'll dig it up no matter how many days it takes!
What do you mean by a few days?
Who are you blaming, Eve?!
I got it, I got it.
Huh?
Isn't this the company in Nagagawa?
Oh, they're doing construction to extend our subway.
I see. This can be used.
Then there's a better way to dig it up than this.
Senior, could it be...
Hmm, I'll look for it up close.
Could you lend me a hand?
S-Sr. President, what are you doing here?
There's a new type of tunnel cutter.
Could you lend me a hand?
Huh?
N-No...
Huh...
Hmm...
This should have a metal detector.
Okay!
I did it!
Now I know where the time capsule is.
I see, I see.
It looks like it's pretty easy to operate.
I mean, it's a little...
No...
N-No, no, no, nooo!
Wait, Eve!
I'll be right back.
Okay.
What is it?
What's wrong!?
Where is the time capsule?
Here it is!
Honda, we're getting metal reaction from the upper right!
I got it!
Alright, let's keep going straight!
It's a water pipe!
It's a water pipe, it doesn't matter!
Now!
This is Tokugawa's treasure!
Alright, let's stop!
Stop!
There's no way to escape!
Eve!
The water pipe!
There's something in front of us!
Wait for me, Eve!
I'll find you no matter what happens!
Eve!
Damn it! Where's the water pipe?!
"Akatsuki"
"I've finally found it, Eve."
"This."
"This is a time capsule from my childhood."
"The other day, you were talking about your ring, right?"
"Honda-san, you came all the way here to find it, didn't you?"
"Brother..."
"I'm sorry, Eve."
"Huh?"
"Here you go."
"This ring was given to me by my brother."
"It won't fit."
"That means Eve has grown up, too."
"That's right. She has to grow up."
"Brother, I've made up my mind."
"I'm going to leave home and live in Ryo."
"What?"
"Eve..."
"I've been thinking about it for a long time."
"When I become a college student, I have to fix my shyness and be more solid."
"I think it would be better to live together with a lot of people in Ryo."
"So that's why you chose a university far away."
"But I can't get a good result in the end."
"Thanks to you, I finally got a good result."
"That Ryo is my new home."
"Eve..."
"W-what?"
"Oh!"
"Why is that group..."
"They escaped from the nearby Tama Zoo!"
"Oh!"
"They're going to dig the ground up!"
"They're coming this way. Let's run!"
"Oh!"
"Eve!"
"I'm saved. I was just put on my back."
"Hey, I remember your little sister riding on an elephant..."
"Ararararara!"
"The Honda on the motorcycle becomes a violent"
"The little sister on the elephant becomes violent."
"The little sister on the elephant becomes a violent."
"Hey, what are you guys doing?"
"Come on, you idiots!"
"Hey, hey, hey, hey!"
Let's go, Kame-dono!
We're heading to the dormitory of Eve-chan's university!
I'm going to join this dormitory this time!
I'm here to greet you!
Let's go!
Eve-chan won't be able to enter the dormitory for the time being.
How could she destroy her new home herself?
Eve-aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
What a bad dormitory!
Let's build a stronger one!
You will never do that!
♪ Then I can't even meet the real Ibu-sama! ♩
♪ Awaken! Clock! Kick it! My little finger hurts, ouch, ouch, ouch ♩
♪ For now, I'll draw my eyebrows and dash, dash, dash to the station ♩
♪ The main train is the only one sleeping on my dad's back ♩
♪ And this week, I work hard while the sound of the gorillas is soundless ♩
♪ I'm plastic-packed with a bucket in one hand, but I'm so hot and cold ♩
♪ Finally, I get a delete, then I'm done, so let's solve the mess ♩
♪ Everyday is no problem, the hot shower turns the mood blue ♩
♪ Every minute, for every day ♪
Every day is no problem
I'm in my pillow to recover
I love myself like this
Every day is no problem
My heart is beating, Monday
Monday Monday No Problem
Chief, why are you chasing me?
What did I do?
Please stop, Chief
Chief, what are those eyes?
Wait a minute, Chief
Next time, chase a turtle
Chief
Thank you!