Please turn on subtitles from the bottom-right corner.
When you watch TV, please make the room bright and look away from it.
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried about you.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
You'll be fine eventually.
Come to me, you jobless person!
I'm not here, but I'm worried about you.
Look at the red cloud burning.
You'll be fine eventually.
Do you understand?
If you understand, I'll be back!
The
A woman-public security officer
who houses a bank robbery
Indeed, Matoi-chan is amazing
At last, she is number one female that want to get married in fantasy novel
A presence that threatens with Reiko's name
Matoi-chan is young and cute
It's fine. It's a matter of time before I get fired.
As a senior who went to the wedding with Matoi-chan,
I think you have a complicated mind.
Hmph. It's such an old story. I forgot about it.
Old? It's just a matter of time.
Well, it was a marriage with a financial purpose, so it's not impossible for Ryo-chan to forget.
Thanks to that, Matoi-chan's popularity has risen rapidly.
Senpai has made the number one position of men who don't want to get married 12 years in a row.
Shut up!
You should have asked me about that big woman from Jaja-uma!
I'm sorry about that big woman from Jaja-uma.
M-Matoi!
Hey!
Good afternoon, Matoi-chan.
Hello.
A real Koban!
Matoi and I love each other.
If we get married, we can spend the rest of our lives together!
Nyahaha!
Huh?
You get it, right?
This is the true identity of Ryo-chan.
N-No, Matoi!
I'm not lying!
But I'd like to give you a little...
Goodbye!
Ah!
That time...
That... What was it?
I'm already in a bad mood.
I don't mind at all.
Ehh!
Then you should mind it a little!
More importantly, Kankichi, there's something I want to ask you.
Huh? What is it?
Grandma wants you to...
...come to my house.
G-Geppalto?
I refuse!
Anyway, the guy with the amount is going to lecture me about how dirty money is, right?
No, it's not like that.
I'm in trouble because my computer is not working well.
It will affect business, too.
So, I'd like you to fix it quickly.
Huh?
If you want to make me eat a lot of sushi as a repair fee, you can consider it.
It started again.
It's Ryo-chan.
That's cheap.
Alright! I'll tell you tomorrow morning!
I'm on a day off, so I'll pick you up by car until Ryo.
Yeah!
See you!
Hijiribashi! Hakusennagashi!
Next Morning
Oh, no...
Kankichi!
Ah, what's wrong?
Why have you looked at me that way?
I didn't mean to lecture you!
Anyway, could youping the computer out for me?
What's with you?
All of a sudden?
Get me a cup of tea!
Shut up!
*slurp*
Oh, looks like it's fixed.
Yeah, the capacity was too much.
I added a hard disk and memory, so it should be fine.
Look, Matoi.
What?
When Gepard came, he put a network all over the world to make sushi cheaply,
and he started a business on the Internet.
Thanks to that, our sushi became popular as the cheapest and best in Tokyo,
and sales doubled.
Yeah, it's true that it's a big deal to do this much in the first three months since I started using a computer.
But, you know, a computer with such a small capacity will be a big hit.
Besides, what is this?
What? What is this?
Grandma?
Such a bad taste.
He even explained the website.
There are 50,000 websites for young people, but there are no websites for old people, so I made it.
I thought it was good, but...
I'm making such a wasteful thing, so I'll freeze it.
Grandma.
Here you are.
You have a great appetite.
A man with a lot of food doesn't know what tolerance is.
Hello.
Oh, Mr. Nakagawa, Mr. Reiko.
Welcome.
Oh, you guys are here, too?
I came here for work, so I thought we might as well eat sushi.
Then today's my treat.
Order a lot.
But...
Matoi is always taking care of me.
Don't hesitate to eat.
Here you are, senpai.
Oh, I ate a lot.
You even gave us a treat.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
Please come again.
Then, Gepard, call me again if there's anything on your computer.
If I ask you for everything, the store will collapse.
Of course.
Matoi, are you going somewhere?
I'm going to have some tea.
Then let's go together.
Right, Nakagawa?
Yes, please.
Oh, a meeting for the class meeting?
Yes.
It's been a year since I graduated, so we decided to gather together.
It's been a long time since we had a meeting.
Yes.
Huh?
What are they doing?
They're playing the white line.
The white line?
Oh, I remember.
They were doing such a drama on TV.
They were wearing sailor suits on graduation day and playing it on the river.
Yes.
That's right.
Oh, I see.
They were wearing sailor suits.
It's a white line.
At the graduation ceremony in the United States, there was a ceremony.
One, two, three!
It's like a movie.
I know!
There was a ceremony.
I was given a thick dictionary at the graduation ceremony.
It's heavy and big, and it's hard to take home.
I know!
When there was a ceremony, I threw it in the stove.
Then it was passed down every year.
Well, this isn't a ceremony.
It's just a bad thing.
Hmm.
Oh, I'm right.
I got it right.
Really?
I did tell you so.
You didn't the button for the second button for the uniform to be given to girls?
Enoh, my head…
That's no such thing to do!
For the proof of the diploma, you are going to put sculpture on your desk.
Did you get that for your senior's warm welcome?
It's a nice message, isn't it?
It's too cruel.
It's just a scribble.
I'm an idiot because I've been doing that all the time without studying.
Shut up!
Um, are you Mr. Giboshi?
What?
It's Mr. Giboshi after all.
Mr. Giboshi!
We are his juniors.
I see. Today was the graduation ceremony.
Yes, I was a fan of you since high school.
I still remember the finals of the softball tournament.
It was the last round with one point lead.
The senior who was in the lead with two runs and two outs.
That reverse bye-bye homerun.
Even now, when I think about it, my chest is fluttering.
I'm so happy.
That home run is my treasure.
Matoi-chan was the 4th in the ace team.
That's why you're so strong.
Um, if you don't mind, can I shake your hand?
Sure.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Wow, you're so popular.
What should I do?
Thank you very much.
Senpai, please do your best at work.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yay!
Yo, popular!
But how can you shake hands with girls?
I'm used to it.
My school is a girls' high school, so I often got Valentine's chocolate and love letters.
Matoi looks like a man.
That uniform is a part of Olin University, right?
Yes.
Wow.
What is it?
It's a high-level high school.
It's hard to get in.
See? You can see it from here.
Huh?
Behind Nikolai-doh.
There's a high school.
Unbelievable.
Ryo-chan is smart, but he's not.
What are you talking about?
Ryo-chan's brother is a lawyer, too.
Oh, I didn't know Kankichi had such a brother.
What's wrong with him?
He's a guy who only studies and has no brain.
But Kankichi is too stupid, isn't he?
Shut up!
I have too many other talents.
You went to such a good school, but why didn't you go to university?
That's right.
If you're Olin, you could have entered the school by escalator.
Well, think about it.
What if your life force is...
Hmm...
You've got me.
That caused a lot of troubles.
We hooked the X-men.
Now, you're in trouble.
I can't believe this.
You're so good at everything.
I never thought you'd come to this school.
What do you mean "strange"?
You're just known as a bit 'cute' debate.
Why are you such a student?
Police Officer of Fate"
A police officer of fate?
What is that?
That's me, Kou's winter.
I'm really surprised.
And then, if you're a good boy, and then...
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
Big brother, are you okay?
Ah, no!
My shoulder bone is broken, and my motor...
Ouch!
I can't touch it!
I have to go to the hospital.
Hey, sis!
Can you get me out of the hospital?
I'm...
No way!
Hey, guys, stop playing monkey games!
What did you say?
Show me a little.
Ah!
Ouch!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Haha!
Then your bones aren't broken.
Hey!
If you go out of the house, you're going to get hurt!
Ouch!
You kid!
Ah!
Huh?
W-what are you...?
I can tell by looking at you.
Or do you see the prince of the white horse?
Ah!
That...
Ouch!
Ah!
You bastard!
Ouch!
Ah!
Hey, hey, hey!
No, I'm just trying to make up for a certain incident.
That's why you're dressed like that.
Yeah.
See ya.
Oh, um, what's your name?
Hmph, I'm not that good of a name.
So cool.
Huh, it's like a movie or a drama.
It's like a drama.
The police were both so strong and strong,
I still remember them.
Could it be that Matoi-chan was the-
I fell in love with everyone.
Huh, don't be so casually Exodus.
The police handwriting you have is authentic, isn't it?
So, what happened?
What happened from there?
Yeah, I thought we'd meet again.
On a snowy day,
on a rainy day,
on a stormy day,
I looked for him on this bridge, but...
I couldn't meet him.
What? You met him?
On the graduation day?
How dramatic!
There is a destiny, you know.
Yeah, I know.
After the graduation ceremony,
we all gathered here
and tried to make a white line.
This is a farewell to high school life.
But we'll meet again at the university, right?
Actually, I'm not sure
if I should go to university.
What? No way!
Of course you're lying.
You already passed the entrance exam, right?
Yeah, right?
Don't scare me!
No, it's not that.
That girl is in danger.
She dropped the ball on the track!
The kid fell down!
What should we do?
Mr. Ekin!
Hold on to this!
Let go of me!
Move!
La-la-law!
The screen caught on fire in the middle of the day.
Bad's back!
Close the screen!
We're gonna make a headline.
"This is the game."
That's what you've been waiting for, right?
Zoom!
Zoom in on the next game!
*cough*
Now, hold on, kid.
You have to spit the water out!
*cough*
Alright, you're safe now.
The police came right after that.
Thank you, Sis.
Mr. Kendo.
Yeah?
Thank you so much.
Take care.
Hey, don't be so reckless, even if you're a woman.
You're the one who always jumps into the river like that.
Really? I knew it.
Thank you so much for your help in rescuing me.
By the way, your address and name...
Huh?
Just say it. The police will be grateful.
See you.
Ah! Please wait!
I'm a police officer.
Huh?
A police officer?
Um, could you be the one who dressed like Santa Claus and jumped into the river last year?
I forgot about that long time ago.
That police officer is really cool.
You were looking at Kendo, weren't you?
What's so cool about him?
He's against violence!
Matoi, you didn't know who that police officer was after all?
No.
I just wanted to ask his name, but the mass media came.
I was surrounded and photographed.
There were a lot of interviews and interviews, and I was really surprised.
The next day, the police called me and gave me a thank-you letter.
I felt it was a good thing to help people.
So I decided to go out into the world and do something that would be good for people.
That's how you quit college and became a police officer.
Yeah.
I wanted to be a cool police officer like him.
That's what you're like, Matoi.
But who was the police officer of Kendo?
I don't know the name, but the police officer on the scene said that he was the person named Ryo from the Katsushika library.
What?
He was from the Katsushika library?
Yes.
So when I was assigned to the Katsushika library, I thought I might be able to meet that Ryo.
There's no such thing as Ryo in our library.
I wonder if there's a guy named Ryo.
There's no Ryo, but there's Ryoichi and Ryoji.
Hanamura Ryoichi and Nakata Ryoji, right?
But it wasn't those two.
What?
He's in our library!
Huh?
Who?
There! In front of us!
Huh?
Hey, I'm not Ryo, I'm Kankichi!
Matoi, didn't the police officer on the scene say he was Ryo from the Katsushika library?
Yeah.
I'm Ryo.
I thought he was just a name, not a name.
But he's not Kankichi, is he?
There's no police officer who jumps into the river with a kendo mask on.
I remember!
Senpai!
Last spring, when we went to the kendo competition, there was a time when I couldn't take off my mask!
Oh, there was!
If you put in a memory bond so that the mask doesn't get loose, it won't go back to normal.
I won the competition, and the principal treated me to French cuisine, but I couldn't eat well because of the noodles.
So I ended up drinking a straw with a mixer.
Come to think of it, when I came back home, I saw the girls looking at the river below on the bridge.
So I looked down and saw that a boy was drowning in the river.
I jumped into the river in a reaction.
There was a high school girl who jumped into the river with me at that time.
That high school girl was Matoi!
Does that mean that Santa Claus is Ryo?
No, I don't think Santa Claus is me.
Oh, by the way!
When we were doing the bonus in winter the other day, I was stupid to Santa Claus to run away from the debtors.
I knew it.
Yeah.
I helped a high school girl who was involved in a yakuza while she was running away.
Is Santa Claus a police officer?
Well, yeah.
Damn it. Where did you run away?
Huh?
It's over there.
Oh?
So Santa Claus was running away from the debtors, not from the high school girls.
Well, yeah.
No way.
My precious memories...
Oh, it was a nightmare.
I can't believe I fell in love with such a guy twice.
Well, thanks to that, you became a police officer, so that's fine.
Nonsense!
Matoi!
Huh?
Oh, everyone!
You came late, so I came to look for you.
So you were here.
Everyone, how was college?
It was fun.
If only we didn't have a test.
Matoi, don't you regret not going to college?
Yeah.
Anyway, the graduation ceremony was halfway through.
Oh, right.
The kid fell into the river and it wasn't that bad.
Hey, why don't we continue the graduation ceremony now?
Why don't we start now?
Huh?
But we don't have any scarves.
How about we replace it with a handkerchief?
Oh!
That's a good idea for Kankichi.
Huh?
That's not necessary for Kankichi!
Oh, did Santa help you here in high school?
Huh?
You remember?
Yeah.
Thank you for that time.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
You seem to have been overshadowing your image.
It reminds me of high school.
The one a year ago.
It feels like I'm graduating safely.
It's a little short, but...
Okay, I'm ready.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
♪ Naga-San - Kameari ♪
♪ Naga-San - Kameari ♪ ♪ So today it's raining ♪
♪ Naga-San - Kameari ♪ ♪ Tomorrow it's sunny ♪
♪ Naga-San - Kameari ♪ ♪ That day will be in our hearts ♪
♪ Naga-San - Kameari ♪ ♪ And we can believe ♪
Goodbye, my time as a student.
The End
It's like someone is calling me
After the rain
I walked while looking back
My mother held my hand
At that time I felt
A strange feeling
So
I took the Ake-do-gai
Tile
And walked
On the black road
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue-eyed lady
Turn around
And look
At the corner of the street
Everyone can meet everyone
Let's go!
There is a turtle
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Huh? A child is born at Kinjiro's place?
He's a child born at Kinjiro's place?
Oh, I'm a child born too
You mean, he's an old man
It's impressive
Wait for me
Mr. Kanchichi is going right now
Next episode
To a dear brother
I'm in your care
There is a turtle there
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
I'm not sure what to do.