Translation by Hazuki no Yume
I look up at the sunset floating on the river
When I kick the pebbles, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym where I used to work out
They laughed at me saying I was still a baby
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only get a penalty
The cityscape that doesn't change even if I have one bad day is strangely gentle
From the water tank of the Tungari-boshi
The sunset falls to the Kaishakuten
Tomorrow is over already
I lost my happiness again when I was in Katsushika and Shibamata
I realized
I'm such a fool
Okay! Stay better together
I show the Japanese gift
Hold on!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Ok! Say cheese!
Where have you been?
I've been to Nijube Shrine.
But there were a lot of foreign tourists in Asakusa.
But if you look closely, there are a lot of foreigners here.
If you say Akihabara and Asakusa,
you must go to a guidebook for foreigners.
What?
How is the road to Japan so narrow?
You're not allowed to enter here by car.
Stop! Stop!
Ouch!
Are you okay, sir?
I'm fine. But what is this guy?
It's Jaguar.
And it's an old Mk2.
A British guy.
He jumped out of the car suddenly.
He's a gentleman in the UK.
Hey, what are you thinking?
I thought it was a mountain gorilla in Japan,
but it came to the United States.
Who's a gorilla?
Professor Ezaki.
Isn't it Professor Ezaki?
What's up, Nakagawa?
Do you know him?
Yes.
When I was studying in Cambridge University in the UK,
Professor, did you forget?
It's Nakagawa.
Oh, my students.
How do you know?
I'm Nakagawa.
What a coincidence that you can meet me in this place.
I'm glad to meet you in this country.
It's a miracle.
It's a miracle!
I don't know if you're Japanese or a foreigner.
I've lived abroad for a long time.
Hey, it's time for morning tea.
How about a cup of tea?
What's with that outfit?
Why are you wearing a skirt?
This is England's new style.
It's a kilt, senpai.
It's a traditional British national costume.
But I think it's Scotland, not England.
So, who are you?
It's a pair of trousers.
I can tell by your outfit.
Did you change your clothes?
Yes, this is my...
You're the culprit, aren't you?
I'm wearing a uniform, too.
I'm your senior.
My Jaguar is not injured.
If it's that important, you can't come in.
You...
What?
Your pronunciation is wrong.
Jaguar!
J-A-G-U-A-R.
It's Jaguar.
Yes, go ahead.
J...
Jagu...
G...
G-A-G-U-A...
You stupid!
In Japan, it's Jaguar.
Jaa-ga-r.
Oh, my tea time is over.
Why did I talk to you two?
You're bothering me.
I should have put out a table here.
I can't speak English without a cup of tea.
I know the difference.
Ezaki Korosuke.
Korosuke?
What are you doing?
I thought you were a croquette instead of Korosuke.
You're the only one who thinks that way.
The fog is so strong.
It was raining in London today.
It was raining again today.
You're so good at speaking English.
You should say Nikujagwa instead of Nikujaga.
I've lived abroad for a long time.
When I think about it, I miss my days in England.
Big Ben's money that I spend in the fog.
It's Zenzouji's money.
I'm going to build a 2-story building right outside the window of the apartment.
Run.
Thank you for waiting.
Everyone, we have arrived at Asakusa Zenzouji.
There's a double-decker bus.
Recently, I've been running in Japan.
There's a famous detective Sherlock Holmes in Baker Street.
There's a rich soldier under the famous god of Kanda.
There's a famous Tower Bridge in London.
There's a famous Kajino Bridge in Japan that hasn't opened yet.
I hate losing.
Me too.
We're going to take the bus, too.
Oh.
Oh, make me see the bilang chicken somewhere.
What's going on, Blanc?
Because I have to go to work with you.
Well, Professor, would you like to have some sushi?
Oh, I would be happy to.
Very good.
Here it is.
It's good.
Right?
What's wrong, Professor?
Hmm...
Where's the napkin?
Ah, I told you to come!
Here I come!
Oh, Ryo-chan, Kei-chan!
What's up, Reiko? You're here too?
You two are still at work, right?
I don't mind lunch.
Dad, I'd like to have a tuna, salmon roe, and natto roll.
Here!
Oh, Kei-chan, who's that?
Ah, let me introduce you.
My teacher at Cambridge University.
Professor Ezaki Korosuke.
This is the chief of the school's school of the school's principal, Reiko Akimoto.
How do you do, Reiko?
"Mademoiselle" is French, isn't it?
Oh no!
"Mademoiselle" means "open more windows!"
You're so stubborn!
Professor, you've lived abroad for a long time, so you don't need to use the word "wind".
"Wind"?
It means "a base" or "a base".
What would you like to eat, Professor?
How much.
Huh?
"Master", how much you could say?
You mean "how much"?
No, no. How much?
Even if you say it like that...
Got it. How much? How much?
In other words, how much?
Oh, yes.
This is a very good way to say it.
How much is "how much"?
Is "with" like "tontchi"?
Hey, wait a minute.
"Wid" is "ikura".
Professor, you're so reckless.
"Ikura" is "anything".
"Ikura" is "anything"?
Oh, "ikura" is "anything"!
"Ikura" is "anything."
"If you say it so very quickly,"
well, that's okay, but
"Ikura" is "anything".
You got it.
How about you try it this time?
"Ikura" can be said as "waduku".
"Ikura", "waduku" means "pick up".
Ok.
·
"Waduku" means "cooking up leaves".
English people always drink tea!
Excuse me, but I live in front of the Edo.
I don't drink tea often.
Thank you for the meal!
Enjoy!
It looks like the owner of the store was angry.
That's right.
Miss.
Yes?
Please send my Jaguar.
Ah! You're so fast!
But I'm driving.
I'm driving.
Leave the small Japanese cars behind.
It's Jaguar. Jaguar.
But Reiko's car is...
Porsche.
The middle one is Ferrari.
Cars are just cool and fast.
Without an extension like the British car,
it's hard to be a true driver.
Yes, that's right.
Even the British car I have
is Morgan Lotus.
Aston Martin, Rolls-Royce, and...
Anyway, England is the origin of the industrial revolution.
It's a country of adults with traditions and customs.
You bastard!
You should have listened to me quietly.
You're like England, England, and Kirigiri.
Senior, you didn't keep quiet.
Japan is a country of the sun and the sun.
It has traditions and customs.
You're Japanese, aren't you?
Anyway, I've lived abroad for a long time.
What?
London's grey sky is so nostalgic.
Tokyo's sky is too blue.
What do you mean blue?
Look!
Smog makes it grey enough.
There are many other grey-coloured states,
grey-coloured politicians.
If you don't like losing,
you don't lose.
I'll be in your care.
I see.
The British have the world's standard character.
The British speak English.
Tsukudani and instant noodles are the inventions of Japan.
London has London boots.
Geta, Zori, Waraji, Take-Uma are in England.
Is there Mt. Fuji?
Is there Tokyo Tower?
I don't think so.
No!
There's no Mt. Fuji or Tokyo Tower in England!
That's the truth!
Look! Japan has won.
But there's no 007 in Japan.
There's a ninja with a long history in Spain.
What?
A ninja?
You got it?
Tradition and common sense are not the same as the British.
In this case,
I'll have a duel!
A duel?
N-no way!
-What? -That's a stick?
-What? -What?
-No, it's not. -What does that mean?
-What does that mean? -Hip-hop Club!
-What? -What does that mean?
-What? -It means - -What
does that mean? -Hip-hop Club! Mint
y lets the world's best It's
not Tokyo Tower. I can
What does the Tokyo Tower have to do with the battle?
It's an iron tower!
What?
That's why...
Iron tower...
Climbing is the sport of a gentleman!
Whoever climbs to the top of the iron tower first wins!
You're trying to fool me again, aren't you?
Fine, if you're going to climb, I'm not going to win.
Senpai is right.
Even though he was only 2 years old, he was able to destroy 1000 chandeliers!
Start!
Whoa...
I heard the lights!
I can't lose to such a cheap guy!
I better win for real tomorrow!
Wh-What did you say?!
That's not fair!
How could you do that?!
What?
You have to climb up like that to make the rule!
Kosaki, you're going to miss!
Damn it!
Oh!
It's good to see Tokyo from such a high place like this.
Really, I haven't climbed up the Tokyo Tower in years.
I've been forgetting about the
"Early in the Clouds" for a while.
Hey, stand there to take a picture.
Oh, I'll ask that Fuji-san to come in.
Oh, what's wrong?
I-I think Ryotsu was there just now.
No, that's not what I meant.
No way!
I-I didn't think so.
Is this the end of the elevator?
Wow, we're almost at the top!
Just a little low.
H-Huh?
Ugh!
How dare you go to the top!
I-I'm...
H-He's just trying to get in good water, h-heh...
I'm the one cooking!
I-I-I don't know what's wrong!
Hey, why don't you try to climb up the tower as well?
Tot ed.
Hahaha.
You have to climb up with me, don't you think?
Hmmm?
Oh, Professor Eizaki stopped!
Senpai wins!
Hehe, victory is on my side!
Ah, Senpai!
Well, there are times when the electric current is too strong in an iron tower, so be careful.
Say it quickly!
Now then...
This is the real top!
Oh, we're going to make it!
Ah, I hate this place too much!
I'm going to make it!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...
My whole body is still tingling...
Senpai and Professor hate losing too much.
It's true!
I'm a Japanese, but I can't forgive a guy who's wearing a foreign uniform.
Huh?
Yotsu...
What's wrong, Chief?
You didn't go up to the Tokyo Tower yesterday, did you?
Of course not.
No way! Who would climb up to such a high place?
Only fools and smoke can do that!
Fools and...
Smoke, huh...
Hmm...
I guess it's just a delusion.
It's a delusion! A delusion!
That's fine, but...
By the way, Nakagawa and Ryotsu...
There's a training for a car that we developed at the headquarters.
Will you come with us?
A car for safety?
A car for safety, huh...
So we're going to stop a car that died in an accident, huh?
I see.
Today, at the training for this car,
we have a professor from Cambridge University who's in charge of the development of the prototype.
Oh?
You're bringing a professor from England?
A professor?
Senior, it's Professor Ezaki!
What?
What did you say?
See?
It's true!
What's that voice?
There he is!
It's Professor Ezaki!
He drives like a madman.
He used to be a model.
He's like a car that breaks down when it hits.
Hello!
Sorry to keep you waiting, everybody.
Professor Ezaki!
You're back!
You're all fine, aren't you?
We just met yesterday!
And look!
Five of your drivers got blown away!
Oh, that's good news!
You're not the one who got blown away!
I have a lecture, so I'll be back!
Hey!
Professor Ezaki, would you like to hear something?
Here you go.
The theme of the "Car Society" is "Ecology and Safety".
It's important to think about the environment and make cars that are safe.
That's a good point.
I'm a professor of mechanical engineering.
Mechanical engineering?
But you're not good at driving.
So my safety car was made...
The world's most durable,
the Swedish Volvo's durability,
and the German Benz's stable driving.
It is made with the technology of the British Rolls-Royce,
which incorporates Japanese car electronics.
It's literally the safest car in the world.
So it's a mix of both.
I guess it's impossible to do that just in the UK.
Yo!
It's tea time.
You!
Yes, sir.
You always have tea time...
This is the secret to safe driving.
Ah!
You!
Excuse me.
I'm too hot.
Hey, what's the car announcement?
Well, that's fine.
This is the safety car I developed.
It's a Coyote Go.
This is it!
It looks very durable.
All the back seats are equipped with airbags
ABS multi-weights system
All the data is transferred to the front glass by Japanese electronics technology
Wireless remote control
Door opening and closing, and even the gas engine
All the safety features are in this remote control
The car is also...
Sorry, are you okay?
I'm not okay!
That's strange, the engine should only run at N-range
You should have stopped the engine
Right
Stop it!
Stop!
Why are you coming to me?
Senpai!
Watch out!
Where is the safe place for the remote control?
The shock test is over
Don't fool me!
But it's strange
The airbag doesn't work because of such a shock
It's true
What do you mean?
It works when the car crashes at 300km/h
What?
300km/h means the car is broken
You should be more careful
I can drive at 300km/h
Sir, we have prepared a safety test
He's a bad driver, so it's dangerous to be close to him
What?
Help him!
You can't try to be safe at the passenger seat
I'm not a bad person!
I can't trust your driving
Don't worry
It's 100% safe
Don't put that on yourself!
Let's go!
Trust me!
I can do it!
I'm going to the pole!
I can see the front!
Calm down!
I don't have my glasses
Look at the front!
Turn the steering wheel!
This is bad!
It's safe
Come back soon!
I didn't know
What's wrong?
Something's wrong
Something's wrong with the car
I can't see anything!
Hurry up!
The brakes!
It's not working!
I can't release the brakes
What?
Raise the sunroof!
OK!
It's the intersection!
Turn left!
Back to the back!
Like this?
Back to the front!
I was rightpl п
I can't, and now I'm?
Turn left
Do I have to do this?
Look at the GI-
S-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s-s
Left, right, and left!
Watch out!
Tell me!
Turn right!
Right, turning left!
Hey
"The
is
not going
to be cool
" Really
" Where
is
the
safety
card What
you
made
is
dangerous
" The
crew
was
safe
and
no
injured
person
came out
" Everything
is
thanks
safest
car
in
the
" Have
a
nice
day
" Attention
please
Old
people
Thank
you
for
using R
you
tsu sightseeing
today
Thank you
" Then,
please enjoy
the Hawaii
trip as a
souvenir " Next
time
" " " " " " " " " " " " " " " " " " "
"い
" "lit
" ""
" "um
i
was so
good
The power is more powerful than anything
If you all gather here
It's like a dream, the final energy
Tomorrow, the day after, believe in yesterday
Draw the universe, stand on the ground
The planet of Kameari will come to an end
This is good, right?
There's no reason to say it's good, right?