Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming seasons ♪
♪ The brightest and greatest harem ♪
♪ Overcoming the new era ♪
♪ The hero is diving to the city on his own ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing only trendy things ♪
♪ The face is more important ♪
♪ Let it ring ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Running and running ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♪
♪ Let me run ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt even if you stick out a little bit ♪
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♪
♪ Strong and high, strong and high ♪
♪ Let's both get into it together ♪
♪ With a smile on your face ♪
♪ Without a smile on your face ♪
♪ I will reach out to you ♪
♪ And be the first to come to the city of paradise ♪
If it's a public place, I'll be there soon.
I'll take care of it.
Let's take the luggage.
I'll help you.
Chief Ohara, I'll take you to the public place.
That's the true police officer.
What about you, Ryo-tsu?
I went out on patrol, but I was with Honda-san at 10 o'clock last night.
It's bad. The chief's order is already on.
It's not good.
I went too far with the center of gravity.
I can't believe you want to see me.
I thought you'd come back by dawn.
It's a nuisance to say that we're in trouble.
Let's get rid of them at all costs.
Leave it to me.
You're coming, aren't you?
Why are you playing hard to get alone on that wide square?
That's what I'm after, you sons of bitches.
The island of the violence special.
I'm not letting any huge annoying thing get inside the square.
You think you can compete with us?
That's not true.
"Honda Hayato"
They're a tough bunch.
They're 10 years ahead of us.
They're strong.
Who are you?
I'm Honda Hayato from the Aircraft Division.
I'm a later Honda.
I'm Ryo-tsu from the Kamiyari Park.
If you have a problem, I'll be your opponent anytime!
You remember that, right?
Honda Ryo-tsu.
I'm sure the director will give us good reviews this morning.
The garrison has crushed two of them.
I should beat them up with this.
I'm hurt.
Don't worry.
You're going to be fine.
Really?
I'm glad it happened.
Good morning.
Sorry for being late.
Ryo-tsu!
Honda!
I'm going to be your opponent.
What the hell did you do?
I just got a call from the office.
Uh...
What?
You're banning me from going home?
No...
What?
What the hell is going on?
Nothing at all!
I've figured it out!
Thanks to you, the phone's been ringing since a while ago!
I-I'm really sorry.
This is my director, Fuyuki Todoki.
Ugh, you guys!
Lower your heads!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Wait, wait, wait!
We were the ones who defeated the tyrants!
Why do you have to punish us?
You guys!
You're all the general public!
What?
We're all in shock, everyone!
Ryotsu!
This month is the month of the intercourse with the local people!
And yet, you...
You've just ruined the trust of the citizens!
I'll punish you again!
I'll tell you the truth.
I'll ban Ryotsu Honda for a week from today.
And I'll reflect on my actions.
What? Banning at home is the same as getting a vacation.
I'll make a plumber.
What a annoying guy.
You didn't get a single penny, but you got a week off.
You should be happier.
But I can't ride a motorcycle for a while.
What should I do?
Do what you want.
Don't you have any hobbies?
I don't have any hobbies other than motorcycles.
By the way, I don't think you're doing anything.
If you don't have anything to do, just sleep in your room.
Two weeks is too short.
What?
What was that?
A motorcycle.
Honda, where are you?
My motorcycle.
Where is my motorcycle?
I haven't made a plumber yet.
My motorcycle is here.
Stop it.
I bought it from America.
Yamaha V-Largo XV 400.
It's a real-type model.
I paid 500 dollars.
It's a small motorcycle.
I can't get it anymore because it's on sale.
Where is my motorcycle?
Stop.
As long as he's here, I can't live a happy life.
I have to do something.
I'm sorry.
Ryo, are you there?
I'm waiting.
I brought a lot of things.
What will you use them for?
Let Honda have hobbies.
Hobbies other than motorcycle?
Yes.
Look at that.
Honda.
Are you okay?
Ouch. Why am I here?
I just didn't ride a bike for a day.
This is serious.
Honda is like a jobless employee.
A jobless man is married to a jobless woman.
Especially a boss. That's the worst.
What did I do?
What?
Chief! Why are you here?
I'm responsible for your management.
I came to see you so that you don't cause trouble during your break.
The problem has already occurred.
Yes.
Idiot! What are you thinking?
Break is a time of reflection.
You can't take it as a hobby.
I'm sorry.
Chief, look at this.
Where is my bike?
You haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
You'll get sick if you keep this up.
You may never be able to return to work.
No way.
Honda is a capable company.
Of course, you will be responsible for it.
You are fired from the management department.
And your rent will be reduced to zero.
That's why you are abandoned.
Let's go.
The police will concentrate on your family.
Maybe you should consider your service after you leave the esto.
So you will be given more attention and more time.
There are no job opportunities.
I know it.
However.
The canvas you wear is important.
It will make your life easier.
Do you understand?
Eh?
Hmm...
I-I got it. I'll give you a special permission.
Thank you very much.
That is the reason why I am the head of the club.
Because I'm good at putting people on the line.
Ryo-chan's unique skill.
A hobby is as good as being away from work.
A job is like that, and the words of a human who only does hobbies are very convincing.
Don't be so mean!
In the case of women, they are as far away from the motorcycle as possible.
How about collecting coins?
Collecting coins...
Yeah, we can start from today.
It's the effect of Japan.
5 yen, 10 yen, 100 yen, 500 yen.
The 10 yen coin in the Showa 26 is worth more than 100 yen.
I see. Collecting coins.
Oh, this is like a motorcycle wheel.
I see.
It's perfect for you.
How about a real motorcycle wheel?
Chief, you can't do that.
You should say something that makes me think of a motorcycle.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
That's right. How about a knitting machine?
I'm sure it's perfect for Mr. Honda.
Knitting machine?
That's right. I think we can easily make a muffler.
Muffler...
Dance is popular now.
It's a folk dance.
Folk...
That's right.
I'm reading it.
The story of the Trap family of the Trap Dan Shaku is moving.
Dan Shaku, Dan Shaku, Tan Shaku, Tan Shaku...
I like the dubbing the most.
Chief, you should do it quietly.
You should be quiet and dance.
I'm sorry.
Muffler...
I'm going to go.
You're the owner.
Let's go, Mr. Honda.
I'll be waiting for you.
Good morning, senpai.
Are you awake, Ryo-chan?
Hey, you came. Come in without me.
Excuse me.
It'll be over soon, so wait.
Wait.
Were you playing games at night?
I couldn't sleep because of him.
What are you doing?
You know, I'm going to crush him one by one every second.
I can ride the bike with 430,922 pieces of crushed bones.
Do you plan to continue that work during your rest?
It'll be a silver-diamond picture.
All right, I'm done.
Well, Honda, let's start.
What do you mean, start?
You can tell by looking at Nakagawa and Reiko's clothes.
It's tennis.
It's a great hobby.
It's popular regardless of age.
And Japanese women's tennis is world-class.
If you don't play tennis now, you can't be called Japanese.
I failed in the cultural field yesterday.
I decided to go in the sports field today.
It's before work, so I can't be with you for too long.
Let's move your body a little.
You can refresh yourself.
It's okay. I'm doing this.
If you do that, you'll feel bad.
Get ready for the race.
Go on.
Oh, my God!
If I play tennis, my body will break.
What the hell does a bike ride mean?
Ryozu, are you there?
Ryozu, Honda, you're in trouble.
I won't allow it anymore.
Trouble?
What's wrong, Chief?
It's not about what's wrong.
They went to work last night.
They had a big scene at the Kanna.
What?
At around 2:00 last night,
two groups of people who are known as the "Ryotsu" of the Kouki Honda Kameari Park,
appeared in Kanna-na-dori.
They were arrested and were forced to wear many cars.
The Honda and Ryotsu are here!
There are a lot of police officers!
The Kouki army is on the way, so it's a big mess!
That's not us!
Shut up!
Then, do you think you're fake?
According to the witnesses, you two are sure about it.
No way!
The official statement will be released in a few days,
but the Honda is probably a "choukai menshoku" with a license and a license plate.
Choukai... Choukai menshoku!
Ryotsu is no doubt a "choukai menshoku"!
Until the conclusion is made, stay quiet in the dorm.
Okay? Don't go outside!
Anyway, I don't believe that you're just ignoring the police and going around outside!
You're right.
It's natural for you to think that someone is talking about you and going around.
You think I'm not trusting you because you believe in me?
No, that's not it.
If you think like that, you'll...
Huh? He was here a while ago!
What?
Honda!
That guy!
No way!
Honda!
Nakagawa!
Yes!
Renko!
Mr. Honda!
Honda!
Stop it, you idiot!
What are you going to do when you die?
What are you doing?
Mr. Honda!
Calm down.
I'm sure the truth will be revealed soon.
And we'll be able to solve the problem.
That's right.
You have to be careful, Mr. Honda!
If you die, your father, your mother, your sister, and your brother will be sad!
What are you talking about?
I'm just...
I'm just looking at the motorcycle.
What?
Don't do anything stupid!
Mr. Honda!
Ryo!
Ouch!
You're not moving, Ryo.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who got the scratch.
If I were a normal person, I'd be in big trouble.
I had to do everything myself.
I did everything for my mother.
Anyway, there's nothing you can do now.
I'm sorry.
Ryo, you're no good.
You're miserable.
You're not even a normal person.
However, You saved me.
Someone has to pay for your death.
I'll fix it.
Next, it's your turn!
You have to do it together with me.
Ryo.
I'm sorry.
The police are making a scene!
If we cause trouble today, Toyomi's neck will be cut off!
Oh, now it's Honda's turn!
Let's go, Ryochi's boss!
Yeah!
Hey, hey!
Clear the road!
To Kouki's Honda!
There's a ryochi from Poemai Hashijyo who has no money!
What are you doing!?
I hate red cars!
You can pay 50,000 yen if you like them!
No, no!
Don't hesitate!
I'll give you!
This is Kouki's Honda!
It's a ryochi from Poemai Hashijyo!
If you really have it, come on and get it!
Yeah!
What's that?
Don't let him get away!
I'll clear the road!
Let's go, Honda!
But...
How do we get down from here?
I don't know!
What's that?
You don't have to say it!
Get on!
Get off quickly!
Hey you freaks!
Get ready!
Let's go, Ryochi's boss!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Yaaay!
Wh- what's that?
You really did tell us our names!
You guys are not getting away with this!
It's the real thing!
I'll catch you!
Don't let him get away!
I don't care!
Ran right through them!
I'm fine!
I knew it.
Move!
Don't come here!
It's a souvenir!
It's 736 yen.
Welcome.
UNDERSTOOD!
What the...?
Show him your true colors!
Show me your power!
Who are you?
You're the head of the Violence Special!
I'm the leader of Sigma!
I-I've been exposed!
I see. So the two of us were killed in the Sakagura Mission's crime!
What the?!
I'm going to die!
Action!
Damn it. What if I get fired because of Ryotsu?
I don't know how far I'll get!
You bastard!
You're the only one who didn't do anything!
You made me angry!
Go to hell, you bastards!
A-alright, ta-ta!
Let's do it.
We'll prove it was not our idea!
I'm gonna be able to ride my motorcycle again!
Gah!
Y- just wait.
Ryo-chan, Honza, as I thought it was your job.
There's no reason to be so...
I won't forgive you. You're fired! You're fired!
I said you're fired! You're fired!
Takagawa, act more emotionally!
This is the scene of the reunion of the mother and her child who had been separated for a long time!
The ratings will definitely go up!
Camera, stand by, okay?
Let's get to the main story!
Next time, we'll get more ratings!
Thank you for watching!
Ryo-chan, Honza, as I thought it was your job!
We'll get to the main story!
Camera, stand by, okay?
Let's get to the main story!
Next time, we'll get more ratings!
The ratings will definitely go up!
I won't forgive you!
Even if it rains today,
Tomorrow will be clear!
Bye-bye!
Let's wash our hands!
Goodbye to all the unpleasant things!
Oh yeah!
Let's live the way we want!
We have a good thing!
Outside the door
A sunbeam is calling us!
Next Episode
Episode 4
"Kazutakubi Goes to bed"