"A Man Without Money"
"When you watch TV, try to keep the room bright and away from it."
A man without money, come to me!
"I'm not here, but I'm worried."
"Look at the blue sky and the white clouds."
"I'm sure that one day, it'll be alright."
"You know what to do, right?"
"If you know what to do, then shut up and follow me!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried."
"What's this guy?"
"Is he a cop?"
"How could you leave such a man like that?"
"It's the police's fault."
"I can't believe he's a cop."
"How do you feel about the job interview?"
"A wise decision."
"There's no reason for me to say that."
"I don't think he can be a person with a different opinion."
"We are all in the same boat."
"Wait a minute!"
"What? What is it, Tonda?"
"I have something to say. How about we make a decision in advance?"
"Do you think this man is suitable for a cop?"
"No, I'm sure he's a man with a lot of problems, but I don't think he's worth it."
What do you mean?
Well, that's something.
Are you saying you're going to re-educate this man?
What?
Me?
Yes.
I'm going to make sure this man becomes a true police officer.
That's...
What do you say, Tonda?
Tonda-kun!
Ryo-san, finally you're fired.
But I heard that you've lost your job, Tonda.
I heard that you were given a condition to re-educate him.
But that's within a week.
You've been living with that personality all this time, haven't you?
To change that in a week...
Nakagawa-san, did you hear that?
Ryo Tsukankichi is fired.
He's going to be fired.
I heard that.
You're a man of your word, aren't you?
If he's fired, he'll be in trouble.
Right?
Do you really think so?
What?
This is a serious matter, unlike usual.
If you guys really quit, you'll be very lonely.
Ryo-sama...
Maria-chan.
Ryo-sama, I won't say it because you're that kind of person.
But you truly love the job of a police officer.
I-I can't believe you're fired.
I feel so sorry for you.
It's not just Maria-san.
She's always been treated badly.
But if I really lost Ryo-san...
...
Excuse me, President.
I have something to tell you regarding the Ryo-san investigation.
Huh?
What?
I can't believe it.
As the president of the Ryo-sensei...
...
Over there? Over there? Where is it?
Where are you taking me?
Hey! Where are we? Let's go!
What? This is my room!
This is my room!
Ouch!
What is this?
This is a trap!
Damn, it won't open.
It's useless, Ryo. The door won't open.
Reiko! Where is this?
I thought it was Nico Nico Ryo, but this room is fake!
Ryo, listen carefully.
This is the research lab of the Akimoto Group.
Research lab?
We are going to re-educate Ryo here.
He is reborn.
Re-educate? Reborn?
Anyway, you should go to bed early today.
You'll be in trouble tomorrow.
Trouble? What trouble?
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Ryo!
I'm so exited!
I'm really exited!
Uwa!
Huh, what?
I don't know!
What the?
Damn it!
It won't open, Ryo!
I won't get out of this.
It's a virtual чувствate mask.
Virtual чувствate mask?
Gipsu?
Reiko, I'll explain it to you properly!
I'll completely change you in the next week, so be prepared.
I'll change your short-term, violent, irresponsible body from the bottom of your heart and become a person who can protect the rules of society.
Don't joke!
The human nature is the greatest personality.
I'll crush your charm point and I'll change it!
How is it? Does it feel good?
I got it! Stop it!
Ugh, it's like a torture.
Then, let's start over from the moment you wake up.
It's also nice and polite to stop a alarm clock.
I got it.
Is this fine?
That's right! If you do it, you can do it!
When you wake up in the morning,
wash your face and brush your teeth.
Turn it properly and blow it!
I got it!
Is this fine?
It's fine.
Next, let's clean the room.
What?
Clean it within 30 minutes.
Let's start!
Wait a minute!
You can do it anytime you feel like it, even if you want to put a futon on it!
Other things can be cleaned anytime you feel like it!
But,
this is more convenient for a place where you can just go back and sleep by yourself.
So...
No more!
I got it!
I'll do it!
Ugh...
I'm tired.
Is this fine?
It's fine. Then, I'll order breakfast.
What?
It's a meal!
Eh?
Ugh...
What is this?
What's going on?
This is a special meal for you.
Ryo-chan's performance this morning is actually not good.
But, it's your first day, so it's a big service.
Ugh...
What?
I'm so tired!
Ryo-sama and Reiko-san disappeared together!
Where?
Where are you?
I-I'm not here!
You don't have to worry about it!
There is nothing wrong with those two!
Ugh...
How can you say that?
If Reiko-san's gurgling with the charm of a manly Ryo-sama,
What should I do?
You don't have to worry.
Anyway, Reiko-san is gurgling with Ryo-san.
Ugh...
I won't forgive you for insulting my Ryo-sama!
I can't!
It's like a car institute!
We're going to train you for the job!
Get on a bicycle and get to the starting position.
Why are you making such a fool of yourself?
Oh, no!
I got it!
Damn it, Reiko!
Start!
Yes!
What is it?
Don't go near it!
Damn it!
It's not near, it's close!
If you pass the garden of Hattori's grandfather's house, it's a 5-minute short trip!
Don't answer me!
I got it! I got it!
Start over from the beginning!
Damn it, this guy is like a demon.
Oh, the limited plan is...
Don't go near it!
Hey, wait!
Wait!
Here we go!
There you go again!
Stop!
Start over from the beginning!
Start over! Start over! Start over!
That's all for today's training!
You'll be working at the Mogi Exhibition House this afternoon.
Now, we'll take a 30-minute lunch break.
The meal is ready for you in the office.
Meal time!
You can stand the bicycle properly in the back!
I got it!
I'm going to die if I keep this up.
If you think so, don't let your negative points come out.
Reiko, you!
Such a way of listening is also calculated.
I check every detail of your daily life.
If you want to eat a proper meal, do everything in your life properly.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Now, we'll start the excretion training.
Here, this is Kamiari.
This is Kamiari.
Kamiari, I'm here for the 5-yen rice.
Oh, so you've always been watching this.
Excuse me!
Yes?
Is Kamiari Station over here?
Yes, it is!
What?
Well, turn right here and go straight to the station.
Hello!
Excuse me, where is Kamiari Komin-kann?
Go 500 meters ahead.
Oh, I did it!
I did it!
I'll enjoy this.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
Hot.
Oh, it's hot.
Wait!
I think it's hot.
OK.
I will do my best.
Let's go to the train station.
All right.
OK.
Let's Go Let's Don't Stop
This should be enough.
Really?
He's a simple man, so his alive experience will give him a chance to learn these words.
I bet his body would move even back in his daily life.
Understood. Thank you for your cooperation.
It was very delicious.
What? Why is it so dirty?
Oh, I see. I'm back to being a real Nico Nico Ryo.
That noisy demon instructor Reiko is gone.
I'm free and free from now on.
I can't calm down.
Ryo-chan is cleaning.
What's wrong with her? She might have a fever.
Senpai...
How is Ryo-chan?
She's amazing, Reiko-san.
I see.
I understand.
You should watch Ryo-chan for a while.
See you.
Reiko-san, the camera is ready.
Thank you.
This one is ready, too.
Then, both of you, please come to Ryo-chan as usual.
Yes.
Sir, can you see?
Yes, I can see.
Ryo-san will be coming soon.
Of course, we don't let you know about the camera.
You'll see his honest side.
Please watch it and consider the punishment one more time.
That's dangerous.
We just need to play.
I think it's useless.
Then, let's see.
Don't becomes fierce.
But, if this situation gets worse.
Ryo-chan would be dopo resort pneumonia.
Okay?
Okay.
resposta
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning!
Senpai!
Terai!
Look, you have a string on your wrist.
Thank you!
Reiko, tea.
I'll put it in myself.
Terai, show me your schedule when I was away.
Okay.
It's at 5.
What?
Here.
It's okay.
I'll fix it.
Thank you, Ryo-san.
Today's business is...
Yes, this is Katsushikaku Kameyari.
I'm here before the park.
This file is easy to see.
This is the house of the fourth Nakajima Katsuhiro-san.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
How is it, everyone?
You might think I'm a very criminal police officer.
But...
I don't know yet.
Care insurance?
It's too complicated for an old man.
Huh?
What?
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
I think I've been in the pension.
What are you talking about, Ryo-san?
That's ridiculous.
What?
Why is the pension ridiculous?
The pension insurance is important, Terai!
I'm in it.
Ryo-san is not in it.
I...
Ryo-chan!
Are you okay, Senpai?
You have a blue face.
My...
My logo...
My savings...
My future...
The balance is zero.
I have a lot of money.
Ryo-chan!
I'm sorry.
I can't keep this up, right?
What to go about this...
·
I don't know.
If you say that, I'll be...
The poor man has his own family and a family he's been saving up for.
Come to think of it, I'm still a young man, not alone.
I must build a happy family and be stable.
However, the other person...
Reiko!
Yes?
Your pure love for me for the past week...
That's the love for me for you!
Huh? That's...
Please, Reiko! Marry me!
Marry Ryo-chan?
Ryo-sama!
I know it's not what you think!
What the hell is going on here?!
Maria-san, calm down!
What's with this man's nervousness?
Maybe the police is not interested.
What's wrong, Tonda-kun?
Tonda-kun, say something.
That's...
Hey!
What are you doing in this emergency situation?!
Huh?!
All cars moving from Katsushika.
A young man is standing on the roof of the Marugame Department Store in Kameari Kitaguchi.
Please call the police for help at the nearby patrol car.
Don't come any closer!
If you come any closer, I'll break this rope!
What's the situation?
The culprit is a high school student who is a hostage.
He was attacked after being warned of a full-fledged assault.
What's your request?
For now, it's nothing...
So many people gathered here...
It's all over...
If you forgive him...
Shut up!
You can't do this to me!
I'm scared...
He's the only one who can't help us!
We have to do something!
At a time like this...
What can we do to help him?
I...
Yes, now is the time!
It's time to learn from your seniors.
I'm asking, Ryo-chan!
As always, please!
Yes, Ryo-san...
What...?
Y-you all...
That's...
Why do you guys...
I made up my mind to do it safely in safety.
Wh-what is that?
To commit such an dangerous job!
What is the job paid for by a public official?
Why do you have to go that far with your salary?
Are you going to get a ticket?
I can't talk about it at all.
You're all so low.
Mr. Tonda, did you get a wrong education?
What's wrong with you, Mr. Tonda?
After all, I'm a police officer.
I can only do what a police officer can do.
Please don't expect it.
I can't answer.
Mr. Tonda!
Mr. Tonda is not the real Mr. Tonda right now!
Stop it, Maria.
I'm not in the disability insurance yet.
No, I don't like that kind of Mr. Tonda.
What?
Stop it!
Let's go home, Leica!
Okay!
What are you doing?
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
You did well, young lady.
I'm not worried anymore.
Thank you, father!
I'm sorry, sir!
You idiot!
You let me get away with this!
I'm sorry!
Ryo!
You did it, Ryo!
That's my Ryo!
What's going on?
I'm the same as always!
That's right!
My Ryo is the same as always!
What do you think, everyone?
Ryo Tsukanki is still a person who is against the police?
Hmm...
For now...
This time, the punishment is reserved, so how about that, everyone?
Chief Ohara!
I just got a call from the chief.
It seems that Ryo's punishment has been reserved for the time being!
I see!
Is something wrong with my punishment?
No, it's nothing.
Ryo-chan, by the way, you said that you wanted to marry Reiko-san, didn't you?
No, it's not that!
I became a coward!
No!
I'm sure Ryo-san has a little bit of a grudge to Reiko-san!
That's why I said that!
Reiko, this is a misunderstanding!
But, the proposed Reiko-san is actually not Manzawa.
Eh?
Kei-chan!
Well, even so, he is a peaceful guy who doesn't know that he is about to be fired.
After all, Ryo-san has to be like this!
But, the proposed Reiko-san is actually a man.
If you propose to women other than me, I will not forgive you!
That's why you're a man!
Manzawa
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can see everyone
There is a wall there, there must be a wall
Come on everyone to our town
Thank you!
Eww! It's bad!
Why is this Kusaya Natto Ramen with a blue cheese flavor
ranked first in the ranking program?
I can't trust the ranking of others
In this case, I will decide the true ranking!
Next time, the final ranking!
Please look forward to it!
There is a wall there, there must be a wall
Come on everyone to our town
Thank you!