One year ago
When you are watching TV, keep the room bright and watch your shows apart from one another.
A poor man like me, he'll come to you.
There isn't a place I can be alone in.
But don't worry, look at the blue sky
The white clouds
They'll be okay eventually
Those who have no work, come to me
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red clouds
They'll be okay eventually
You got it?
You got it, you got it?
If you got it, then shut up and follow me!
Little Ryozu is a fairy
Why is it so hot?
My throat is dry
I'll drink some juice
Oh no!
What can you buy with 10 yen?
The 10 yen has grown!
Did I become smaller?
That's right, you idiot!
You're a fool!
What do you think?
You're a flower!
You're making me small again!
That's dirty!
Don't make me small!
Did I do something wrong?
You're so mean!
You already have 600 million coins!
600 million?
Look at this!
I'll let you off the hook!
Okay, I'm done!
Taking your boss's eye and eating it makes me very happy!
Bunny
Here!
It's you, you idiot!
Take this!
You idiot, stealing my small octopus
*Haha...*
You don't distinguish garbage, you wash your pants in battle,
you crawl in the elevator,
you make a lot of ugly videos!
Well, that's what everyone else is doing!
You're a cop!
I can't stand to see you act like a villain anymore.
Repent for a while.
You're a coward!
What? Don't be ridiculous!
Get back to your senses, you coward!
I won't do you any favors!
I'll give you a hard time!
*Haha...*
What are you going to do?
Stop it, old man!
*Haha...*
Don't tell me...
Stop it!
*Haha...*
Damn it!
Director Kobayashi!
He did his mistake because of me!
Damn it, I'm so angry!
Director Kobayashi, you idiot!
C-Come again!
Uwaaaah !
Uwaaah !
Damn it, I almost died...
I-I managed to survive.
Phew...
But I'm done for.
There's no one else to bring me back to normal except Hanayama.
And I don't want to lower my head.
Hm?
I smell something burned.
Uwaaah !
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Help...
Damn, those who threw away the cigarette can't get the punishment!
Huh?
Dad.
Where are you waiting for me?
Where are we waiting for you?
Never again.
I'm glad you're okay.
Isn't that a bit dangerous?
Uwaaaah !
Damn, I didn't have time to look at it!
You shouldn't be doing this.
You should have gone back to the beginning.
Uwaaah !
Damn!
I'm going to change my gum this time!
I'm the cockroach!
Damn it.
Damn, the cockroach!
Ah, ah, ah.
... However, if you walk, you'll never walk far, even if you're far away.
I'd better have some rest.
Uwaaah !
Meow!
Help!
Finally, I escaped.
But I got away from the escape room again.
Ryo-tsu is still not working.
If I find him, I'll beat him to death.
I'm sure he's playing somewhere.
Boss, I'm here!
It's me, it's me, Boss!
I'm here, Boss!
Didn't you hear Ryo-tsu's voice?
No, I didn't hear anything.
I see. It's just my imagination.
Boss, don't do that.
He'll get caught.
I'll be back.
Hey.
Ah.
You don't read books, do you?
Do you want to play soccer together?
Eh? Ah...
Um, umm, I...
What?
I can't do this. What should I do?
I'm so tired. I can't move anymore.
Hmm...
Wow!
Could it be a real fairy?
What, is it all a dream?
That's right. I can't believe you made it so small.
What is this?
I, I can't believe...
Where am I?
Ah, you're awake?
Who are you? Where am I?
I'm Shoichi. This is my room.
The fairy made me hungry and fell down so I brought her here.
What? A fairy is like me.
Yeah.
See? It's exactly like the fairy in this book.
Hmm...
No, it's not like me at all.
No matter where I look, it's not like me at all.
Ah, that's right.
A fairy must not reveal her true identity.
It's written in the book.
Yeah.
I can't keep up with you anymore. I'm going home.
Ah!
This is the 32nd floor.
Hurry up and tell me!
If I fall, I'll die!
Eh? Isn't the fairy able to fly?
It's not a fairy!
Ah, so you were hungry.
Eat this.
Oh?
Can I eat this?
Yeah.
So, um, instead...
Um, um...
Huh?
Can you be my friend?
Friend?
Yeah! I'll give you food, and I'll give you lunch.
Right? No?
Hmm...
It's not the time to be relaxed here.
I'm not free in this body.
If I'm with you, I can eat for free.
Yeah, I can't help it.
I'll stay here a little longer.
Really? Thank you!
What's wrong?
See? You're not following me at all!
Hehehe.
Here we go!
Wow! You're amazing!
Shoot!
Go!
Yes!
What? It's no good at all.
I can't be your opponent.
I'm sorry.
This is the first time I've ever been with someone.
What?
Are you playing alone?
Um...
Hmm... I can't help it.
All right! I'll do it again!
What? Really?
Yeah. It's my thanks for the dinner.
I'll tell you how to win this game.
Wow! Really?
As expected of a fairy!
You know everything.
I'm not a fairy!
You're not a fairy!
No, you're not a fairy!
He's a fairy!
What's that?
Hey, it's nothing.
DDGlessing?
Hey, Shouichi! Good morning!
Let's go.
Hey, answer me!
B-but I can't speak well...
I'm embarrassed...
So I can't speak...
Shouichi, you can't make friends because you say so much!
That's why you can't make friends, right?
I'm talking to him right now, so all I have to do is answer him.
But I'm...
Hey, what should I do?
Oh, right! I wonder if I can do something with the fairy's magic!
You can do it!
It can't be helped if you make friends with magic!
That's right.
What should I do?
I got it, I got it. I'll help you.
Really?
Leave it to me.
But you know what? I'll help you, but it's up to you whether you can make friends or not.
Got it?
Ryo, you're coming again today?
Ryo hasn't been back since yesterday.
What?
I haven't heard of him going on a trip, but he suddenly disappeared.
Did something happen to him?
Oh, well, he must be selling oil somewhere again.
He's really been slacking off lately.
I have to teach him a lesson and get him back on his feet.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
All right!
Now, that's the first strategy: say hello in the morning!
Yeah!
Hello...
Hey, I'm just saying hello!
You're listening? Hey, you, just answer!
I've never been so nervous before!
Okay! Who can solve this problem?
See? The second strategy!
Raise your hands while you're in class!
Raise your hands now!
But it's embarrassing...
I told you not to cry!
N-no way...
I'm so frustrated...
You're the cat from yesterday!
The last one, Miyahara!
I knew it wouldn't work...
It's not just that!
Do something about that!
What's that cat doing here?
Okay! The third strategy!
Invite everyone to class!
Go on!
Okay...
What's wrong? Go on!
Move, Giant Shoichi!
B-but... it's embarrassing...
Idiot!
You can't make friends with that kind of thing!
If you don't do it, there's nothing you can do!
I-I know... I know... but my body is...
Hey, lend me a ball...
Thanks!
Hey! What are you doing?
Are you motivated?
B-but...
Ugh...
We're working on it right now.
You can do it later.
You know, Shoichi...
Don't make me say it again!
Right now, I'm...
Hey, let me go!
Help me!
This way!
Miss Fairy!
Hey!
Are you okay?
I'm fine...
I see...
You're really pathetic!
You couldn't do anything after all, huh!
Y-yeah...
Do you really think you can make friends by just running away?
You just have to talk to me!
You can play with everyone if you do that!
If you can't do that, you're alone in your life!
Do you get it?
No... I'm...
What?
You don't have to make friends with me anymore.
It's fine. I have a fairy.
Shoichi, you...
If I have a fairy, I won't be alone!
Right? You'll always be by my side, right?
Don't joke!
I've never had a child like you!
Friends are no joke!
I don't care about you anymore!
See ya!
No, fairy!
F-fairy...
Okay, anyone who can read this kanji?
Wait, how pathetic of him.
He shouldn't have cared about that guy and should have gone home.
Okay, anyone who can do the next question?
See, it's exactly the same as the fairy in this book!
Oh, you were hungry, weren't you?
Eat this!
Wow, you're amazing, fairy!
I-I'm sorry, this is the first time I've ever said "someone".
Hey, line up! Line up!
Let's eat!
The lunch we're having soon won't be the same as the lunch at the family restaurant!
Huh?
Fairy-san!
You came home?
Well, it was a promise to let me eat.
That's right.
Shouichi, show us your guts this time!
Okay!
Listen, Shouichi.
This is your last strategy.
The one who played an active part in the gym is a class hero.
You have to get excited and shoot!
Yeah, but...
But what?
I'm not good at sports.
I taught you yesterday!
It's the same as the game!
Don't look away from the ball!
Leave the rest to me!
Huh? No way...
Look! The ball is coming!
Idiot! What are you avoiding?
Get a good trap!
But...
Don't be so stubborn!
Chase the ball!
Yes, sir!
Thanks!
OK, I got it!
Good!
I got it!
It's coming!
You did it!
Yes! Triple, Shouichi!
Yes!
Three in front!
To the left!
Keep it up, Shouichi!
Stop!
Right!
Left!
That's amazing!
-Wow! -It's true!
-There's another one! -Cheers!
Can you hear me? Everyone's cheering for you!
Yeah!
-Wow! -Wow!
Alright, trap and shoot!
Alright!
Hit it!
Shoichi!
That was amazing, Shoichi!
I've never seen a dribble like that before!
You were hiding something you're good at!
Oh, what?
That's right.
It's a trick.
Ms. Fairy...
Did you come to make friends for me?
Thank you, Ms. Fairy.
Alright, the match is over!
Hurry up!
Yeah!
"Chess"
He's quite a lively guy, isn't he?
I'll get him back to normal soon enough.
"Battle Państrum"
Finally! It's the F Dios!
"The Fellowship"
Yes!
Banzai!
I'm back! I'm back to normal! Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Ryo-chan, where did you really go?
You got caught up in a big case, didn't you?
No way!
I'm sure he's thinking of excuses to get rid of me!
When he comes back, I'll tell him this and that!
Buz-chan!
Ryo-chan!
Reiko! Nagagawa!
Senpai!
Buz-chan!
Ryo-chan!
This idiot was in the way until now!
Buz-chan, there's no reason for this!
Kikumi-mon!
Please listen to me, Buz-chan!
No excuses!
Where are you walking?
You're not listening to me, Buz-chan!
Wow, Shouichi! What a hot trick!
It's a trick! Let's play soccer again!
Yes!
Fairy! Help me!
Oh, it's summer again this year!
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
I see!
It's big, small, big, small,
Out of the way!
Big, small, big,
In the southern wind!
It's big, small, small,
It's large, small!
In the southern wind!
Oh, it's summer again this year!
It's here, it's here, it's here!
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
Oh, it's summer again this year!
It's here, it's here!
It's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
It's here! It's here! It's here!
Oh, it's summer again this year!
It's huge, small, small,
Out of the way!
In the southern wind!
Nagisabe
What? A cursed camera?
You said that I'd be unhappy if I didn't take 100 pictures of your swimsuit within a week?
It's not that easy!
Wait a minute! I'll take as many pictures as you want!
Get a swimsuit picture!
I'm counting on you!
There's a turtle over there
There's a turtle for sure
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!