When you watch TV, make the room bright and take a look away.
Come to me if you're broke.
I'm not here but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll get through it somehow.
I have no job.
Come to me if you're broke.
I'm not here but I'm worried.
I have no job.
I'll get through it somehow.
I'm not here but I'm worried.
Hoi!
The Yes!
You saw a train going in front of Hakuchu Highway, you've got guts!
No! No it's not! This is my car!
What?!
The Man Who Has Missed Too Many Locks
Then, to keep your car from being stolen,
get rid of your tires and lock on the car.
You're saying you're getting rid of the gasoline?
That's right.
You didn't come here to sell the tires, did you?
If I was this cautious, I wouldn't have been robbed.
I don't want to regret it for taking so much trouble.
So, what do you want from the station?
Oh, that's right!
Actually, I heard strange sounds from a house where no one was.
Akisuka!
Where is the house? Is it near here?
It's the third floor. I have to hurry.
Um, screws, screws...
Is it this house?
Yes, it's the top floor.
It's the door in the back.
What is this number of holes?
There are 30.
30?
And they are all dimple key types that are strong for picking.
As an anti-theft model house, I received a medal from the Anti-Theft Association.
Then are you the owner here?
Thanks to you, I sold all of them.
I have about 5 more houses in the city.
Huh? It won't open.
Oh, I made a mistake.
This way. This way.
Just opening the door won't make it any better.
However, I don't think there are people who can break through this kind of equipment and work in the office.
Look!
Just hurry and open it!
Yes!
It's open.
Good.
What is it?
This is...
A spear!
What is this door?
It's 1 meter thick.
Is it a safe?
The window...
The glass is intact.
That means...
Ah!
I did it again.
I forgot to close it.
Close?
Forget?
I'm not going outside yet.
You can't go inside.
Ah! Senpai! Over there!
They're there.
I'll call for support!
I don't think I can wait!
No!
Senpai!
Huh?
What?
Ah!
We can't take anything!
Ososuke, what is that thing?
Ah...
To be able to jump from this height...
It's just a piece of cake.
"Akira"
It was a high-frequency signal.
But the security equipment inside was perfect, so it seems that only this gold piece was stolen.
Thank you very much.
But, it's still insufficient to enter the Aki-su even though it was so well-protected.
I have to be more and more strict!
Um, it's just a matter of forgetting to close the window.
Ana, Ryu-chan, did you change your cell phone?
Yeah, I borrowed it from Jomae-san. It's a hotline.
Senpai, Jomae-san's house has been asked for special security.
I'm worried because after something like that happens.
It seems that if something happens, he will be able to contact me immediately.
Hmm...
Oh, I didn't expect you to promise to receive money personally, Ryu-chan.
What?
It's just a security within the scope of the police officer's duty.
That's it.
Of course, Senpai.
Of course! I got a thousand yen of money!
It's our job to protect the safety of the citizens' lives.
Ah!
Yes, yes.
What's the matter?
Yes, I understand. I'll be right there.
What happened?
It's an emergency. I'll be back in a moment.
He must have received money.
Hmm...
Let's focus on Birulli!
"Police Force"
This is...
Are they running?
There's no way!
I'm going to start this!
The door will open when I get there!
No way!
Why?
What?
Alright, let's go.
What the hell is this?
This is a side-respirator.
If the visitor does something suspicious,
it automatically activates the anti-aircraft system.
What do you mean, "something suspicious"?
I just got a little close to the wall.
I'm in trouble.
What the hell is this?
There's a infrared sensor going around the corridor.
What?
Please use this.
An infrared gobble?
There's a sensor going around the corridor like this?
There's only clear space on the ceiling.
I can't see anything.
Did it go through?
I did it.
What?
This time, it's a trap.
The suspicious will be sent directly to the underground parking lot's safe box.
Excuse me, but Mr. Ryotsu, please start over.
What?
We can't let anything come in front of us, right?
Hey, Yotsu!
Why don't you just open the door?
No, you have to press the code to open it outside.
Code?
Please press the 26-digit code next to the door within 5 seconds.
What?
I know it's just one time, so you have to remember it.
The code is 635025.
231895447139652824059
That's it.
What did you say?
635002318954471396...
Time out.
Again?
Please start over.
Yes.
Yes!
This is the third time.
63500231895447139652824059
Lock removed.
I'm sure there's no more.
6350023189544713965
Temperature sensor!
Laser!
I'm going to kill you!
Let's start over.
I quit.
I'm going to stop.
Oh, my God.
It's faster than I thought.
6350023189544713965
Mr. Ryotsu...
As expected of Mr. Ryotsu.
Climbing the outer wall...
But I have to set up an electric power line for the outer wall, too...
Well, what do you want me to do?
Yes.
Yes. I would like to show you the latest defense device.
What?
This security system is perfect for all the closures in the house.
The window is a 30cm thick bullet glass.
There is also a sensor alarm on the support.
There are also many infrared TV cameras and laser devices installed on the balcony.
The wall inside the house is 1m thick.
You can shoot missiles inside.
And here is the central control room where you can see all the TV cameras and control all the defense devices.
How is it?
This is perfect for security, isn't it?
Ryochi.
Is this the Earth Defense Army?
Yes. Ryochi security service.
Yes.
I will ask you right away.
Today is the third time.
Ryochi, I'm sorry.
Please look at the gas.
I forgot to close the window of B.
Ryochi, I'm sorry.
I forgot to wash the laundry.
Ryochi.
What a worried guy.
Jomae calls more than 10 times a day.
I will call him more than 10 times a day.
He really likes the plug.
I'm sorry.
Maybe a friend will be angry at me if I leave.
It's not a problem.
Right.
Thanks.
Ryochi.
I hope you don't explain to the employee.
That's the truth.
In thenimari Basin
What a strange man you are.
What is a nice person?
What?
Ryozu-san!
What's wrong? What happened?
Here, have a drink.
I'm asking you what happened.
I can't sleep so I thought I'd have dinner.
What?
Cheers.
No, stop kidding!
Don't!
You said on the phone, "Please help me!"
and now you're yelling like you're dying.
I came here at this hour!
I can't sleep so I thought I'd have dinner!
I'm sorry!
I was alone at night and I was so lonely.
Alone?
Then what's this picture?
You have a family, right?
My wife and children left.
Huh?
A few months ago...
It was last summer.
I bought my son a bicycle on his 10th birthday.
My son practiced every day.
When he finally got to ride it by himself,
the bicycle got stolen.
Did you give it to him?
Yes.
But in the end, he couldn't find it.
I'm sorry.
When I saw my son cry that day, I decided.
Thieves don't go away from the world.
That's why I will protect my family with my own hands!
So, you started to lock up everything.
Yes.
But this is a bit too much, isn't it?
My wife told me so.
My wife and I often argue over the keys.
One day...
I said, "I don't want this house full of keys anymore."
I took my son out.
So you live in a big apartment like this alone.
Yes.
Well, I don't know if you're lonely alone.
But what your wife says is the best.
I'm not proud of it, but I've never locked up a house.
What?
Aren't you worried about that?
Zhin, zhin, zhin.
When we were kids, we were...
We didn't have a house with a lock.
That's why the neighborhood next door was free to go out.
It's because it was a peaceful time.
In this day and age, if there was no lock, I'm just worried.
Hmm...
Huh?
A chain.
What's this chain?
I...
Th-thief!
Oh, no!
Bastard!
Ugh...
What's wrong with me?
You idiot!
I made you a secret!
Ugh!
What, what is this apartment?
I've forgotten to lock the toilet door.
I've got a bad feeling about this!
Well, I'm glad I was there.
I can't say it's still safe.
Hmm...
We have to make it more and more serious!
Hey, Naoko Komachi! Are you here?
What's up, primitive man?
What do you need us for?
Actually, I have a favor to ask you.
Oh, Senpai.
There's no call from Jomae at all lately.
What's wrong with him?
He's calmed down, hasn't he?
No, he hasn't.
I don't think he'll be able to calm down so easily.
Oh, I heard a rumor.
Yes, Ryozu Security Service.
What? You moved?
I guess it's around here.
You said it yourself.
I came to the Nasa Bunch, but there's no home.
Huh? There's an antenna here.
What? There's a keyhole here.
Oh, this is...
No way!
Oh, Ryozu!
I was just about to pick you up.
Is this the house you moved to?
Yes. It's the underground shelter that NASA has developed.
I sold all the houses.
I transferred all my property.
There's only one exit here, so I didn't forget to close the window.
I think it's the best place for a freak like me.
But underground...
But you still locked the door?
I'm worried about a house without a key.
Huh?
How is it, Ryozu?
Mr. Ryozu, if there's anything you're worried about, please tell me.
I want to make amends.
It's true that there's no window, so it's hard to get in.
All the furniture is locked and can't be taken.
It's a house like a safe example.
But it's not hard to live in a place like this, is it?
Huh?
Safety comes first, so that's not a big problem.
I'm worried about the house.
The heavy rain in the Kanto region has brought great damage to various areas.
According to the City of Kanto,
Hitchhiking is pouring down over 500 mm per hour in the south of Kanto.
The house, which has been flooded from above and below the floor,
has reached 500 mu...
Well, if you like it, I don't care.
No matter how safe I am,
I'm sorry if you live in this house even if you get paid.
Is there still any danger?
Please say anything.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm saying whether this place is suitable for a human to live in.
The most important thing is safety.
In other words, a house is like a fortress protected by the enemy.
I'm happy if the rain stops.
It's the 21st century now.
I think you should rethink that idea.
I don't remember being lectured by you.
I'm going home.
Wait.
There are still many security equipment that Mr. Ryotsu wants to see.
Don't worry.
There's no thief who can enter this house.
What's this door? It's very hard.
You bastard.
Ouch!
It's a sea.
Mr. Ryotsu, do something quickly.
I know.
I know, I know.
But the water pressure is too strong.
It's dangerous here.
Let's go out.
You can't leave this house.
That's not possible.
What's important is home or life.
What's important is the future.
I understand.
I just want to make a living.
What is this?
Run!
My house...
What should I do?
I lost everything...
What did you lose?
I lost everything.
Everything?
You just lost a house.
What do you want to protect?
Why did you lock your house?
That's...
You locked an empty treasure chest!
Dad!
Shinya...
Sakiko...
What's going on?
My wife and son came to visit me because they were worried about you.
How have you been, Shinya?
I'm fine. How about you, Dad?
I'm fine.
Shinya said he'd be lonely without you.
I see.
There he is, Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
I found the bike you asked for.
Oh, you found it!
A bike...
This is the bike you were looking for, right?
This bike...
Shinya Jomai.
Yes.
It's your bike.
Oh, my bike!
You're good!
Of course.
Don't underestimate a commuter car.
Ryo-tsu!
Thank you so much for this trip!
From now on,
I'm going to work together with my family.
I'm glad.
Don't try to lock the car too hard.
Okay!
Yes!
By the way, about that bike...
Yeah!
The house I inherited all my property was washed away.
Ah!
What are you going to do?
You said you'd pay me 50,000 yen per month!
You called me out 10 times a day and 20 times a day!
That's not true.
I'm not going to do that!
Ryo-chan!
You didn't promise to personally get paid, did you?
You were just guarding it within the scope of your job as a policeman, right?
That's right!
I didn't promise to get paid at all!
N-No.
Y-Yes.
By the way, Ryo-tsu.
You promised to bring me Tokujou sushi if I found a bike, right?
That's not true!
I asked for special help from 300 commuter cars in the entire Kanto area.
Tokujou sushi 300 yen.
I'll take care of it.
300 commuter cars!
I lost everything too.
What are you talking about?
I'll definitely have you pay for 300 commuter cars!
Ehehe!
Even if you lie and cheat a little
Sometimes you're helping someone
Baby, do you know me?
I'm headed for tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't get sick, I'll do what I have to do
Cute breathing
It's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than seeing it again
Nakagawa and his father meet for the first time in a long time
But the meeting place is far away
Speaking of Nakagawa Ryuichiro
He is the busiest businessman in the world
Where will he meet?
Space?
Next time, visit the base of Nakagawa
Thank you
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Come to our town
Thank you
See you