Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♪
♪ Overcoming the new age lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city in yellow ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing trendy things ♪
♪ Because my face is 100 times more decided ♪
♪ Let it bleed ♪
♪ Everybody come on ♪
♪ Let's start running ♪
♪ Dreams always can't be stopped ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Love you one ♪
♪ Everybody can do ♪
♪ Just a little bit ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt to spit it out ♪
♪ I don't want to be in a hurry ♪
♪ I want to be strong and high ♪
♪ Be strong and brave ♪
♪ It doesn't matter what I do ♪
♪ I'm sure that I will find a new home ♪
♪ But tomorrow, let's move on ♪
♪そう, the wind is blowing ♪
♪ The wind is blowing ♪
But...
It was all a failure.
We were only left with a heavy sense of defeat.
Sendai was only one step away.
I still remember the humiliation two years ago.
Thinking about this man, I can't sleep at night.
But it's the end of this year.
I'm sure I'll be the leader this year.
This year, I'll make sure Ryo and Kankichi get their money back.
I know it's a big deal, but I don't want you to get involved.
I know.
So, everyone,
let's start the 21st Ryo-Kankichi Bonus Battle.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It'll be over soon.
Kikuchi,
you shouldn't have brought a baby to an important meeting.
It can't be helped.
His wife is a man who can't even pay off his debt.
So he left home.
I'm being pulled out of my pay, which is the amount that Ryo doesn't pay.
But in fact,
if Ryo is your opponent,
I don't think any hand will be able to reach you.
What are you talking about?
Your father,
the former manager of Sato Deki,
was the president of the 8th shopping street,
and he risked his life to get Ryo's money.
He was determined to do anything.
He started the sports festival as Mr. Sukeroku.
But thanks to that, he became a kikkuri.
He was a bad guy.
That's right.
This time,
I prepared a new weapon to take Ryo's bonus.
A new weapon?
I've been living in a plastic shop for 30 years.
I've used all the technology I have,
and developed it over 90% of the shopping street and for three months.
Wow.
This is the Ryo's Navigation System.
In short, Ryo Navi.
The preparation is complete.
All that's left is to catch Ryo on the day and take the bonus.
Oh.
The name of the operation is "Sky Eye Operation".
"Sky Eye Operation"
Mr. Ryo.
Mr. Shinhika Ryo Tsukankichi.
Yes.
Here's the bonus.
Yahoo!
As I thought,
for 180 days and two days,
every day,
I went to the 8th shopping street
and continued to go to school.
The day you arrived at the school.
It's all for you.
It was all for this cute bonus.
Mr. Ryo.
What is this year's bonus used for?
In fact,
I have a one-tenth of a rarified model of the limited-edition NASA-specialized Radicon Space Shuttle.
You always do that.
Well, let's go to the bank right away.
If you don't pay the deposit today, it's canceled.
Paragraph 28
I don't think I can use it for a while, just 30 people.
I'm always the most alert of you all.
No matter how strong the situation gets!
Time's up.
We should make a move with a couple of more of them.
Where are you going?
Don't push me!
No problem.
My them is good at disguise like sunglasses.
Oh, damn.
Hey, young lady.
I'm dropping this.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Huh?
What is that?
I think it's like a tried-and-runśnie много.
I thought I'd be able to see her.
But she's more beautiful than a bride.
Oh, that's scary.
Well, then...
Be careful.
That was close.
But they're not blind.
Hey, Ryo!
Huh?
I forgot my handkerchief.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What?
Oh, no!
It's Ryo!
Give my wife back my salary!
You're not going to get away with that.
Take this, Nippon!
Take this, Kumogakure!
You bastard!
You're not going to get away with this!
Well, then.
I'll give you a bonus.
That's the ramen shop's camera.
What's wrong?
It's right there.
I'm sorry.
I was just about to ask you the same thing.
Damn it!
Mr. Ozaki, could you answer the call?
This is Kazuchika Shomae.
The waiting is a failure.
Ryo ran away.
The embassy has launched an action.
Roger.
Mr. Ozaki, are you okay?
It's quite possible that Ryo is running away now.
We're now on the front line of the Sky High operation.
Ryo has a navigation computer embedded in his belt.
wird
『その電波を人工衛星がキャッチして and have a technical help...
『つながるのはいつもの謎で、 where is where...
なんだかチンプンパンプンだね! It's weird...
こんなのでホントに上手く行くのかい? Will things go so smoothly?
ざいにち米軍も使ってるシステムですよ It's properly built in the making.
『信頼度は200%以上です』 I've made it more than 200%, though.
『でも私はどうしても新しい機械は信用できなくてね』 But I'm still unconfident about new machines and* all.
はいはい。今回 you can go on with your camera once.
『ようなびサドロ開始!』 quero bodo!
"I'm here to find you!"
Welcome!
Here We Are!
Street Riders Start!
" fug...!
"I got to show you the power
"of a motorcycle I got in front of me!
I'll show you now!
He even brought a bike!
Then...
Buddy!
You're 10 years too early!
You're so naive, Ryo!
I used to be a pro racer!
I heard you talk about that so many times!
Hello?
I'm out of Street Riders.
He's going to the next town.
Ryo is heading to the next town.
Shoot him in the middle of the bridge.
Damn it!
They're not in a good mood this year.
It's safer to leave the town and go to the next bank.
We're not going to leave here, Ryo!
N-no way!
How did you know we were going to leave here?
Ryo, there's no escape.
What's going on?
Bonus!
That's enough!
No!
I-I can't believe you jumped into the M zeon's river...
Damn it...
Run!
I'll get you!
Wait!
Let go of me!
I'm a human being!
I will die if I jumped into this fine river!
Let go of me!
Right.
What are you doing?
What?
Did you drop this misubo-like gate ball?
Or is it Nagashima Shigeo's sign ball?
It's Nagashima's sign ball.
It's a gate ball, of course!
I'm going to borrow the fire.
Damn it.
How did he know where I was going?
What's this code?
There's a battery in the glovebox?
You were watching me through the navigation system?
That's a good idea.
But I'm not the one who's going to get caught like that.
I have an important mission, which is to go to the bank all day long and deposit money so that I don't have to cancel my reservation for the radio control.
What?
You're a fool!
Oh, you're right.
The hot pot I made isn't as easy as it is to break when you jump into a river.
Is this really where Ryo-san is?
I can't trust you at all.
Hey, Ohara-san.
How is it?
Did you catch Ryo-tsu?
It's just a matter of time.
This is also thanks to Ohara-san's help.
It's very cheap to exchange the four belts.
I won't bother you anymore because of him.
No, no, please be on a large boat.
I'm counting on you.
Mr. Osaki!
What is it, Grandma?
He suddenly stopped moving, but I think he's broken.
That can't be true.
It's closed.
It seems he's running away and taking a break.
Ohara-san, I'll see you at the end of the trip.
Is it finally?
Please get on.
Yes, sir!
Please stop!
The contingency has increased.
Ryo-san is currently hidden in a Kameari Hybrid Hotel.
Let's clash at once!
The Skyeye Operation is now entering the final stage.
Everybody, head for the hotel!
Yes, sir!
Yeah!
Thanks to you.
Good luck!
Is Ryo-san really here?
Please believe the latest technology.
Good luck!
This option CD ROM is connected to the radio waves from the satellite and finds Ryosan's location in the hotel.
This room...
Everyone, Ryosan is on the 817th room veranda!
A-Han is on the 816th room veranda!
B-Han is on the 818th room veranda!
C-Han and D-Han, enter from the 817th room!
Enter from the hotel!
The Kameari Shopping Street is in this area.
Everyone, be ready!
Be sure to win!
Yuki, we finally have two people.
I'm going.
B-Han, the location is complete.
B-Han, please.
B-Han, on the 818th room veranda.
The Kameari Shopping Street is complete.
C-Han, D-Han.
C-Han and D-Han, also complete.
Roger that.
Countdown, start!
Go!
Report! Did you succeed in capturing the target?
It's a crow!
A crow?
No, no, no, no!
Come on, it's 'a crow!
It's a crow!
It was C-Han.
It wasn't 'a crow, but 'a crow.
No, it was a red crow.
You're right.
If it wasn't for him,
we wouldn't have been able
to catch him this quickly.
We'd had to do this.
We were all selling a lot of energy.
He's up to the rock we had stuffing in this one.
Damn, I'm so scared.
I'll wash the money.
Oh, money is falling.
Money?
Money, money, money, money.
I found it.
Children's Bank?
Damn it. I'm a coward.
I was caught easily without using the machine.
You're right. This may be the best way for Ryo.
As expected of an old man.
What have I done?
Come on, get in line.
Is that okay, Mr. Ohara?
Please, take it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ryo. I'll take it.
What's wrong? It's strange.
It's better not to pay.
I'm sorry.
Please, take it.
I see.
You're going to be in trouble if you don't say anything.
I'm sorry, Sachiko.
I can't wait to pick you up.
Who is she?
My sister, Sachiko.
She works in a cold place in the Northland where her limbs are numb and her bones are itching.
What?
She's still a child.
Why?
If you talk to me, it will be long.
I won't forget.
I won't remember anything.
Sachiko was born on a cold, snowy night.
Her parents were happy.
They wished her to have a happy child and gave her a name.
But...
Ryo
What happened to Sachiko?
A sudden accident of her parents.
Her insurance should have been paid.
and the insurance money was taken by a bad broker.
Furthermore, the house collapsed,
Besides, the dead parents failed their studies
and found out that there was a debt of 200 million yen.
Sachiko's relative who helped pay the debt took her away.
However,
the relative was actually the president of the Akutoku Construction Company,
and even the young Sachiko was forced to work.
He didn't let me eat.
I tried to get rid of Sachiko,
but every time I got a debt of 200 million yen,
and I made up my mind.
If I had just earned it,
I wouldn't have made it before Sachiko got older.
I would have to pay all my salary and bonuses for the debt.
I don't care how much people in the world hate me for that.
I want to be stronger in the future.
But young Sachiko was wrong.
Even though you are didn't mean it.
He suffered a lot of bad things for so many people.
My brother is a species that can not survive.
Oh yes he is.
I can't believe you are a species that can't survive.
Please forgive me.
It's okay.
Everyone,
maybe I did the wrong thing.
But he will have the enemy's attention.
I was trying to live as a human being.
Please forgive me in the name of Daijiro Ohara.
I was trying to get a bonus without thinking about the situation of Ryo.
Ryo, it's your bonus.
Give it to your sister soon.
But this is...
I don't care about the debt.
I'm a million times happier than Ryo.
Good luck.
Don't lose.
I will never forget your kindness.
I'm sure my sister will be happy.
Hello, everyone.
What's wrong with you?
What is this?
That's Ryo's sister, Sachiko.
That's strange.
Um.
This is a magazine cutout.
And I don't think he has a sister.
Ryo, if you get caught up in that story, you can't take my bonus.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'll just go to the bank.
What's this?
Who did this?
You did this to me?
Based on past data, you are 95% sure to stay in this cafe.
It's as you thought.
There was a reason why I waited.
P-Promo's father?
What's this?
This is a debt-free weapon against Ryo and Kikuchi.
Debt hex.
Is this Debt hex?
I secretly developed it for the next year's bonus runoff, but...
It's 80% complete!
I'm sure I can defeat you even in these calculations.
I'm not going flexible!
The link between Shocking X...
It's Ryo's work!
How did it work?
No!
Ahhhhhhh!
This is bad!
Electric Shock!
Uwaaaaaaahhh!
Is this too much!?
Don't worry.
I will consider your strength and set it to a voltage that will not die.
Well, I think it will be able to make you faint.
Nyaaahhh!
Electric Shock!
Uwaaaaaaahhh!
This is my bonus.
I don't want to do this.
You are the one who didn't pay the debt.
How about I give you the bonus?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Uwaaaaaaahhh!
It's only one step away!
What on Earth!
As you all see
there is no way you can take it!
There is no way you can take it!
Even if the chief allows it
God won't allow it!
Oh, God is also...
Wait!
What's happening!?
We're almost there!
We got it!
Hey, what's Ryotsu up to?
What are you doing?
If you have any money left in your bank account,
you can pay it back at the bank.
What a hard work.
Hirotsu, if you want to pay back the debt,
you can help me.
Stop talking!
It's a job with concentration.
My bonus!
I'll pay you back next year,
Ryotsu Kankichi.
Haha! I did it!
I found the secret
and got the highest exchange rate
with the bank account.
Men are not about their faces or bodies,
but their hearts and minds.
Do you get it?
Next time on Ryotsu Mecha-Mote宣言!
Take care!
Subtitled by 方 Hou.