"Ryo-chan's Money"
Hey, Reiko, please!
Give me 1,000 yen!
No, just 500 yen!
But, the head of the department told me not to lend money to you.
You're so annoying.
I told you I wouldn't lend you money, but you didn't!
I'm not asking you to do it.
I'm asking Reiko to do it.
We're going to eat lunch now.
It's in the way, so go over there.
Wait a minute.
Please, Reiko.
If you can't afford 500 yen, you can pay 300 yen.
No, if you can afford 150 yen, you can buy ramen.
I'll go around three times and say "one".
Kankichi.
Lemon.
What are you doing?
I'm imitating a dog.
There's a hide-and-seek competition outside the school this time.
It's more like a practice.
I have about 150 yen.
Huh?
Are you sure, Lemon?
Yes.
I'll lend you the money for your lunch.
Reiko's so sweet.
If you saw it, tell her that from the beginning.
By the way, what are you doing here?
Actually...
A baby is born.
What?
A baby is born?
When watching TV, make your room bright and look away.
Try walking and couldn't find a baby?
Go away, too.
Look where you're going.
You have no money to sleep.
Come near me.
Please.
Don't be scared.
What are you doing?
Listen.
Look at his face.
He has more scum than I do.
A friend.
What?
I wonder if it'll work out somehow
Those who have no job, come to me
I don't have one, but I'm worried
Look, it's on fire
I wonder if it'll work out somehow
Those who have no job, come to me
I know, I know, I know
If you do, just come to me
Eh? You're gonna give birth?
I-I didn't know you...
W-what are you doing?
You don't give birth when you're in kindergarten, do you?
I-I didn't know that
That means the baby is...
I didn't know that!
I didn't know that! I didn't know that!
Matoi-chan, are you okay?
Eh?
I'm okay, I'm just a little bit sick
Huh?
M-Matoi-chan!
I-I thought...
Why are you staring at me?
Eh?
No way!
Matoi-chan!
Eh? What are you talking about?
Matoi, I can't help it if I can't do it
Huh?
So?
Why?
When will you give birth?
Eh? Why do I have to give birth?
Eh?
Kankichi, are you okay?
Oh, Reimu, why are you here?
I'm here to tell Kankichi about the baby
Oh, so...
Matoi-chan didn't give birth to a baby, did she?
I don't remember saying that
But...
I was touching my belly
That's because...
When Matoi-chan ate 50 dumplings for 10 minutes,
she just ate them and ate them all
Eh?
Hehehe
Then, who gives birth to a baby?
My mother
What?
Then, Matoi and Reimu have a brother or a sister?
That's right
I see, that's good, Reimu
Kankichi, please give birth to a baby
I'm embarrassed
Hahaha
I see, I see
You're going to be a big sister soon, aren't you?
Big sister?
Heh
Lemon will be a big sister
Now, come in
Reiko-san, Nakagawa-san, welcome
Good evening
Sorry for suddenly interrupting you
No, it's okay
It's no big deal that you're in the way
You came here often
No, Matoi and Lemon's mother
didn't notice that you were pregnant
It has nothing to do with Kankichi
Mom?
Hehehe
As usual
This is boring
From us
Please
Kankichi's boring things are really boring
Sorry
I'm grateful to you two
Thank you
Seriously, I'm just getting more and more hungry
Hehe
Are you going to give birth at your home?
Matoi and Lemon are also giving birth at home
Hmm, if you ask me, when I was a child, it was normal to give birth at home in the city of Chita
But is there any Samba-san now?
There is
The veteran is quite old, though
It's Samba-san who took me up
Huh?
Grandma is 101 years old
How old is that Samba?
Tome-san is 119 years old
Are you an ambulance?
Even if it's Matoi, the neighborhood people put most of the Samba-san in the top
There are 10,000 babies who were adopted by the Samba family in the 114th year of the Samba era
Yeah
Come to think of it, I'm also going to give birth at home
What? Nakagawa too?
The rich Nakagawa is the same as me
I feel a sense of intimacy
Really?
I think that 50 doctors and 100 pregnant women came to my house
There are so many doctors of hope that I'm going to give birth
It's so close
There's TV broadcast used in this hospital
There are also the broadcasts broadcast in the United States
We don't have a lot of lives
Right, there are no Linda
I feel a little bit of intimacy
But I made a mistake
Did you change your name?
Is it still?
Yes, I'm just going to think about it
My father and my stepson are depressed
My step-daughter is Matoi
So I can't take off the clothes
What about this?
"Giboshi-bara"
"Bara" huh. Cute.
There's more.
"Shouyu-kikai-kirin"?
It's not like the letters have too many "kakushu" letters!
Why is it "shouyu"? Are you stupid?
You're trying to fit in with your brother, aren't you?
I get it.
Then, since you're a sushi restaurant kid, what are these names?
"Saba", "Tako", "Maguro", "Kisu", "Shimaji", "Surumeika"?
Kankichi, you're not just a sushi restaurant kid!
What kind of name is "Giboshi-Surumeika"?
They're all so noisy.
Then, what are "Rommel", "Tiger", "Leopardo", "Melkaba", "Challenger", and "Kyuji-shiki"?
Why did you name your grandchildren after me?
I get it, I get it!
Then, what are "Giboshi", "Karugustaf", "Mako", "F", and "Beradonna"?
Which country are you from?
What's your name, Lemon?
I don't know yet. I'll think about it after I see your face.
I hope you're born healthy.
I'll be fine, Lemon.
Oh, Lemon, what's wrong?
You're born again?
No, I'm not.
Where's Kankichi?
He's on patrol.
I see.
He'll be back soon, so you should wait.
If he's not here, then it's fine.
See you.
Oh, here they are!
It's been a while since I've seen so many of them!
Huh?
Lemon, what are you doing here?
How long have you been on patrol, Kankichi?
Oh, there's a lot.
Anyway, what's wrong?
Hmm...
Hm?
Kankichi...
What?
But, can you really be my sister?
Huh?
Actually...
What?
Well...
I'm here!
Master Nakoto!
Well, what are you working on here?
I'm taking care of my little sister.
Talk about cute.
You're really cute.
Should I give you a hug?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Ah!
Oh, what do I do?
He puked and started crying.
Makoto, do you know that?
Yeah.
Oh, Mako, you're so great.
You're really like your brother.
But I don't think I can be his sister.
You were depressed because of that?
It's okay. You can be a good sister.
Really?
Of course. I guarantee it.
That's not true.
You can have a younger family for the first time.
You have expectations and concerns, don't you?
You're confident.
To point out opportunities,
you have to get yourself a partner to support your child's birth.
How?
How.
What?
You want Lemon to come here?
I'm a home-born, so I must go and get Miso.
To raise a baby.
Has Miso been here recently?
Yes.
I have to talk to you at this hour.
Here you go.
Okay. I'll do my best.
Happy, Lemon asked me to do a job.
It's an important job.
You say good things sometimes.
Oh, right.
Hello?
Oh, Geppardo.
I see. You got the job.
I think it's okay.
But sometimes I have to say yes.
Then you'll take responsibility and look after me.
Don't worry. I'll get more.
It's a useless job.
I understand. I'll follow you.
See you.
This is the right way.
Oh, right.
You should remember the characteristic buildings.
Yes.
Be careful because the traffic is intense.
Okay.
Turn the alley next to this post office.
The second building is Sanba's house.
Okay.
I'll go see.
Is it here?
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Wow.
You came, Lemon.
You're here.
Are you still okay?
No, it is in deep pain.
I'm fine.
That's great.
I thought you wouldn't make it in time.
Even today is scheduled...
huh ...
uh ...
Is it okay?
Ah ah...
I-it's tough.
What!? The X-ray started!?
Where's the lemon!?
I see. All right. Leave the rest to me!
Yup.
Did you catch him?
I'm in a bit of a trouble.
Is it alright if I take a left and turn right?
I wonder if it's okay.
This is too much traffic in Tokyo.
There's too much road construction.
This is the right.
Okay, I'm ready.
Is this also under construction?
Here too?
It's probably this way.
Lemon, no.
The other traffic light is on the left.
Damn it!
Lemon, notice me!
This is strange.
I should be able to find a post office.
But I'm getting further away from Samba-san's house.
I should tell him as soon as possible.
Listen, Kankichi.
You can't find it even if you try.
It's important to do it by yourself until the end of the year.
Damn it!
Okay, I can do it!
No, I completely got the wrong way.
What should I do?
You seem to be lost and in trouble.
Huh?
Yup, yup.
How did you know?
I'm a good reporter.
I can tell everything just by looking at my face.
A reporter is a person who makes fortune-telling about the times, right?
In short, it's a job that helps people in trouble.
Perfect!
But I'm really in trouble now.
How should I go to Samba-san's place?
You're going to Samba-san for your mother?
Of course, I'm a good reporter.
I'll tell my daughter the truth just for free.
Huh?
Alright, alright!
Here!
I found it.
Turn the way you're going now and turn the first signal to the left.
If you go about 50 meters, you'll find a post office on your left hand.
If I know the post office, I'll know the rest.
Thank you, reporter-san.
Phew...
Mr. Omawari, are you done?
Oh, sorry.
I'm saved.
*Pant, pant, pant*
*Sigh*
If you've come this far, you'll be fine.
*Pant, pant, pant*
That's strange.
It's been five minutes.
*Pant, pant, pant*
What?
Tome-san is on leave?
There's a housekeeper at my home in Nezu.
She's been going to that house since last night.
Didn't a girl come a bit earlier?
Yeah.
I wrote down the address of the house in Nezu,
and I ran to pick her up.
Oh, no.
Grandpa, tell me the address, too!
*Pant, pant, pant*
Ugh, damn it.
Ugh, I left it at home.
*Pant, pant, pant, pant*
Ugh, damn it.
Where is it?
This way?
No, maybe this way?
*Pant, pant, pant*
No, this way!
Oh, Lemon!
Where are you now?
Ugh, what the heck?
It's Gepard.
Is Lemon lost?
What are you doing?
*Pant, pant, pant*
What's wrong, Tome-san?
What?
What? Are you going to another pregnant lady?
*Pant, pant, pant*
What do we do?
I'll make you guys feel better.
Hurry up!
*Pant, pant, pant*
Turn the next, next signal to the right.
You're at Kurihara-san's house on the third stop.
Thank you.
What?
*Pant, pant, pant*
What? Did you just leave?
Then, didn't the girl from kindergarten come to visit you?
No, she went home alone.
Oh no, did you go the wrong way?
If the girl comes back, I'll ask for a message to call her home.
Oh...
Hey, Lemon!
Where are you?
I'm here!
Answer me if you can hear me!
Hey...
I'd like to ask you something.
I'd like to ask you in the back yard.
You're the one who's around here, aren't you?
Oh, I see.
Where do you want to go?
Well...
You're still here, Samba-san?
You're going to be born soon.
I have no choice.
I'll pick you up.
Are you sure?
I have no choice!
Grandma!
I'm back.
Sorry for being late.
I'll leave it to you.
This way!
You have a nice face.
I'm sure you'll have a good child.
Now, it's all right.
Take a deep breath.
You brought me here.
I'm not worried anymore.
Now, leave the rest to Tome-san.
We'll be leaving.
Oh...
You're finally born.
You sound so happy.
What?
Hiya!
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry I can't be with you.
your sister is coming.
I'm sorry, but I can't come her.
More me:
I want to talk to you in my space.
Holy crap!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're so small and cute.
I've been waiting for you to come home.
Oh, I see. You've been waiting for me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ah...
...
You're so strong, Lemon.
Hmm?
Really?
Yeah. You came alone to call me to bed.
You're really strong.
Lemon, Tome praised you.
You're my big sister from today.
...
"You look like a grownup."
You're so confident, huh?
...
"You're a grownup."
You have a cute name!
Out of the many candidates I had in mind,
Lemon chose you.
Wow!
So, you're the chef.
Hahaha.
...
Hankichi?
Ryo-chan...
...
...Senpai!
Where have you been all this time?
Well, it's been a long time.
Lemon is safe, and so are the babies.
Lemon, how do you feel? Hold this for a bit.
Huh?
Yeah.
What?
Lemon, can you hold it for me too?
What the?
Take it. Leave the rest to me.
Okay.
What? Why?
Take it. Lend it to me.
It's called "a mandarin orange."
"A mandarin orange?"
Ryou-chan's amazing, right?
Hehehe, an orange has eyes that look at men.
Here, a lemon.
Yes.
Kakishi!
Huh?
I won't forgive you for even eating an orange, not just a lemon!
Hey, hey, hey!
You're a newborn baby, there's nothing to eat!
Hey, Kikumi-mimoto!
Stop it!
You're making it hard for me!
What is this?
Stop it!
You're so annoying!
Show me your mouth!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Huh?
You're really cute.
I don't want to be the one to be loved
If I make a road on the corner
The moon will run away
Because now is not everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat
Sometimes you help someone
Sometimes
Baby do you know me
I'm going to tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't be rotten
I'll do what I do
Cute breathing
What's hard to understand
I want to show you
It's better than seeing
the moment
I'm sorry
If you're Japanese,
you must eat watermelon in the summer.
I eat 3 kinds of watermelon.
Next,
you can eat 300 watermelon in a week.
I'm looking forward to the next.
Thanks for watching.