Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the passing seasons ♩
♪ The best harem shines ♩
♪ Overcoming the freshness of the era ♩
♪ Hero, I'll dive into the city alone ♩
♪ I wanna dive into paradise ♩
♪ Rather than just wearing the trendy clothes ♩
♪ I'll take off my face and make it so ♩
♪ Let it bleed ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Let's run ♩
♪ Dreams can't always stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♩
♪ Everybody can do it ♩
♪ Even if you're a little bit out of it ♩
♪ It doesn't hurt ♩
♪ Embrace the bustling curiosity ♩
♪ And jump high and strong ♩
♪ Jump high to the sky ♩
Theénomone
Awesome!
They're both amazing.
I'm not just telling you how fast they are.
Just look at it!
Can you see it?
What?!
Definitely best cornering.
Incredible!
Put on the disc brake.
Turn on the lights.
The Gyorin's independent three-speed transmission.
Twin-motor method.
I modified it with a hundred thousand yen.
It's my best masterpiece.
My machine is amazing, but my operation technique is also amazing.
Awesome!
Ryo-san is good.
Cool.
What is it?
This time is even more amazing.
Go!
Super Jump!
Turn on the lights.
It's the captain's fault.
He suddenly appeared in such a place.
How about the Bugatti?
It's not broken at all.
The frame is strengthened.
It won't break if it hits someone.
Gyoza.
Yes.
What is it, captain?
This is...
Where?
I don't like it, captain.
You're not old enough to be stupid.
It's in the exhaust.
Did you lose your memory because of the shock of the gold bullet?
It's me.
It's Ryo-tsu.
Do you understand?
Idiot!
Ryo-tsu.
What is the exhaust?
Is it a playground for children?
Is it a competition ground from the radio control?
No, it's not.
It's a place where we police officers apply for jobs.
Even if you don't yell at me in such a loud voice, I know what you want to say.
The captain is not losing his memory.
You know that, don't you?
I can't stand today anymore.
From now on, I will ban all private items related to work.
It's a ban on private items.
What?
What a bad guy!
How could you carry so many private items?
There are still so many things left that I can't load all at once.
You need three more.
Listen.
Come back as soon as you leave it in your room.
I understand.
It's not a good time to distinguish work and playground.
Who is he?
It's him.
The one who hit me earlier.
I want to break him into pieces.
He said he'll pay 100,000 yen.
What?
He'll pay 100,000 yen for this toy?
I don't know how he can pay 100,000 yen for this.
What is this?
Is it a radio?
I can't hear.
I don't know the switch.
Is it true that 100,000 yen is 100,000 yen?
Yes, I think so.
It's the end.
I'm on the road.
If we don't stop it now, the car will come.
How do we stop it?
It's getting faster.
Please change the car.
I can't do that.
It's coming.
Oh, no.
Don't stop at such a place.
That was close.
It's coming from the opposite side.
It's not coming.
I'm going to die.
I think I know what it is.
I think my guilty conscience.
Oh, no, I've got lucky.
It's me.
I've got lucky.
I can't stop.
It's a rabbit.
It's not coming.
It doesn't make sense.
It's a rabbit.
Come on.
All right, come on.
It's bringing me.
Yes.
I'm leaving now.
No, it's okay.
It was fine to hit someone, but there was no one in front of the tire roller.
What are we going to do?
They'll get angry.
I was too fast.
You should have told me to come back soon.
You're the chief, right? There's still some left.
I guess so.
I can't forget things when I get older.
Where did the Bugatti go?
Chief, have you seen my Bugatti?
It's a radio control car that hit the chief.
I see.
I should have left it here.
By the way, the kids just borrowed it.
That's right.
Did you lend it to them?
What?
Yeah.
That's strange.
I met Junpei and the others here on the way back.
I think they were other kids.
You have a lot of acquaintances.
Chief, did you really lend it to the kids?
Of course.
I wouldn't lie.
You're right.
I'm not lying.
Why are you looking away?
If you're not lying, you should be able to see me.
Of course I can see you.
Damn it.
I lost when I heard that.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Let lost!
You're right.
I don't know why it's there.
I'm not going to lose anything.
You're right.
Don't leave this to your wife.
I'm scared.
I don't know why you're here.
I really feel bad now.
Stop it.
Why is this story?
Tell me what it is.
You're not!
I'm a victim, too!
I was hit again!
So you're saying I can destroy my treasure?
I did something unwise about that.
In the end, I'm bad at what I do, so I'm going to get this result.
Migo, be careful!
What a bad habit!
I won't forgive you for crying while licking my feet!
If you're going to lick your feet, you have to forgive me!
Well, we're not adults, you know.
Shut up!
You're such a...
What's that?
This is the corner for the treasure.
What?
The treasure of Chief Ohara of the Kameyari Park Branch is a recently renovated Hinoki bath.
If you enter the Hinoki bath at the end of the day, you will be exhausted.
You will feel like you are in heaven.
Don't joke!
Make this treasure messy.
What is Hinoki bath?
Hey!
Don't get in my way.
I'm going to brag about the bath.
Wait a minute.
The bath is the treasure?
This is fine, isn't it?
The filling of the bath is...
Why did you buy this?
I'm giving it to the chief.
However...
I will change the contents.
Special...
I will put the ingredients in the bath and rub them with pepper, wasabi, and pepper.
This will improve the quality.
Honda, taste it.
Me?
Just a little.
Don't talk nonsense.
But...
Hey!
I'm shocked to put this in the bath.
It's a big deal.
This...
I'm really shocked.
I will put the powder milk and make it mild.
I will put this in the bath and put it in the bath.
I did it!
The special bath is completed.
It's called the extremely spicy bath.
I'm sorry that the chief can't see me panic.
Hehehe.
Next, the second step.
The powder of the mouse and the powder of the hornet.
In addition, the powder of the chicken and the powder of the goldfish are also mixed and completed.
Where did you get it?
The scent of the forest is renewed.
The scent of the voice pot.
It's intense.
Next is miso soup, tea, and consomme soup.
I think I can get a good soup stock from the chief.
What should I mix next?
That's right.
The extract of the carrot is more powerful.
It's fun to mix something.
I'm getting scared.
Finally, the ultimate special bath.
This is a special mix.
It hardens quickly.
When you notice it, it's very easy.
The chief's shoulder can be removed.
You can make a doll.
It's a wonderful gift.
I will deliver this.
I will send it to the chief's house.
Wait.
If it's my name, I will be careful.
I will send it to the chief's name.
It's a bad boy.
Please enjoy the chief a lot.
Special New York style hinoki bath.
I will ask him a favor.
I am listening.
Please look video.
This video should be published in a second.
I was
This is a problem.
Hey, I have a good idea.
What? You want to treat me to dinner?
You want Reiko and Nagawa to treat me?
Yes. I always thank you for your help.
I see, I see. What will you treat me to?
That's for after you get there.
Kei will come pick you up by car soon.
If that's what you want, take me anywhere.
I'm sure you'll get special drinks at the headmaster's house.
I hope you have a great day.
Ryo, I'm coming!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, hello.
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you in person.
We have drinks, TV, and a karaoke.
Let's see.
Here.
I'm getting more and more excited to eat dinner.
I'm here, senior.
Well, what can I serve you?
A fancy restaurant with a perfect view.
Maybe this is...
That's the headmaster's house!
Chief Ohara, I've been trying to get along with Ryo-chan.
So...
Hey!
I'm going back to Nagawa.
Wait, Ryo-chan.
So what?
I'm getting more and more excited to eat with you today
and I'm ready to go.
I have delicious food to eat today,
so I hope you'll thank me.
I'm glad to hear that.
I can't wait for some sashimi or tonkatsu.
The job lines are too sluggish.
Ha!
pushes the trigger
Get the hell out of here.
I see.
What?
Ryo-san, I saw a smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart
smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart... smart...
You put the one you bought at the supermarket three days ago in the fridge, didn't you?
And this tonkatsu is the cheap part of the meat.
All the other dishes are cheap ingredients.
Including the sake table, one person saw it as 850 yen.
What a sharp guy.
If you break 100,000 of them and make them for 850 yen, it's cheap, isn't it?
What are you talking about, boss?
I don't think this dish will replace the radio control car.
I plan to make a good compensation if I get a bonus.
What? Really?
Today, I called you to eat, in the sense of apology.
Then you should say that first, boss.
I'm a bad person.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Oh, my tonkatsu.
No, even if it's cheap ingredients, depending on the way you cook it, it will be so delicious.
Hey, eat yours, not mine.
It seems that they have reconciled.
Cheers!
By the way, boss, you changed the bath to a large bath, right?
Would you like to see it?
Oh, that's fine.
You can enter 24 hours at any time.
Reiko, you should come in, too.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, yes, yes, boss.
Oh, sorry.
Is it a bath?
That's good.
Bath?
Oh, boss.
Do you use bath bombs at your home?
I usually use them, but unfortunately I cut them.
Oh, is that so?
That's too bad.
It seems that my special bath hasn't arrived yet.
You should come in later, too.
Yes, thank you very much.
It's a good feeling.
Oh, it's really fun tonight.
It's been a long time since I've been to a party like this.
Exactly.
Ryotsu, I think I really did something wrong to you.
Please forgive me.
Oh, I got it.
Let's go to the bath together and pour all the red and the red together into the hot water.
All right, I'll pour it on my back.
It was a really nice bath.
Really?
Then we'll go, too.
I'm looking forward to it.
Reiko, are you going to come in with us again?
I don't care.
Boss, you're rarely drunk.
Who's at this time?
Ryotsu, please come in first.
Yes, yes.
I'll open it now.
Oh, it's a good bath for a stubborn boss.
Oh, that's good.
Yes, Ryotsu.
The boss sent me a delivery of bath water.
My special bath water.
It was just right.
I'll use it right away.
Where are you going?
I thought about the pay.
There's about time to go to the bath.
Actually, I have a hot bath allergy.
That's a nice joke, Ryotsu.
Actually, because of my late father, I don't think I can go into the hot bath alone.
Your father is alive, isn't he?
Well, let's go in together.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you have any problems?
Okay, let's use this one.
The scent of the forest.
The scent of the hot bath.
Mix it well.
Oh, that's hot.
Oh, that's a nice scent.
I didn't notice anything at all because I was drunk.
Ryotsu, after all, a beehive bath is good, right?
Yes, that's right.
After all, the bath is a beehive.
Ah, feels good.
I feel refreshed.
Now, let's go.
Hey, don't get in the bath!
Stop it, Chief!
Men can't be together!
I told you to go into the bath and put everything in the hot water.
I got it.
I just have to get in, right?
You have to get in to your shoulders.
Why are you looking at me like this?
I'll put more in.
Super hot sugar.
No, I can't do that.
I'll put it in!
You're getting tired of it!
What's wrong?
I have a cold.
I mean, I've been bleeding lately.
I thought I was going to be shocked.
I'm sorry.
It's cheap, you know.
I'll fill it up now.
Okay.
Next time, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
No, it's fine.
You're not going to let me do it?
I got it.
Please.
I see.
I'm good at washing.
Okay.
I can get any kind of dirt out of you.
Chief!
It's a wire!
Oh, no.
I made a mistake.
I'm so dense and I can't be warned.
Why would you make mistakes?
It's tight!
That's an alternator for tires.
I got it!
You.
You're not in there yet.
I told you not to cling to it, didn't I?
You're weak!
Then, let's go in there, Ryotsu!
Let's go out naked, men and women!
It's hell.
Chief, it's a waste to be in such a big bath.
Can we leave?
Yeah, right.
Which one? Do you want to add more bath?
That's not good!
Oh, no!
We have to get out of here quickly!
You just got in.
You don't want to be in a bath with me?
No, it's not like that.
It's really bad if you don't get out of here quickly.
What's bad?
I just put in a plaster.
Why is the bath bomb a plaster?
I feel like my body is getting heavier.
The gyo-ko effect has begun.
So it's a plaster.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Let's get out of here quickly!
Wait a minute!
Why did you know this gyo-ko is a plaster?
You're planning something bad again.
Rather than that, let's get out of here quickly!
What was that voice?
It sounded like Ryo-chan's voice.
Somebody! Help me!
It's a bath!
Nagagawa, help me!
But I can't move.
What made you make this?
You idiot!
Speaking of the original, it's bad that the chief broke the radio.
You're still saying that?
It seems that we are back in the first place.
It can't be helped.
I can't do anything about it!
It's going to be fixed!
Are you the security guard of the Hina Festival?
Please forgive me, chief!
March 3 has been a good day since I was born!
It's a holiday!
I hate the Hina Festival and Tsukudani!
Next time, "Sanzan Hina Festival".
Thank you!
Even if I try to stop the clock
Time will pass
Don't look at me
Laugh and live
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
Let's wash our hands
Goodbye, unpleasant things
Let's live as we like
There is a good thing
Outside the door
The sun is calling
The sun finely shines
Don't you want to come out of the window?
Let me show you
This is a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video of a video