Elise
After watching a moonlit day floating in the river
Throwing an stone of love, I flip my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the kitchen where I saved up
I was laughed at as a child
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are Katsushika and Kameari
You don't change even from yawn
The cityscape is good
From Chusuito to Kaishakuten
Sunset hits the sky
I'm getting up and going back home tomorrow
Hey, Kazushika Shibamata, you lost your happiness again
But now you realize, you're an idiot
"Gekichin Ninja-G-san"
I-I'm getting excited...
You have Jody, so you don't need this man.
I-I don't think there's a better woman than Jody.
I don't think there's a better woman than Jody, but...
there's always a chance.
That's right, open it.
Okay, then...
I-I thought my eyes were going to get hurt.
Help me! I don't want to see her!
You can just say you have a fiancée and say no.
I said that when I was talking about seeing her.
Then she said, "bring her here!"
Yeah. I said, "bring her here!"
Then you can take Jody with you.
But she's in the Navy now, and I can't get in touch with her.
First of all, if I don't win against her, I can't get married.
Please, do something.
If this goes on, I'll get married to this guy.
There's nothing you can't do, but it's not easy.
I'll pay you as much as you want!
Leave it to me!
You called me a crazy guy to get married to self-deceived prick.
N-Ninja!?
Your grandfather is a ninja?
It's been like this for generations.
My grandfather in reality wants me to get married.
He'll be my successor.
He doesn't think he'll get married...
This is the same thing that happened to me!
Um, well, in that case...
You're gonna make a good fiancee, Maria.
I'll do my best!
Thank you.
That's my home.
Yeah, you're right about that.
It's a nice house.
It looks like a real ninja is going to come out.
There's no one in the house.
Huh? You can't see him even though he's not in there?
If he's tied up in a red ribbon, he's a loser.
In a place like that?
He should have told us where he was going with a stone.
With a stone?
There's a stone sign on Boy Scout.
Like this.
Oh, it looks like a ninja.
There it is!
It looks like he went shopping.
That's not how it works!
It's easy to understand.
It can't be helped if he's a loser.
Let's wait inside.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Grandpa is very diligent, so he's making traps here and there to avoid the fire.
If he gets caught in one of those traps, he'll die!
If you're going to say that, tell Grandpa!
There!
I know!
It's a success!
Grandpa!
What? Is this a trap?
But why is he so frivolous?
He's going shopping in a very old-fashioned way.
He's wearing a very unsightly outfit, so that the ninja can't find out.
That outfit is even more conspicuous!
But I often see it in historical dramas.
Huh?
Hmm...
This girl is...
You're the one who's going to marry her?
Yes.
I'm Ai Asato.
You're so big!
I'm jealous of this beauty.
You mustn't let your guard down.
Yes.
We'll try it, too!
Shut up!
Why are you so noisy?
I'm Ryotsu, and I'm here to help you with your work.
And this is Nakagawa.
Nice to meet you.
I'm not interested in men.
Ah...
Come on in.
What are you doing?
I see.
What a great trick!
Follow me.
Huh?
Hey, you should be walking on the ground.
Why are you walking on the baltang?
Grandpa...
I was magic-watching you.
I was waiting for you.
Don't worry about that.
Get in the back of the car, and I'll show you the through-ắtner.
You think I'm ill-mannered, too?
It hurts.
What's wrong?
Uh...
Hey, what is wrong?
You think you're like my grandpa?
Oh, you don't know, right?
I have behavior problems.
My school is a well-nurtured school.
What's wrong?
What happened?
So, Wansa, you collect the students and make a lot of money.
I'm going to change a little, so wait.
There's even a souvenir corner.
Hey, give me your signature.
There's a little bit in the main video.
Huh? It's your 188.
Huh? What's this?
It's a tape. It's cheating.
It's cheating.
You're touching it without permission.
Grandpa.
You're a dangerous guy.
You're a grandpa of a Volvo.
But you look like a ninja and you're cool.
It's really nice.
Is that so? Well, it's just tea.
It's herbal tea for your body.
Oh, my God.
But one of them contains a medicinal herb that can cure diarrhea.
What?
It's a training to make excuses.
I've been doing it since I was a child.
It's like Russian roulette.
I'm going to drink this.
Ryo?
Yes.
This is wrong.
Grandpa.
That's what you said, right?
Yes.
It's a big hit.
What?
Why are you doing this to me?
I drank it.
Don't worry.
It's called Shinobi medicine.
Ninjas are familiar with various herbs.
It's a mixture of various herbs such as wound medicine and blood.
Aall in this world, there are various herbs such as eczema,
and those he can't do without it.
So, you're really enjoying this.
But it's a matter of course, right?
But if you can do this to me,
you can't do it to me.
That's right.
I learned how to make it one by one and it helped me.
Yes!
The details are here.
Oh, I've seen it all over and over again.
What's this?
- It's 1,500 yen. - That's too high!
Then you can enjoy the
- I got it. I'll pay you. - Here you go.
- Here you go. - Here you go.
Boss, it's dangerous to throw the shuriken in the room.
- All right, get out of here. - I'll do it.
- I'll do it. - Master Ryo!
- Master Ryo! - Master Ryo!
Let's go.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- I'm going to win! - I'm going to win!
- I can't believe it. - Can't believe it.
How about this?
This is the ultimate ninja technique.
The technique of crushing the ground.
- It hurts. - Give me back the shuriken!
It's a unique technique.
Grandpa!
Balbo, stop being a cop and come back with that girl.
Huh? Why?
You'll be the successor of my ninja school.
No, I...
Why are you hesitating?
If you become my successor,
you'll be the successor of this land of 6,000 barrels and ninja school.
Huh? 6,000 barrels?
Hey, you! Who are you to do this?
Master!
Huh?
Please make me your disciple.
What? You?
I have learned a lot of your techniques.
I want to become a ninja as well!
I see. That's interesting.
Your technique is pretty good.
I'll take it!
Master...
What are you thinking?
Fine, I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
Huh?
Master, if you're going to open a ninja school,
why don't you make a female ninja, Funo Ishika?
Huh?
That's a good idea.
You like it, don't you?
Not as good as you.
Huh?
Hahaha!
I knew you'd say something like that.
Hahaha.
Master, I have a good idea.
I'll take your ear.
Huh?
What?
I'm uses irrigation tool.
Heel...
Nose...
*Nose*
You worked hard, Kunoichi!
Hahaha.
This is the real Kunoichi.
He's a Bunny Girl, right?
Don't say that!
Big ears to protect enemies!
Hanging shoulderasse on himself.
undergoing the Block,
I'm Kunoichi, right?
That's the one!
You're totally wrong!
I can't help it. I'm wearing this costume because it's popular.
I like the one before.
I still feel like it's too colorful.
Why are you taking pictures?
I'm going to use it as a pamphlet for the ninja school.
You know, the pamphlets and covers of travel companies are usually pretty, right?
It's a beauty that attracts young people.
I see.
Maria, raise your hem so that you can see your thighs.
Like this?
Yeah, nice.
Okay, the next pose.
Leave it to me.
It's colorful when you put your shoulders out.
As expected of the master.
Let's go, Maria.
Okay.
In addition, close your arms in front of you and close your chest.
Why is your chest so small?
It's bad.
I see.
I pretended to be a fiancé of a Volvo.
I can't help it.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'll take care of it.
Maria is a man.
What?
Are you really a man?
Yes.
Hey, did you fool me?
No, there's a deep reason for this.
Yes.
Jody.
Excuse me.
What's Jody?
This is it.
What?
Did you have a real girlfriend?
And she's a nice American.
What?
It's not a penalty.
That's right, Master.
You could model Jody and take the cover of the pamphlet.
That's good, right?
I see.
It's good.
And you can make Maria join you.
I can't stand it.
Well, then.
Jody's aircraft carrier has arrived at Yokosuka Port.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
I'll go too.
What?
Why are you going with Grandpa?
Your grandchild is the same as yours.
I'll make you the model of the pamphlet of Ninja School.
What?
Okay.
Let's go to Yokosuka together.
No way.
Just do it.
What's that?
The helicopter is coming.
The landing schedule isn't working.
Episode 1
What's the matter?
I was passing by, so I came to see you.
Long time no see.
Gun!
No!
Well done, Jody.
Don't shoot me instead of greeting me.
I'm sorry.
Captain Bakuryu, welcome to my ship.
I'm always indebted to you.
I've always heard the rumors about you.
I heard that you have played a role in many wars and warships.
No, it's nothing.
Well, I was about to say...
Captain Bakuryu
It's a great ship!
I found it.
You did it on purpose.
This is what I got from Mr. Ruby.
This is the time of the room battle.
This is the time of the first Ultra Operation.
Wow, another unauthorized helicopter is coming.
What?
What is this?
Mr. Jody.
Bomi.
Oh my darling.
Darling!
Long time no see.
What?
You're here!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hi, Jody.
It's a long time, Mr. Ryotsu.
What's wrong?
I'm a ninja's apprentice.
Master!
Let me introduce you.
This is my master, the grandpa of my grandpa, Ko-ganemaru Saigo.
Oh, Grandpa! Nice to meet you, I'm Jody!
Ah, me too.
Is this beautiful lady the bride?
Yes, well...
Grandpa, are you a ninja?
Oh, yes.
My apprentice, hold this.
Now, everyone, get out of the way!
What the...
Thank you.
I'm tired.
Oh, wonderful!
Fantastic!
Master!
Alright.
Hey guys, a shuriken for ten dollars, please.
Thanks.
I didn't think you'd come all the way here to do business.
Show me more ninja skills!
OK.
Nice shot!
Nice!
Grandpa!
A water cloud that can walk on water costs 30 dollars.
This Shinobi縄 is 25 dollars.
Give me a water cloud!
I want a Shinobi縄.
Yes, yes, don't push.
It's a long time ago.
This... this is completely ignored.
Yes, yes, welcome.
It's very popular.
In America, ninjas are popular.
All right, all right.
Yes, cheese.
Yeah!
Don't get carried away.
Ninja are children's tricks after all.
What?
Are you trying to insult Japanese tradition?
Papa, it's rude to your darling grandpa.
Is it rude?
In front of the latest weapon of the ninja army, it's the same as a baby.
Shut up, bald gorilla.
What's this?
Hey, I won't forgive you if you make fun of the master.
Grandpa, stop it.
This person is my superior.
He's Jody's father.
Shut up.
I won't let you make fun of the ninja.
I'll let you taste the ninja's goodness.
Yeah.
Hey, don't make me stand up.
Oh.
Don't run away.
It's a fire.
No way.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'll show you what a naked soldier is capable of.
Damn it.
I'll make you get mad seriously.
You'll see what I can do.
Hey, where did he disappear?
There it is.
Yeah!
Got it?
S- Mr. Ryo!
Sir!
Senior!
In your face!
Get him!
Watch your mouth!
Master!
No, I can't even use my Dragon Ball!
You bastard! You won't get away with this!
Now, let's get to work!
Even if you say that, I can't use my ninja skills yet!
You'll become my successor and take over the land of the Sixth Sense!
Yes sir!
Understood!
Take this!
Stop!
Ouch!
How's that?
You bastard! You won't get away with this!
Damn it!
-Let's go get some water! -Yes sir!
You're so hard-working!
I'm gonna kill you!
Take this!
You bastard! Stop the missiles!
How are you gonna do that?
Here you go, Mr. Horse!
Change the direction of the missiles!
What?
This way?
Or this way?
Alright!
Hey! Don't come back!
What did you say?
I'm gonna destroy the Eight-Sense-Tsubo in America!
Don't come back!
What? Eight-Sense-Tsubo?
Alright!
What?
You're betraying me?
That's the Eight-Sense-Tsubo!
I'm gonna destroy the Five-Sense-Tsubo in Urayama!
Alright!
I'm gonna build Hawaii's best-seller!
How about my new apartment?
Alright!
Let's build it!
Come on!
Florida Orange Battle!
As an apology to the president, I,
Oh, no!
Huh?
He's coming this way!
It's an island!
Three of them!
That's right!
For you!
-Oh my god! -He's very sharp!
-What... -What?
He's sunk!
What should we do now, old man?
It's not my fault.
-He's the one who shot the missiles. -Dad!
Oh, no. It's practice time.
Old man, I'll take care of this for today.
Farewell!
Hey, don't run!
I want to laugh!
I can't help it if there's no one to fight against!
Go!
A giant Nymph!
Farewell!
Hey, wait!
What's going to happen to the land of the Six Seasons?
Can you trust a traitor like Horokoro?
Don't make him your disciple!
I'm not joking!
Hey, wait!
Stop!
Hey, Yu!
Our ship sank because of you!
Let's eat!
That's right!
I'm not joking!
Wait!
Why am I the only one...
Lord!
Senpai!
I'm sorry.
It's my grandpa's fault.
No, it's my dad's fault.
Help me!
I hate ninjas!
Traffic Safety Market!
You're Ishizu Tetsuo!
There's quiver and nine in this area already!
Besides, look at those armor-wearing foto!
No matter how much traffic is,
the war in the Luxembourg period was completely different!
Next on Traffic Safety Demon.
I'm counting on you!
I'm in awe!
Don't flinch!
Nonsense!
♪ With the spirit of the solution, ♪
♪ it's a quick and quick move. ♪
♪ It's decided, ♪
♪ it's sparkling, ♪
♪ it's bouncing, ♪
♪ it's gathering, ♪
♪ it's moving, ♪
♪ it's flying. ♪
♪ It's more than anything else, it's full of power. ♪
♪ Everyone, gather up! ♪
♪ If you come here, ♪
♪ it's like a dream, the final energy. ♪
♪ Tomorrow, the day after, yesterday, and the new year. ♪
♪ If you draw the universe and stand on the ground, ♪
♪ the planet with the turtle will change its shape. ♪
♪ This is good, right? ♪
♪ There's no reason to say it's good. ♪
♪ It's a dream, it's a dream. ♪