ENG SUB by
You should look at the face of the room like a mirror.
Hey!
I kicked the love stone, and I flew to the shoe
I wonder if I'm going to go to the gym that I was saving
I laughed at the fact that it was still a
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can't win
Sushi,
It's kind of perlex
From the water channel of the Tungari bus,
The sunset goes down to theesi
Tomorrow is also a blue sky
Yes, I put my head down
It's over, right?
If I win, I'll lose again
I lost my happiness
I realized
Because I'm an idiot
Don't call me papa!
Huh?
It's a baby!
Who are you? Where did you come from?
Who's there?
The baby is crying!
What are the parents thinking about?
If they're left in front of such a cold place, they can't take a nap, can they?
Hey! Don't be so quiet!
You're laughing
Is something on my face?
I'm home
Hey, Reiko
What a cute baby!
Whose baby is it?
It's a stolen one
What?
It seems the search request has not come out
After all, is it a stolen one?
I can't believe that they abandoned such a cute baby
Who is it?
You don't know who left it?
It must be sleeping
It's the time to report an emergency or deliver a stolen item
Don't lie
I can't believe you can't satisfy even the hotel
Shoo! Shoo!
What?
It says Shoo! Shoo!
The diaper is wet, isn't it?
I think there was a new diaper in the car
Oh, this one?
Who is it?
Let me see
Here
What?
Good, good, it felt bad
You have a good hand, Chief
When my grandson Daisuke comes, I always change diapers
What?
It looks like a letter
It came out from under the diaper
What?
I'll read it
This is your son
Please take Taro with you until he comes to pick you up
This baby is called Taro
Didn't you just say your son?
What?
Come to think of it...
Kazue
So, someone here is Taro's father
What?
Who is he? Tell me honestly
According to the probability
What?
Are you doubting me?
Anyway, Nagagawa is a housewife who comes from over there even if she is silent
He is a strange man
It wouldn't be strange to have ten or twenty children
Senpai, don't say like an old man
Nakagawa, look into my eyes
Do you really remember me?
No
Nakagawa is white
So, you believe in me? Chief
I'm sure that you are a policeman
If I say white, you are white
That's right, Ryo-chan. Kei-chan is not that kind of coward.
That's right, Ryo-san.
What?
Rather than playing around like Nakagawa,
a guy as serious as you is the real deal.
See?
Your nose looks exactly like mine.
Ryo-san...
Hurry up and put on some weight, you old man.
I-I-I'm not going to cheat on you!
Look at my eyes.
Chief...
It's white.
These eyes are the eyes of the honest who don't lie.
Thank you, Chief.
No, the honest who don't lie may have made a mistake once.
Ryo-san, I'll get angry if you don't stop!
Then, the Chief will stay.
Here.
What?
No way.
Chief Ohara is suspicious.
I can't believe he's so suspicious.
That's right, Ryo-chan.
It's not true, is it?
I'm the son of a grandchild.
In this case, the probability that the person who no one thinks is the real culprit is very high.
I-If you say so...
No way...
Only the Chief...
What's with that "maybe"?
There's a medicine that can help you soon.
I can't be compared to you because you're an old man.
You idiot!
Good night!
I'm sorry, I was so surprised.
Chief, please look at my eyes.
What?
If you don't remember them, you shouldn't be afraid.
Of course, I want to.
There's an unusual movement in the black eye.
It's because you're all together!
I don't think I'm the Chief.
I think so, too.
Yes.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm going to be interesting from now on.
What's wrong with you, Ryo-san?
That's right. Ryo-san is still here.
That's right. Senpai is one of the suspects, isn't he?
I don't care.
Can you prove it?
Look at this round-eyed person who doesn't lie.
I can't even see the truth.
It's a big liar's eye.
It's an eye that's trying to get rid of the responsibility.
It's an eye that can't even be placed on a man's umbrella.
It's a cowardly eye that can't even be placed on a man's head.
You're all so mean!
When Ryo-chan is in a bad mood, he'll make a big noise.
Papa!
What?
He just said "Papa."
He said "Papa" when he saw Ryo-san's face?
I heard it, too.
Me, too.
Here, Ryo-chan.
That's not true, is it?
Papa!
Hey, don't say anything bad about him.
Hey, this old kid can only say "Mama" and "Papa."
So, he can say "Papa" and "Papa" to anyone he sees.
What?
You're such a fool!
Ryo-chan, you're such a coward.
No, I'm not!
That's proof that your eyebrows are not moving.
You're a coward, Ryo-chan.
That's true.
You don't remember anything at all.
I don't know anything, Chief!
Until your mother comes back, you'll be responsible for her child as a person and father.
You can go home now.
No way!
Papa!
I'm not Papa!
I'm Nureginu!
Good work!
I wonder if he'll be all right.
I don't think he can take care of a baby all of a sudden.
No matter how much he cares about his father,
he's still a child.
Wait, Ryo-chan!
I'm coming with you!
Which one do you want to have your hair dyed?
Papa?
The one you'll never have to get a new one.
There's no way that's possible.
Why do I have to do this?
Oh, my cute boy.
You're just like your father.
He's not my child!
Papa! Papa!
Papa!
Hey, you're calling me Papa, aren't you?
Huh?
You're just kidding.
I'm your father, so you have to behave yourself.
Don't talk like that, Papa!
Ryo-chan,
you should just talk to him like that.
It's because you call me Papa!
That's what I'm saying.
No!
Papa!
This is a nightmare.
Ah!
I cleaned up, because it was so dirty.
My Promo!
My game!
Hello, Mrs.
Welcome.
The head of the club asked me to take you home with your baby, so I asked to make a phone call.
I was too nervous.
Because I had no other choice but to come to this room.
If you stay here, I don't have to worry.
He's dead.
Come on, Taro. This is your home.
Welcome.
You're a strong kid.
Oh, a triangle robot.
You were safe, weren't you?
Good, good.
Hey, don't break it.
Taro, you won't just give away toys, right?
It's not just a toy.
This is a toy I made for the boy jet
as a model for the triangle robot.
It's Yonezawa's robot that's gone now.
Ryo, you're already a father.
It's not the time to play with toys.
That's why I'm not a child.
Hey, that's not food. Give it back.
Boy, you must be hungry.
I'm preparing the rice.
Ryo, you take Taro to the bathroom.
Me?
Well, good luck, Dad.
Oh, Reiwa.
I'm going.
Yeah, yeah.
Why don't you say "Mama"?
Papa.
I don't know.
If you're going to be a human, say "Thank you."
That's Ryo's hidden treasure.
Yeah, the hidden wife made a debt and ran away with a young man.
The story is getting bigger and bigger.
Good.
I'm going in one more time.
Okay, huh?
Uh-oh.
I'm going to be the first who get any food from the original costs.
Huh?
Get dinner on time.
Uh-oh.
I'm calling for it.
Don't push it so hard.
Keep it really gentle.
You're weak.
I'll take care of the other two kids.
You're fine.
Take care of Yoro-chan, too.
Let's go, advice is always helpful.
Come on.
Wow wow...
Hey, what's up, Grandma? You're acting so differently!
I've always said that children are precious!
I'm not kidding! I've been being swung around by this guy since morning and I'm sick of it!
Once the real parents show up, I'll give you plenty of baby-sitting pills!
I understand. This is a service, so you have to take care of it properly!
I have to do that...
I knew it, Grandma! You know what to do!
I'll give you a glass of water...
What's this?
Wow wow...
You're just like the mischief lovers!
Hey, Maro! It's 11 o'clock! Stop sleeping already!
Teiju!
Are you serious? Go to sleep!
Go to sleep!
Ugh...
Do whatever you want! I'm going to sleep!
Grandma!
Shut up!
I said I'm going to sleep!
Grandma!
Huh?
You're a piece of shit.
Here.
What is this?!
Taro!
Ryo?
This is your job, right?
Taro, where have you gone this whole time?
This is me, Ryo.
Taro! Where are you? Taro!
Dad!
You're the father? I just bought it!
I'll have to pay for it!
N-no way!
You're such a good boy.
Yeah.
Listen, you and I have the same eyebrows, but we're different people.
We're different people.
That means I don't have any rights or responsibilities to take care of you.
Do you understand?
Taro!
You should be grateful for taking care of me.
No!
Shut up!
Go somewhere!
Dad!
I don't care anymore!
I thought you were a baby, but you were just a baby.
Taro!
Hey! Where are you going?
Taro! Stop the motorbike!
Where's the floppy?
It's here.
In here?
Yeah.
The guys in the company are starting to notice.
I want to stop them this time.
Don't be so cocky.
This is a deal.
You pay for it, don't you?
Huh?
What?
It's gone!
That car!
Dad!
What are you doing?
Chase after him!
Stop!
Taro!
It's a cut!
This is bad.
Hey, Ozo!
Get on!
Are you alright?
Hey, listen...
Stop this car right here!
He's getting out of control!
It's not a lorry, daddy!
Stop!
I'm on my way!
He's getting out of control!
Hey, stop it!
Please stop the car!
What are you doing?
Stop the motorbike!
Stop, stop the motorbike!
*Slow motion*
Hey!
Haven't you seen the baby?
No way...
Batman!
Huh?
*Slow motion*
Why are you over there?
Is there no one else?
The stairs?
I can't help it.
The police kid.
It's bad if we get back to them first.
It's bad.
*Slow motion*
It's heavy.
Let's help him.
Sorry.
*Slow motion*
Watch out!
Are you alright?
I'm just a kid.
I got it.
*Slow motion*
*Gasping*
Eh?
You're not moving!
*Gasping*
*Slow motion*
Taro!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
When did you get here?
This is ours!
It's mine!
Taro!
Wait for me!
I found it!
No, it's not.
This isn't the robot I brought.
Then the kid will still be here.
Let's go!
Let's stop.
This is very troublesome.
Don't joke!
This started when you were a child!
Hey, the police!
You idiot! Are you going to kill me?
But...
It's fine.
Call the police!
A strange police officer took my trainer!
Please help me!
No!
I'm tracking down the DAP and a strange sedan with a strange engine!
Ask the police for help immediately!
The police officer's child!
Let me go!
I have nothing to do with it!
It's over!
You're a thief too!
If you don't get your revenge, you won't have a life!
What is it?
Are you sleeping?
Why are you crying?
There's a strange child!
I'm glad I'm safe.
It's Taro!
Ryotsu!
Senpai!
Bujo!
Nagata! Reiko!
I'm fine.
I'm not hurt.
Don't worry about me!
Ryo-chan is a teacher from the chief.
Senpai, please reflect on yourself as a father.
I'm sorry.
I'm a fool to let a child be in such a dangerous situation.
If it's a terrible situation, it's our fault, chief!
Baba!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with the robot?
Huh?
This isn't my robot.
There's a gap in this place.
What's this old thing?
A floppy?
Ryotsu-san, actually...
Oh, I found it.
It's a floppy!
Those two were working part-time as industrial spies in the police office.
And this is?
Oh, it's mine.
A good gift.
Yeah.
Well, I did the normal job as a policeman.
I knew that they were criminals at first sight.
It just happened to be a coincidence.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's part of the skill.
Dad!
What?
Hoshi!
The award ceremony for Taro has just ended, hasn't it?
Yeah. Ryo and the others are late.
We're back!
Huh?
What's that?
I'd like Taro to appear in our show.
For now, we'll pay him 100 million yen.
I see. 100 million yen.
And you?
I'd like Taro to appear in our new show.
The cast is Ryoko Hirose.
I see, I see.
Ryo is just like Taro's manager.
In the end, Senpai is changing love for money.
He's so stingy.
I see, I see.
And who's next?
Ryo!
I found Taro's parents!
What?
They're connected!
Taro...
Dad!
Hey!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Taro...
Dad.
I'm so glad.
I'm sorry, Taro.
Dad!
You can say it yourself?
Taro...
Mama...
Why did you throw it away?
I didn't!
We got divorced right after Taro was born,
and she took Taro.
But I lost the confidence to raise him on my own,
so I left Taro in front of his apartment.
Huh?
But the cart was in front of the station!
My apartment is three blocks from this station.
I put three of my papers next to it.
Maybe he came here to take something.
I saw the news this morning, and I was surprised to contact him.
It's a shameful story.
Thank you very much.
Taro!
You'll never forget this!
Hey!
Wow!
Hehe.
Bye, Nato.
Hm?
Taro!
Bye-bye, Baba.
Huh?
Bye-bye!
Taro!
Come play again!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ I want to warm up my body and my friends ♪
♪ But I want to see my friends ♪
♪ I really want to be loved ♪
♪ The more everyone says it ♪
♪ The more we feel like we're melting ♪
♪ I want to be with you ♪
♪ Love is cowardly ♪
♪ Don't hide all the strong feelings ♪
♪ Sakonji Tatsunosuke ♪
♪ I'm Sakonji Tatsunosuke ♪
I'm Sakonji Tatsunosuke.
I swear I'll continue working hard in America.
To keep that promise, Saori, I'll have to forget about you!
Next episode
on Sakonji: New shallow