"When watching TV"
When watching TV
Make the room bright and look away
I look at the sunset that floats in the river
When I kick a pebble, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I was working out
I was laughed at as it was
Even this year, the cityscape that will never change
Is strangely gentle
From the fountain of Tongari-boshi
To Kaishakuten, the sunset is falling
And it's over
Even if I lose my happiness
I'll be fine
I'm a fool
"Ton Demo Koukuu Keisetsutai"
"Nakagawa"
"Kashu dispenser"
What do I need to do?
"It's okay to move, right?"
Let's see
" laptop"
"Aerop TS-404"
Demorganized
Another shows up. The cash dispenser thief.
The one who used the similar plane,
this is his fifth time.
It's other people's money.
It's none of my business at all.
Well, this is your business, eh?
Good morning, chief!
Good morning.
What's going on, chief?
You said you had something to do with Senpai?
Actually, to solve this case,
we have formed an Air Police Force.
Air... Police Force?
Air Police, right?
Air Police?
It's been around since the U.S.
They use helicopters as a helicopter.
I've seen that in movies.
You were recommended by the chief of the Air Police Force.
What?
This is the recommendation form.
That's amazing, isn't it, Gyo-chan?
The chief of the Air Police Force?
Me? The chief?
I see.
So you finally recognized my excellence as the chief of the police force.
I think it's just a human error.
Who recommended Senpai?
The chief of the Air Police Force
is a technical expert.
I don't know much about him.
I've seen him somewhere before.
This is the map of the Air Police Force headquarters.
You have to follow it.
Chief, are you worried about me?
No. I just don't want you to come back here again.
Hmph!
I'm sure you're right.
What on earth is this map?
There's a mark on the bridge.
I can't believe there's an Air Police Force here.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Huh?
Wh-What?
I-Is this the headquarters?
The greatest genius of the Renaissance, Leonardo da Vinci,
was inspired by the Italian Borgia family
and created numerous works of art and inventions.
I can't believe this voice.
No way.
I didn't make it practical,
but there are many designs of airplanes.
Let's bring them back to the present!
Ciao. Long time no see, Gorilla-kun.
It's you, Professor Ezaki!
Huh?
Then who recommended me as the chief of the Air Police Force?
It's me.
I knew it.
Hey, are there any other members?
Are they still here?
I think they're all here.
Then, I knew it.
The Air Police Force in Japan starts with you and me.
Kairu!
I'm sorry to be alone with you!
Wait, Gorilla-kun!
We're still two members.
If we improve our performance,
the Air Police Force will grow bigger and bigger.
We'll have ten, twenty, and a hundred more members.
You'll be at the top of that.
The top of ten thousand?
Will the pay rise?
Of course.
It's twice, three, no, ten times.
What?
Come to think of it,
I'm the only one who can do such a difficult job.
Oh, you'll do it for me?
Yeah.
Let's protect the sky of Japan together.
So, this is the most important airplane?
Don't worry.
I've calculated the resistance to the wind.
That's not the problem.
We can't fly it like this.
What are you talking about?
I made this with the design of Leonardo da Vinci.
It's called "Leonardo Ezaki No. 1:
A combination of Italian genius and modern Japanese genius of the Renaissance period.
It can't fly.
Did you take a test flight?
You can fly if you have confidence.
Of course.
Then, let me fly it again.
No, I can't.
It's time for a siesta.
Siesta?
In Italy, we have a habit of taking a nap after lunch.
If you work hard, you can't get great ideas.
So, that's why...
Good night.
Stop fooling around!
Stop fooling around and go for a test flight.
Hey!
What?
W-what's going on?
I'm an experimental team?
Fly, Leonardo Ezaki No. 1!
No!
No, no!
I told you, you can't fly.
I thought it would be simple if you had the power.
It wasn't there, due to the structure.
If you know how to fly, then don't make one from the start.
But, don't worry.
What you catch a plane is not just this one.
What's this?
It's the design of Leonardo da Vinci.
I made it with my own design.
It's called the model of the current helicopter.
There's a proper helicopter now, right?
Just in case, I'll ask you, but did you take the test flight properly?
Well, how was it?
Don't fool around!
Oh, it's time for siesta.
I did siesta just now.
You're a man who cares about the details.
You'll be hated in Italy.
This is Japan.
Don't say anything and go on the test flight.
Burn the pedals!
Fly, Leonardo Ezaki No. 2!
After all, Leonardo Da Vinci was born on an airplane.
He was a man 400 years ago.
It's impossible to make an actual airplane.
If you knew, don't make it from the beginning!
But don't worry. There are still more airplanes.
What is this hut?
It's the secret storage room of the Air Police.
What's the secret?
If you put your skin in it, you have to cross the bridge to move.
Don't worry, look at this.
This is the secret storage room of the Air Police.
I'm surprised.
This is called the "Leonardo Ezaki No. 3."
From just now, there are only manned airplanes.
The Air Police has just made it, so there is still little budget.
But this time, it seems to be flying.
Did you make this based on the design of Leonardo Da Vinci?
No, that was the idea of the "Surprised Chicken Human Contest."
Then you don't have to put "Leonardo" on it.
If you care about the details, you will be hated in Italy.
That's why I say this is Japan!
This time, the test flight is...
It was useless just to ask.
Anyway, I'll try it.
Finished!
No!
There is no meat inside!
No meat inside!!
Maybe I forgot to tell you...
The price is also a point, isn't it?
There is no meat inside.
Listen!
What!?
What?!
I'm going to burn!
Y-you did it! It flew!
Don't tell me it really flew!
It's like it turned into a bird!
What's that?
It's an Akihito, right?
Hey, Nakagawa! This is bad!
It's the third Asahi-style Akihito!
Roger that!
It's coming!
Stop the motorcycle there! Stop it!
Why did you find out? Damn it!
Oh no!
The criminal's motorcycle is heading to the third intersection!
Wait a minute!
It's on the side road again!
It's a guy who knows the back road well.
I might be able to escape from here.
If this continues, I'll...
You can't catch me with a motorcycle!
Wait a minute!
I'll arrest you!
You're a pain in the ass!
Senpai!
We did it! The Air Police Division has been performing well since day one!
Senpai, you can catch the cash dispenser thief at this rate!
Leave it to me!
But where is the plane you were on?
It's already there!
There's nothing to be surprised about.
That plane perfectly copied the record of the amazing bird contest.
It's flying to the ends of the earth.
But that's the ocean!
You should give up already.
I think we should get a new one.
What?
What a decent plane!
The Air Police Division
The criminal has been arrested.
It's time to show the power of the Air Police Division.
So, what have you done so far?
Look at this.
The Air Police Division
I'm aiming for a plane that's gentle to the environment.
That's why I made this plane move with electricity.
But there's one flaw.
Flaw?
It takes a lot of time to charge.
It takes about five hours.
Charge it from the beginning!
Then, let's get the siesta before the charging is over.
Ouch, good night.
You're a good sleeper.
*snoring*
It's already evening.
Get up!
It's a refreshing awakening.
Beautiful.
What a beautiful morning.
It's a sunset.
If you care about small things, you'll be hated in Italy.
I'm telling you, this is Japan!
The charging is almost over.
Which one?
Hmm, looks good.
Then, let's go for a drive.
Huh?
Is this plane a double seat?
Yeah.
I put two engines on it, and it just put two seats on it.
I see.
What?
No way...
There are two seats.
Let's get on it together.
I'm sorry, but I have to get the data from outside.
You can get the accurate data if you get on it.
It's siesta time.
I have to sleep.
I slept a lot until just now.
Or are you not confident in the plane you made?
I can't help you.
My plane is perfect.
Then, get on it.
*snoring*
I can't help you, Gorilla.
You really are a strong guy.
Well, let's go.
Engine start!
*sir*
In that case, let's start!
limits...
...
*sir*
We're already at Snow Mountain.
You're getting much happier than when you first came here.
One off, two off...
Have you got a 높dorfer's memory?
I can't even say that as a joke.
Hey, you're in all the danger!
Nothing can scare me!
Subscribe!
Well, now you know that I'm not a coward or something, right?
Even though you were fainted!
Hm? What's that sound?
It's a power outage. The electricity's gone.
Hey, wait! It hasn't even been 5 minutes since it took off!
If you fully charge this plane for 5 hours, it can fly for 5 minutes.
Then it's useless!
Don't worry, Gorilla-kun! It's for this kind of situation!
For this kind of situation!
Wh- what's that?!
Step on the pedal! That's how you charge it!
What?!
-Get on it already! -I know!
I did it! It's a success!
This is no different from a manned airplane!
It's no different from a manned aircraft!
-Set complete. -Roger.
You're playing in the middle of the night?
I-it can't be! That's...
It's a special flight with a cash register!
I think we've got a lot of stuff in today's plane.
Japanese police can't even move their hands or legs when they run into the sky.
It's a piece of cake!
Wait!
Huh? Did you hear something just now?
No way, it's above the sky!
Wait up!
Whoa!
It's the Air Police!
We're going to arrest them for the murder of a cash register!
I-I can't believe there's an Air Police in Japan!
We're running away!
I know!
We're not running away!
Hey, speed up! They're going to catch up!
The cash register is too heavy!
Don't you dare! You can't run away with that kind of stuff!
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Take this!
I'm still here!
Here! Take this!
What a quiet guy!
If this happens...
This isn't funny.
I'll get you for this!
S-true...
We'll get you for this!
We've been going through the same kicks...
That's how it's going to go.
Are you crazy?
If you don't leave now, the world will be on our hands.
You'll see!
I'll get you, too!
The End
Ah, there's a hole!
This is why the cloth-based wings are troublesome!
It's okay.
This is also a matter of fact.
I have prepared spare cloth.
What?
Then, I'll sew it up,
so I'll leave the control over there to you.
Eh, me?
Who else is there?
Or are you going to sew it up for me?
Hahaha!
I'll leave such a delicious role to you.
I'll do the back part.
It's okay to just hold the control and step on the pedals.
Don't do unnecessary things.
Hmm.
It's a pity that I can't show my brilliant control technique,
but I can't help it.
Hahaha!
It's really hard to do.
Ah!
Ouch!
What are you doing suddenly?
A-a little...
A little...
It's a test of performance.
Hahaha!
Damn it!
The cloth fell!
Don't you have any other spare cloth?
Ah!
What did you say?
It really fell!
Eh?
What happened?
Oh no!
It's not enough yet!
Damn it!
How about this?
Ah...
Ah!
It's going to crash!
I can't trust this guy!
He is really useless.
Deuuh!
Ah!
Uhh, we're in trouble now.
It's time for you to appear in front of the acrobat.
I'm just Gosh!
Hm?
All right!
Are you all right, thinking like you are now?
Good!
I'll just smash it from above at once!
I'll get you!
Let's go, you pervert!
What?
The moon is very blue!
If you look at the pattern,
a perverted man was flying.
The moon is the moon, right?
It's also Venus!
I'm back!
Why are you guys coming out?
And don't stand in the air!
It's too natural!
I don't think I'm feeling well tonight.
I have a strange illusion.
It's reality!
Oh, no!
The escape device!
Sorry, Gorilla!
I'll take care of the rest!
You're irresponsible!
That perverted man!
I'll arrest you for being a pervert!
Wait, it's me!
Don't you remember me?
A pervert who was flying in a full tank!
You know it, right?
I'm not a pervert!
You didn't tell me!
I'll take care of the moon!
Wait!
I'll let you go!
It's a shame
that I couldn't steal the dispenser.
You managed to escape.
What?
The pervert has been arrested!
The mission is complete!
Wait! I'm a pervert!
What's going to happen to the Air Police?
It's all over.
But the cash dispenser robbery
was arrested, right?
Yes.
But the perverts who flew in the sky
don't need a second team.
So we're going to make
the underground police force.
Now, Gorilla,
let's make the underground police force bigger.
The peace on the ground
is in our hands.
Shut up!
What crime will happen
in such a place?
The End
I'm a monk!
I'm still embarrassed!
Since the police officer's death,
I've been a monk!
I've never arrested a criminal!
But now,
the time has finally come to
use my hands!
Next time on
"The First Monk's Experience as a Monk!"
Thank you for watching!