"Ski-Ai!
The sunset came forward
If I set off a love stone
it would fly to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I used to work out.
I was laughed at as it was.
Even if I try to lose my energy somewhere,
I can only win, and even if I have a bad temper,
I can't change a single thing.
The city is strangely kind.
From the main street of Tongari-boshi,
I'm heading to Kaishakuten.
The sun is setting.
Tomorrow will end like this.
It's over.
If I win, I'll be happy again.
I lost and I realized.
I'm such an idiot.
Speed Battle
Ryotsu, is Ryotsu here?
If it's Senpai, he'll go on patrol.
Patrol?
If he goes on patrol,
I'm going to be suspicious.
That's right.
Is there something you want to tell Senpai?
No, he said that he has been ahead of his salary for this month.
I thought he would use it for something bad.
I see.
I noticed.
Thiseps, I think you're right.
This parliament may be important, too.
It's going to be interesting.
That's what you say, Senpai.
There are so many stalls.
Oh!
What's that strange crowd?
Now, now, welcome!
The New Wave of the Yatai Ginda!
A new type of three-story store with ramen, oden, and beer halls!
Oh, this looks interesting.
Let's have a drink at the beer hall.
Welcome!
Ryo!
Huh?
Reiko Nakagawa!
Senpai!
What are you doing here?
You can tell by looking at me, can't you?
The Yatai Ginda is in a big boom right now.
That's why I decided to start running a stall as a side business.
I thought you wouldn't be able to see me.
I heard you stole the money, but you're using it for this again, right?
Huh?
I'm free to use my own money however I like.
If both Nakagawa and Reiko are not customers, then I'm going home!
Hey, Sakonji!
What is it, Ryo?
You two are trying to stop me at the beer hall!
Huh?
Even Sakonji!
Ryo got caught up in it.
Hey, why don't we have some oden?
Yeah.
I'm hungry.
Hey, you guys.
I want ramen!
Welcome!
I want yakitori!
You two get to the beer hall!
No one can stop Ryo now.
Seriously, Senpai is in trouble too.
Hey!
Wait for the beer.
Ryo!
Hey, Nisan!
You haven't brought the yakitori!
Sorry, I'll bring it right away.
Hey, Sakonji!
You haven't brought the yakitori!
Hey, Ryo!
You're too busy to carry it.
I'm still hungry.
I'm waiting for the showtime at 11 p.m.
Showtime?
There are so many stalls lined up.
If we don't do something that impressive,
we won't survive on this market.
That's fine, but who will do it?
You're the only one.
Me?
Yeah.
I'm not joking.
You don't want to?
Of course not.
That's a shame.
I got a new figure for the Doki-Memo.
What?
Really, Ryo?
Victory!
This time, the figure is one-in-one,
with 200 joints and all poses are as you like.
As you like?
All right!
Showtime!
What's this?
It's hot!
Hey, bro.
The yakitori is burning.
Hey, hey.
Is the oden ready?
Don't shoot.
I'll shoot.
Don't waste it.
Yeah.
A bottle of beer, please.
I'm home.
Hello?
The yakitori isn't here.
I'll be right there.
Hey, everyone.
It's showtime.
I'm not saying you should go home after watching the show.
Enjoy it.
That hurts.
It's burning!
Amazing!
Thank you!
Oh, that's great!
Amazing!
He's got a lot of customers.
We have to be that flashy.
Look, look, look!
It's a big profit as planned.
But I can't get tired in just one day.
I don't have the strength.
I see.
Then let's have Honda buy it.
Instead, we'll have the Doki-Memo figure...
I'll do it! I'll do it! I'll do it!
Are you motivated?
Then, from tomorrow, we'll have not only the night,
but also the daytime.
The daytime?
Yes.
If it's this popular,
then there will be people who will copy this store tomorrow.
It's such a competitive world.
But, from the daytime,
Oden and beer hall won't be a business.
That's right.
The daytime store
has to meet the needs of the customers who use it in the daytime.
It's just around the noon.
All right, I think this is good.
Hey, Sakonji!
This is good!
Hey, Ryotsu.
What are you going to do by stopping here?
Well, well, you'll see.
This is how the night market is in the daytime.
Eh?
What is this night market?
The first floor is a backroom.
Even in the busy hours during the daytime,
you can keep it clean.
On the other side is a pachinko house.
You can relieve the stress in a short time.
And on the side is the
And on the side is a
And, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more!
On the third floor, you can eat cakes for the OLs!
It's designed for all busy office workers, OLs!
It's also called the "Ryo-chan's Yatai", which is a place where you can reach the sickest of places!
A-Amazing! I might be able to go there!
All the office workers and OLs passing by!
Come on, come on, come and take a look!
You can take a quick break and refresh yourself!
You can go to the shop, go to the pachinko, go to the butter golf, and go bowling!
You can also eat cakes for the OLs!
Sounds interesting! Let's go!
He said he can eat cakes for free!
You don't have to eat them!
I did it! As expected of the boss!
Next, the Adagokuren!
Yes!
I-I don't have any money, but I can't do this.
Hey! I'm not going out!
Hey, Ryotsu! Please change a little!
Come on!
I'll just get in the car for now.
I'm wet! I'm wet!
But this won't be enough for your body!
That's right! We still haven't got enough stalls!
Are you going to increase it?
Huh? You're going to patrol the stalls?
Yes.
The number of stalls has increased recently, so there may be trouble with the customer's reception.
Then, I'll leave it to you.
Ah, Chief!
What should we do? If we know that the trouble is the senior...
But, you know, it's just as usual.
I knew it. As I expected, someone who would immediately follow us has appeared.
But we're already a step ahead.
Ugh...
How is it?
This is the world's only 7-story stall.
Ramen, oden, yakitori, okonomiyaki, takoyaki, kaitenzushi, yakimo...
A thousand salaried men will be able to enjoy the best menu.
See!
Huh?
That is a stall!
Then it's not a stall. It's the same as a building!
It's illegal construction!
Huh, Chief!
Oh, Ryozu!
What are you doing here?
No, I'm not a lion!
Who's a lion?
No, I'm not a lion! I'm a lion!
Hey, lion! Stop!
Stop?
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Hey, you idiot!
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
You're not going to do that kind of thing again.
Yes, I won't do it again.
Really?
Yes.
I'm not giving up on this kind of thing.
I've already come up with an idea for the next stall.
Ah, ha, ha, ha!
Ramen, oden, yakitori, okonomiyaki, takoyaki, kaitenzushi, and yakiimo.
This is also a special version of Ryo-chan's "Yatai Ressha" weight transformation!
And with the addition of a computer,
you can pay the electricity bill from the concert ticket.
And you can also get a real station ticket as a family souvenir.
From one to another...
You're going to keep it up like this?
Of course, you can't go to the concert without the ticket.
You have to choose the method.
I'll do it.
Here, ramen.
Hey, can I have an order of oden?
Of course!
Hey, Sakonji!
I'm asking for an order of oden.
What?
Hey, can I have a beer?
Yes.
Hey, can I have an extra yakitori?
Yakitori? Not yet?
Yes, I'll bring it right away.
Thank you, sir.
It's been a while since I've had a drink.
I'm hungry.
I'll go get some food.
Thank you, sir.
That's right.
I'm hungry.
Ah!
It's the Apache of the Bakuryu Captain!
What's this place?
Hey, hey, give me the money!
Damn it!
Hey, the Apache of the Bakuryu Captain!
You're interfering with people's business!
Hey, you're interfering with people's business!
You're the one who's the "Bakuryu Captain"!
So it was your shop.
I came to drink with you.
Why are you riding a helicopter in a place like this?
The customers must have run away.
Don't worry.
I'll pay for it.
Everyone, get ready!
Roger!
Hey!
Let's begin drinking!
Roger!
I want to drink Yakitori's tongue and liver.
Y-Yes.
If these guys are here, I can't start a business.
I'll make them drink quickly and give it back.
Come on, let's drink, Captain!
Hey, Ryosu, don't get too excited.
He이랑ик
We are waiting for Yakitori!
Yakigataran!!
This is a helicopter of the great Great Defense Division, No. 2.
Yes!
My name is Dragoon...
Go to Dragon Arrow.
Roger!
Action code 68.
Codename, Dragon Arrow.
Hey, Captain!
Dragon Arrow!
I need one yakitori lever.
Target, one yakitori lever.
Target locked.
Begin attack.
Fire!
He's still alive.
He's just one yakitori.
How arrogant.
All right.
Now, I'll take your lunch.
Give me some potatoes.
The potatoes are still hard.
What?
Do you think you can afford to do that?
I'm Kaen Houshagi.
Kaen Houshagi?
Roger!
Fire!
All done.
The operation was a success.
Are you going to leave me alone like this, Ryo?
Well, just get me drunk as soon as possible and get on the helicopter.
All right.
Now, now, Captain.
Let's go further.
Okay.
Well, the
Ten Ki sure feet do.
Why are there eight octopuses?
Whoa.
I have enough just for one, and why do you need it all?
All right, all right, all right.
Gimme some.
Here, here, here.
Yeah, here.
Huh?
It ain't too bad, Baki!
Here, here.
One more.
There.
I'm good.
I'll call you later.
Ah, it feels good.
Yes!
Oh, that's right. I'll show you something good.
That's fine. You should go home already. You look pretty drunk.
Don't say that.
This is the new type of speed-reactive bomb our army developed.
The name is "If you stop, you lose, Pooh-Pooh."
Speed-reactive bomb?
If you set this to a car or something, the speed will be below 30 kilometers per second.
As soon as the speed is below 30 kilometers, the device will switch on.
It can also be used to connect multiple vehicles.
We have it equipped for everyone in our unit, just in case.
Hey!
What?
We are training to be able to set it within a minute.
Let's go!
Yes!
Why don't you train in a place like this?
We don't have to train.
If you can do it properly in any situation, the army won't stop.
Set complete! Set complete!
54 seconds.
All right.
What if you set it up and explode?
Don't worry.
If you press the switch on this remote control, the bomb's dimensional device will stop.
If you do this...
Don't panic.
No matter what the situation,
the bomb will stop.
My motto is to deal with it calmly.
Ah!
Hey!
If it really explodes...
Whoa.
It's about time for the joint training.
All of you, go to the helicopter.
Yes, sir!
Hey!
What are you going to do about the bomb?
Anyway, run!
If you run over 30 kilometers, it won't explode.
No way!
You're kidding!
Whoa!
You'll be fine as long as you keep running.
See you later.
No way!
My Sendai-san is also in this store!
Let's go!
But...
Are you sure?
There are also figures from the documentary in this store!
Y-Yes!
Whoa!
Wow!
U-Um, wow!
Well...
Wow!
Hey, don't slow down!
What are you going to do?
You have to find the bomb's structure!
Ryo-tsu!
Is this it?
How's this, Ryo-tsu? Can you do it?
No! The red and blue lines are sticking out!
If you miss the structure of this type of bomb, it'll explode!
Then what are you going to do?
Ryo-tsu, go back! It's uphill!
What?!
You're going to die, Sakonji!
I can't let you fall below 30 kilometers!
Hey, Sakonji!
The explosion is getting more and more intense!
Now you must run!
This time it's downhill!
That's right!
I can't stop! My legs are starting to break!
What are you two doing?
Oh, Honda! We've made it to the right place!
What are you doing?!
Once this was over 30 kilometers per hour...
This yabana will explode!
What did you say?
I'll take a break for now.
Hey Honda, don't drop it below 30kg!
I didn't say that!
What a joke.
He's pulling it so hard.
That's not a human trick.
Okay, in the meantime...
What are you going to do, Ryotsu?
I'm going to find the remote control that the colonel dropped on the hot spring.
This is...
What's going on?
The track has been cut off because of the construction of the road.
What?
The road was cut off because of the construction!
Are you okay, Ryotsu?
What's going on, Ryotsu?
I'm here!
I'm going to turn off the gas.
What?
Why do I have to do this?
Hurry up!
Please hurry up, Ryotsu.
It is...
Hey!
No!
Y presente!
Now it's too late.
I shouldn't have done that either.
It'll be okay.
I'm saved.
What?
Oh, is it already this late?
I have to contact Teiji.
This is the remote control of the Dimensional Bomb.
Then, what about the one before?
This is...
just a phone call, isn't it?
My vegetables!
Kaori!
What? It's me too!
I'm hungry!
That drunk old man!
If we meet again, I won't leave him alone!
Transform! Transform! Transform again!
You guys are just cosplayers!
Stop it!
I won't do that kind of thing!
Why are all the special police officers
all so perverted?
Next time,
"Exchanging to Gourmet"
"Gekko Deka"
Look forward to it!
Translated by: Hikari
"I'm surprised."
"I'm excited."
"I'm calm."
"I'm resolved."
"I'm fast."
"I love you."
♪ Baku! ♪
♪ It flutters ♪
♪ Uyaa! ♪
♪ It bounces ♪
♪ Debe-debe! ♪
♪ It gathers ♪
♪ Bakibagi! ♪
♪ It moves ♪
♪ Byaa! ♪
♪ And flies ♪
♪ It's more powerful than anything else ♪
♪ If everyone gathers here ♪
♪ It's like a dream, the final energy ♪
♪ Looking at tomorrow ♪
♪ Believing in yesterday ♪
♪ Drawing the universe ♪
♪ If you stand on the ground ♪
♪ The planet of Kameari will turn into a circle ♪
♪ Isn't this good? ♪
♪ There's no excuse! ♪
Thank you for watching!