Rollin'
Fly into the river
As I wait for a day to come
With my love at stake
I fly to my shoes
From the water tank of the Tungari-boshi
The sun sets to the Taishakuten
Tomorrow it will end like this
I was happy again with the Katsushika Shiba
I realized it
Because I'm an idiot
First love, that's Ryotsu
Oharo, please have some tea.
Oh, sorry.
If you fill too much, it's not good for your body.
No, I have a job I want to do all day today.
Is that so?
Then don't force yourself too much.
Thank you, Asada-kun.
Please call me Yuuko.
Really?
Then, Yu...
Yuuko.
Yuuko...
Hey, Omari-san.
Are you listening?
Yes?
Which bus stop should I go to at Bakuro Yokoyama Station?
The bus stop should follow this road.
I see.
I hope we can find it soon.
Yes.
I see.
Then I'll go to the bus stop.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Katsushika.
I'll go to the bus stop.
Thank you.
Good night.
Yes.
Don't make me laugh.
Good night.
Get out of the way!
No, no, no! The ship is currently on a mission.
But...
If you want to get it, please line up as soon as possible.
This is the last day.
If you want to buy a photo book with Yuyuko Asada, please line up here.
I'm sure he'll go back to my place.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Why? You've been so quiet since before.
Thank you.
Ah, my...
Chief!
Oh, I'm so glad.
One picture...
No, one more picture than before!
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy!
Roger!
Ryotsu, why are you here?
You can't fool me.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You're the head during your work hours.
What are you doing with your hands?
I was just reading the news while patrolling the man-eating hat.
You were patrolling?
Don't be so harsh.
Show me instead.
What's this?
Isn't this HK?
Of course.
Who do you think Yuuko Asada is?
It's so beautiful.
I love the same woman.
She's a Japanese actress.
Only the actress with these hats can match her taste.
Really?
I put a lot of effort to it.
I didn't see her like that before.
Ryotsu!
Be brave!
It's very good taste.
Not everyone likes her.
You look too close.
Don't get your eyes bent!
Wait a minute.
I met this actress somewhere.
I've met her somewhere.
What? You mean Asada Yuko?
I think everyone who's seen her on TV knows her.
No, I'm not. I've met her somewhere.
What is that?
It's a TV station car.
Cheese!
There's a Kanchan from Ryotsu, right?
Yes, there is.
What did you do again?
I don't know.
You're Kanchan?
You're so unique!
Nice! It's a TV station car!
What is a TV station?
I'm actually the director of KTV.
I came here to ask you to appear on TV.
TV?
Yes, I can't help it.
I'd be happy if I knew that you're a first love.
What do you mean?
Tomo.
What a charm!
You seemed to be a first love.
Did you say that?
NO!
Were you mistaken?
That's right! I was wrong.
I'm not sure if you're real or not.
You always do such things.
It's possible to say I'm the best KTV usually.
Here's a new story.
Kanchan.
It's me.
I've been reading the album on TV since I was in elementary school.
I'm similar to Yuko's mother.
I'm checking with my mom.
You have a good eye for the camera since you were a kid.
This is a picture from the time of the parade.
Ah, by the way, there was a big girl in the back of the elementary school.
That's right.
That girl is Yuko Asada, who is excited about the present.
It was true that I had said that I had met before.
Oh, you're good.
I see.
I see. You were in love with me at that time.
I was always hiding and watching my first love, my beloved Kan-chan, while I was excited about the sad girl's heart.
Don't you hate me?
No.
I can't believe that a girl like Yuko Asada is like a primitive man.
It's impossible to believe.
But I've never talked to her.
It's because of her love for you.
I've also looked up the story.
She said she was a long-legged, cool sportsman.
Long legs?
It's hard to say that she was long-legged.
Even though I thought she was long-legged, I was wrong.
Her nickname was very nice.
I remember that nickname when I was in elementary school.
I think it was when I was in high school.
It was a perfect nickname.
Very nice?
Is it a mistake of the data?
There is no mistake in the country's KTV.
That's right. This is decisive.
I got a love letter from the trash can on the day of graduation.
What? A love letter from the trash can?
Was there such a happy thing?
I got it, right?
Yuko-san wouldn't lie.
That's right.
Try to remember, Ryotsu.
Come on, remember.
Remember, come on.
I remember.
I feel like I had it.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Look at me.
After all, there is no mistake in my research.
I remember something.
The color of the blanket between the trash can was pink, wasn't it?
Pink?
A big hit?
Is that so?
That's right.
I'm the first love of Yuko Asada.
Is that so?
Then, I'll call you later.
Thank you.
Isn't he amazing, Ryo-chan?
Well, Kan-chan, I called him Yurin.
That great actress, Yurin.
I don't know what will happen in the world.
That's where I'm going, Ryotsu.
I have a favor to ask you.
A favor? What is it?
When I meet Yuko-san,
can you get me a signature for this photo book?
I want to give a love letter to Mr. Ohara.
I'll write a love letter to Mr. Ohara.
But, you're the first love of Yuko Asada.
You can't do something so vulgar.
But, I'll do something about it.
If you say so, you can think about it.
I see.
If you can imitate what I do here,
I'll do something about it.
I did it in elementary school.
It's a gag that invited all the students to a big party.
What is that?
It's suspicious.
It's about Ryo-chan.
It's a joke.
You're right.
If you don't want to do it, it's fine.
I'm sure Yuri was staring at my gag.
I see.
Then, I'll definitely get a signature.
Of course.
It's a promise from a man.
Not only a signature,
you can do it with him.
Then, you can shake hands.
Shake hands?
No.
All right.
I'll do it.
How?
First,
put your fingers in the nostrils.
What's wrong?
Hurry up.
Chief,
you're so motivated.
No.
How is it, Ryo-chan?
If you're really not motivated, it's fine.
What?
Did I do something wrong?
It's over or there is no high çıkarion.
High...
A high...
You'll see Yuko Asada who you yearn for.
As you do that...
I got it...
-H Gina! -A agora!
-Gira! -A agora!
Have you done enough?
Aren't you ashamed?
What?
I mean, it was a joke.
Fine.
Ryo and Kiki,
I'll count on you.
I'll be going.
Ohara-kun!
Yes, yes.
Good work.
Chief, you're like Ryo-chan's manager.
You're like her lover.
I can't help it.
Thanks to you, I can meet Asada Yuko.
Oh, it's the TV station.
Look, Ryo-chan.
The TV station is huge.
Ryo-chan.
It's okay, it's okay.
Can you call the director, Mizusawa-chan?
What?
Hey, Kan-chan!
Wait for me!
Yo, Mizusawa-chan!
Oh, oh!
The Omutaguni of the swap is going up and down!
Oh!
Chief, Chief, it's Omuro-Namie!
Oh, oh!
What?
What did you say?
What did you say about the Omuretsu with Matsutake?
Oh, I don't know about the director.
I can't tell you how moved I am.
I'm Asada Yuko's only son.
It's thanks to this first love that I can meet that Yuuri.
Please understand that.
I understand.
Kan-chan, you're determined today.
Let's go to the usual place as usual.
Yuuri!
Let's go
Wait!
It's 3:00 in the morning.
Wait here quietly, Kan-chan.
Can you keep the star waiting?
I'll wait!
I see a가
Ouch!
I know that the tonkatsu and the nori noodles from the store are delicious.
What's wrong, chief?
I'm in the bathroom.
Chief, don't be so nervous.
I'm going to puke.
I feel refreshed.
You should take a shower by yourself.
I feel a little bit sad to be alone.
That's why you are in trouble.
Well, well, well...
Huh? Where did it come from?
Well, whatever.
Hey, Ryozu, it wasn't here, was it?
I'm worried about you, chief.
Leave it to me.
Was it here?
I'll do the makeup.
Excuse me.
Hey, you're leaving.
I'm the one who's leaving.
The device was wrong.
Hang in there, Ryozu.
I left it to you.
It's okay.
You can go to the studio by the time it's time.
If I make a mistake this time, I'll be sorry.
Huh?
Do you think you don't have to see Yuyuko Asada by saying that?
It's a lie. It's a lie.
Ryozu, don't say that.
Please.
I hope you understand.
Then, please come with me quietly.
Ryozu...
What's wrong, Ohara?
No, nothing.
Is it really okay here?
Yeah.
Huh? Chief, we're on the screen.
Huh?
Is it this camera?
What?
Who's on TV?
Is it me?
Is it this?
Hey, get out of my way.
Chief, Chief, look.
I'm on the screen.
It's someone else.
You're...
What are you doing?
I'm...
Who do you think I am?
I'm the first love of Yuyuko Asada.
Why do I have to run away?
No, no, no.
I'm the first love of Yuyuko Masada.
Watch out, I tell you.
What the hell are you doing?
You're the first love of Yuyuko Asada.
When did he take your body to see me?
What the hell are you doing in my house?
I'm the first love of Yuyuko Asada.
The one in charge of such a thing.
I'm a ex-boyfriend.
It's not good, is it?
This is delicious. You should eat it.
But...
I'm the pekingian of cooking, introducing a Chinese dish.
Today's dish is this.
Idiot!
You haven't eaten all of it yet!
Ryo, we're running out of time.
I know, I know.
This is great!
Russian human pie.
I'm Iwana Petya.
Ryo, is this good?
It's good.
Why?
Looking at the set from the back, it looks like a simple one made in a convenience store.
Oh, I see.
Why am I the only one who looks like this?
Ryo, where are you?
Oh, I'm here.
What are you doing? The show's about to start.
Oh, yes.
It's about to start.
Ryo, are you okay?
I wonder if the director will be able to see me.
I'm nervous.
Ah, my heart is beating so fast.
Hi, everyone.
It's time for 3:00 PM.
Our guest today is the famous Japanese actress, Yuko Asada.
Hello, I'm Yuko Asada.
You're beautiful, Yuko Asada.
When I look up close...
...you're so dazzling.
You're so beautiful.
When you meet her, give her this bouquet.
Okay?
Thank you.
And when you're a child, you can ask Yurin about how much I was attractive.
Leave it to me. Don't worry.
Now, it's time for the "Memories" segment.
Finally.
Let's go, Asada.
Oh, no. I'm nervous.
First, the silhouette quiz.
Who is this person?
Excuse me. I don't know much about this.
Well, it's not impossible.
It's just that it's different from elementary school.
Well, I'll call you by the nickname of Asada at the time, so listen carefully.
Here you go.
Yurin.
I don't know much about it.
If I knew it, Yurin would be very impressed.
Ah, you're...
Kan-chan!
Yuriiiiin!
Yuriiin. What's wrong?
What if she asks me to marry her?
I'll give you a big hint.
The first name of the name is "Ri".
Ri...Ri, right?
You're even more beautiful when you're worried.
Okay, then. Here's a big hint.
My name is Kankichi.
Kankichi-san.
You still don't remember?
I won't call you by full name.
Hey, hey. What's going on, Mizusawa-chan?
Please.
It's okay. It's okay.
The actress seems to be in trouble.
Well, let's say it.
The full name is...
Ryo-tsu Kankichi-san!
Yes, Ryo-tsu Kankichi-san!
Who are you?
I'm...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Hmm...
Even if the actress doesn't forget her line,
will she forget her name?
After all, it's something she did since elementary school.
So, I'll give you a special hint.
Please come out to the stage.
Even if she forgets her name,
she should remember my face.
Ryo-tsu Kankichi-san, please.
Yuuri!
Who is this person?
What's going on?
His nickname is "Funkorogashi".
Now, you remember, right?
I see.
Oh, I see.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hey, let me take a photo of you.
It's a love letter.
Ah, it's been 20 years to do so.
I can't remember anything.
Oh.
Ah, I forgot something important.
Asada-san has once put a love letter in a trash cans.
A love letter?
In a trash cans?
Oh, yes.
This person is the one.
I think you can remember something from the photo.
It's her.
This is the one.
I'm Ryochi, a leader of the school.
Oh!
I think you'll remember this gag if you watch it.
Gag?
Yes!
I was popular in school at that time.
I made the whole school laugh at me.
It's a gag!
Then please watch it!
Okay!
Oh, my God!
I remember!
Yay!
It's a touching encounter!
Oh, my God!
I'm Ryochi, the leader of the school, who made a joke about my uniform.
Ryochi Kankichi!
What a fool!
But, your mother said that this photo is her.
I gave you my love letter.
You idiot!
I'm not your enemy!
I'm sorry!
I can't live any more!
This man is the least good person in this school, Kankichi Ryochi.
Kankichi Ryochi!
Is this the national internet?
Idiot!
Come on!
Eat up!
Ryotsu, don't lose your temper.
Do it harder!
I'm trying!
Just stop it already!
No!
I'm paying you back for messing up my show!
Now, you guys!
Let's get rid of all the grudges!
Yes!
I'm so scared!
Don't you dare, Ryotsu!
Yo!
How was the show?
What?
You!
Actually,
the one we did last time
had the best ratings.
That's the fun of live broadcasting.
So,
I'd like to have you on every show
and make a segment about you.
Sure!
Don't mess with me!
I'm never going to be on TV!
No matter what they say,
I'll show you my wani-kou!
This guy's character is easy to misunderstand.
He's no stranger to me!
Besides,
I had a dream of buying a wani when I was a kid!
Next time,
"Wani-kou! The Soul of the Artist of Tears!"
Don't miss it!
She's a girl who can't fall in love
Rumor has it
There are many things she wants to do
I'd like to run in a bike
across the vast desert
I want to ride a vacuum motorcycle
I want to be more free than a bird
A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a telescope
I'm sorry for my love, I'm sorry
The future of the panorama
The dazzling light that dives
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me