Unwanted Person"
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and look away.
"The Unwanted Person"
Come to me, the unwanted person!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'll be fine in a while.
Unemployed person
"The Unwanted Person"
Come to me, the unwanted person!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the burning red clouds.
I'll be fine in a while.
I wonder if it'll work somehow
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
Laser
Star
I did it! Spot on!
I can do it too!
Next, let's match it!
If you do this, you'll have more fire range!
Listen closely...
It will explode in a couple of hits!
Wow! As expected from Kankichi!
That's right, Tomo. I'm a genius!
Hey!
You guys are the ones who did this!
Tompei! Chikichi! Run away!
Hey, wait!
Wait!
The child shrine maiden is a middle school student this year.
It's all rusted.
It's dangerous if it breaks.
I've repaired it many times.
I'll order a new one next year.
There's a way to carry children in the temple.
I'll hit you with a sword soon.
That's the silver bar of the Sukudaniya, isn't it?
That's what shortened the life of the shrine maiden.
What was he doing in the shrine?
Hey, Kankichi! The key is not locked!
Hmm...
I did it!
I got in first place!
Getting a date for the shrine maiden before Miyada...
...is such a relief!
I'll find a place for you tomorrow!
Here I am!
You pick one good place!
This is my place every year!
This is it!
No! This place is mine!
What is this?
Let go of me!
Stop it!
It's broken.
What should we do?
You fell because you pushed it.
No, it's Tonbei's fault.
It's your fault for trying to escape.
This is not the time to say that.
We have to do something about this.
It's broken, what should we do?
Is there a way?
Let's exchange it with the eighth one.
What?
The eighth one is just like ours.
We can't find out if we take it back.
But the eighth one is quite big.
We can take it back by morning.
But it's too heavy for three people.
We can't take it back.
Are we still going to the Shrine?
Not yet.
Can we take a break?
Our shoulders are about to break.
We can't.
We won't be there by morning.
We don't need to carry it for ten years.
That's right, it's a shortcut.
If we go through here, we can reach the Shrine.
The eighth Shrine is under the dodo.
But the train is not coming.
It's okay. It's still early for the start.
What?
It's a train!
Kakichi is lying!
Hurry up!
The train can't cross!
Kakichi!
No! Jump into the river!
Damn it! I had a hard time.
It was a festival after all.
You're doing something dangerous.
I'm sorry.
I want to tell you not to copy a good kid.
Speaking of festivals, when we were little, it was a big event.
It was fun.
I got my pocket money and searched for what I wanted under the acetylene lamp.
Acetylene lamp?
I don't know.
I don't think the Nakagawa and Reiko generation knows.
Instead of a light bulb, they use a lamp to light up a shop.
By the way, is there anyone who's too close and burns their hair?
The color and smell of that flame,
I still remember it well.
Ryo-chan is a festival lover.
Well, well.
By the way, what about the club president today?
It's the last day.
But later, he said he would come to the festival with Hiromi-san and Daisuke-kun.
By the way, Mr. Honda and Komachi-chan also said they would come.
We're busy with our work, but we're all going to the festival.
By the way, Mr. Honda and Kumachi-chan also said they would come.
By the way, didn't all of you say...
I think they're all going to come, too.
What!?
Then let's go get my friends to celebrate the festival.
Well...
It's going to be special, so we're going to celebrate it together.
Ryo-chan, it's fine, Ryo-chan.
I got used to being the one who plays the acetylene lamp,
But still.
Hahaha!
What's so busy about K-Law?
It's like we're back in our childhood.
Don't worry about it, Ryo-chan.
Let's patrol by ourselves.
Yes!
Wow!
Awesome!
What's going on?
Listen, look closely.
Look!
It's 10 yen from here.
Wow!
What's going on?
That's amazing, old man!
Hahaha!
Show us more!
Show us, show us!
Show us!
Alright, alright.
Then take a good look.
What's going to be missing this time?
Hmm...
Wow!
I think that's...
Ah!
It's my wallet!
When did you get it?
That's a great trick!
That's not a trick.
It's a trick!
Excuse me, but can you show me again?
Huh?
Oh, Mr. Omawari!
I'm just a child.
I'm a child-loving boy.
Bye, kids!
Bye-bye, old man!
You're the best at eating like this, Anzahm!
That's awful!
Huh?
It's not what a police officer in a uniform does.
How is it?
It may be a poison to the primitive.
What?
Two Demekins?
What did you say?
It's exactly the same!
That flashy yukata is like a Demekin with goldfish.
Huh?
What?
I don't have any beauty-sense.
Huh?
Ah, Senpai!
Good evening!
Ah, you're with Otohime, huh?
Ah, you two shouldn't get too close.
It's a poison to those who can't have a boyfriend.
What?
I don't want to be called a "poor, young man."
Hmm.
Nana, let's go to the shrine.
Yeah.
Huh?
Let's go to the shrine.
Daikichi, huh?
I'm so scared!
But...
I'm scared, too!
Ahaha!
Well, what should we eat next?
Grandma, two hot ones!
Sure!
You're working, but you're quite hungry.
Y-Yes, Chief!
Hey, Hiromi!
Good evening!
You've grown up, Daisuke!
Yeah!
You're just like Hiromi, Sakura.
You can't even look at a man who looks like you.
What?
You can't look at a man who looks like you.
Well, Chief, you're a little too young.
At the festival, a young man can have a lot of fun.
You're right, Papa.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey grandpa, let's count them.
And a tishtime!
Do you understand, Ryotsu?
The festival is the place for money.
Pay much attention.
Yes, I know that.
It seems that the chief is not a good fit for me.
Yeah, maybe he is.
Oh, come on!
Take your time!
Hurry up!
Geez!
Excuse me!
Be careful, man!
What's that?
Grandpa, let's go quickly!
Ah, yeah...
Could it be that guy...
No, that can't be.
It's Grandpa!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Oh, look, look.
I can't run.
Hey, wait, goldfish!
I'm gonna arrest you!
Wait a minute!
Hey!
I told you to stop!
You...
Come on!
You can't run away!
Hey!
I got you!
Oh!
No!
Nana-chan's manga character is on it.
Give me that!
No, no.
Mine is delicious.
I'll give you a bonus.
Three million yen.
Thank you.
It's a waste to eat.
Yeah.
Hmm?
That's weird.
Where did my wallet go?
There's no "Sai-sen-dorobou" here.
I'll take care of this place.
I have to save you all.
You are the only one who can do it.
I'll take care of it.
I'll see you here.
Thank you very much.
And thank you for your help.
You found me.
I'll keep Mr. Ichigo.
What's the number?
I'll give it to you the next time.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Huh?!
Well, are you good?
Calm down, Mr. Ichigo!
Well, you two, good luck!
Good luck to you, too.
Let's go!
Wait.
Huh?
My wallet has gone somewhere!
There's a 6-month-long deposit in that!
Senpai!
It's a suri.
Alright! Let's split up and catch it!
Yes!
I got a suri!
Papa, it's a suri!
What?
N-No way...
What? My wallet is gone! I got a suri!
What?
That means there's a criminal nearby!
That guy over there!
Hey! Wait!
You're not getting away!
You bastard!
You're a criminal!
You're under arrest!
Give me what you stole!
Hey, let go!
You're not getting away!
You rascal!
You're a rascal!
I'll get you!
Hey, boss!
Why are you getting a suri?
I'm not getting a suri!
You're running away!
I just wanted to go to the bathroom!
I...
I found it this time!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm sorry!
I...
I lost it!
I think it came this way.
Where did it go?
Ryotsu.
Ouch!
What are you doing here?
Boss!
Didn't the suri come this way?
Suri?
No, I was looking at this shrine for a long time.
But no one came here.
Oh, I see.
That's strange.
Where did it go?
Hang on.
Look over there.
Yes, yes!
You can come out.
It's been a long time, Karasawa.
Mr. Ohara...
15 years.
No, I think it's longer.
Hiromi was a junior in elementary school.
Thank you for your help.
I'm sure you've made some progress.
Please give him my gratitude.
I'm very thankful to you for your kindness.
Mr. Hinamatsu I'm grateful to be a part of the hu census.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad you came to our house.
I'll think of her more.
Thank you.
And thank you.
Thank you so much.
Good night, Takahashi.
Good night.
See you next time.
"Karasawa Masagoro"
That man is the high-ranking officer of the police, Karasawa Masagoro.
Ouch, papa!
No, don't hold me so tightly!
It hurts, Hiromi!
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's gone!
I can only arrest the high-ranking officer for that.
Oh, no.
Where did Karasawa go?
There he is!
One, two, three...
Oh, damn it!
It's gone!
Look, papa! Papa!
Papa?
That was close.
I saw it, Karasawa!
You!
You're the police!
It's time for you to take your revenge!
Dad!
Masaru!
There's something interesting over there!
I'm waiting!
Want to go see it?
Oh, yeah.
Later.
You go first.
Let's go right now, dad!
No, you go first!
Then, I'll go first.
Come right away, dad!
Thank you for your help.
It's a problem if the children see us.
Papa!
Look, look!
I did it!
You did it, Hiromi!
I'm a little busy with this old man.
I'm a child, so I can wait alone.
Yeah.
See you later!
Karasawa, when you get out of the office, I'll be your guarantor.
If the children are cute, you'll get a good job.
Don't come back here, Karasawa.
You're never coming back.
Haruta!
You've done a good job.
You're all set.
I heard you want to come back tomorrow.
I'm glad.
You've got a new start.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I will never do that again.
Yeah.
You can't leave Masaru and your wife alone.
It's a promise.
At that time, Mr. Ohara's kindness was in my heart.
No, it's the source of his hard work.
What happened to your wife?
Two years ago, we were working together.
I was relieved.
I see.
I remembered something bad.
So, what now?
Masaru and his wife are in trouble.
Oh, that time.
Come back, dad.
But there's not much good things in the world.
Did something happen?
Masaru's company went bankrupt.
After his life became unstable,
I thought I had to take care of my unpaid salary.
But I didn't get a job.
And I couldn't stay at home.
I see.
Grandpa!
Oh, Daisuke.
Grandpa, buy us a robot.
We promised.
I know.
Later.
I'll go later.
Go to your mother's house.
Yes, I promise.
I'm his grandson, Daisuke.
And my little sister, Sakura.
We're brothers.
Masaru is my son.
Is Masaru's wife pregnant?
She's the only one.
They're about the same age.
Oh, I see.
That's cute.
It's true that you don't want to see your grandchild.
Just being with them makes you feel at ease.
But I can't buy anything for my grandchild's birthday.
Who do you think has the heart?
I just happened to see it.
I told the kids it was a handkerchief.
But it wasn't a handkerchief.
It was a handkerchief of a mule.
I understand that feeling.
But giving money and things isn't the only way to express your love for your grandchild.
Don't you think so?
Where did she go?
I can tell by looking at her face.
Nakagawa! Reiko!
Did you find the mule?
Kei-chan is looking for someone who looks like it.
I told her I saw it today.
There are too many people and I can't find it.
Nakagawa!
The mule was arrested by the police.
You can't escape or throw away your evidence wallet.
I understand.
I won't let you go.
More than money and things,
you need to follow the rules of the world.
You need to know what's good and what's bad.
You need to keep your promises.
Promises?
I'm always speaking seriously about my promise to you.
Thank you.
I'll never give it to you again.
Don't make your wife or Masaru cry.
I promise you.
Ohara...
I will not say anything more than this.
The key of the Sandra High School
Who is CEO Ohara speaking to?
What's the matter, Nakagawa?
Chief Ohara, who's He?
He's my friend, but he's...
A friend of the chief?
Kei...
Anyway, I've been yelling for you, but you're really here.
You're right!
Mr. Honda and Komachi's wallets were stolen, too.
You might be mistaken.
Try looking again.
Chief.
I'm sure he doesn't know where he put them because he's wearing a new yukata.
Yeah.
Nakagawa!
Tell the other victims to look again to see if their wallets were really stolen.
Y-Yes, sir.
I know.
No.
It's him!
Slimei, you're in trouble!
I got you!
You hid it here, didn't you?
Senpai!
Look carefully!
This is my wallet!
It's mine!
Mine, too?
That's good.
What do you think? It's a fire that can't be moved!
Darn it!
Well done, Ryotsu.
Senpai!
Huh?
It's not just mine.
H-Hey!
Excuse me, sir!
Can I ask you something?
Naka-air!
sinners
There it is!
The money and the yuka are safe!
That's good!
But, chief, I...
What about me?
I said that it didn't matter a little bit, but it's not!
Right, Nakagawa?
Meaningless
It was my bad.
I'm very sorry.
It's nothing.
Oh, it's Grandpa!
Dad!
Grandpa!
You guys...
I'm glad. I was worried you wouldn't be quiet.
Masaru said he's always liked festivals, so he'd probably be here.
Dad, I've decided on a new job.
The conditions are better than before, and I'm getting really nervous.
I see. That's good.
Grandpa, Grandpa said he likes sushi today.
I see. I love sushi, too.
You're Tadashi?
Yes. I'm Tadashi, which means "honest and honest".
That's a good name.
Well, then, Mr. Ohara...
Bye-bye!
Grandpa!
I thought I saw him when I was little.
I think he's not here.
Oh, that's right. He's my old friend.
I don't like it.
The chief has a lot of tears in his eyes.
Well, he says there's no bad guy who likes festivals.
Ryotsu, you...
Idiot!
No matter how much you like festivals, you can't just leave work to a fool.
Hurry up and get that man to join you.
Yes, yes.
Let's go!
The End
♪ When I walked along the street ♪
♪ Looking back at the days of rain ♪
♪ That someone calls me ♪
I walked while looking back at the day after the rain
I was drawn to the gacha
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk only the black part of the Akegogai Tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above his eyes
Go up and see that corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Thank you for your support for a long time
This time I really became a police officer
Reiko, why do you work so hard for me?
Is it love for me?
Next time, goodbye Ryo
Reiko, marry me!
The last time, let 's meet again
I want to keep my family
The third child
Such a wonderful Spencer
My family is giving him a lot of love
Thank you so much
I'll leave
"I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love