Translated by Releska
♪ Looking at the sunset that floats in the river ♪
♪ When I kicked the stone ♪
♪ It flew to my shoes ♪
♪ I wonder where it went ♪
♪ It laughed at me saying it was still a
♪ Even if I try to cheer up ♪
♪ I can't help but laugh ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes ♪
♪ Is strangely gentle ♪
♪ Even if I try to cheer up ♪
♪ From the water of the Tongari City ♪
♪ To the Taishakuten ♪
♪ The sun sets ♪
♪ Tomorrow will end like this ♪
♪ Katsushika, Shibamata, and even happiness ♪
♪ I lost them and realized ♪
♪ I'm such an idiot ♪
Katsushika, Shibamata, and even happiness
Katsushika, Shibamata, and even annoying
♪ I wish the sky would always be blue ♪
The nearby patagas are under our control.
Roger that.
Let's go, Maria.
Okay, Reiko.
The Cosmo's name is not a joke.
If you connect the lines with the artificial satellite we gave you,
you can accurately see the movement of the ground from the navigation.
Maria, will you take out the car of the culprit?
Yes.
The manufacturer is an old man.
The name of the car is PearlyDX.
It has five cars in total.
The color is black.
I've got one.
The number is being displayed by UTMS.
It's a car of the culprit.
There are three passengers.
There's no doubt about that.
What's that?
It's a patagas!
When did you...
PearlyDX over there!
Stop right there!
What?
It's scary.
You won't catch me.
I'll show you how to use the A-class license.
I'm going to run away, no matter where I go.
Damn it!
I have to get up.
Here you are.
A gift from Super Cosmo.
Do you know this?
No, I don't.
I can't believe you have this power.
That's my first time in this car.
I can't believe this is your first time in this car.
Close this place.
If I see you in the middle of the street,
I'll come on up.
Don't tell me you're not done with the school record.
Are you the king of school?
I'm not doing anything.
Don't you agree?
As you can see,
Who does that?
We can't miss out on the activities of Reiko Harimoto and Junsa Asato Ai.
There are many men in Japan who want to be caught by them.
They became very popular.
We want a car like that too.
Don't you know?
Actually, today, a new car developed jointly with the United States will come here.
What? Really?
I'm going to drive it!
It's true! This car is amazing!
You seem to like it, Mr. Gorilla.
Why are you...
Professor Ezaki, then, who developed this new car?
Right. This is the famous super car I developed.
Ezaki G1.
Wow, what a wonderful car!
You're with the chief?
I'm glad to see you.
You were chosen as the driver of this super car.
Me?
But, that guy developed it, didn't he?
Exactly.
Ezaki G1 is the best robot car I've ever developed.
Robot car?
Are you going to transform it?
No, no.
It has artificial intelligence.
It can control the car and decide by itself.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Wow, he talks!
Is he really talking to himself?
Yes. I'm talking in my own will.
What's surprising is that he's still imitating it!
Can you do it?
Hahaha. It's a face.
It looks nothing like you.
And the game for the first time in a long time!!!
You're a mess than usual!
I'm not going to let you do that!
You're going to make a comedian out of me?
What are you doing, Chief?
Watch your mouth!
I'm a police officer!
What?
You're a police officer?
What are you talking about?
Yes, yes.
You're a police officer?
I'm a robot with artificial intelligence.
You got it?
You're far better than me.
But why am I your driver?
It's a test job, so it's dangerous.
Yes!
Maria and Reiko's Cosmo is far more powerful.
You're the only one who can stand up even if you get hit by a tank.
Isn't that a risk of your life?
Okay.
Frontier Spirit!
The soul of America!
Before I knew it, you have become an American cowboy.
I'm only a switch politician.
The water in America is water.
King of Beer!
I'm no different than you, call me Eizaki Korosuke.
Remember this style.
You don't even drink and still get out of the way.
Anyway, Lyots,
I'm going to be your boss today.
I'm going to work hard every day.
I can't believe this car is your boss.
Ouch!
What's the point of being a boss?
Natsu!
You're going to die!
This is my special skill.
Headlock.
Damn it!
That's right.
If you're far from me, it's my fault.
What's the point of being a boss?
You're a car, but you're not good at talking.
You're naive.
I'll tell you this next time you run away.
I'll visit someone more capable.
He's bigger than you!
Of course!
Your smart index is more than three times your own.
Then you change your mind as a paragon of male and female.
I'll tell you why I watch a movie.
The American computer industry is the leading global industry.
How to fool people does not exist.
I can hear you.
What are you talking about?
I got it! You're the boss! I won't fight back!
If you understand, you're welcome.
He seems like a tough boss.
The waxing is finally over.
It looks like it's going to be a lot of work.
It's a car made by that crazy professor.
It was made in opposition to Reiko and Maria's Cosmo.
I wonder what kind of special feature it has.
Look at this.
It's a different car!
It's a double-sided patrol car.
I see. No one would think this is a patrol car.
I don't wanna know what a patrol car is!
Ryo-kun.
Put your hand on my door.
Like this?
The fingerprints.
Their names.
Ryo-kun, Yuki Kanchi, and Jun Sakusho.
Love of love.
Millionaires who are like-minded.
One who isn't interested in getting married in the opinion poll.
Number 1 in seven years in a row.
Don't give me that kind of name!
Ouch!
I'll teach you how to fight!
That was a rough one.
Hi! Ryo, Kei, Ryo!
Oh, Reiko and Maria.
I heard your rival was stolen, so I came to see you.
I'm not a rival.
Hello, Lady Reiko, Lady Maria.
The car's talking!
I'm Ezaki Z1.
I'm a robot with artificial intelligence.
You two look so beautiful.
You're so good, Scott.
You're wrong.
Reiko is a woman, but Maria is a man.
Hey!
I like singing!
You're right!
Hey, Maria!
Yeah?
Yeah.
Maria is a man.
Reiko is a woman, and Maria is a man.
Hey!
Maria is a woman.
Stop....
Stop thinking too much.
It's going to break in the end.
But the first place of the score is...
It's going to be the first place of the score.
Ryo, you're right.
But the number one ago is indeed the number one.
Everyone's staring at it.
I'm getting used to it.
It's easier to drive automatically.
What's the matter with you?
You didn't put on an airbag, did you?
Watch your step while driving.
I got it.
Then I'll just listen to the CD.
I'll just listen to the CD.
You're not my type.
You're my type.
What are you doing? I love listening to it.
You're going to fight your boss?
Then I think you're in trouble.
You'll be kicked out of your course and you'll get a bonus.
I got it.
Don't worry about it.
I'll laugh at you every time.
I've been doing it for a long time.
I told you I'm a police officer.
Emergency call.
I know where to get the water.
It's in the warehouse over there.
All right. It's your chance.
Don't lose, Z-Wing.
I'm going to eat you up.
Emergency food.
Hey, don't come over here.
Come back!
Let me go.
Not there.
Over here.
Let me go.
I will try this again.
Gamgam Umi.
What's happening?
Cut it out!
It's a threat!
You're even more lethal than Kuinigehan!
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
We're a little late, but we have the Gamgam and Missile, and the Mitsudan.
We're the best!
It's our fault!
Go!
We found the evil injection vehicle! Move immediately!
Again?
Let's forget about that!
We can't let this crime go!
Fire the grenade!
This is no good.
Look at this.
There's not a single piece of paper about Z-1.
It's all about Maria and Reiko.
Hmph. That's strange.
What is the Japanese press looking at?
You're doing it the wrong way.
If you keep this up, Cosmo will be in deep trouble.
What do you think will happen then?
What will happen?
That's obvious.
Z-1 will be judged as incompetent and disqualified.
Scrap!
No! No! No! No!
Then I'll do as I say!
What did you say?
What do you mean?
The Japanese are most interested in...
the mito-ko!
It's a trap!
It's Goto!
Wait!
No, it's Goto!
It's Goto!
No!
Young man, wait!
This window is the key!
Listen! Listen!
What's this?
It's the Net-Dan!
Net-Dan, fire!
Damn it!
How's that?
This brain-based strategy
that used a Japanese's brain
to make a fool out of a ghost!
What's the problem?
If you do something that stands out,
you'll become a real reporter.
I see.
From now on,
you can do as I say.
Listen!
This is Japan!
Japan!
I must work hard
to make the Japanese happy!
Good.
Ryo-chan,
I'll give you a special mission.
Teach me how to make the Japanese happy.
Alright!
Leave it to me!
Listen!
The song is Enka and the name is Bushi.
I'll treat my subordinates well,
and I'll show them my guts!
Sons!
I'll show them the true power of my spirit!
It's time for our match.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Hey!
I won!
It's time for our match.
Hey!
I can do it!
Ryo-chan!
You can do it!
Kei-bouho!
Special drink service time!
-The best wax... -This is so nice.
The more you polish it, the more glossy it gets.
Oh, really?
Should I add a bottle?
Boy, a new bottle.
And two water-resistant bottles, please.
Kei-bouho, I can't drink anymore.
You idiot! Let's do it again!
I'm sorry, I can't drink anymore.
Ryo!
What the hell is this?
A yakitori shop, a karaoke box, and a cabaret!
I don't want to, Chief.
It's all Kei-bouho's money.
What?
I just got paid for it.
I can't refuse my boss's invitation.
It would be a punishment.
You're really good, Senpai.
You've already got a D1.
There's no way the D1 would do that!
You did it all!
You should be punished!
"The terrorist in the ICPO's international mission is found!"
Emergency call!
What?
That violent guy?
Ryotsu, go arrest him with the D1 right away!
But you have to take off all those stickers.
"The terrorist is heading towards Tokyo Bay."
"He's probably going out into the ocean."
"There's a car behind us that's coming very fast."
"This is it."
"This is Ryo's car."
"There you go, bros! Let's race!"
"He's in a bad shape."
"He's affected by a car. His AI is changing his character a little."
"That's pretty amazing."
"Hello?"
"How are you?"
"I don't get anything."
I can't lose to a criminal arrest.
Reiko, you're speeding up. Don't lose, Z-1!
Don't get any closer!
Watch out!
Can you see this window?
Is that going to surprise me?
Emi and Sherry, the missiles are being launched!
All units, fire!
What? Hey, what about that?
Fire!
Watch out!
The boss is running away!
It's not over yet.
The sea and sky are a gift from Cosmo!
He's running away!
But...
Now's your chance to get a chance to do something!
Fly, Z-1!
Be brave!
You can do it!
...
Ryo, what are you going to do?
Fly, you'll be a hero!
...
Ryo!
"Ryo-chan"
Where's Senpai?
It can't be... Ryo's...
Ryo-chan! Ryo-sama!
Senpai!
Ryo-sama!
Ryo-san!
I'll save you right now, Z1!
What?
Whoa!
Hang in there, Z1!
I-I'm fine...
It's nothing...
Z1!
R-Ryo-san...
We were best partners, weren't we?
Yeah! We're best partners!
So don't die, Z1!
R-Ryo-san...
Z1!
I'll take care of you!
I'll never forget you!
Z1!
Hey, everyone.
The Chief is here today for an inspection.
The Chief?
Ryo-san, don't be rude to him.
Oh, the Chief is here!
Everyone, I'm the Chief!
Hahaha!
Little brother's back!
Z1-chan!
Look, Z-1, I was just being polite.
Now then, let the matter of honor BE relax!
Wh-what do you mean?
Hey, Mr. Lawrence.
Ryo-tsu!
Let me apply wax for you.
Ohara-kun,
I'll do the glass polishing.
The boss is on his side.
Yo, Rei-kokumaria-kun!
Let's go to Rainbow Bridge together next time.
You've been more selfish than before.
The tears I shed...
Why didn't you put me in Tokyo Bay at that time?
I was told that.
Hey, Ohara-kun, Ryo-tsu-kun!
Yes!
What are you doing?
You two, come here quickly!
I'm here, Mr. Head Office.
The right side is still dirty.
The boss is more strong.
Oh, that feels good.
Such selfish people.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Oden, ramen, beer, nya-tsukan.
Here is the mass-produced store we're talking about.
Are you the father of Bakuryu again?
Please don't get in the way of business.
What is it?
What?
It's a bomb!
Next time, "Gekisou Speed Yatai!"
Please stand by!
Truth
The sudden
You make the answer
soon
You make the answer soon
I'm ready.
Beep, beep, it's decided.
Bang, bang, it's a flash.
Wham, bang, it's a bang.
Beep, beep, it's all together.
Bang, bang, it's an action.
Wham, bang, it's a fly.
Power is the greatest thing.
If everyone gathers here,
the final energy will be like a dream.
If you look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday,
draw the universe, and stand on the ground,
the planet Kameari will turn into a circle.
Isn't this good?
Of course it's good.
Thank you for watching.