Translated by Releska
I look up at the sunset floating in the river
I kick a pebble and fly to my shoes
I wonder if I'll go to the taiku I was saving
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is only a single punishment and one bad habit
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of Tongari-boshi
To the taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again
I realized
I'm an idiot
The Terrifying Box Man
Lockers
A box of metal that stores clothes and daily necessities anywhere, such as at work and school.
This is the tale of terror related to its lockers.
Zenin
Ah! Director!
Don't open his locker quietly!
This is awful!
I thought I could organize this later
Don't take any unnecessary actions, Can you wait?
Don't you dare!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I told you not to bring toys to the escape room!
It's only a little bit.
It's for a break.
You're saying you're playing games with your kids, aren't you?
What?
Really, Ryo-chan?
It's a rumor, chief.
I'm a police officer.
There's no way I would do that.
Ryo-san!
Give me Final Paradise!
Give it to me!
I'll look for it on my own, Ryo-san.
Where?
Here!
Ryo-san, give me this!
Okay, I'll pull it and give it to you.
See you, Ryo-san.
Give it to me again!
They're strange kids.
They must be mistaking this place for a game store.
Right, chief?
Bakkabon!
I'm going on patrol!
Cool your head off outside!
24 hours in a row!
He's a quick runner.
What are you doing, Ryo-kun?
You said you were going to exchange old lockers, didn't you?
Oh, I did.
I really want to get rid of all the lockers, but I won't let you do that.
It's so cold out here.
I can't control it.
Hey, Ryo-san.
What's going on?
I just came to the right place.
Why do I have to do all this?
Shut up!
Go away!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
What's that?
"I'm sorry."
Senpai!
It looks like no one's here!
I'm going back to my old life.
The documents are out of stock, too!
Senpai, what's going on?
My treasure!
Damn it!
He just threw it out!
He's not going to take it out, is he?
I really miss him.
The chief's back!
It's a disaster!
If he finds out that I'm skipping patrols, I'll get a big hit!
Alright.
I'm sure the master is going to let the chief know.
But where are you hiding?
Here.
Why me?
If you stay here alone, you'll be suspicious.
I'm sure he'll be arrested!
Let's have some tea.
Sorry.
Hey, Terai.
Oh, you're the chief.
I thought you came back.
Ryo-san? No, nobody was here.
Oh.
Hey, Terai. Let me introduce you.
Hm?
We've been friends for a long time.
I'm the drug lord now.
I happened to meet you there.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Are you the drug lord?
Sounds like a lot of work.
Well,
we're actually doing a huge drug deal nearby.
We're about to catch them.
Hey, hey.
Is it okay to talk about that here?
Stop talking about that.
Go somewhere already.
Senpai.
I told you not to speak.
I want to go pee.
What?
No.
What did you say?
I heard it from around the locker.
Yeah.
Now that you mention it.
Oh no.
He noticed me.
I'm going to pee.
Excuse me.
Oh.
I've been told that you're going to replace the old locker with a new one.
Oh, that's right.
You're going to replace the locker?
Yes.
I can get out of here.
Oh, no.
Where should I put it?
I think you should move this old locker and put it there.
Yes.
Ready?
That's kind of funny.
It's weird.
Reiko was cleaning it up for me earlier.
Anyway,
if there's only garbage like the one your dog collected,
throw it away.
Yes, sir.
OK.
Senpai, it's hot.
Damn it.
I put it in front of the stove.
Oh.
Ugh.
I don't like it.
Senpai.
You, too.
It's hot and it's burning.
Yes.
Gen-senpai, it's more painful to see two naked men together like this.
That's true.
Oh, pee.
What's wrong? Did you pee?
No, I'm fine. I'm just sweating.
That's okay.
What? It's starting to stain.
What's in there?
Oh, no!
Are you okay, Ohara?
It was just a little hot. I'll go cool it down with water.
Terai, move the stove away.
Yes, sir.
Senpai, are you okay?
It was a dangerous place. If we get caught here, it'll be the end of the first volume.
I'll bring you an old locker.
Please.
Ready, go!
Okay, okay, if we get out, we're done.
If we get out, we'll be out of here.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Ready, go!
Go!
Be more careful, you bastard!
Okay, bye!
See you later.
Okay, we're about to get out.
Hurry up. You can't stay like this forever.
Damn it! I can't use the door! I can't get out!
What? No way!
And what do you mean, you can't get out?
Wait, This is ridiculous!
Hey, you're congratulations on your graduation!
We're not graduating.
But Senpai...
But...
but...
Don't do that to everyone!
I don't have the time!
Don't be angry!
I tried everything I could to kick you out!
C'mon..
Hmph!
Seriously?
It stopped.
Wh-what's going on?
I feel like something's moving.
It looks like it's on the belt conveyor.
Oh, that thing.
It's the sound of the plushie!
The locker's turning and the door's opening!
The plushie's right there!
Help!
It's crushed!
Hey, Honda, you too!
We managed to escape.
Senpai!
We did it!
Huh? What is it?
Senpai, it's sinking!
I can see it!
Senpai, senpai, senpai, senpai!
Honda!
Senpai, it's sinking!
I'm going to the sea.
I peed.
I almost drowned.
What's that?
You're a big man.
Wait.
We're not suspicious.
Shut up, monster.
If you think you're a child, get up.
Stop it.
It's narrow.
Come on.
I'm sick.
Mr. Moriru.
What are you?
The monster is chasing the child.
It's a suspicious creature.
Catch it and send it to the police.
Yes.
You're a big man.
What's that?
What's going on, senpai?
I don't know.
A group of muscular rugby players is coming this way!
Senpai, why are you running away?
You fool!
How dare you let the public know that two police officers were chasing children in the locker room!
How dare you make excuses!
It fell!
Senpai, let's break the locker and get out of here!
You're right.
Senpai, why are you running away?
Oh no!
I hid behind the counter.
This is bad!
If I find you here, I'll be killed by the chief!
What's that?
Pretty Yuri, the popular female wrestler!
Senpai...
Quiet!
She's in a good place!
Senpai, what are you doing?
Be quiet!
Get out of my way, Traktor!
I don't want to see you naked!
Oh no!
I almost...
No!
Nozaki!
What's wrong?
Nozaki?
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
You're not getting away from our locker room.
Everyone, get out of here!
Yes!
Nozaki!
Ouch!
girl: Hey!
Nozaki!
Chiyo!
NOZAKI!
What the hell?
Chiyo!
It's that locker.
I hid the items in there.
Get out of the car.
Damn it.
It's hard to get out.
It's shaking.
Is it still rolling?
Ouch!
It's hard.
Why is the sky outside?
I'm going to die.
It's going to be hard.
What the hell...
I got to the garden, but I can't get out.
Don't worry about it.
If you don't want to die...
Well...
Did you bring the cash?
I did.
Here.
This is it.
Is the item in there?
Yes.
I hid it in that locker to distract the police.
Then, let me check the item.
No, you can't.
I'll count all your money.
Count it.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
What's going on?
We're at a drug deal.
Why are we in such a place?
I want to go home.
I'll contact the police somehow.
There it is.
I'll go to the police.
One hundred and forty-one.
One hundred and forty-two.
One hundred and forty-three.
One hundred and forty-four.
One hundred and forty-five.
One hundred and sixty-six.
One hundred and sixty-seven.
One hundred and forty-eight.
I don't have any 10 yen bills.
Don't worry.
This button is for this kind of situation.
I'll get out of the car and come back.
It's fine if you pull it like this.
I see.
2,999 pieces, 3,000 pieces.
Okay.
That's right.
Now, please check my item.
No, I don't have any.
Boss, look over there.
When did you...
What's going on?
He's my brother.
I don't think he's making a strange fuss after this.
What's this?
Alright, let's hurry.
1... 1... 0...
Oh no!
Commander!
It's Locker!
What?!
This is 110.
Darn it!
Ah!
It's cool!
I'll be fine as long as I stay inside of the torches!
You've played a very interesting trick.
You did the job, didn't you?
Yes, we didn't know about it.
I'll kill you with my own hands.
Ouch! Why did you use the gun?
Too bad. It was close.
You shot my car on purpose, didn't you?
No, no! I'll kill you this time.
Too bad.
My limousine!
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
No, no. I didn't hit the locker.
Well, please watch the next one.
Honda!
Hold on!
I can't do this.
It came out...
What!
How's that?
I caught him.
I jangan't hold it for a second.
Shall I give you a cool face before being killed?
Power Locker Burn!
Locker Kick!
Don't mess with me.
Honda, are you fainted?
Don't move!
It's the police!
Amigata!
Thanks to the first caller who called me from this port.
But, who is it?
It's dangerous. I almost got caught by the chief.
Let's get out of this locker.
What?
What are you going to do this time?
Hey, we don't care!
Where are you taking me?
Where did Ryo-chan go?
It's been a week since then.
He must be playing somewhere.
It's not a new thing.
I see.
It's amazing!
When can we go back?
I'm sure we can see the town where many people live.
It's so hot.
I want to go home soon.
Don't cry. It's almost time.
Even if you find an empty locker, you can't get inside.
If you do, you may meet me.
I want that! I want that!
You tricked the chief.
You are a pimp.
You tricked the chief!
Oh, no.
If you don't try to hide your face,
you will be caught by the chief.
You're a coward!
You're following his direction!
It's too dark.
I heard a voice from the outside.
I know a girl that can see us well.
I have a hug for you!
Oh my God.
I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited
I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited, I'm excited,
Thank you for watching.