When you watch TV
Make the room brighter
And try to get away
Like someone calling
The rain after the rain
I walked looking back
I was drawn to the gacha
I felt
A strange feeling
So
I tried to walk
The black tile of the arcade
Go to the left
I saw the darkness
The black tile of the arcade
I saw the black tile of the arcade
And I took a deep breath
What should I do
♪ Ah, it must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
Ah! The Hellish Life of the Beast
Yagi, I won a lot of games today!
I'll clean up the room!
That's it! I have one more step to go!
Uryaaaaa!
What?
What's this? Ryo is gone!
Oh, Ryo, you're here!
I'm not here. What's going on, old lady?
You have to rebuild it!
Huh? Rebuild it?
Another male Ryo in the Katsushika office was caught in the department's management,
so he was going to meet up with my Ryo.
Huh? So you're going to rebuild it?
Yes, to increase the number of people.
But there's no need to do it so suddenly.
No way, Ryo!
You've been writing it down on the bulletin board for three months!
Huh? Is there a bulletin board in my Ryo's room?
There is!
But where should I live?
It looks like everyone is renting an apartment or moving to a friend's house.
I'm going to my daughter's place too.
See you in two months, Ryo!
Hey, how are you?
I'm fine.
I have to find a place to sleep.
Huh? You're staying at my house?
Yes, I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm sorry, but the Arabian ambassador will be staying at my house for a while from tomorrow.
What? Are you saying I'm the only one left in Japan?
That's not what I mean.
Then what?
Huh? Ryo, you're home, aren't you?
Oh, Terai! You're back at the right place! Actually, I...
Wait.
You have about three and a half hours of work to do, right?
Yeah, but what's that?
Nothing.
Reiko!
No!
I haven't told you anything yet!
No, no, no!
What are you thinking about going to a single woman's room?
If you can live with Ryo for two months, it's even better to live with a cockroach.
Stop talking about that!
Who would want to live with you?
Pekka!
What happened, Ryo?
Ryo's apartment has been taken over.
That's terrible.
That's why I'm telling you, there's no trouble in your house. Don't worry.
Thank you.
Bunchou!
Oh, I'm so busy, I'm so busy.
Reiko, this is all right, so please give me your documents.
Yes!
Bunchou! Bunchou! Bunchou!
Bunchou! Bunchou!
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, this is it.
Bunchou!
Bunchou, listen to me!
You idiot!
Don't get too close to your bad face!
Then listen to me.
No, no, no.
It's really wonderful to live in your house for two months.
I see.
Then you have a book in your closet.
If you bring a blanket in there, you'll live a great life.
I can't believe you would say that even though your wife is suffering.
You always say such jokes.
I'm not kidding.
If you have more vitality than cockroaches, you'll be fine.
I'm not fine!
How about the back yard?
I don't have to worry about getting late and getting close.
Well, the back yard is where the riot gangs gather at night.
I wonder if I'll go into the riot gangs and rampage.
You're a useless man, but how can you buy a bike?
Are you a riot gang or a parking lot?
Anyway, I don't know.
Oh, I see.
I got it.
I'll really get it when it's like this.
And when I'm arrested, I'll say like this.
I'm not that bad.
It's the fault of Ohara who set up the park.
If you had stopped me at that time, I wouldn't have moved.
I'll let everyone yell at me that I'm the chief of Ohara.
Ryo-chan is quite a person.
Yes.
If that happens, the chief's neck won't fly.
I got it, Ryo-chan.
Come stay at my house.
Thank you very much.
After all, I can understand if you ask for mental justice.
Where is mental justice?
Instead, treat your family the same.
You're different from a lowly man.
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
I walk from JR to the station and then to the bus stop.
I often go there every day.
Don't say that.
Follow me.
You're going to work as a clerk on the same route for two months.
Yes, yes.
I'm back.
Welcome, Ryo-chan.
It's been a while, madam.
Come on in.
I'm not here as a customer.
I'm going to stay at your house for two months.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Please relax.
What are you talking about?
It's a nuisance to relax when I'm free.
Father.
Be patient, Ryo-chan.
It's been two months.
I'll have lunch before the bath today.
I see.
What's your favorite food, Ryo-chan?
Anything.
Hey.
Yes.
You can come to me every day.
Think of it as air.
You're talking about what you like.
Remember that.
It's time for the news.
The bill is being paid.
The bath after a delicious dinner was also pleasant.
Ryo-chan.
Would you like some tea?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You don't have to put it in.
Ryo-chan.
Put some tea in it yourself.
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
I don't get it at all.
Director, is this show interesting?
It's not such a question.
As a policeman, it's better to know this much.
My suggestion is the story of their house in Akashiyama, Fuji.
Do you always watch that kind of show?
No, it's not.
I want to watch NHK, but I can't find it for some reason.
It's a good opportunity.
It's late. You should watch NHK here.
Oh, I suddenly have a cold.
Yoichi-san, are you OK?
I'm fine.
You must be tired from today.
You should rest.
Really? That's too bad.
I wanted to watch NHK.
Go to sleep.
I'll leave you to it. Good night.
The TV news is totally against the director.
I have to get up early.
I have to drink.
I can't sleep.
Pocket Pin, you're my only friend.
It's hard to have a superior.
Yoichi.
Yes?
I'll wake you up early tomorrow.
Yes.
Go to bed.
I'm being watched all day.
I'm more of a coward.
Yoichi, wake up.
It's already morning?
How long are you going to sleep?
When you wake up, fold the futon and come to the garden.
It's still dark. What time is it?
It's still four o'clock.
Old people wake up earlier than you.
Did you say something?
I'm going to bed.
Don't go any further.
68.
69.
70.
Why?
What are you doing?
My lower body is not in.
I see.
Let's take a break.
He's not a coward.
It's ridiculous to sleep right after you wake up.
I haven't even seen the sun yet.
I'm on a six o'clock bus, so I can't wake up in time.
If it's six o'clock, you can wake up at five o'clock.
What?
I'm a cop.
I have to train my body.
I do this 100 times a day.
You should do it 200 times a day.
I understand.
I'll do it 300 times.
You said it right.
73.
71.
75.
76.
127.
128.
129.
130.
172.
173.
174.
203.
204.
205.
206, 207, 209, 210, 211, 250, 251, 222, 295, 296, 297, 298, 299, 300!
Boss, it's over.
Alright, that's enough.
Now, it's time for dinner.
The food after exercise is delicious.
Ouch!
Is there anything else?
Look at that.
I'm starting to feel a lot of bad luck.
I'm going to do some gardening.
Is that so?
Well, good luck then.
I'm going to go sweat first.
In this case, there should be people who can help you.
For example, a man who's eating just rice.
Alright.
I'll do it if I have to.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't know you'd do it on your own.
No, no, no.
I think I made it too much.
Damn it.
Ryo-chan, are you alright?
I just went to the manager's house and it's only been a week.
I feel like I'm under a lot of pressure.
You know how hard it is to work long distance, right, Ryo-san?
Shut up.
It's not just work.
I get beaten up every morning at 4 o'clock.
I'm being used as a scapegoat.
Even on Sundays.
Dad, let's call a taxi.
What?
I can't do anything about it.
Right, Ryo-tsu?
Ehehe.
I'm sorry.
I thought you'd done it.
Besides, you're even my best friend.
Let's go to bed.
That's no good.
I told you tonight's the last game.
Ryo-tsu.
That's my big hand.
But I'm going to do whatever I want.
Just leave me alone.
Besides, I can't play baseball or play the pachinko.
Just let me stand.
You're going to get stressed out.
I wonder if you'll last another two months.
I don't think so.
Just watch.
I'm going to get out of this life.
And now, the weather for tomorrow.
Ryo-chan, have you gone to bed?
I think so.
He said he'd be up early.
I see.
Then I'll go to bed, too.
I won't have to train him again tomorrow.
Good night.
Well, he's gotten even busier since he came.
He's gotten much better.
Your father seems to have been enjoying his day since he came.
-Madam! -Yes?
I have a TV show I want to watch. Is that okay?
Sure, go ahead.
I can finally watch a show I like.
How about it, Ryo-chan?
Do you want to watch a lot?
Is that okay?
Here you go.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's delicious.
Ugh.
Your father will be fine.
He's been sleeping well lately, so he's been sleeping well.
Is that so?
But he suddenly came out of the window.
You're afraid of your father, aren't you?
I'm not afraid of him.
He's like a frog that's been lured by a snake.
Oh, really?
Here, have another drink.
Thank you.
I didn't think I'd be able to drink with you.
Your father is a good man.
It's not fair to drink so much.
In fact, Ryo-chan is happy that you came.
What? The chief?
I have a daughter.
I heard he wanted a boy.
I'm sure Ryo-chan came to my house, so he'll be like a son.
Hey, I don't think that scary chief...
Ugh.
I'm sorry.
It's a sleeping thing.
You always get angry at Ryo-chan.
Even when he's asleep, he only thinks about work.
Oh, I'm surprised.
I don't want to scare anyone even when I'm asleep.
If he's a father, I don't feel like I'm alive.
Really?
How about a drink?
What?
Sometimes it's good.
I know.
I wonder if I should have a drink.
You should have.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Huh?
It's a good drink.
Let's have another drink.
Let's make the chief's bad words known to the fish tonight.
Sure.
Let's drink.
Well?
Huh?
You didn't even kiss me before the wedding?
Not only did I kiss you, but you didn't even hold my hand, father.
You've always been stubborn, chief.
That's the only reason.
But you can stay with that stone head for almost 30 years.
You must be out of breath.
I'm used to it now.
But it's better to be a little softer.
It's better to be a little softer.
That stone head will never heal.
But it's true.
It may never heal.
It's morning, Ryozu.
When are you going to sleep?
Wake up.
I smell like alcohol.
Hey, Ryozu.
Wake up.
I can't drink anymore.
Wake up!
I'm cold!
You woke up?
What are you doing, chief?
You're killing me!
Shut up!
What's the point of drinking secretly in the middle of the
But yesterday, my wife said she wanted to drink no matter what, so I
went out with her.
What?
Your wife?
That's right.
She was crying while drinking.
Why the hell did your wife refuse to drink?
She's too stubborn.
She didn't even hold her hand when she got engaged.
That's right.
It's true that she was young, but it was common in the past.
That's not all.
She's just an order.
She said it would be better to be a little softer.
She was crying while she was saying that.
Is that true?
Dad.
Dad, I'm going shopping today, so I'll head out first.
I've already prepared dinner, so I'll be in your care.
City Hall...
You're going to get your divorce letter, aren't you?
What?!
It's been a while since you've been getting divorced, right?
As long as it's mine...
The wife who got divorced receives her retirement money as a car loan,
and she throws her husband out of the house.
She says that's what a "permanent divorce" is.
Permanent divorce?
Permanent divorce?!
Ryotsu, what should I do to prevent you from getting divorced?
First of all, you have to soften that stone head.
I will! I will!
What should I do to soften it? Tell me!
First of all, this.
What's wrong with the city?
Stop pretending not to do it every morning and picking up the bonsai.
What?! That's not good!
Ouch!
Ryotsu!
If you want me to teach you how to soften your head, you have to be a manager!
I don't care whether you get divorced or not.
R-Ryotsu! I got it.
I'll do anything, so help me.
I got it.
Then there's no "this" every morning, right?
Of course.
This!
This is a complete reversal of the situation.
Okay, let's go with this.
Pants are okay with this.
Okay.
Okay, bring me a sneaker and a hat.
Yes.
Why do I have to dress like that?
To be a soft-headed human, you need to change your appearance first.
But...
Your wife wants you to dress younger.
But this is...
A proper divorce.
I-I wonder if I should come!
Oh...
Ryotsu, everyone is watching.
That's because the manager is dressed like this, so they're watching you.
I don't think so.
Ryotsu, as expected...
Proper divorce!
Proper divorce...
I won.
Well then, chief. Let's gamble a little bit.
Do you understand?
If anyone turns that corner, it's either a man or a woman, so let's bet on the wine.
Let me go first.
First, the woman.
I am a man.
Okay, I'll have one at first.
Okay, then the next is the woman.
Then I am a man.
Yeah.
Yay, a man.
I got the second one.
Okay, next is the woman.
You're on board, chief. You're quite a gambler, aren't you?
Shut up! Anyway, I'm a woman!
Yes, yes.
I did it! I'm a woman! I'm a woman!
Ryozu, I win!
It seems that I win again this time.
What's wrong with you, father?
I said I didn't want to.
But somehow you look young and good.
See?
Really? I haven't thrown away my old clothes yet.
You're so mean.
I'll be proud of you if you make me a pig.
Mom, tea.
Here you are.
Father, are you not going to eat dinner tonight?
No reason.
Ryozu, news.
Change it to NHK.
It's FUJITELEVI on Sunday.
I'll let Chirimaru-chan do it.
I'll be watching the GTO anime,
"The Dog's Adventure",
"The RR Daiji-ten",
"Super Night",
and "Music Fair"
and watch the "Chuou Keiba Digest".
That's the right way to spend Sunday night, right?
You!
First, you have to watch the anime and make your head soft, right, mother?
That's right.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, it's NHK news at 7 o'clock.
It's so boring not to watch NHK news.
Chief, you're so young.
Yes, that's right.
Sometimes, I like watching anime.
Right?
What?
I can't stand it.
I'm going to bed tonight.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Sometimes, I don't eat dinner,
and I don't take a bath,
and I have to go to bed early.
What do you think, wife?
Chief, you have to sing "Dragon's Feet"
in karaoke now.
Your wife will hate it.
And you have to do skateboarding
and show your young side.
And if you can do it on the Internet,
you might be seen again.
Oh, that's right.
My wife sometimes goes to amusement parks
and says she wants to do bungee jumping with me.
Chief, what's wrong with you?
You're so grumpy.
Yes, and in return,
Ryo is feeling a little nervous.
Yes.
What?
What's wrong?
Oh, no.
Mr. Daijiro Ohara
called me saying he wanted a car.
So I brought a pamphlet and a letter of recommendation.
Hey, Mr. Goburo.
What?
Ryo, what's wrong?
I thought it was convenient,
so I called you.
Don't do anything to yourself.
My wife said
she would divorce me if she didn't buy me a car.
Don't lie to me.
My wife will buy a car,
so I won't get in the car.
Oh, really?
What are you talking about?
You're so...
Forget it.
I don't want anyone like you in my house.
Get out of here as soon as possible.
Oh, really?
I don't have any more money in the headmaster's house.
What?
Well, the car...
Why are you following me?
Go home.
I'll go home after I take my luggage.
Oh, that junk is your luggage?
It's a junk.
I don't have such a good house or luggage anyway.
Don't turn on the light at the entrance.
What's wrong with it?
Where have you been at this hour?
Isn't it just that the divorce was early?
What?
That's not the case with my wife.
When she gets late,
she always prepares dinner...
I didn't.
If you really go out...
No way...
I understand how you feel.
Let's have a good time tonight.
Ryo-tsu!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Ryo-tsu, you're a good guy.
Headmaster.
Come on, cheer up.
I'm home.
Mom?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I went out by bicycle today.
I bumped into you on the way.
Mom!
Dad!
I'm glad you came back.
Dad, what's wrong?
I think you got divorced and left.
I don't want to, Dad.
I'll be with you until I die.
Mom?
But you said you don't like people with a hard head.
You cried and went to Ryo-tsu, didn't you?
I did.
I said I'd like to be a little softer,
but I don't cry.
What?
I'm happy just to be with you now.
Mom, thank you.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry that I have to go to Ryo-tsu.
Huh?
Oh.
Ryo-tsu!
What?
You're lying!
I won't forgive you!
You said you were a good guy!
I'll get you back to your old self!
Stay here forever!
No!
I don't want to!
Wake me up!
Watch me!
Kick me!
My little finger hurts!
For now,
When I brush my eyebrows, I'll go to the station
DASH! DASH! DASH!
On the main train, I'm sleeping on my father's back
This week as well, the Go-Kurou Go-Muri is a Go-Moto
I'm holding the bucket in one hand
but it's so hot and cloudy
I'm irritated by the continued work
So I get irritated by it, and that really may trouble me
Everyday is no problem
When I pass through the hot shower
Recovered from sickness and well-being
Everyday is no problem
I really love myself!
I like you, every day is no problem
My heart is flying on Monday
Fun N' Nonsense
The chief of the mecha-house bought a mobile phone
but I thought he didn't use it at all
Chief, what are you going to do if you get turned over for not using the tools?
What? The phone is gone?
It's not my fault!
Next time, "Phone Panic"
See you then!