"The End"
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
I walked back and forth
"Mom, please lend me your hand"
At that time I felt
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk
Only in black
Everyone was a child once
But
Everyone forgets
Politicians with a big face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around
That corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Come on, Come on, Come on
Everyone come to our town
to our town
Thank you very much
Luke
I can't find it.
I was robbed here.
Isn't this a serial robbery?
But the police will be robbed?
Right?
So it's an internal crime?
What?
The culprit may have left a clue.
What do you think?
Hey, what is this?
What is this?
A huge robbery! Ryochi vs. Crows
Huh? This is strange.
Hey, Reiko.
You didn't clean up the desk without my permission, did you?
I didn't.
What happened?
There's not enough parts here.
What?
We promised to deliver the finished product to the company in time.
Why don't you buy the same plastic model
and use that part?
This is my original plastic model.
I only have one piece of each.
If I lose it, the Crows will be a bubble of water.
Isn't that part this?
This is it.
I'm done.
I knew it.
Everyone's here. What's wrong?
Ryochi Kankichi is a thug!
If you're a thug, why hit him?
W-What?
HUGGYYyyy!
Don't fool around.
You know how I've always told you not to mess with my dunno.
You know what I'm gonna do, don't you?
I told you so!
It's your problem instead.
You can't make money just by stealing our things.
Yes, I can.
That's not only a charity thing.
I guess it's for Mother's sake.
Then, why is there only one Plum item in this world that has fallen into the
unauthorized locker room?
I don't know.
I just want to hear it.
Be quiet!
Anyway, it's not me!
How about proving your alibi?
Senpai.
That's right.
Well, I went to Shimatsu-shoda City, Katsushika-shou in the morning and ...
My ring was stolen in the morning.
After all.
I don't remember going to a
unauthorized locker room.
That's right.
Even if it's Ryo-chan, that's the case.
What's wrong?
There's no earring that should have been left here.
Don't look at me!
I don't know!
Huh?
The wristwatch I left here is gone.
So don't look at me!
The corner cigarette shop is gone.
How do you steal that?
I don't know.
Hit me.
Hey!
I'm playing games with you!
You're kidding me, aren't you!
You arrested 5 people, and it's really尖 tied up, you two!
It's all white mods.
I'm going to tighten my sanitary gloves!
It's better if you indicate that you recognize your rights before you feel it!
Shut it!
Is this so?
When this is over, I'll find the real culprit and prove that I have no alibi!
This is for everyone!
Well, I'm going to to the toilet and take a shit.
g g g g.
I'm going to to the toilet and take a shit.
Wow! It's a genius!
It's a genius!
So this is the only way to get in from the outside.
Now even a kid's head won't fit in here.
It's impossible to get in through the outside.
Komachi, what's with him?
He's just being chased around and making fun of us.
There's nothing in the room that looks like the culprit's belongings.
So it's a crime against the inside.
Now it's time for you to investigate the whole family!
What?
Why are we being investigated?
We're the ones who are investigating!
Shut up!
You've been calling us the To-Dai Motokurashi for a long time.
But before you start questioning me,
first prove your innocence!
What?
I'll tell you what,
if you're not cooperative enough with the investigation,
you won't be able to see through this.
Fine.
At this rate, I'll make sure it's all clear.
First, we'll thoroughly investigate
the people who came into the locker room from yesterday to today.
We went to the bathroom at 9:25,
and went back to the locker room at 9:45.
Right.
It's too long.
What were you doing in the bathroom for 20 minutes?
That has nothing to do with it!
You went to the locker room alone at 9:28,
why?
That's because...
You were in a locker room with no one in it,
and you were doing things that no one could say.
Because the stockings were electric,
I went back to the store.
You're a crazy guy.
The stockings were electric.
That's terrible!
Scumbag!
You're a pervert!
All the alibis have been proven,
but what about the culprit?
What?
Oh, you found the culprit, Detective Me.
It's our turn next.
You also called the guard?
I have a paper for you.
I'm not the culprit!
Ryo-san!
Chief!
Actually, it's not just the book,
but the public housing department, too.
I know that there are a lot of
metal theft victims in the neighborhood.
So I'm going to investigate it in earnest.
Even the chief
doesn't suspect me, does he?
I don't want to doubt it either.
I don't want to doubt it, but...
You're suspicious enough!
You're lying, aren't you?
If you're a lie detector, you'll know everything.
You have to answer all the questions with a "no."
Do you understand?
Why am I so annoying?
I'm asking if you understand.
I understand.
Then,
I've sneaked into your locker room.
No way.
I don't object.
What?
That's terrible!
I'm the one who stole the metal.
you're the one who stole the metal.
No,
I don't object.
You're lying!
What?
Now you understand, right?
The machine is broken, isn't it?
I used the coffee machine.
What?
No,
I objected.
See?
It's not broken.
That's right.
That's strange.
Stop it!
You're so annoying.
Who is the culprit?
Hmm...
The escape case is all in the time of the empty time when Fukie left the locker room.
Hmm?
Ah!
Damn!
Damn it!
Shit!
Damn it.
He tried to do a lot of hard work.
You do all of them.
Damn it!
Move.
This is the last straw Hat!
It has только none left, but I have another, you fool!
That's all.
What a waste of time!
It has only made ashire!
That's all!
Now it's yours, you fool.
You crow!
My ring!
My necklace!
My key-holder!
My...
What is this?
You still don't get it?
So the owner of this nest is the culprit of the serial robbery case.
The culprit was a crow!
A crow!
A crow?
It's been widely reported in the news.
Crows have the habit of collecting rare things such as light.
So I stole a pair of plums from my desk.
If you think I've been to your locker room, I'll explain everything.
So you're saying all of them stole them?
That's right.
You're doubting me so much!
You're doubting me because you're always the same!
That's right. It's my fault!
You're calling me a criminal.
You're going to be punished for what you did to me!
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
The culprit of the serial robbery case is a crow!
What? A crow?
Look! Look!
Look!
There's even this one!
It looks like it's in line with the defense range of someone.
What? What's with that look?
You're blaming the crow for what you did, aren't you?
You're making a big deal out of it!
Is that so, Ryotsu?
I'm not that kind of person. I'm aiming for the cash first!
That's true.
No one was robbed, right?
So the culprit was the crow!
I'm convinced.
You're doubting me so much, Chief!
You even used a lie detector.
I'm sorry. I was a police officer. I'm sorry.
But it was a quick solution.
What's a quick solution?
Ohara, you're in trouble!
The doll you got from the chief is broken.
It's a big deal.
I forgot. My radio was stuck in the window.
I broke it.
If it's your job, you should be ashamed.
If I were to be honest, I wouldn't forgive you.
I'm not going to do anything to you.
If you're going to keep quiet like this,
you need to investigate it thoroughly,
find the culprit,
and get rid of him.
I ran away in a hurry.
There might still be parts of the radio-controlled helicopter on the scene.
I should confess to the police now.
Chief, that doll...
Chief, this could be the crow's doing.
Crow?
Yes.
Actually, there have been many domestic injuries caused by crows in the area recently.
That's right! The culprit is a crow!
I saw it with my own eyes.
Crows that kick and run away with a strong doll!
Is that true?
Yes.
It seems to be exactly what I was looking at, chief.
As expected of the chief, you're a master!
It can't be helped that it's the crow's doing.
Crow, you're a suspicious return.
W-Who's the provider of the misdemeanor of the spirit medium here?
Crow, I hope?
Hey, Ryo. You're late.
It's a crow! A crow!
It's a crow?
When I was leaving the town,
the crow attacked me and it ran around.
That's why it came back late.
Do you still suspect me?
It's not like that.
It seems that crows can remember people's faces.
So, you should be careful.
This is convenient.
My bed!
A while ago, a crow sent him to the east sky.
But, it's using chopsticks.
Crows have a good head like a stone man.
This is strange.
The number of phone calls this month is so high.
It's a crow.
What's wrong with this?
A dango is here.
It's a crow.
Who is it?
Our window is full of crows.
It's a crow.
Ryo said that it's all because of crows.
What do you think?
I told my senior to take off his clothes.
So, I can't say anything strong.
But...
That crow is always staying there.
I think he has something to say to Ryo.
This is bad.
Everyone's starting to suspect me.
I have to investigate this.
The meeting room is under fire!
What's this?
How horrible!
Check this footprint.
And this black wing.
It's a crow's wing.
We can't just check it.
It's all a crow's doing.
But can we make the crows move to such a heavy cage?
Certainly.
Have you ever seen crows up close?
They are so big!
But this footprint is very unnatural.
It's like a stamp.
That's the plan of the crows!
You don't know that they are doing it on purpose?
Ah! There is a surveillance camera in that place!
Was there such a thing?
Let's play it again.
Oh! A crows is on the screen.
Then the culprit is a crows.
This is the proof that it doesn't move.
There is no doubt about it.
But this crows...
It moves strangely.
Yes. It's as stiff as a white bird.
That's the plan of the crows.
They are doing it on purpose.
They are the brainwaves who are hiding us.
You can't fool us!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Damn it!
Ah!
"A spreakeple leadership"
"Hai! This is nothing but an價."
"Hai! This is nothing but an價!!"
Huh?
There's my underwear!
They're twins!
It's a trap.
I'll listen to the order, so don't push it.
All of them?
Yes.
All the underwear I had been keeping was stolen.
I also bought something, but it was the worst.
My bra was also stolen.
It's a very familiar underwear thief's crime of not seeing the culprit alone.
I don't think it's a German criminal.
There are too many victims.
It's impossible to do it alone.
It's difficult to operate if there's no clue.
Um, this was dropped at the store.
Are you a monster?
The culprit likes to fight.
I picked it up on the balcony, too.
This is a pachinko ball, right?
I also picked it up at the store.
Isn't this a pier?
Senpai, don't you have something similar?
Oh, it's a limited edition of premium.
Of course I have it.
The culprit likes pachinko figures.
There's another person like that here.
Hey, you're doubting me again?
There are a lot of other people like that.
I told you earlier that the culprit wasn't alone.
I'm sorry.
What is this mess?
It's a underwear thief.
Underwear thief?
All of these people were stolen?
Yes.
It seems that they were damaged in this area.
What?
Chief.
They call me underwear thief again.
Did you do it?
What's wrong with the chief?
I'm not doing it.
If you doubt me,
please check the locker until you feel like it.
Okay?
Come on.
What?
Well, where is it?
What's wrong?
Why is my locker broken?
It's broken.
It's a uniform.
No, it's not me.
It's me.
It's someone's conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy.
It's him.
Listen, everyone.
It's a crow.
This is a crow! This is all a crow's plot!
Ryo, you're still saying such things?
Because crows are...
Whatever you do, you're always pushing crows, crows, crows, crows...
I can't believe you're such a scum!
Because crows are...
You're not allowed to come back until the punishment is decided!
I'll make you pay!
Damn it! That damn crow!
I can't stand it anymore!
In this case, I'll have to face that damn crow!
Honda! Balboa! Shuga!
That's the guy...
Tohoku!
I finally got rid of the crow!
Is that the frowning you made on Senpai?
Yeah, I can't forget that face of his.
He's sleeping soundly.
I'll wake him up!
Fire!
I-I-I-I can't move, Senpai!
That's the only way, don't move!
I-I-I-I-I-I can't look, Ryo!
What the hell did I just see?
We got to go now!
Hm.
But what should I do?
Take this, Ryo!
And this!
The lights are broken!
What's this road?
I'll kill you!
Ouch!
Senpai!
You're dead!
I'm scared!
Please change the car.
What?
I'm talking about the handle!
What are you going to do, Porpo?
I'll take you all down!
You should be more careful!
Damn it!
Take this!
What?
Ouch!
They're even more fat!
And the number of cars is increasing!
We have to run!
Let's go, Honda!
I don't want to!
I'm glad the crows didn't mess up the garbage.
Yeah.
It's not just Tokyo.
Crows are everywhere.
They're all over the place.
Where are they?
Did they move out of the forest?
I don't think they're here.
Where are they?
I don't know.
They're not here.
Ouch!
Stretch!
Such terrifying violence!
Ouch!
♪ When I brush my eyebrows, I'll dash to the station ♪
♪ On the main train, I'll sleep on my dad's back ♪
♪ This week too, I'll do my best, even if it's not enough ♪
♪ I'm putting my bucket in one hand ♪
♪ But the beef bowl is so warm ♪
♪ I hate the annoying work-to-work routine ♪
♪ But I'll get through it easily ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ When I pass by the hot shower ♪
♪ I get well in the sleeping pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ On Monday ♪
♪ No problem, no problem ♪
Listen, Reiko Nakagawa!
I'm your master from today on!
Don't go against your master's words!
If I say I'm black, then most and banana are black!
I will make sure to make you a splendid mansaishi!
Next time!
Keiichi Reiko's "Neoto Banzai"!
See you!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!