"Gacha"
It's like someone's calling me
After the rain
I walked while looking back
"Gacha, hold my hand!"
At that time, I felt
A strange feeling
So I walked on the Ake-do-gai's
Black tile
I saw
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look
"Ake-do-gai"
How about that?
You'll see everyone
Over there is Kame-Ari
Ah, Kitto Kame-Ari
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What? A date?
Shin, don't make a loud noise.
This is a change of mood again.
So, who is your partner?
That's it. He is super handsome.
I see. Komachi is a handsome guy.
So, how do you feel when you compare him to a talent?
That's right.
Kim Takuta added Sorimachi and Kaneshiro.
And he divided them by three.
And he added Takky.
In short...
Both are Kanjichi.
I'm sorry.
Don't underestimate me.
Joke. Just a joke.
There is a limit to jokes.
Sorry.
Anyway, take advantage of this chance.
Whatever it is...
Whatever it is, you are absolutely against it.
What?
You can't say no.
Why are you against it?
What do you mean, Komachi?
No matter how much you are the chief, you don't want to interfere with my meeting.
We were talking about Ryosu's trip to America.
What?
I'm sorry.
Komachi, let's go.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute.
Ryosu and Kanjichi said they were going to America for training.
Yes.
They were invited to a two-week training from New York City.
What?
Why are they invited by a wild gorilla?
Bakuryu, a good friend of Ryosu, is a best friend of the chief of New York City.
The chief asked him about Ryosu.
He said he wanted to invite Ryosu.
So I was against it.
He is the Japanese police's shame.
You don't have to go to America and expose his shame.
I think we should let him go.
What?
If Ryosu and Kanjichi are gone for two weeks,
even then, the Katsushika prefecture, no,
the whole country will be peaceful and quiet.
I see.
But, Ohara, this is a decision.
I'm begging you.
Please educate Ryosu.
Please let him go to America without any shame.
Yes.
I'll try to do what I can.
Mr. Ryosu is going to America.
Hey, Ryosu!
Ouch!
Don't sleep!
Please let me sleep.
I want to expose the shame of the Japanese police to America.
Ouch!
Nakagawa, water.
Yes.
This is terrible.
We stayed up all night studying about America for three days.
What?
Then, show us where the American capital is.
Well, I think it's around here.
That's Los Angeles.
I thought so.
Well, the capital is New York.
It's Washington.
When did you change?
Idiot!
I studied for three nights and nights.
You are such a...
Chief, calm down!
If you get too excited, your blood pressure will rise again.
Oh, I see.
Well, it's just exaggeration to go to America.
Shut up!
You're a loser and rude to money.
You can't even speak English at all.
Do you know what will happen if you go to America?
What?
What will happen?
You'll be carried by the dynamite.
You'll be thrown into a fire.
That's a good thing.
Why are you laughing?
If you do something bad, you can't even fight America.
Right?
Chief?
My stomach hurts.
Reiko, give me some medicine and water.
Yes.
Dr. Sato takes care their stomachs.
I'm going to have to be careful.
Good.
I want to take this with me to America.
What?
He'll be replaced very soon.
I've already told Mr. Sato.
I could not tell him he would regret it.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Water tower? Why do we have to put such a thing?
The plane ticket for the return and the hotel stay are free,
but the other expenses are all the cost of the Katsushika office.
What? It's quite troublesome.
I wonder if I'll go to Hawaii with just money.
What did you say?
I'm kidding. I'll go there properly.
The next day
I've finished all the procedures for the return.
Here's the ticket and passport.
Oh, sorry.
And this is the trunk.
Hey, hey, are you bringing such a big thing?
Because it's for two weeks.
This is the one that I made small.
Show me. There are so many unnecessary things in it.
Oh, I don't need to change clothes.
I don't need a camera. I don't need medicine.
I don't need this either. What's this? I don't need this either.
I don't need this either.
This is enough.
And this, and this, and this.
Why do you bring English words and ballpoint pens?
American kids are more addicted to computers and TV games than Japanese kids.
I thought I'd teach them a nostalgic Japanese game.
It's like Ryo-chan.
That's fine.
But why do you bring souvenirs to the president of the New York City Court?
And a note of the English conversation that Reiko made for us.
I'll give your letter to him.
I don't like it. I'm bad at using things.
Hey, hold it.
Hold it like this.
It's done.
You've forgotten about the changing paper from Director Nonda, right?
Yes.
That's right. It's all right.
So, you want me to hold it?
Yes, I do.
I know.
referee Ryo Stsukan in New York City is now going to New York City.
We are departing to the capital!
Finally, we have survived.
Don't worry. Senpai has a strong vitality.
Even when we went to Africa and the 8-minute island, we came back safely.
Come back safely, Yotsu.
I can't eat anymore.
Finally we arrived.
I said I would come to the airport, but no one came.
What is this music?
Who would do such a thing?
Idiot! Stop!
Yotsu, it's been a while.
As I thought, Captain Bugryu!
What are you planning?
What are you angry about?
You welcomed us.
What?
You welcomed me?
Welcome to New York.
You can't do that in a short time.
I knew you would die.
Hi, Ryo.
Hey, Johnny. You are here too.
Long time no see.
I knew you would welcome me.
New York is divided into five countries.
Manhattan
Brooklyn
Queens
Bronx
Staten Island
Where is the 57th station I'm going to?
Manhattan Island with the Matenro.
I'll introduce you.
What?
The 57th station in New York City, where you will be taken care of while you are staying.
It's Max.
Oh, I see.
My name is Ryo.
This is the great famous policeman, Japan's President.
Japan's President.
Your English seems a bit faster than mine.
It's true.
I'll tell you the truth.
What?
I hate Japanese.
Don't talk to me in a way you like if you don't have to.
Oh, what?
No way!
Why not?
Max lost his grandfather during the Pacific War.
Don't give me this nonsense.
What do you mean you didn't lose each other?
We have been completely burned out by the city below our living condition.
You don't have a choice.
R-Right.
Let's go.
Yotsu, do you have a place you want to go before you go to the 57th station?
Eh? Is that okay?
Then, if I have to go to New York, it's the Statue of Liberty!
Alright!
Whoa! As expected, it's really awesome!
I want to go to New York!
Whoa! I came here!
I wanted to try this when I came to New York!
I didn't know! It feels great!
It's a good place to climb, too.
The rural yellow monkey!
We'll be there in a little while!
Whoa! Beautiful! As expected, New York is different!
The scale is different from the high-rise buildings in Shinjuku!
Ryo, it's dangerous to start riding too much!
Dad!
Ryo!
I missed!
Don't worry. We're on Hudson River.
The 57th station is right up ahead.
We'll be waiting for you there!
Hey! Help!
Colonel, is it okay if I don't help?
His vitality is more than five times that of a monkey.
Don't worry.
Max, your Ryo-sensei...
If you follow him, you'll know his good qualities.
Hey, Sire!
Colonel Dark Dragon!
You remember me!
Oh, great!
Your souvenir.
The president is very pleased.
Of course. It's a replica, though.
Thank you very much, Mr. Ryo-tsu.
I'm sure he'll like it.
Today, you can take a rest at the hotel.
Let's start training tomorrow.
Of course.
Colonel, Jody, thank you for today.
You're welcome.
I'm home during the break.
If you need anything, feel free to call.
Oh, thank you!
Avenge your army!
Oh, thanks to you, New York.
So big.
Oh, hey, stop.
What is it?
I found a shop at G.I. Joe's.
Shopping?
Oh, there's a Godzilla character shop.
I'm gonna take a shopping trip, so wait a second.
Hey!
Damn you!
You're gonna go on a sightseeing vacation?
Hey, shut up!
I'll be here at 9 tomorrow, so wake up and wait for me.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow, too.
The chief will get angry if I don't put on the water bottle cap properly.
The special version of G.I. Joe, and the American version of Godzilla, and also...
Ah, stop it already! Why do you have to put on a water bottle cap like your husband?
Huh? Ah, it's money!
What? A list of souvenirs?
Are you telling me to buy it with this money?
You're mistaking me for a import company, aren't you?
I can't do it.
Huh?
What? I slept well.
Hi, Max.
Huh?
Hi, Sunday.
Hey, you're a pretty sister.
Hurry up and get on.
Is it your sister you were talking about?
I'm Saishimochi. Don't ask me unnecessary questions.
Yes, yes, I understand.
I don't have any other opinions.
Huh?
Whoa, that's awesome!
As expected of New York, the prison of crime.
The police are not enough, no matter how many lives they have.
This is different from Japan.
The reason why Japan's security is good is because it's obvious that ordinary people don't have guns.
That's why.
That's why even a guy like you is a police officer.
You know what? From now on, you'll change your clothes more than a week.
You're going to be...
What's wrong with that guy?
It's a robbery!
What?
Don't move!
If you move, I'll shoot you!
Put your hands on your head!
As usual, you're great.
You're great.
Max!
Leave the rest to me.
Wow, that's a really rough arrest.
It's over.
Thanks.
Oh, it's that girl from before!
This is Zebra Six.
I was in the alley at 52nd street and arrested Mike Goat in the current second half.
You're the Japanese policeman who came to the training, right?
I'm Sandy. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryo Tsukankichi. Nice to meet you.
Max, why don't you two come to my house tonight?
I'll treat you to dinner.
Oh, I don't mind.
What? Really?
Yes. Then, I'll see you at 7 o'clock tonight.
Be sure to come.
Yeah!
This is Harlem.
Huh? What is this place?
Harlem?
I thought it was a place where pretty girls gather.
But it's just a bunch of people with bad taste.
Tourists, you should come in.
I'll beat you up.
It's just a small place.
Hey!
You bastard!
I'm not coming to you!
Get out!
You even hit the bus.
It's a big deal.
It's a real crime scene.
Oh, the building is on fire!
Hey, it's a fire!
You're the one who set the fire on purpose.
You're supposed to help the fire department.
Huh?
You do it well.
So the firefighters won't come here either.
But what if it's a real fire?
Huh?
Oh!
There's someone in the fire!
Hey, stop!
Really?
I didn't see it.
It's true!
Hey!
I knew it!
Don't you have any water?
No water!
I can't do it.
Huh?
It's too late to burn that much.
Stop!
Are you going to die?
What...
What are you going to do, Kamikazem?
Hey!
Use this water to extinguish the fire!
He's going to die!
What are you going to do?
Yeah!
He's alive!
Are you OK?
Oh, That's great!
You're this old woman's husband?
Yes!
That's great, old woman!
Thank you so much.
What a favor to beg you, Yala.
Don't mention it.
It seems you're dressed nicely, huh?
If you didn't help me, you would be in trouble now.
What? You want me to pay you back?
What?
I didn't know there was a policeman like you in Japan.
You're pretty good too.
I'm not a policeman.
I didn't expect Max, who hated Japanese people so much, to get along with Mr. Ryo-tsu like this.
Ryo-chan is special. He's a real man.
Ryo-chan?
Yes, Ryo-chan.
Oh, you came with Ryo-chan?
Okay, I'll call you Ma-chan.
Ma-chan? That's good.
I like you.
Bye, Ryo-chan.
Okay, I'm a loser.
A pervert.
You're not a pervert. You're a pervert.
I'm not a pervert.
Look at this.
Look!
Oh, my God!
This is Japanese pervert dancing.
Ryo-chan is great.
I've never met him before.
I don't know if I can do it myself or not.
How should I name you, Mr. Ryo-chan?
Mr. Ryo-chan.
At present, Mr. Ryo-chan is your tengo.
Next, more than just a teddy bear.
Mr. Kato.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Oh, nice to meet you too.
But, what's the matter, Ma-chan?
Actually,
Huh?
I'm going to escort that boy
who's with Sandy
to Los Angeles.
I see. You've done a lot of work
until today.
I'm grateful.
I had a lot of fun, too.
Enjoy New York until you get back.
Sandy, shall we go?
Yes.
Let's go, John.
John,
we're going to Los Angeles for a long time.
Let's get along.
Come on, John.
Max, Sandy,
if you ever come to Japan,
please visit me anytime.
I'll be very happy.
See you.
What's that?
Max, he's being targeted with a rifle!
What?
Max!
Sandy, hide!
John! Max!
R-Ryo...
The criminal...
Okay, arrest him immediately!
Yes! Sandy, it's an ambulance!
Okay!
Max, hang in there!
Ryo...
Hey, don't talk anymore!
I'm fine.
But I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
The one who shot me is a member of the Mafia.
Mafia?
I'm sure they were aiming at John's life.
They were aiming at saving Sandy
Would you take John with you to Los Angeles?
All right, I got it!
I told you not to talk anymore!
I thought Ryo would take the leading role.
Max!
I'm okay.
I just slept under the magic water.
Okay, I get that.
I'm sure Ryo Tsukakichi
will definitely bring John to Los Angeles.
I'm sure he will.
I have to do something!
Episode 1 The
King of the Mafia
Even so, who is this man who is aiming to kill the mafia?
An important trump card to make the mafia's boss, Don Castanino, the one who has power over the whole of America, guilty.
A trump card?
Don Castanino killed his parents and siblings.
What?
His father is a informant.
He told the police about Castanino's drug dealings, and thanks to that, we were able to arrest a lot of the mafia.
As a revenge, John's family...
Yes.
At the time of his mother's death, before Castanino and his family came to us, John was the only one who hid in the closet and escaped from the crisis.
He was wrong.
Do it!
Our others were in terrible trouble.
Later, Castanino was arrested for another crime.
But for the John family's murder, he didn't feel concerned about what happened.
I didn't know John was watching.
I see. So he's an important witness.
Then, if John witnesses the fact that the Castanians ordered to kill his family,
he can be accused of guilty?
Yes. The trial will be held in the court of law in Los Angeles in three days.
Three days.
Four days.
All right, the fuel is ready.
Anytime.
Mister, have a nice trip.
America is a good country.
Bye.
Checkmate King 2
Hello, this is Checkmate King 2.
My name is Kankechi Ryotsu. I'm John's family...
I'm going to take you to Los Angeles to avenge your family.
I'm done for.
I wonder if my English is not working.
That's true, but John was shocked that his family was killed,
so he couldn't speak.
He couldn't speak? He couldn't speak at all?
Yes.
Poor thing.
I see.
Um, Sandy, what do you call a toy in English?
Toy.
John, it's a Japanese toy.
Watch carefully.
What?
Well, how's that?
Good, isn't it?
Hey, you try it too.
Uh.
John, what are you doing?
Ryo is your ally.
Take off your knife.
Uh, oh.
Geez, American kids are not cute.
Ryo, forgive him.
I was in the same situation when I first met him.
Adults are all enemies.
I think he's an enemy.
Hmm, well, it's not impossible.
But why did you go to Los Angeles by car?
The plane is faster and safer.
Kennedy Airport, of course.
The airport near New York, the heliport, and the railway stations.
I heard that Don Castanino's assistants were in a mess.
I see.
Of course, in order to hide John's mouth,
he's a child of the island.
Yes.
It takes three days to Los Angeles,
but it's better to disguise like this
and pick up a child-and-child traveler
so that they don't notice.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I thought they wouldn't notice,
but it didn't seem to go that way.
Look behind you.
Huh?
Ah, the trouble is that he came here.
He's trapped.
Hmm.
Ah!
He can't go back.
What should he do?
Ah!
Oh, no!
He's going to be pressed completely.
Good.
Joe?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Ugh!
Damn it!
What a jerk.
Ah!
Joe!
Don't make a fuss.
I'm not tired of the fact that
Ryo-kun is so stubborn.
Gya!
What the hell!?
Hey, Ryo!
Ryo, where are you?
What's wrong?
My God!
Are you okay, Sande?
Ryo, you're okay, right?
I'm in this car!
I'll open the road, so accelerate at once!
Okay!
Alright!
Sande!
Now!
Okay!
Alright!
Sande!
Alright! Next is the one behind you!
What's wrong?
Let me go!
Sad 비룡
Ryo!
Hey, I'm here!
What?
Ryo!!
I'm okay.
I lost my sandal, though.
That's great!
Seriously!
This is no good.
Mikazeme!
No good.
Not only the body, but the engine is also destroyed.
It can't be helped.
Let's leave this car here and rent a rental car.
Where are we going to rent a rental car?
The town is stupid.
I can't see a single house.
I'm going to hitchhike and go to the nearest town and rent it.
Hitchhike?
Oh, here it comes.
Hide in the shadow of the car.
Why?
If you're a child, the car won't stop for you.
I see.
Hey!
Come on!
I want you to put it on!
It's so powerful.
You're a child!
Oh, it's gone.
I'm bored until Sandy comes back.
Corn seeds?
A net for evading birds?
I have a good idea!
John!
Lend me a knife!
A knife!
Thank you.
How is it? Is it interesting?
John, get the net over there.
Net, net. There's a net for bird's nest in the field over there.
Take it and make it a little deeper.
Like this, like this.
Okay, it's done.
John, there's a newspaper and a tape on the dashboard of the car, so please bring it.
I'll take it.
How is it, John?
The Japanese kite octopus is pretty good, right?
Oh, you like it?
I'm finally here, Sandy.
Hey!
Ryo, I bought sandals, too.
Thank you.
It was fun.
It's okay.
It's a present for you.
You became really close while I was away.
That's right.
Anyway, Sandy, I think you'd better not stop anywhere from now on.
It seems that they already know that we're using this road.
That's right. But it's impossible to drive for three days and then go to school.
If you take a car with me, you'll be able to go non-stop.
Okay!
Let's go home.
Okay.
Goodbye, Sandy.
Bye.
Good-bye, Sandy.
You have to watch out for the depicted
Hahaha.
All right, then.
Good boy.
What's wrong, you two?
You haven't eaten anything at all.
I'm tired.
I can't get my appetite back.
Oh, right.
You've been running for more than two days.
I guess you should take a rest somewhere.
I'm sure they haven't noticed that we're moving in a rental car.
You're right.
We're already in California.
If we leave at 1 a.m., we'll be in time before the trial starts.
All right.
When I'm done eating, I'll go look for Negra.
Do you want to eat that chili bean?
Can I have some?
What?
I'm hungry.
All right.
Let's go.
Listen, John.
You're going to sleep here like this.
Then, Sandy will be in the middle.
Do you understand?
And you don't have to know the reason.
Just go to bed in that order.
If John sleeps, you can choose from Sandy.
What's the big problem?
Just go to bed.
I'll be back in just a moment.
He'll come to guard you until the next hour.
Ah, I see.
Then I guess I'll take a shower or something.
Wait.
Before that, why don't you ask Captain Bakuryuu for help?
Huh?
If John tells you the truth,
Don Castanino will be guilty for sure.
The servants will be desperate,
and will come to stop us from entering the path.
I see.
Okay.
Then Sunday, take a shower and wait for me.
Wait for me?
No, no, it's nothing.
I'll call you right away.
Who's that calling at this hour?
It's me, Ryo Scankichi.
Oh, it's you.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Sunday!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Ryo!
Sunday!
John!
Damn it!
Huh?
You made me punk!
Damn it!
John!
Sunday!
Ah, I see.
Hello?
Ryo, what's that sound?
I'll tell you later!
Anyway, come with me!
Damn it!
That bastard!
He must have done something!
No doubt he turned his back on us.
It would be better to stand still along the wayside.
Where are you going, ha?
There's a warehouse where we can escape from.
Where on earth did that red bear go?
Where the hell did he go?
The police are watching over him on every street.
He's not going to get out of this town.
Sanze, John, stay safe!
Now, stay still here!
He's not going to get out of this town.
Patracchi's brother said to kill him, but he doesn't have to do it.
I hope he doesn't make it in time for the trial.
I'll leave it to him to do it.
Patracchi's brother said to kill him, but he doesn't have to do it.
You had a knife, didn't you?
There you go.
Okay, I'll borrow it for a while.
Patracchi's brother said to kill him, but he doesn't have to do it.
I'll leave it to him to do it.
I did it!
Come on, hurry up!
Please.
It won't open any further.
Then it's impossible to escape from there.
What if you use an octopus or something?
What?
That?
I see! Good idea, John!
Now! What are the cops doing?
Now we're not going to make it to today's trial!
Oh?
What's that?
It's John!
I made the octopus for John!
I'm here.
Oh, I finally found it.
Colonel, land in a place they don't notice.
Got it.
Hmph. I didn't know I'd be killed in an hour.
You slept well.
It's all right.
After we find that octopus, Ryo will surely come to help us.
He's already here.
Huh? Ryo!
Hmm. Sandy, how many enemies are there?
Two. But there might be more.
All right. There's no time until the trial.
It'll be rough, but I'll help you right away.
Go to that corner and hang on.
Got it.
I'm counting on you!
Okay.
Run!
Wait!
John, this way!
Run! Run!
John!
Don't move!
You bastard!
Don't shoot!
John!
You bastard!
I won't forgive you!
Don't move!
Uhhh!
Ugh!
How dare you!
You bastard!
I killed John!
Stop, Ryotsu!
I'm sorry, sir!
I know how you feel, but don't do it anymore.
Damn it!
Ryo!
John is alive!
What?
Jo-John!
Why are you...
A B-goma?
The B-goma Ryo gave me protected John.
Ryo...
What's wrong, John?
John!
Ryo!
You can speak now?
Thank you, Ryo!
I'm so glad!
Judge, we can't wait any longer for the prosecutor's witness.
If the witness is not here, please go to the police station.
If it's the witness, he's here!
What?
Judge!
I'm sorry to be late, but I'm the witness.
Please allow me to ask you a question.
Hmm...
John, who ordered you to kill your family,
that is, the Wilson family?
Do it!
It's this guy!
What?
No way!
What this kid is saying is a lie!
I'm the one who ordered you to do this!
Hey!
Now the Castaneda family is finished.
Yes, the death row is definitely a mistake.
Well, everyone.
I'm sorry to see you off, even though you're injured.
What?
It's a scratch.
John, let's meet again.
Yes.
What?
Ryo-san, thank you so much!
What am I even grateful for?
Well, three of youってall are OK.
Will it be all right to do that?
Okay.
What?
No...
W-w-w-what?
Ok, it's my turn.
Hey, Ma-chan's fine!
Come on, you can touch injury.
Oh?
I see.
Too bad.
See you.
Be careful, Ryo.
I'll definitely go to Japan.
Goodbye, Ryo.
Welcome back, Senpai.
Oh, Nakagawa.
You look fine.
Of course. I haven't worked for two weeks.
Huh? Where are the souvenirs? Did you bring them to the airport?
No, not really.
I bought G.I. Joe and American Van Gogh, but I gave them to John.
You didn't buy anything for the director or the chief?
Was it bad?
Reiko took care of me.
I see.
Nakagawa, lend me some money.
Welcome back, Ryo.
Chief, I'm back.
Did you have any trouble while I was gone?
Thanks to you, everything went well.
Come back again.
You'll stay in Alaska for about 50 years.
That's a tough joke.
You must have bought souvenirs for the chief.
Of course.
No, I'm in America.
I'll go with you and give everyone souvenirs.
Wait a minute.
G.I. Joe.
Show me what you bought.
No.
You're suspicious.
The chief had a list of drinks, so I'll take the drinks.
It's a big whiskey.
What?
Hey.
It says, "A manly taste of sake."
It's made in California.
It's made in America.
Why did you buy sake in America?
Show me other souvenirs.
I bought a doll for the chief, a camera for the regional chief, and a tea bowl for the chief.
The boss is the boss.
Ta-da.
It's a Hakata obi and a Zori set.
Did you really go to America?
You must have been hiding in Tokyo.
No.
I bought everything in America.
It's a so-called reverse imported product.
It's a really valuable item.
Then I'll ask you.
What does it say in the broadcast paper that it's a New Tokyo International Airport?
No.
That's wrong.
That's not Tokyo.
It's Tonkin.
I went home to Tonkin, next to Beijing.
So there.
Do you think I'll be fooled by that?
Ryo.
You didn't even wear a water bottle cap.
I'm not good at such small things.
What about the new book that the chief wrote for the chief over there?
I have it properly.
Idiot.
It's meaningless if you don't give it to me.
Wait, Ryo.
Oh.
I can't study abroad.
I hate studying abroad.