"The
Greatest
Festival of
It's lively.
Well, when it comes to a festival, it's always lively.
Senpai knows about the festivals in Tokyo.
Oh, look inside.
Yes.
It's lively.
Especially the second one from the left is good.
Is it that girl?
Yes.
Ah! That woman!
What the hell are you doing?!
Don't mess with me!
Where are the idiots who step on the holy amikoshi?!
I don't know where you're coming from, but get out of here!
Oh! That's good, sis!
You!
Wait a minute!
I see! This right hand is the bad one!
W-W-What the hell are you doing?!
I want you to do more!
Hey!
I-I'm screwed!
There are many guys at festivals!
Be careful not to get hurt!
Hey, Nagawa!
Yes!
See you later!
I've seen him before!
He comes to the Kanda Festival every year!
He loves festivals!
He's a fan of Tokyo!
I think he's wearing a holy amikoshi!
It's the famous Ryotsukan Kichi of the Katsushika Shrine!
The Katsushika Shrine?
Big news! Big news!
What's wrong, Terai?
Did you win a thousand yen in the lottery?
Why is that the big news?
I'm a small townie!
If you're a small townie,
you can't make it that big!
No way!
So, Terai, what is the big news?
Right.
Actually, I've heard it in the book,
but it seems like the new minister has been dismissed today!
Oh.
So what kind of person is he?
He's a very very beautiful 19-year-old!
Very very beautiful?
That's what the book says!
I can't expect much from him,
but it's worth seeing him!
Let's go inside!
Oh, Senpai!
Oh, he's gone!
Well then, Terai, see you later!
What?
Even Reiko?
Huh?
What's wrong?
This uniform is too small.
It's the book manager's mistake.
Matoi, take it off.
I'll tell him to change it.
But what are you going to do until it arrives?
It's fine.
With a T-shirt.
Eh?
Isn't a T-shirt bad?
That's right.
There's something good.
I think it was at the shopping street event.
Here we go.
What's this?
It's like a party for a pachinko shop!
It seems like it was sent to a new minister.
Huh?
Gita-kara-tama...
Eh?
What's this word?
Is it a four-letter idiom?
It seems like a name, but...
It's Giboshi Matoi.
Huh?
Ah!
You're the one from yesterday!
I'm Giboshi Matoi, who has been assigned to my office from today!
Ah, it's you.
I'm Reiko Akimoto, a postman at the park.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa.
And, did you see that gorilla over there somewhere?
You...
You're not here!
I've been asking you for a while now,
and you're asking me for a reason, even though you're a new member!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm just talking to you!
Shut up!
What's the big deal with that?
You're wearing a uniform, so you're wearing a uniform!
I don't have a uniform!
The size of the uniform I was assigned didn't fit.
Matoi, when you talk to him,
it makes you look like an idiot.
That's right!
He's the worst policeman in the past!
He's the number one man who's not married for the past 11 years!
You're lower than a cockroach!
You're trying to say whatever you want in a trance!
Senpai.
Huh?
Ah, Matoi-chan.
Ah, the old lady of Sakamoto!
What's up?
What's wrong with the Kanda Myojin Shita Association?
Congratulations on your new job, Matoi!
Thank you! But I don't need to do this.
This is from my master.
Sorry.
Is your tooth getting better?
Yeah, thanks to you.
Anyway, Matoi, everyone is supporting you!
Good luck, Matoi!
Catch a lot of bad guys!
Thank you!
You're being loved, Matoi.
You're very popular.
You said you became a Kanda Myojin Shita.
Is he born in the same year as you?
He was born and raised in Kanda.
He's a nice boy.
I knew you were bad at talking.
Hmm, so you're Kanda.
Hey, Matoi!
You came here, too?
Today is Matoi's lucky day!
I'll give you a gift of celebration!
Yeah.
To everyone?
I'll give you a gift of celebration!
Can I have a card, please?
Hey, Yomachi!
Oh, my!
As expected of a famous soba restaurant in Kanda.
It looks delicious!
It's fresh from the market.
Oh, my!
It's delicious!
I've never had such delicious soba before.
It's 100% soba.
This restaurant has been here for a long time.
Wow!
As expected of a Shita town.
Please come again.
I live here for seven days a week.
So I can eat the best foods.
Oh, I see.
This is the fifth generation of that.
You are the 5th generation of the Asakusa.
Are you from Asakusa?
Ok.
That's not a good sign.
You've looked down from the roof,
and you're always in the right place.
That's not what you think.
What do you mean?
Is that so, senpai?
Y-Yeah...
I ride it no matter how many times I try to be careful...
I was also able to put a triangle on the handle bar so that I won't get on it...
Hey, you must remember this!
Shut up!
It's a festival, so you should be excited!
Be excited!
I can't stand it when a man with such thoughts is in the city!
Don't say "I'm ticked off"!
Even though I used to live in a farm, I don't have the habit of living in a building right now!
Then, what about you, Mr. Atsushi?
Are you a "Samba Carnival"?
Why are you a Samba Carnival?!
Y-You're making a sharp comment.
It's okay!
I can dance in front of the camera while drinking while looking at myself naked!
You're a fool!
You're not being a ryo at all!
You're right.
It's more embarrassing to hear it.
You can do it, Matoi!
That's amazing that you don't even take a step back against Ryotsu!
His voice is so loud.
Good luck, Matoi!
Don't be so mean!
Shut up, Gaiya!
What?
I'm losing, so don't get me into trouble!
That's right!
You always brag about your "tick-off" behavior, but you're more like a "tick-off" person!
Matoi is also good at "Begoma"!
"Begoma"?
Well, I've never lost to a boy!
You're so stupid, Ghiboshi!
What?
There is no human on Earth who can beat me, the king of "Begoma"!
Don't play with me and get involved!
What?
Let's have a good game!
You're going to regret it!
Look!
I'm a "Begoma 2" who likes to carry things around!
What?
That's none of your business!
I always have it with me!
What?
Hey!
As expected of the town girl!
I'll make the topo, so wait for me!
Okay, it's done!
Asakusa man, it's a game!
We don't have Asakusa man, do we?
Call me Ryotsu-san or Ryotsu-senpai!
That's not a big deal, right?
Hurry up and roll!
You were caught well, Giboshi.
I didn't know that this piece was King Kaizo's.
Okay, I'm ready!
Chi! Chi! Chi!
It's really slow!
I won this game!
I won!
I can't beat a man!
There's no doubt about that!
What's with that "beigoma"?
I'll take that!
Amazing!
Are you okay, senpai?
Ha ha ha!
Women can't be serious with others.
You didn't seem like that at all.
Yeah.
I said, "I'm serious!"
Damn it!
Next, it's a game with menko!
No problem!
But I don't have menko, so please lend me Asakusa's.
It's not Asakusa!
It's Ryotsu-Kankichi!
Here you go.
I was convinced.
You
I'll put this menko in oil for a month,
so it's three times heavier.
Ouch!
It won't crack!
I'm not going to be a victim!
My treat!
Eeeh!
I can't beat a man after all!
Hey, hurry up and do it!
Huh?
Here, take it.
You can do it first.
Then, without hesitation!
Yaaaaaay!
I did it!
Yay! We won again!
Ryouchi Kankichi has been boasting a lot so far!
He was really bad at it.
Shut up!
Yay! Gimoshi! Let's fight with the "begoma" again!
Are you going to use the modified "begoma" again?
Meat!
There was one in my school.
A boy who used to use only cowardly hands.
He shaved the king's belly and modified it,
and he made the face fat-soaked and made it heavier.
Eeeh?
Ryo, is that true?
Y-Yeah, um...
You're a cheater, as I thought!
You pervert! You scum!
You!
I got hit in the head!
I'm going to beat you up!
This has nothing to do with the seniors!
Eeeh!
Ryouchi Kankichi is being boasted about being a new member!
Huh?
I'm going to do this!
The new member's name is Gimboshi Matoi.
Oh, Junsaka!
Is it true?
The senior lost because of "begoma" and "menko"?
Shut up!
But a new member has come.
Damn it!
Gimboshi Matoi, remember this!
A computer?
Yes.
Oh, perfect!
I run a sushi restaurant in Kanda,
but I'm going to make a store's homepage next time.
That's the only thing I can do.
Do you know who is familiar with this?
Well,
if it's an email or an internet,
I can do something about it,
but not to make a homepage.
If you're a gorilla man, you might be able to do it.
Gorilla man?
Oh, from Asakusa!
You know what it is pretty well with that face.
But I'm sure you'll get paid for it!
Oh, really?
Not only you have a bad face and personality,
but you're also dirty about money!
For money, I'm a man who sells souls, you know?
He's a good man.
Then I'll go fishing with sushi.
What?
Oh.
Mr. Giboshi is very popular.
He's the second most popular person, after Reiko.
He's like an idol in the public transport industry.
Hey, shut up!
I said it's been three days, but you're still talking about it.
The police chief often uses such a way to get back.
What's the standard of the police chief's application?
Don't say that!
You're such a snob!
You're making me proud!
If we meet again...
What are you going to do, man from Asakusa?
Snob?
Hello.
Hey, don't show up suddenly!
And stop calling me a man from Asakusa.
Don't call me that with the title of Enka.
You're so annoying!
Oh, you finally got your uniform.
Yes. I liked the flip side, too.
Well, it looks really good on you.
I wonder if that's true.
Are you here to brag about your uniform?
No.
I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Hey, can you choose a computer?
And make a homepage, too.
Oh.
I'm busy.
I heard that Matoi-chan's house is a sushi restaurant.
Yes.
What sushi?
If you help me make a homepage,
I'll treat you to as much sushi as you want!
You can eat as much as you want!
You can eat as much as you want?
But you're the one who made me proud.
You're the pride of a man.
That's what I'm trying to say.
You want to take pride from a man,
or the much-eaten sushi!
Look, here is a great "Kanburi"
"Kanburi"!
That's all I need!
I'm done!
I guess I have no choice.
I'll help you, for my junior.
I can't believe it cost 50,000 yen for everything.
I'm an Akihabara person.
If I work a little harder, I'll get 30,000 yen.
You're making the shopkeeper cry.
This is our shop.
Oh, it's here.
It's a very old shop.
I'm back!
Welcome back.
I bought a computer.
Hello. Good evening.
Who are you?
I'm your colleague, Asakusa.
Oh, Asakusa-san. Good work.
Hey, say your name properly.
Asakusa is a good place.
Oh, good.
There's quite a yard in the middle of the city.
Really?
So, where are you going to put your computer?
It's my grandma's room.
Oh, it's a room that feels nostalgic.
I'll go and get some tea. Wait for me.
Yeah, I'll set it up.
As expected, there's only the old woman.
It's clean and tidy.
She must be a nice old woman.
I'm very impressed.
Hmm?
Huh?
These buttons are the same as my own.
Grandma!
Huh?
Oh!
What?
This is a mystery!
Huh?
Oh, no!
Grandma, he's not a thief!
He's a policeman!
What?
What? Is that your colleague?
I thought I'd just make him mine.
What a scary old lady.
All right, setup complete.
Can you record the water level of the shop?
Of course!
The special software is installed.
It's installed?
Installed? Setup?
There are so many letters.
Yeah, yeah.
That's why you don't like computers.
It doesn't matter if I remember.
Let's try to calculate the sales or something.
Really?
This is the water level of last month.
This is this one.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wow.
Amazing.
That's great.
How is it? Easy, right?
Wait a minute.
Huh?
I'll check if it's correct.
What?
The water level of the water tank.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's a five-ball.
It's old.
What?
Hmm?
Huh?
It's correct.
What?
What was that?
I didn't see my finger at all.
You're pretty good at computers.
A machine.
Mr. Asakusa,
could you record the data of the shop up until now?
All right.
I'll record everything.
What?
Huh?
Can I start from the 17th year of Kyohoku?
I think it's OK to start from the time.
Wait, wait, wait.
How many years ago do you intend to enter?
About 300 years ago.
Don't joke like that!
If you put such a huge data,
you wouldn't have known how many days or weeks it would take.
It can't be helped.
It's OK if I start here from the year I arrived here.
Then, this guy.
I'll ask you from now on, Mr. Asakusa.
I'm not Mr. Asakusa.
I'm 12 years old.
How old is this old lady?
99 years old.
Oh, she's almost 100 years old.
Yeah.
100 years old?
Why is she older than my old man?
This is your grandmother's handwriting.
Did you leave the store's record to her when you arrived?
My father in law liked it.
That year, the fish was poor.
So,
I went to buy it by bicycle with a single yen bill.
The bonito was 5,000 yen and the sea bream was 10,000 yen.
And then, in the second year,
it was finally 15,000 yen and 23,000 yen in black.
I was relieved.
Hey,
you don't need a computer in this house, do you?
Your grandmother is very good at memorizing and she's fast at solving problems.
Don't be silly.
After work, I'll treat you to our super special sushi.
Oh, that's right.
Super special sushi.
I'll put it in from the 12th year.
I've finished writing the entry form and the website for the 88-year water tower.
Good job, Asakusa.
I told you it's not.
I don't have the energy to deny it.
Well, I'll prepare the sushi you promised.
Oh, thank you.
I have something to ask you about the website.
What is it?
When accessing the website,
data is cached to the proxy server, right?
Domain name system server,
and the secondary and primary are also cached?
What an old woman.
Do you already understand that?
What?
What's wrong?
I don't need to learn such a difficult system.
I just need to press the internet.
I can do it in one go.
I see.
Thank you for waiting, Asakusa.
This is the super special sushi.
I'll enjoy it.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Well,
I asked this person to do a job worth 1 million yen.
Isn't this rude?
I'll give you 1 million yen worth of Otaro sushi.
I understand.
And you have a good sense of humor, right?
Yes, I do.
I thought you were a ridiculous old woman.
But you are a great old woman.
You have a good salary.
Have some.
Anything?
What?
Do you want some?
No, I'm asking for some.
I'm asking for some.
What's wrong, Asakusa?
You love sushi, don't you?
I only use the best quality sushi.
I'm sure you can get 2 million yen for 3 pieces.
Damn it.
I should have gotten a normal sushi.
I'm a ridiculous old woman.
I'm going to burn you.
It's a good meal.
I like it.
I'm here.
It's painful.
It's been a long time, and I haven't seen such a happy old woman.
Asakusa, thank you so much for today.
I got 2 million yen worth of sushi.
It's not an honor.
You should give me an applause at times like this.
Yeah.
I had fun too.
Oh, really?
Well, good night.
Oh!
Wow!
Ryo-chan made this?
No, it's all from the music to the CD.
It's all made by Ghiboshi's grandma.
But, you were a beginner at computer.
What a great grandma.
I made sure to receive the business card by mail.
Is this person the manager's name?
This is called Ghiboshi Gepard.
Gepard?
My father's name is Ghiboshi Yoroshiku.
My sister's name is Ghiboshi Lemon.
My brother's name is Ghiboshi Yuzu.
It's almost the same.
It's half the world.
What?
You can't kick me if you're a loser.
What did you say?
Give me back my car.
What?
What's wrong?
She's angry because I moved the car by myself.
That place is not allowed to park.
The resident's complaint was already out.
I can't talk to a little girl like you.
Call the boss.
What?
Hey!
Stop, Ghiboshi!
You're not going out.
Hey, Ryo stopped the fight.
Ryo is the one who started the fight.
Give me back my car!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Shut up!
Ghiboshi!
You're going to get a girl!
Don't hurt a girl's face!
Asakusa!
Your face is so...
I'll make you a girl!
Please stop!
What?
This is what happened.
It's because of Ryo.
"Machinima"
Hello.
Excuse me.
How did it go?
I was able to escape the neck.
But, I was supposed to be in quarantine for a month.
Like always.
When you're injured, you were fine, weren't you?
It's nothing serious.
You did all this for me.
You were managed by one.
Now, don't worry about it.
I'm the home run king of not going to go to the bathroom.
Am I laughing?
Ryo.
I'm going back to the only.
However, you are not going to use "Ryo".
I'm working overtime.
Yes.
Thank you for your help every time.
Well,
I don't have any pay during overtime,
so I have to find a part-time job.
Then I'll take care of you at home.
What?
At Cho Kanda Sushi?
I was just looking for a part-time job.
How about 300,000 yen for a month of living?
What?
Can I get that much?
Thank you.
That's right.
Grandma wanted to see you.
Huh?
I completely forgot that she was there.
Asakusa,
I'm grateful to you for giving me a job.
Oh, that's good.
By the way,
I'm raising a post-pet Momo.
She won't come home after taking a walk.
I'm working overtime at a sushi restaurant.
You can do that later. Come on!
Huh?
Hey, wait!
By the way, what's her name?
What's her name?
Hmm, I don't remember her real name.
For now, this is fine.
Huh?
Ichiro Asakusa?
Is this really okay?
There's a bigger room.
Yeah, it's better to stay in a small room.
Well, I'll bring a futon later.
Yeah.
Take a bath while you're at it.
You'll be busy at 6:00.
I'll be busy at 8:00.
Roger that.
Oh, it's like a hot spring.
It's amazing to have a private house.
After living like this,
I can get paid.
I wonder if I'll really get a job.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ichiro, I'll give you two cups of hot springs.
Yes!
Ichiro, a banquet at Fugusashi.
Yes, yes!
Ichiro, a beer with Okunotatsuki.
Yes!
Ichiro, 50 cups of rice balls.
Ichiro, 100 cups of tea.
Yes!
Ichiro!
Since when did I become Ichiro?
Yes!
You're such a gross.
You're telling me your name.
Ichiro!
Yes!
Ichiro, Ichiro!
Ichiro!
Please wait!
Oh, it's finally over.
This is a cheap 10,000 yen per day.
Good work.
If there's a banquet, you can tell me first.
What are you talking about?
Every day this week, there's a banquet.
I'm in the first floor.
What?
Oh, it's already midnight.
I'm hungry.
Here.
Huh?
It's a night meal leaflet.
I made it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Hohoho!
Toro, uni, abalone!
Goka, kenda!
It's a feast at night.
I'm glad I came to the sushi shop for a part-time job.
Let's eat!
It's delicious.
Um.
It's sweet!
Getting sleepy.
Good morning, Asakusa.
Did you sleep well?
I'm not sleepy.
I was beaten up by grandma before dawn.
It's a full rotation.
You'll get used to it in a couple of days.
Then, I'm going to work.
Yes.
Nice to meet you all.
Miss, take care.
Hey Ichiro, come and feed me.
Yes.
Huh, this is a high voice again.
Ha ha ha.
Good, good.
How is it? Are you a little used to it?
I didn't think the customer business was so hard.
By the way, that frame looks pretty old.
Yeah, it's from the Meiji era.
Can I look inside a little?
I wonder if it's okay to look inside.
It seems like there are treasures.
It's just a warehouse.
Huh? That scroll is from Tessai Tomioka.
No, everyone else is famous artists.
It's a mountain of treasures, seriously.
Can I go inside for a moment?
That's the Akazu-no-ma.
What?
It's made of sturdy jomai.
I've never been inside one.
Yeah, he's an amateur.
My acquaintance has a jomai shop, so let's let him open it.
Huh? But I have to ask the old lady.
You're going to open the chest?
If you ask the jomai shop of your acquaintance, you can open it in two or three days.
I wanted to organize the inside.
It was just right.
Please do it.
Yes, there is a request there.
A request?
I'd like to have a roll.
Do you really want it?
It's a lifelong request.
If you work hard, I can give it to you.
Thank you very much.
I'll work hard.
Welcome.
Two people will come in.
Good morning.
Come on, come on.
Ichiro is very enthusiastic.
Sushi is not that good.
I have to be good at cooking.
Huh?
Did Ichiro sharpen this knife?
That's right.
I don't think it's part-time.
It's the main dish.
He has a good sense of direction.
As expected of the man in the lower town.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Ichiro, please wash the dishes.
Yes.
The owner of the inn is also ...
If it's real, I'll give you 5 million yen.
I'll forget it.
Is it true?
I haven't noticed it yet.
It's a wonderful day off.
It's interesting because this is the world.
You really work well.
He's good at making dishes, and he's a good craftsman.
What?
He's the son of Matoi.
Marry!
Wait a minute.
Matoi is still 19 years old.
Women are in their teens.
Matoi is clearly dressed.
It's a girl who is in her teens.
It's perfect for a man like you.
But ...
I don't like him.
Matoi has been married to someone who has been in my eyes for a long time.
But ...
What?
Do you say you don't like Matoi?
No.
I think she's a good girl.
Then the story is too early.
From tomorrow, I will make you a good craftsman.
What?
If you pass, you will be a good craftsman.
See you!
I never expected this to happen.
This land is a great fortune.
I will be safe for the rest of my life.
But you are more concerned about your wealth than your wife.
What the hell am I?
Akegarasu ...
What? You know that song?
I learned it too.
I didn't think that my relative, the old woman of Yanagibashi,
was playing it.
You learned it from your old woman.
You like it, don't you?
I don't think it's in the center of Tokyo.
It's quiet at night.
There are many people and cars around here during the day.
But there are only empty buildings at night.
That's unexpected.
Come to my room.
What?
It's getting cold.
It's a room with nothing.
I don't like to put things in it.
You want to drink, right?
Oh, sure.
Wait a minute.
At this time of night,
you might be interested in me
Here you are.
I can't answer.
All right.
You drink too.
I can't.
I'm still a young man.
My grandmother stopped me.
In the Yuboshike family,
you must obey the orders of the old woman of Yanagibashi.
Of course.
The old woman is the most important.
Rather,
you look completely different than when you first met me.
What?
I misunderstood you so far.
You are a good person.
Did you understand now?
It's too late to notice.
When I see you,
I feel like someone else.
What?
No.
Is this a confession?
Is it a proposal for the Yuboshike?
It's already empty.
Actually,
I feel like someone else.
there is no one.
All right.
I understand.
As you say,
I have a cash.
Do not lose your way
in the treasure.
What?
You are not a Yuboshike.
Are you here already?
Yes.
The treasure is empty.
Hurry up.
Hey, old woman.
What about the scrolls?
Don't worry.
I have prepared them.
Don't surprise me.
All right.
Here.
The scrolls.
Now,
you are in charge.
It's not a scroll of sushi.
It's a scroll in the treasure.
It's not?
I have burned most of the scrolls in the treasure.
You are a beauty, old woman.
Hello.
What is this?
I made you a high-quality scroll.
Wow.
This is my first time to eat the scrolls.
By the way,
do you know where the scroll is?
for three weeks
when I came to the shop.
Well,
you eat it and see.
you ate it and see.
the string after it was tied up a lot.
The scroll of the scroll
have good shape.
It was printed thoroughly.
My good grandma did it the best.
Brings back
And he drinks fast too.
He's also very active.
He's gonna be a great craftsman.
What?
He wants to own a restaurant?
I'm more of a customer salesman.
Like a super Kanda sushi chef.
He's been training for 10 years to own a restaurant.
You've only been here for 3 weeks.
Interesting!
I'll let you own a restaurant.
What?
Grandma!
Our store is opening next month.
You can use the store for a week until the opening.
It's like a demonstration.
I see.
I'll deliver the content.
No, no.
I won't take care of the store.
I want to do it by myself.
Is Asakusa okay?
Leave it to me.
What?
Ryo-chan is opening a restaurant?
He's the owner of our branch store, No. 1.
Is that okay?
He's on a break.
Kouki's...
What was his name?
Mr. Honda?
Oh, right.
He said he'd help him.
Mr. Honda is being swayed by Ryo-chan again.
Welcome!
Three bowls of raw rice noodles.
Two bowls of chirashi.
Please wait a moment.
Sea urchin and salmon roe.
Okay.
Honda!
We haven't started yet.
Okay.
Please take this off.
Excuse me.
Ouch!
You're such a pain in the ass.
How many years have you been doing this?
It's only been a day since I started this job.
There's not enough people at the branch store today.
We'll wait for you.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Leave the rest to me.
What? Me?
Kouki and Kouki.
Okay.
Sayori.
I wonder who's Kouki and Kouki.
I might get scolded if I make a mistake.
I'm a little worried.
How about octopus?
It's fine.
I know what octopus is.
Idiot!
Don't use the sashimi knife!
Octopus is a wild animal.
It's a wild animal.
Put it on the wheel.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
You're good, but I don't feel like washing my hands.
It'll be clean as soon as you hold a few.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's a cheetah.
Perfect.
Yeah.
I've got a water-toothed knife.
A water-toothed knife.
The first day sales are 2 million.
What?
No way.
Yes, yes, don't push.
One person only.
That's strange.
Sir, I'm calling from Major MacDowell.
It's abalone, sea urchin, red sea urchin, sea urchin, and shrimp.
It's okay if it's Russian.
Hurry up.
Take it with a military plane.
Use the food and money.
Where are you from?
I'm from Aori.
My own route.
We're selling all sorts of seafood, and the store is big.
Hahaha.
What?
I changed the entry and can't come over here?
My own route has shut down.
What should I do?
I'm inviting the Chiefs of O-Hara today, right?
Go buy the material in the supermarket.
You're coming.
Hurry up, from behind.
Go.
Hello.
It's a nice store.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad you came.
He came to see me.
Ryo-tsu, you look fine.
Why is this bag here?
It's a secret.
Then, Ryo-tsu, I'll take the big one.
Me too.
Yes, yes, the big one.
The freshly caught big one has just been imported.
Here you are.
Is this the big one?
It looks like a normal red one.
This is why amateurs are troubled.
The original big one is here, the bottom part of the tuna.
This is the special big one, which is called the red diamond.
Is that so?
It seems so.
Then, senpai, the crab.
The crab.
What is this?
It's a crab.
This is a kamaboko with crab wings.
It was cheap.
What are you talking about?
No, nothing.
Wait.
Isn't this a crab kamaboko?
It's the other way around.
It's a kamaboko-like crab that hardens the crab meat and makes it into a kamaboko.
Is that so?
Then, I'll take the scallop.
Sure.
It's the only one I have.
And give me the squid.
Here's the scallop.
Is this scallop raw?
Of course.
It was moving a while ago.
The taste is different, isn't it?
It's definitely different.
This squid isn't a salmon, is it?
That's the high class. That's the common.
It seems to be doing well.
Gepard, why are you here in Ghiboshima?
I came to see how it's going.
What's your recommendation for today?
Well, I've got kappa-maki and oinari-san.
You can't do that, senpai.
I've bought all of them at the supermarket.
You idiot.
What do you mean?
No, no, no.
It's not that.
There's a reason for this.
Here it comes.
Huh?
Whoa!
I've been waiting!
What?
What's going on?
Ryo-tsu!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's the bug dragon.
I've purchased a lot of new ones from the Middle East Route.
Thank you.
You saved me.
I'm so happy.
You're laughter, right?
I love you, Ryo-tsu.
Ah, with a stick.
I didn't know there was a stick here.
Mom, Hime-kiji, Ryo-tsu feels a little like a movie star.
OK, well, I'll be looking forward to it.
Let me stay here.
I don't know if you know this but I'm seeing a woman who loves you.
Really?
Yes.
I don't care.
I love you.
She is so kind.
It's all you.
It's a waste!
Why would you marry her?
Because I like her.
You're really getting married?
Yeah.
They came to my place to ask for a na-code.
I'm greeting the director right now.
That's a great development.
Oh, there they are!
Ryo, Wato, congratulations!
Congratulations!
I-I feel like I've got a sudden shock.
Huh?
G-Gevalt!
Ichiro, Matoi, follow me!
Yes!
I'm going to borrow the two of you.
Oh...
I panicked because I was getting married.
Of course.
There are things called order in the world.
I haven't greeted your parents yet.
I see.
You're going to greet my parents?
I'm going to go now.
Hey, that's sudden.
They're going to panic too.
I'm going to be a troublemaker.
What?
Are you serious, Kankichi?
You're in trouble, old man!
Kankichi is going to bring his wife.
His wife?
Huh?
I'm going first.
Oh, it's Tsukudaniya's old store.
Tsukudaniya...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Oh, hey, congratulations!
You're getting married?
Why are you here, old man?
I'm in trouble, old man!
You're in trouble, you're in trouble!
Pull him out!
That's terrible.
Hello.
Good evening.
Well, have a seat.
It's a dirty place.
Sorry for the trouble.
What a beautiful lady.
Yeah.
They're my old couple.
I'm Ginji.
I'm Yone.
Thank you for this trip.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you.
My name's Matoi Giboshi.
I hope you'll accept Shugen.
I don't care anymore.
I'll cook and cook and cook.
I'll enjoy my life.
What a nice house.
It reminds me of my old house.
Yeah.
It's a dirty house.
Where are you from, Mr. Giboshi?
I'm a sushi seller in Kanda.
Oh, I see.
Sushi seller in Kanda?
My grandchild is a policeman.
Oh.
That's...
. . . ?
You remember?
Hey, don't come out!
Huh?
Why is this guy here?
You know him?
He's my grandfather.
You're Ichiro Asakusa, aren't you?
That's the name Giboshi gave me.
I'm Ryo Tsukankichi.
It was an unrecognizable name.
We used to call him that.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
Everyone calls me Ichiro Ichiro, so I'm Yuhima.
Ryo was the name before I came here.
So why did you call me Ichiro Ichiro?
You're a big deal to me.
It was Yuhima.
When did I know you before?
When I met your mother.
You thought that one day there was going to be an incident, like this?
But I didn't know the situation.
What happened?
Defense, defense.
Defends himself.
How?
Yes, this man is my brother.
Before I became a super-kanda-sushi, I used to run a tsukudaniya at home.
The business was good, and I started to make my own store.
Then, my siblings left it to me.
But, I worked hard every day to raise the store's sales,
but I was just playing with the Kanbei people every day.
You are so stupid.
You are always making a mess.
What's wrong with you?
You are not making a mess, so I run the store.
So, if I go to the store, the store will be broken in 10 days.
Wait a minute.
To summarize, Kanbei and Gepal are siblings.
They are the children of the children.
So, Matoi and I are twins.
No way!
Why didn't you notice me when we were close to Kanda and Asakusa?
There was a fire.
We have met more than 80 years.
It's been 80 years since we met.
We didn't know each other at all.
We are the parents of you.
I thought you were strangers from the first time I saw you on the street.
We are close friends.
If I knew your name was Ryotsu, I wouldn't have let you go.
What?
The women of the Ryotsu family are German and Swiss, and they are noble.
But, the men of the Ryotsu family are Latin, and they are all good-for-nothing.
Good-for-nothing.
If Gipo family has a good-for-nothing child, it will be the end of their lives.
What about getting married with another man?
We are relatives!
What do you care?
What matters is the feelings between us.
Matoi, I'll tell you.
Kanbei.
Leo, let go!
I'm going home!
Hey, wait!
Matoi!
Matoi! I'm not giving up!
K-Kankichi...
Poor thing...
Kanbei, say something!
Let's go to the radio station.
That's why your sister hates you!
Grandma, I've never been against you saying things like that.
But...
But this time...
I did it on my own will.
I want to decide.
Do as you please.
Grandma...
I...
Miss!
The door to the village is open!
What did you say?
I heard a strange sound from inside.
So you came after all.
I didn't know there was such a treasure underground.
I'm surprised when I discovered this secret underground.
This is the real satchel!
Aren't you?
Right?
That's right.
We are close since long.
I have been married for six years.
I wouldn't feel the need to live here anymore.
No, I don't want!
I don't want!
You.
Have you taken it?
Bingo!
What a waste of time!
Now you understand, don't you?
This is the real Ryouzuke!
No, no, no, Matoi!
I don't have any feelings!
But first, I have a treasure...
No, no, let's talk about it.
If we talk about it, I'm sure...
Goodbye!
Hey, open the door!
It's a misunderstanding!
Please!
Open the door!
This time, you didn't see me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see you.
No, no.
I've learned a lesson.
I won't date a man from Latin America ever again.
No, no.
You should have someone who suits you more than that man.
Will I be found?
You won't be found.
Because you are my grandson.
That's right.
All right, I'll do my best!
Matoi!
Let's talk about it again!
I love you!
Isn't it a listen-al  to look so realistic?
I love you so much
I love you!
I love you a lot, I love you so much!
stands up
I love you so much, I love you so much!
I love you so much!
I love you
I love you.
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black tile of the arcade
I saw
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgets
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt on top of his eyes
Turn around and see that corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall there, there must be a wall
Everyone come on
It's over
To the town of the city
Thank you!