"The Summer of the Year"
Ah, the summer of the year has come again!
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here!
It's a big, little, little, awesome boba!
Ah, the summer of the year has come again!
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, here, it's here!
It's a big, little, little, awesome boba!
The big, little, little, awesome boba!
Nagi - Sade
Purin-purin-purin-purin-purin-purin
Ah-Ah!
The wind blows south
Nagi - Sade
Purin-purlin-purin-purin
Megumin
Reiko's Wrath of Anger
Move!
The tomato has entered the million-spin red zone!
And now, it's time to power up to 2 million spins!
The reaction is a curve of 90 degrees!
This is scary! It's dangerous!
Stop at the corner once.
Look to the right and left to see if a car is coming.
And then check the safety.
Got it?
Run!
Don't jump out!
No!
It's okay.
If I'm late for my shift, Ryo-chan will be noisy.
Hey, Riko.
Hello. How's the old man's cold?
He's already feverish.
He'll be able to go to the store in 2 or 3 days.
It's hard for Grandma to do it alone.
I'm sorry, but take care of yourself.
Then, take care.
Wait.
I'm grateful to Reiko-chan who always cares about me.
It's business, but bring it.
Ah, um, I was told it was 12 o'clock, but I'm totally late.
Yes.
Ah, thank you very much.
She's a good girl, isn't she?
There aren't many good girls with such a good temper.
She's a good girl, and she's a special one.
I can't take her home with my wife.
Really?
Just a second.
Let's cross the road, Grandma.
Well, if we go around the street, there's a road sign.
There are many cars here, so it'll help us.
There's a signal here, so hold on.
Yes.
Hurry up!
Huh?
Please wait a moment.
Yes, yes.
What is it?
Well, um...
That old lady has waited a long time to cross this road.
If you can hold on for about 30 seconds...
Yes...
Thank you for your cooperation.
Oh, thank you very much.
Thank you so much!
No, I have to be careful.
That's great, Reiko-san.
Would you come here for a moment, please?
Eh?
Reiko-san, could you come this way.
I have a message for you.
Come back here tomorrow!
What's your problem?
hover
This is for a while every day.
It's in front of kindergarten, and children will get drunk with their car.
I'm careful many times, but I don't ask.
Isn't it the center of the street, Tsuzushi?
Please move the car with the handCard that is stopped in front of the kindergarten.
Speedy
"Captain's House"
So, we've been standing here.
We're at the repair shop nearby.
I think they're already here!
They said the same thing yesterday.
They're lying!
Here's your license.
Please forgive me.
I don't have any more points.
You're cute, "Captain's House"
I don't have a license.
I don't even have to move.
Do you understand?
Please forgive me.
Then, I'll give you a hand.
What's that?
It's supposed to be a bomb for jacking up.
If you raise the level to the maximum, it will swell up to anywhere.
On!
Hey!
Hey, idiot!
I don't know how to stop it.
Because it's my first time using it.
Oh, no!
Damn it!
What the hell!
Charge!
Sucker.
You've got the same color legs!
What?
How frightening!
These legs...
"I'm sorry, but I can't let this go."
"Of course. Pay the fine."
"Oh, no!"
"Welcome home."
"Ah."
"You're late!"
"Sorry, Ryo-chan."
"The time to change is 12 o'clock in the afternoon."
"It's past 1 o'clock."
"Hey, I'm a mess in this town."
"I'm a mess in this town."
"A patrol and my life, which matters?"
"Even if you want to change, you'd still be there at 11 o'clock."
"Today, Doctor Ohara isn't coming, so I'll try to stay the same."
"I'm going to the patrol!"
"Ah. You look hungry."
"You'll have to come back anytime."
I couldn't go out for lunch.
Don't boil the noodles too much.
Add more green onions.
It's not like I forgot the change time.
It was hard.
This and that, and now and then.
Reiko!
What's wrong, Ryo?
Take a picture of that newspaper.
Isn't it faster to take it yourself?
There are so many bad people out there.
They say it's a car accident, but it doesn't work at all.
They think it's a bad thing, and they just ignore it.
Take a look at your back.
Lower.
Not there.
There, there.
Push it.
That's it.
Like this?
No.
It doesn't work at all.
That's why I'm telling you.
That's why I'm being underestimated.
It doesn't matter.
What patrol needs is the power of the face.
Your face doesn't have the power of the face.
It's itchy.
Draw the bottom part.
Here?
Yes, yes.
Hey, is the noodles okay?
Don't boil it too much.
It's itchy again.
It hurts!
What are you doing?
The last one is the power of the face, right?
The last one.
What?
It's itchy.
I'll hit you with the second one.
I'll run away with the second one.
What's that?
It's the special pillow for hitting the Ryo-chan.
It's handmade.
What?
How's that?
Uncertainty.
Start attacking!
Be aware of the power of men!
Thatialic!
I fried you!
The match is just beginning.
Fight with your own power if you can't have strength!
Come on!
I got it!
I can take the hell!
It's over!
Wait! Wait!
What a hard-working woman!
Yes?
I saw the poster.
Huh? Who did you get it from?
It's Reiko, right?
Who are you?
Please go on a date with me.
Eh? Who are you?
Why do you have this number?
It was written on the poster.
What's that?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do with the poster.
It's a strange number.
Hello?
Is that Reiko?
Who are you?
Can we go to the beach together?
No, you can't.
Then, I can't?
You can go on your own.
What's this?
It's so annoying.
You don't even have to say my name.
Date?
Okay, let me borrow it.
Reiko?
Oh, right.
Are you applying for a date?
Yes.
Okay, first, I'll give you 5,000 yen as an introduction fee.
Don't say stupid things.
Or I'll arrest you.
Reiko.
Huh?
There are so many of these on the surface.
What's this?
The guys just now picked up the phone by looking at this.
What a terrible hidden photo.
Who put this here?
I took a lot of pictures, but it's still a mess around the national highway.
It's stuck on the wall.
It's a good one.
Reiko, what about this?
There's no way.
This is Naoko.
Answer me.
Hm?
I found a large dumpster.
It's following us.
It's heading north.
Please support it.
The driver was sticking a poster of Reiko.
Roger that.
I'll use scissors to cut it open.
It's so big.
It's Reiko's big dumpster.
I think it's Reiko's big dumpster.
Neither of them knows the signal.
That's great.
Reiko, they're taking it away.
Can you see it?
Hm?
Oh, I see that.
Hey, you're in a hurry, Ocho!
Huh? What's that, hey?
Watch out!
The End
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That's good.
Mira! I'm getting my hands on you!
Ouch! My back hurts too.
I won't forgive you!
Reiko, you're too rough!
Ouch!
Put on your seatbelt!
I'll report to the police.
I'm Ryotsu. I'm tracking the dump truck of Adachi Number.
The driver of that dump truck was on Reiko's poster.
Okay, let's go!
You guys go straight to Mid-Kaido!
Put on your seatbelt!
Ouch!
I won't let you get away!
Huh?
Ah! I found it!
Arrgh!
I found it!
It's just as they say.
What happened, Reiko?
Oh, come on, you guys.
We were about to lose the kids.
Besides,
why should I have any grudge against you?
I-I don't have any grudge against you.
Then why did you guys
stick these things all over the place?
Reiko!
Look over there.
It's them!
Them?
I found them!
You guys are coming, right?
I'll leave the rest to you!
Yes!
Hurry up, Ryoichi!
Arrgh!
It's the car that was parked in front of the kindergarten.
Those guys are illegal parking.
Anyway, it's a very bad car.
It's probably a natural monument.
What's going on here?
They're not just running around!
Shut up!
Hey!
Don't let them get away!
If that's the case,
we should have tried to kill you more thoroughly then!
Shut up!
It's Godot here!
Damn, what tough and stubborn!
What?!
My way of doing it is quite annoying.
That is indeed violent.
You dare drive me with a allowed car, just a few bucks.
If you have original deal, you should go back to my house.
That's right, that's right!
No more others!
Wait for us!
Calm down Reiko!
I get how you feel but the Mini Patto is a 550cc light car.
There's no way you can catch up with a 2000cc like that!
Hey! It's still following us!
It's not just a light car...
It's so fast that it can go that far with a light car!
Let's go into high speed.
That car can't go at high speed.
It's running away into high speed.
We can't catch up with it with this car.
This is Reiko.
Yes, this is Kamehameha Park.
Kei, I have a favor to ask of you.
I can't see anymore.
Hey, Reiko!
Oh no!
Hurry up and stop it!
Stop it!
Oh, here it is!
Oh, it's the Audi Quattro.
Sorry I'm late.
It just arrived yesterday.
This car won the Monte Carlo Rally.
I got it from the collector for free.
I'll borrow it then.
I didn't see it until now.
But it's coming after me.
Hey, maybe they're...
I'll see you later.
Go, go!
I'll be right there!
Oh.
What? What's wrong?
It's like a gas station.
I'm so frustrated!
What's the matter, Nakagawa?
You don't like gas and you're always full of it.
There's no gas station at high speed.
You're driving at high speed at high speed.
Look, you found no gas station!
Reiko.
Slow down.
I'll go for the car from the back.
What?
What are they doing?
Damn it!
I'm exhausted.
I can't reach it!
100 yen for 1 liter.
45 liters for 4510 yen!
Huh?
Great.
Reiko, pay me 4500 yen.
That's enough for fishing!
"That's enough"?
Does that mean you don't need it?
Alright! I'll take the fishing rod!
What is this?
Hurry up and give me the money!
-The fishing rod is... -Youji, hurry up and take it!
Give me the fishing rod!
My money!
I want the fishing rod!
It's here again!
I don't want it anymore!
Damn it!
My money!
Damn it, Presta!
You're too naive! Are you trying to escape?
Reiko, go! I'll forgive you!
Wait a minute!
The highway! Don't turn around!
You're too naive, Reiko!
Sakotan, it's too snowy!
How far can we climb with that car?
Stop it, Reiko!
No matter how many Audi cars there are,
the snow is too heavy!
The snow is too heavy!
I did it!
I got rid of the car!
Help me!
This is scary!
It's scary when a woman looks down, you know?
Let's not allow him to be the enemy, at all.
He may climb, but it won't be when we're impossible to take him down.
And no!
Stop it!
Don't make me stop!
The
Good morning!
I'm so exhausted.
Ehehe.
Good work.
What happened to those two?
They fell in love with Reiko's driving technique,
and they entered the test drive without permission.
I see.
It's been a while since I had such a terrible feeling.
I've had such a terrible feeling for a long time.
I hope you'll be careful about Reiko.
Okay?
Ryo-chan!
Did you call me?
Yes.
Here's your tea.
Thank you for your delicious tea, Reiko-san.
Thank you.
It's nice weather.
Be careful.
I know.
Oh, it's the old lady.
She's very kind.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Reiko-chan!
Oh, grandma.
What's wrong?
Actually, Reiko-chan has a good story.
What?
You're an old lady after all.
You're so old, grandma.
Hey,
if you marry her,
you'll meet a great man, right?
Yes.
Oh, my.
I wonder why you came here.
I already told you.
I've coming to your hospital.
I wanted to test your politeness.
I want to understand what you're thinking.
I'm a niob to you.
For a long time.
So you're a niob.
Emotions!
All right.
So let's go.
Shut your mouth.
Yes.
Nice to meet you!
Hey, please smile
You're not bad
You're in the same condition as before
Please always smile
The woman who is serious is not beautiful
You should smile right away
You're not a child