Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset floating in the middle of the river
I take off my love stone and fly to the end
I wonder if I'm going to be jogged
I was laughed at by the captain of the taiko
I'm fine anywhere
Even if I'm a man, I have no choice but to fight
The cityscape that doesn't change even if you are a devil is tender
The sun is already going down because the crows are crying
I'll take the yakitori
I'll take the beer
I wonder if I can enjoy this
I check the bill again
But the sunset is falling
Tomorrow will end as well
The year-end-thrills will also lose their happiness
I found it's just me who realized, eh
The Little Ryo-chan
Nice. I want to go back to being a kid and play with my friends.
Hey, Ryo-san!
Hey, Chief! I didn't skip school!
I want to make the world a better place!
You think you can fool me with your lies?
You idiot!
If you keep spilling oil here, you'll lose your salary!
Go back to work!
Okay!
I got a fever after running so fast. I can't take it anymore.
Help me!
A kid?
Kids are great.
They have a lot of toys to play with.
They don't have any bad bosses.
Don't say that, kid.
Ezaki! Don't show your face!
Calm down.
The fact that you're angry is proof that you're short on calcium.
Eat this stew and replenish your calcium.
Thank you very much!
So, what are you doing here?
This is a bad invention, isn't it?
This is an invention that was created for you.
It's a brilliant and wonderful invention that remains in the human market.
How hard have you been to buy this?
Stop looking at me and show me what you've got!
I see. What is this invention?
It's a pumpkin!
Is it candy?
Yes, it is.
If you're so young, you can say candy.
This is a brilliant and brilliant invention.
Hey, that's enough. How are you going to eat that candy?
It's just the first thing that comes to mind.
Let's see this.
Wow, the frog is weak!
And then, if it's a bird, it's like this!
It became an egg!
Now you understand?
This can make the one who licked it come back to life!
Which means, if the tiger eats it...
...it becomes a child.
How about that? This is a very, very, very revolutionary invention!
Give it to me! Give me that candy too!
I know! This invention is for adults like you.
Don't hesitate to lick it!
Now I can become a child again!
Huh?
Whoa! It's a child!
Of course! My invention is perfect!
I'm going to make a child's life a living hell!
That's awesome!
Hey! I want to be licked too!
Who are you?
It's okay, it's okay.
Here I go!
Wow!
I've never seen anything like that!
Okay, here I go again!
I'm a child, so I can take the train and the bus without any problems!
So, a child can also be a woman, right?
Yay!
I'm good at everything except for the job and my jobless boss!
Ryo!
Where's Ryo?
Why hasn't he come back?
Uncle Mooharam!
After getting so mad at me,
What's wrong?
Honda, did you see Ryo-tsu?
Hm?
Senpai?
No, I didn't see him.
That stupid guy.
Where is he selling oil?
There's no other way, chief.
Because it's Ryo-san.
What?
That's right.
You can't tell a bad person anything, right?
Hmm, Senpai's bad human-like attitude is full of money.
Let's give up on Senpai.
If you say so.
If you say so, that's true.
I'll just ignore it.
That's right.
Oh, chief.
I bought some delicious buns.
There are only five of them, so let's eat them secretly.
Oh, that sounds fun.
Then I'll put some tea in.
Those guys.
Don't think they'll just live like this.
Excuse me.
One kake-soba, special tempura soba, and oinari.
Three more croquettes.
It was delicious.
Right, papa?
Huh?
Oh.
Here.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for the meal.
How was it?
It was all 1,060 yen.
Huh?
What?
Did you pay the price?
No.
2,060 yen for the kake-soba and 3,080 yen for the special tempura soba.
With the oinari and croquettes.
W-Wait a minute.
Why did you have to pay for that girl?
What are you talking about?
She's your child, right?
What?
I'm satisfied.
All right.
The other guys are going to do the same.
Let's go!
What?
That's so annoying.
Come with me.
Wait for me.
The frog's head is moving!
What's wrong, Boku?
What are you doing?
It's a feast!
Hurry up and open the cat bowl!
I don't want to do this!
Plum, plum, plum!
That was fun!
Kids are the best!
Oh, the new house is open!
All right!
Yes, boy.
You can't let the kids in.
Hey! I'm not a kid!
I'm...
Oh, I see.
I was a kid then.
That means...
If I don't grow up,
I can't drink and play the pachinko?
Kids are more inconvenient than I thought.
Found you!
Boku, where are you from?
Can you come to the station?
You don't have to be afraid.
Two of us?
You know him?
He's kind of grumpy.
Everyone was seeing each other
through his mischief.
It's a mischief for kids,
but할 dad's mischief.
Now it's Ryozu, it's a nosy situation.
So, what's your name?
U-- Um...
Actually, my dad and my mom
are at work.
They haven't come home!
Well...
I was so lonely, so I did that. I'm really sorry.
It's okay. I didn't know that there was such a situation.
I'm sorry. I couldn't understand your feelings.
I'm disqualified from the police. It's pathetic!
Great success. All of them are good people, so they are weak in this kind of story.
Okay, I understand.
Let's stay at the escape room until our fathers come back.
That's right. Let's do that.
This is not lonely anymore.
The sisters are with us.
But what about the night?
Then I'll stay at my house at night.
What are you saying? I'll take care of this child.
No, it's me.
Me? You can be spoiled by thinking that your sister is your mother.
What?
No, it's me.
Then you can take care of it as a replacement.
I see. As expected of the chief.
These people are also good people.
Anyway, I'll let you stay here for today.
It's a small room, but I won't make you feel lonely.
Yes, yes.
Why do I have to go back to Nico Nico Ryo?
That bastard!
He's hesitating to make a speed change in front of me!
He's being fierce!
Stop! Don't stop!
Stop!
So you ended up going to the Noto Peninsula?
I'm sorry. I found a speed violation and my body moved on its own.
Poor thing.
Then let's go to my house tonight.
Really? Yay!
What is this?
Where is the house?
It's over there.
It's so big.
It's for your health.
If you rely on a car or a plane or any other useful tool, your body will get numb.
No way.
Let's run.
Let's sweat together.
Hey, wait!
I'll give you five hours today.
Five hours?
The wind feels good.
Wow, that was great!
I'm so tired.
Kei-chan, you can't do that.
I'm just a kid.
I was just so used to the place I wasn't aware of it.
I'm making sure that I'm OK.
I can't take it anymore.
I want to live in a normal house.
So tonight it's our turn.
After all, this is a normal house and we need to be safe.
So you can rest in peace.
Oh, yeah...
Are you okay? Be careful of your feet.
That's my line.
Don't step on it!
Please be careful of the open door.
I'm going to get a little in from this station, but please be patient.
What? Then what was it until now?
Can you ride more than this?
I'm used to it, but it's still hard for children.
It seems that only I am here.
Let's go to my sister's house from today.
Hmm...
I think I can do it easily.
Oh!
It's a normal room.
You can use it freely.
If you have something else, don't hesitate to go.
Yes, I understand.
All right.
I can live as good as I want here.
Hey, it's heavy.
Move away!
Oh, it's exposed.
Oh, Seara.
Were you there?
Seara is happy to have made friends.
No, it's not that.
Then,
Seara, please do you a favor.
Hey, wait a minute!
Uh, uh?
Uh-huh?
Uh ...
It's a butterfly.
Wait, wait.
Hmm...
It seems that he is mentally very tired.
What's wrong?
It's difficult. It's a young age.
That's right.
But what if she goes on like this, she'll be alone again.
Okay, then come to my house today.
Right?
No, I'll be nice and say no.
Oh, you know difficult words.
I've been wondering about it all along, but I've seen that face somewhere.
What are you saying, uncle? It's just my imagination.
I see.
As expected of the chief, he's sharp.
I have to be careful not to make a mess.
I'm home.
I'll be in your way.
Welcome.
I've prepared a room, so take your time.
Okay.
Eat a lot.
Looks delicious.
Thank you.
Home made food is the best.
Here's your change, madam.
Good morning.
What's wrong with her?
She's still sleeping.
What?
Get out.
Adopt a child as soon as possible.
Start radio exercise.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Come on, cheer up more.
Why am I doing this?
What is this?
Let's eat.
Idiot!
Before you eat, you should put your hands together and eat!
I-I'm sorry.
Don't get lost. You're being rude.
Yes.
It stinks.
Idiot!
You don't know how to use chopsticks.
Start practicing properly from today.
O-Okay.
I'm a customer.
Did you say something?
N-No.
Idiot!
Is there anyone who's been rolling around since noon?
Children, play outside!
O-Okay!
That's why I didn't want to go to the chief's house.
What?
I see. As expected of the chief.
Isn't it a little too strict?
Not a little. I don't want to go back to that house anymore.
Okay, I'm going home soon.
Idiot!
Oh, today is...
What are you talking about? Let's go.
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thinking about the things I did after I got home is so hard.
Hm?
Oh, a new item came in.
I have to go buy it now.
I'm so out of work right now.
Hm.
Hm?
It's food!
Oh, I'm hungry.
Hm?
Ah, ah.
I'll eat it.
Now, keep eating.
Y-Yes.
How is it? Is it good?
Yes.
I see, I see.
Now, keep eating.
Don't hold back.
Ah, ah.
Hmm, strange.
I suddenly changed my attitude.
Is it my imagination?
W-What?
I saw this earlier.
But why is it here?
Is that good?
Huh?
Um, wh-why?
Well, somehow.
What?
I-I don't know.
I can't believe it.
The manager bought me something.
Oh, oh, and there was a bath.
Um, can I come in with you?
What?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh, no, no.
Nothing.
Strange.
It's definitely strange.
Suddenly, you became so kind.
I'm sorry.
I was strict.
What?
When I look at you, I always remember Ryotsu.
Huh?
Ryotsu is my subordinate.
This is a useless guy.
His manners are not polite.
His attitude of living is also the worst.
If I leave you alone like this,
I'll become a bad adult like Ryotsu.
When I think about it, I've become strict.
Huh?
I-I can't get angry.
I'm not Ryotsu now.
But...
Huh?
But, after all, children are nice.
I have a daughter, but I don't have a son.
If I had a healthy son like you, I would have taught him various things.
Oh, I see.
That's what that face meant.
That's why you became strangely kind.
That's why you became like this.
You're not Ryotsu.
You're Ryotsu.
Uh, Ryotsu.
T-That means...
You're Ryotsu.
Ryotsu?
No, Ryotsu.
That's what he meant.
He's Ryotsu.
And he's Ryotsu.
Ryotsu!
I'll buy it for you.
Then, you'll need a radio, a plastic model, a game, a TV, a DVD...
Yeah, yeah...
And then, you'll need a bicycle, an air gun, and a new cell phone.
And then...
Oh, right! You'll need a computer.
Right, Dad?
Buy it, buy it...
What?
Ryo-tsu.
What are you talking about, Dad?
I'm not Ryo-tsu!
I'm your son!
When did you...
Did the candy effect go out?
I see.
So that child was you after all.
You see, there are various reasons for this.
All the causes are in the candy that I made!
Shut up, you idiot!
I'll take this!
You idiot!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, you idiot!
That's it, stop!
Stop, stop!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
You idiot!
Hey, stop!
Can I have a candy?
I'm a fish that bites the sand.
Jyugem Jyugem
I'm always wearing sandals.
I'm always a scandal.
Don't worry.
I play with a cool nail.
Everyday.
I threw it in the trash.
I'm just stupid.
I'm a good-for-nothing and poor.
I'm not poor.
I always try my own way.
How about that?
A single iron in a book.
I'm the oil.
I run around and escape.
I'm a Noel in a camel's head.
I'm in the middle of nowhere
and there's a ludicrous typhoon
and a precise round trip.
Ki-are-ri
I'm gonna come on and make you right down!
Jyugemujugem
Go-ko-no suriki-re
Gai-sari sui-gyo
Sui-gyo-matsu
Un-gyo-matsu
Gu-rai-matsu
Kuu-meru-tokoro-ni
Sumu-tokoro
Ya-mura-ko-ji
Mura-ko-ji
Paiko-paiko
Maiko-no-shu-rin-gan
Shu-rin-gan-no
Gu-rin-dai
Gu-rin-dai-no
Hon-po-po-ki-ro
Hon-po-ko-na-no
Cho-kyu-mei-no
Chousuke!
I love festivals!
When I hear festivals, I can't stand or stand!
I can't stand eating yakisoba with Mikoshi Katsui!
Hey, Lemon!
I'll teach you how to enjoy festivals!
Next time, "Memories of the Yatai"
Please watch!
"Kame-ari"