Hearsay
O- O- O- When you watch TV
Dry your hair and look away
In the middle of the river, gazing at the rising sun
The cityscape doesn't change a wink Love is strangely gentle
From Shu Sui-to, the place where you wear a hat,
The sun goes down to Taishakuten
The sun sets and the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
If I win, I'll lose happiness again
I lost it and I realized
Because I'm a fool
Wow, Honda-san!
What happened?
Alright, it's done. What's wrong, Honda?
Senpai...
The plastic... Damn, it took three days!
Hey, Honda, thanks to you, the result...
Senpai...
What?
You're so mean, Ryo-chan.
You can't make me cry just because that toy is broken, right?
What? Is it my fault?
Alright, stop crying.
What? You can make something like this again.
No, Nana-chan...
What? Otohime Nana?
Speaking of Otohime Nana, she's Honda-san's girlfriend.
She was a famous girl manga artist with the pen name Aino Miko, right?
You don't have to explain it so well. Everyone knows.
So, what happened to Otohime Nana?
She hasn't been seeing me for a while, and she hasn't called me.
Honda, cry with all your heart.
Senpai...
Everything is over. Give up.
No...
Ryo-chan, it's so sad to make such a decision.
That's right.
It's a common pattern, right?
You have a new boyfriend.
Don't cry.
How was the two of you recently?
Even if it's something I think of...
It was two weeks ago that I met you.
I bet you did something you hated at that time.
That's not true.
It was just a normal date.
Didn't you try to kiss her out of the blue?
Ryo-chan...
I didn't do that.
At first, I went to see a movie.
After that, I took the Tokyo Bay Aqua Line by bike.
In the middle, I ate soft cream by a firefly.
On my way back, I had a meal at the family restaurant and sent it to her apartment.
You don't seem to hate anyone.
Rather, we're a lovely couple.
Hmm...
Don't you have any other reason?
Okay, I'll ask the editor who was in charge of Otohime.
Hyo Ryusenshi?
Yes, that's her.
I'll ask her.
Let's ask her.
Here.
Hey, copy this.
I don't need this.
You have a good writing skill.
Yeah.
Then, I'll do it.
Huh?
You two...
Yeah.
Actually, Miko is in a slump now.
She couldn't figure out the direction of the new series that was scheduled to start next week.
And she didn't call me.
What?
That means...
That's good, Honda.
She hasn't been dumped yet.
Yeah.
That's not good.
Huh?
Miko is an important time as a manga artist.
I don't know what her future will be like.
Huh?
As a girl manga artist, this is the boy's version.
We editors use our nerves quite a lot.
Being dumped by him,
or a pet caught a cold,
or having a lover,
or having a crush on someone,
his mental state affects the work.
I see.
Editors are also difficult.
Speaking of editors,
everyone here seems to have jumped out of the boy's manga.
Yeah.
It's the editorial department of the boy's manga.
The editorial department of the boy's manga is completely different.
By the way,
this is a photo of when I was in Young Dandy,
when I was in charge of the boy's flower road.
The author of the former Boso tribe,
Mr. Takenaka, took this photo.
It looks like a friend of the same tribe.
What's his name?
How do you read it?
Bari Bari?
It's written in gold,
and you read it in gold.
It's Bari Bari King.
I see.
And this is a photo and a name
that I took with Mr. Ero-kichi Ogeretsu
when I was in the Eros Heaven.
What?
Ogeretsu Ero-kichi is a big fan.
I like that pervert look.
What kind of face does he have?
It's the pervert look as in the manga.
But if you match it up to here...
What's his name?
It's easy to understand.
Is he a pervert with no sense of purpose?
And now,
this is Hyo Ryu,
in charge of Aino Miko.
It's a relationship
since she debuted in the third grade.
It's a long relationship
than the Honda.
There are many cases
where the editor in charge
and the girl cartoonist
get married on the street.
Don't say such a bad thing,
Senpai.
Don't worry about that.
Miko is a great help to Mr. Honda.
When Mr. Honda confessed to her,
her name became faster.
And the heroine
got a sense of motivation.
You bastard!
No way.
So,
I would like to ask you
to help Miko
to get over her slump.
If you don't put her in the printing house,
she will be in a real trouble.
No!
I can't do it!
It's not like that.
It's okay.
Hey,
Nanachan,
don't cry.
What kind of manga
are you trying to write?
This time,
to open the new possibility
of the girl manga,
we are focusing on
the friendship between men.
The friendship between men?
Miko,
what's wrong?
I can't draw the scene
the friendship
between men.
What?
Is that so?
Ryouchi,
can you help me?
Yes, sir.
I'll leave it to you.
How is it?
Hey,
stop it!
I don't need to stop
the friendship between men.
Right, Miko?
Yes,
but
not just hitting,
but also
dropping your heels.
I see.
Drop your heels.
Okay.
How is it?
Like this?
No.
It's like a shrimp.
I'm screwed.
No.
How is it?
Exciting.
Just like I said last time.
If you fancy it,
you can do like
rock, paper, scissors,
one,
2.
3.
4.
Five,
It's better to fall.
Don't call me a fool!
Alright.
It's alright.
With your strength, this height is fine.
What are you talking about?
You'll find out how to calculate what's alright!
Hmm. Falling is impossible after all.
Yeah.
Ah, I fell down myself.
Hey, help me.
Help me.
I see.
You ride like that too?
Yeah.
It's really helpful.
Nana-chan, you can't see around you if you get into the world of your work.
Damn.
Nobody came to help after all.
See?
I was okay after all.
Don't copy everyone.
Ryo-tsu-senpai saved me.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'm not immortal either.
Senpai, are you okay?
I'm not okay!
It's so hard to write a manga.
What's wrong this time?
To make sure that men are friends,
I'm going to make a scene where they hug each other.
There's no such thing as friendship!
Yes!
It's the proof of the beautiful friendship between men.
It's absolutely necessary.
You don't have to cry, Miko.
There are two men here.
They'll do it.
Yeah.
Idiot! What are you saying?
Senpai!
Let's do it!
Calm down, Honda!
Miko's life as a manga artist is over?
It's your fault.
Eh...
Senpai!
No, stop it! Stop it!
Put your hands on your waist and your cheeks closer.
Smile.
Yeah.
Ah, okay.
What's this time, Miko?
The police uniform doesn't match my image.
What?
Senpai, it's for Nana-chan.
Let's do it!
Hey, stop it.
No!
Let me do it, Senpai!
Let me do it!
What?
You told me to do it.
I'll do it when it's done.
I'm sorry.
Senpai!
No!
I can't do this.
I don't have the talent.
No, you don't.
The model is too ugly.
What?
I'm not kidding.
You're not wearing this because you like it.
You bastard!
It's not because of Miko.
I'm sorry.
I'll go outside for a moment.
What?
I told you.
I'm a girl cartoonist.
I'm a delicate.
What should I do?
I don't have time.
There's a hole in the manuscript.
It's not our fault.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
I can't ask anyone else for help.
Senpai, I was mistaken.
You can't make excuses.
Hey, how many pages is that manuscript?
It's 30 pages.
What?
30 pages?
I can write in 30 minutes.
One page, one minute.
What?
Really?
Senpai is quick to do anything.
If it's true, I want you to write 30 pages.
Right now.
Instead, I'll take the manuscript.
That's...
All right, bring the paper and ink.
Yes.
I can't write on the stairs.
I can't write on the desk without a draft.
All right, it's done.
Here you are.
Wow, this is...
It's a masterpiece, right?
Senpai, you have a talent for manga.
It's too bad.
But maybe readers will think it's an illusion.
All right, let's go.
I did it!
I'm a manga artist's debut.
Ta-da! Robodeca!
Saku, Ryozu, Patricia, Kanco.
I have a masterpiece.
I'll buy it for 1 billion yen.
Wait, Senpai.
Oh, Robodeca!
It's over.
Robodeca appears!
What?
Go, Robodeca!
It's small.
It's not scary.
Gusha!
Gyafun!
Is this the manga Ryo-chan wrote?
Robodeca?
That's the real deal.
The manga is full of big eyes and stars.
It looks fresh and wild.
I don't see it as wild and wild.
I can only see it as a hand-picked drawing.
I can only see it as a bad and dirty drawing.
The viewer will know how good it is.
I wonder.
There's ink stains everywhere.
I drew it in 30 minutes.
I didn't have time to think about it.
But I think it's better to draw with my hands.
Ryo-chan!
Yeah?
What's wrong?
Ryo-chan, I did it!
He said he was a teacher.
That manga got 3rd place in the reader's survey!
What? Really?
Well, it's a natural result.
I didn't expect it to be this good.
I can't believe it.
This kind of manga...
I didn't have enough gag, so I gave it to the reader.
The reader was impressed.
Please give it to me next week.
You see, I'm busy.
You can't help it.
Please.
Wait a minute.
I have a lot of work to do in a month.
Please.
I'll double the amount.
No, I don't care about the amount.
It's the official duty to help ordinary citizens in trouble.
Please write.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well then, I'll report to the editor-in-chief right away.
Don't forget to give me some when you come again!
Understood!
Isn't that amazing, Ryo-san?
You're one of the most popular manga artists!
Well, it's obvious from my ability.
If you're able to publish comics, you'll be rich in debt!
Comics?
It's about the comic book.
There are also comics that have been published for 1 million copies in the first half of the year.
How much is the tax on 1 million copies?
Well, one comic book is 390 yen,
and the copyright rate is about 10%,
so it's about 39 million yen.
39 million yen?
For just one comic book?
Yes, of course, it's a popular manga that people all over Japan know about.
Good! Let's go to the editor-in-chief right away and ask him to publish 1 million copies of the comic book!
Yes!
Ah!
Senior!
Ah, it's gone.
If it's like that, even if you stop it, it won't work.
Oh, Mr. Honda, you've been quiet for a while.
Well...
This is it! Here!
Hmm?
Eh?
Nana-chan, are you going to take a break?
Nana-chan...
What?
You want me to publish a 1 million-publish comic book with a special limit?
Yes!
If you have three days left on the remaining pages, you can do it!
Don't be stupid.
Can you suddenly publish 1 million copies of a new person?
Because my manga is third in the popular vote!
It will definitely sell!
I think it was just a rare thing.
That's not true!
Next is third to second!
From that next, you should get the first place of the bid!
I'm kidding!
This world is not so sweet.
What?
I've been in this world for 25 years, but when I saw it, this manga will be much more popular from the next time.
Then what if you get first place in the next time?
That's impossible!
Then if you get first place, you'll get 1 million copies of my comic book!
That's great!
If you can do it, try it.
This person is a hard joke!
All right! I made a promise!
Good!
Ryusei, come here!
Yeah...
How do you take a survey?
It's a survey postcard.
You can take a survey postcard of your favorite manga or manga artist.
You collect the number of postcards sent from all over the country and collect the data.
Every time, you will put out the popularity ranking of the work.
This popularity ranking determines the winner.
So the ratings of the TV are almost the same.
I see.
You mean the number is the power.
Look at this.
Oh, right!
I came to the editorial department.
I'll write a novel for next week here.
What?
Well...
All right! This is fine.
What?
I'll borrow a pen.
All right! It's perfect!
What a person!
Please help me!
Do you have a weekly Sapphire?
I'll take it all.
But you have to pay for it.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Welcome.
Do you have a weekly Sapphire?
What?
I'll take it all.
All right.
Please! Please!
Good luck.
General, hurry up!
The more you do it, the more you'll get paid.
Good luck!
But Ryotsu, is it really all right?
Don't worry.
If you have a million comics, even if it doesn't sell, you can get a tax.
Really?
Yes.
That's why you should be on the big board.
Yes!
Now the first place in the survey is certain.
What?
The first place in the survey for the Robodeca class?
I can't believe it.
I have overwhelming support.
Idiot.
All my readers are fools.
That's rude.
My manga was such a masterpiece.
Do you have a weekly Sapphire?
Yes.
This is the first place...
What do you mean by the first place?
I'm sorry.
It's a matter of principle.
As promised, I'll get you a million copies right now.
But a million copies for this?
It's a common sense as an editor.
It's a promise.
All right.
A million copies of the comic book?
That's right.
Ryo, you did it.
Now you have a lot of money.
I'll take the 3,900,000 yen tax.
Hahaha.
I was wrong.
I'm here again.
I bought Nana's favorite cake.
Nana.
Oh?
Mr. Honda.
What's wrong with everyone?
He asked me to leave.
I can't work here.
I see.
Since I'm here,
Mr. Honda.
Nana.
What's wrong?
I can't.
I can't believe it's the new serial.
I've never had a genius idea.
Nana.
Have you been riding a bike lately?
Let's fly a bike once in a while and change the mood.
I'll go with you.
Mr. Honda.
You don't have to worry about a bike rider.
What?
Hahaha.
Nana.
You can't go with me.
He's gone.
You're right.
I'm going to the police station.
OK.
Mr. Honda.
You can leave now.
I'll be waiting.
Nana.
But you look different when you're thinking about manga with a difficult face.
Really?
I guess it's because I like bikes.
Um, why did you like bikes?
Me?
That was when I was in high school.
I was suddenly in a bad mood while I was bringing a manuscript to the editorial office.
Then, a rider who happened to pass by brought me to the hospital.
The rider at that time was like a prince riding on a white horse.
Hmm, I feel the same way...
Ah!
That rider didn't put a shooting mark on his helmet.
Eh?
Come to think of it...
He did!
The location is near Tamagawa in Kawasaki.
It's a little in front of the vending machine.
Yeah, why?
Why do you say that?
Oh, is that...
Honda-san?
Hmm...
What?
No, he used to be a good rider.
Even so, he was Nana-chan.
Honda-san and I were destined to meet God.
Yeah, to the God of Bikes.
Hahaha.
Hey, Nana-chan.
Next new year's festival,
how about you draw your favorite bike world?
Bike world?
Yeah.
Bike world...
Thank you very much, Honda-san.
Then, I feel I can draw something.
Really?
That's good.
I'm a big fan of Aino Miko-chan's manga.
This is Nana-chan's new year's festival.
Finally, an idea has come up.
Thanks to you.
To have a white horse appear in a girl's manga,
If that happens,
it'll surely be a mistake.
You're so naive.
How true.
I've passed the first task,
like the one given by Robotical President.
Come on!
Stop!
Say good-bye!
Hey, you...
There's a book.
It's so expensive
that it's like lost in a lost.
What?
Don't worry about it.
Stop!
No!
-The End-
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
Once I put it out, the money will be mine!
Ryotsu!
Pay the money for the manga and the money for the sketchbook.
I know, Ryo. How much is it?
The manga I bought costs 7,500,000 yen for 300,000 copies.
300,000 copies for 500,000 yen, that's 1,500,000 yen!
And the part-time wage we hired is 5 million yen.
So it's 9,500,000 yen in total!
So the total is 5,600,000 yen.
5,600,000 yen!
Don't run!
I need to remember my business!
I'm done with my tax life!
"The End"
♪ Even at midnight, I get up ♩
♪ If you're here, ♩
♪ Even the boring story will warm ♩
♪ Everything in me ♩
♪ Even if my hands get hot ♩
♪ I wish to see my friends ♩
♪ It's for sure that I want to be loved ♩
♪ The more people say, I fall ♩
♪ The more I want to melt ♩
I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not! I'm not