Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
When you watch TV
Make sure the room is bright and look away
Hello, goodbye
Goodbye, goodbye
If you live just for the night
You'll be home soon
Don't panic
In this small town
Where are you going?
Hurry up and turn around
Maybe
You're a better person
Than me
If there's someone
Let me hear it
Let me hear it all night
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
Da, da, da, da, da, da
I don't hate waiting
Because I'm a woman on a camel's back
I don't want to lose
I'm a woman on a camel's back
I've loved you
I'm in love
I'm a woman on a camel's back
It's no good!
There are three of them in the village!
Help!
Help me!
"The Greatest Shinkai SOS"
Hey, Ryotsu!
You ate shaved ice during work, didn't you?
No, not at all!
Then, show me your tongue.
Huh?
What?
Look. Your tongue is green.
What? You idiot!
Do your work seriously.
It hurts. I keep getting bad comments.
Your tongue is too green.
What's wrong with you?
You ate shaved ice with three people just now!
Reiko,
show me your tongue.
What?
It's not colored.
We ate ice strawberries.
They're normal strawberries.
You're so dirty.
Ryo,
Why do you eat shaved ice every time?
Huh?
Ryo,
I'm poor since I was small.
I've been attracted to shaved ice since I was little.
Really?
Yes.
I've been spoiled by poverty.
When I ate shaved ice when I was young
I was the cheapest ice water expert.
What is ice water?
It's sugar syrup.
It's colorless.
Did they have such a thing?
Sugar water is like a beetle.
It was a great era.
So I always ate ice melon.
This is all because of poverty.
I wonder if there's any money in the bank.
What?
A treasure worth 20 billion yen?
The Shuin Line that sank in the Edo period was full of gold.
It's been a long time since the place where the Ogasawara River sank.
It's a bit romantic.
It's like a 10,000-meter-long sea.
20 billion yen?
I'm a fast learner, but I can't do it in the 10,000-meter-long sea.
Well?
What's this?
Dear people.
The sea is beautiful.
Professor Ezaki?
Isn't it you?
I'm moving around on a railroad, and I don't want to be spotted.
Where is the sea in the Tentacles?
You need to know that the sea is the source of all life.
It's the source of life. Even if there is no sea in front of you, you can hear the sound of saltwater if you close your eyes.
The sea is the home of humanity.
Apparently, he did everything in the world and now he is in the sea.
That's right.
Oh, no. It's time for tea.
The man of the sea drinks only small tea.
Why does small tea belong to the man of the sea?
I don't know.
So I have a question for you, Gorilla.
How many percent of the total area of the Earth is the sea?
What does that look like and what does that question have to do with it?
Well, I think 70% of the Earth is the sea.
That's Nakagawa-kun!
To be precise, 70.8% is the sea.
2.42 times the land area is the sea.
So what?
What the hell are you talking about?
The man of the sea must understand the sea.
The flat seabed around the land area,
the part that suddenly falls into the deep sea from the coast to the ocean,
what do you call it?
It's the continent.
Then what is this?
You're not looking at the Ancho-go, are you?
Anyway, our future cannot be told without the sea.
You're overreacting.
That's why, Gorilla-kun,
you need your unbiased vitality.
What are you talking about?
It seems you've finally got to the point.
Let me be frank with you.
This is the invention of Professor Korosuke Ezaki.
I will give you the honor of wearing the first suit of the deep sea!
Deep sea suit?
That's right.
The deep sea suit I invented can move freely even at a sea level of more than 10,000 meters.
I hope you like it.
Your name is Mr. Kankichi Goro.
Gorilla can be written down in history as Ryotsu.
Stop using the middle name Gorilla!
I'm not joking.
It's not funny.
I've thought you were doing something terrible with your invention.
You're already a Gorilla.
Oh, nice joke.
Gorilla-kun is already a Gorilla.
Let's go to the sea.
I told you I don't like it.
You don't understand.
Wait a minute.
Could it be that the deep sea suit is...
Is it?
This is the story.
Ah, I like the sea.
I'm glad you took a break.
The chief and Mr. Torai will be in trouble.
What can I do?
I'll have a 200 billion yen coin when I get home.
I'll tell you what, I'll go and get it myself.
I won't ask you for a single penny.
If we get caught by Ryo-chan, the sea romance will be a profit.
It's okay, I won't get it.
He's saying that, but he's expecting a lot.
Oh, sea, the sea is so wide.
Oh, the sea is my hometown, isn't it wonderful?
Right, Aodaisho-kun?
Aodaisho?
I'm thinking of a series of Aodaisho by Yuzo Kayama.
Tanaka Kunie, from the north, did the rival Aodaisho.
I thought it was Shinji Maki from the Ukulele Band.
But Ryo-chan, it doesn't feel like Aodaisho at all.
Then let's do this.
Because I'm a gorilla in the sea, I'll call you Sea Gorilla-kun.
You have no sense of naming at all.
It's tea time.
Hmm, I don't think it's a good idea to call you Sea Gorilla.
I think a tropical drink would suit you well.
The man from the sea wasn't a turtle, was he?
Anyway, Senpai, it's about time for the Tsunbo-tsuji Line.
Hmm, it seems that we're the best.
As expected of the high-speed line in Nakagawa.
Hey, you crazy beast.
Hey, Ezaki.
Ezaki Korosuke.
Maybe I should call you Wakadai-sho?
You can't do that.
Hmm, what a good-for-nothing guy.
He's pretty good at it.
Well, it can't be helped.
Hey, Wakadai-sho!
Hmm? You read it, Sea Gorilla-kun?
As expected.
Senpai said he wanted to start experimenting with suits soon.
I thought so, too.
Let's start experimenting.
This is the new suit I invented.
It's called 8823-1.
This is just a suit.
I'm a waiter at the Ryugu Castle.
Don't worry.
The fabric of the suit is waterproof even in heavy rain.
You can't get drenched in this!
It's a joke.
I don't know how serious you are.
Then, let's start over.
This is the new suit I invented.
It's 8823-2.
It's like a snowman.
If you dive about 10 meters deep, the water pressure increases by one volume.
That is to say, the water pressure increases by 1,000 kilometers.
The water pressure is 1 ton per centimeter square meter.
Even 1 ton?
The water pressure is prevented by this suit 8823-2.
Even if its shape is like a snowman, its function is wonderful.
That one looks great.
Ryo-chan, it suits you.
I'm not lying.
But this is really heavy and difficult to move.
Yeah, because it weighs 20 tons.
20 tons?
I'm going to fall!
It's okay. It's got a weight on the bottom, so it won't fall.
Wow, that's funny!
Hey, stop it already!
I have to get up!
I'm tired.
Don't you have a better idea?
Don't worry.
I'm going to make sure I get this one right this time.
Shinkai Suit 8823-35!
It's a real one!
Oh, it's a real one.
This is going to be a real dive.
Of course!
If you have one, get it out of the hole!
This is going to be easy to move.
It's like a space suit.
The unknown deep sea is the same as the universe.
It's mysterious.
This 8823-35 is designed to withstand the water pressure of 10,000 meters.
It should be.
Hey, wait!
What do you mean "should be"?
It should be.
You must have done a water pressure experiment.
It was my bath.
Don't compare a bath with 10,000 meters!
Umigori Runa, you shouldn't be saying such a funny thing.
Look at that!
Huh?
It's the official investigation team's ship from the newspaper.
Oh no!
We're going to be left behind!
Two billion! Two billion!
Stand by, OK!
Now, please, Umigori Runa!
I wonder if he's going to be okay.
Yeah.
According to the data we've used, it should be okay even at 20,000 meters.
Really?
It's going to be okay.
If anything happens to him, he'll be back alive.
I'm nervous.
7,800...
8,000...
Hey, hey!
Are you really going to be okay?
This...
Oh!
It's a sea fish!
It's only a sea fish, isn't it, Umigori Runa?
Don't be so silly!
Your suit is going to be torn apart!
Haha!
It's going to be okay!
Maybe.
Hey, don't say maybe!
The water pressure is at 9,800 meters.
It's about time to get to the bottom, Senior!
Ryo, can't you see anything?
I can't see anything yet!
Ah!
Ugh!
Ryo, what's wrong?
It seems that it's arrived at the bottom of the sea.
Yes!
It's a success!
Is there any water leaking somewhere?
Is the heart moving?
Of course!
How about the sinkhole?
Can you see around you?
Sinkhole?
Well...
That's strange.
I can't see anything like that.
What?
What's wrong, Senior?
What is that?
Be careful.
It may be an unknown creature living in the deep sea.
Unknown creature?
What should I do?
Okay.
I'll just shut up and let it eat me.
If I do that, I'll be sure it's a creature.
Don't joke around at a time like this!
Ugh!
It's coming over here!
Stop it!
I won't be good at eating!
Go over there!
Sh! Sh!
Ah!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Just watch me!
What!?
It's the furthest thing in the area!
Hey, watch me!
There's only a few left!
Don't give up on it!
You're definitely the strongest one!
I can't be too quick!
I can't take it anymore!
It's scary!
Why was the aradama there?
Come on!
Use this knife!
*Bang!*
AAAAAAHHHHH!
-S-Senpai! -Ryo-chan!
Umigurira-kun! What happened? Answer me, Umigurira-kun!
*Bang!*
This was so close...
Who is this unknown creature?!
It's the Unmanned Survey Team!
But it even has a missile in it...
It seems that you've seen me again, Umigurira-kun.
By the way, the blue button is a self-destruction device.
Where are those idiots who self-destruct at the bottom of the ocean?
I found it! It's a submarine!
The explosion just now showed that it was buried in the sand of the sea.
It's all calculated.
You did it, Ryo-chan.
Then, let's find the treasure!
Let's go!
This was taken before the video of the unmanned survey ship was cut off.
What's this?
It looks like a creature, but it's actually a human or a gorilla.
But it's a 10,000-meter deep sea.
Perhaps this is a great discovery of the century.
This mysterious creature is called the Underworld Genjin.
Let's investigate thoroughly!
Understood.
All right, let's get off the survey ship!
I'm going, too!
Roger that!
To be continued
That's right.
It's a long-standing submarine.
With this, a million gold coins will be mine!
Gold coins, gold coins!
Ouch!
Ryo-chan, what's wrong?
Ouch! I tumbled!
No! You tumbled!
Nice joke!
Joke!
Don't laugh! It's echoing in the suit!
No, no, no!
Who told you to find something like that?
It's the Gold Coast! The Gold Coast!
I know that without you telling me!
Gold Coast!
Gold Coast! Where are you?
Two billion yen!
What's this?
Gold Coast!
I found it! It's the Gold Coast!
You did it, Gorilla!
It's the Gold Coast!
You can't carry it all at once.
This is the romance of a man in the sea.
I'll pack it in my backpack as much as I can.
I see. It's a backpack.
My hand won't reach its back!
Crap!
There's a blood vessel in its structure!
Ouch! My arm!
Ouch!
It's a miscarriage.
All right.
I thought I'd finally get one out.
Now it's time for this Magic Hand!
It's so slippery that it's hard to grab it!
This is the Tsunbo Line.
Doctor, shall we start the investigation?
The Gold Coast worth two billion yen won't run away.
First, we need to find the Underworld.
Yes, sir!
If we can capture the Underworld alive,
we can make a world-wide discovery.
It might be the Nobel Prize.
This is the New Underworld!
Damn it! It's worth two billion yen!
Where are you, Underworld Genjin?
See, see! You're a good boy, Genjin-chan!
What's going on?
Something seems to have jumped on this ship!
No way! It's the Underworld Genjin!
What do you think, you bastard?
Da... Da... Da...
Wh... Wh... Wh... Wa...
P... P... P...
Damn it! What a brutal guy!
Drop it!
Roger!
Huh!?
What a Society-Gun, huh?
This is easy to get down easily!
W... Where's the Underworld Genjin?
Wh... Where's the Underworld Genjin?
C... Can't be! It's the Underworld Genjin!
Hurry and catch it!
Conversely, after the group is captured,
a capture wire will be fired.
And then...
ч…
...
Hey, what are you doing?
Let go of me!
Oh no! Ryo-chan's...
Ume Goryera-kun, press the button on your arm.
This can't be a self-destruction operation!
No! Hurry!
This is...
What's this?
It's a diamond cutter. There's no way it's a wire!
Alright!
Ah, the wire's been cut!
No, it's going to escape!
I-I can't do anything about that!
You're doing a great job, huh?
I'll pay you back this time!
What's this?
It's a floating body! A floating body! Hurry!
Look at this!
My butt's shaking!
Slowly, slowly!
You're going to be surprised!
It's gone.
As expected of you, senpai. You're really good.
Alright, Ume Goryera-kun.
With all the money you have, you're going to be a floating body.
I'll get it!
You got it?
Yeah!
With all this money!
Now I'm a rich little man, too!
For the sake of the whole world!
With all the money, I'm going to have my paradise!
Ah ha ha ha!
Ryo-chan!
There's something coming near!
Be careful!
What? About what?
Where?
It's there, Ryo-chan!
W-wait, you idiot!
No good...
But he hasn't bathed in a week!
You're so unruly, you shark!
I'll kill you!
I can't stand this guy!
Hey, get me out of here!
What a troublesome guy!
Get him!
Professor, we have to get him out of here!
I know, but this is a full speed!
Senpai!
Idiot! Don't bite me like that!
Ryo-chan, what's wrong? Ryo-chan, Ryo-chan!
The cable's out!
Senpai!
Hey, the gold is heavy and it's sinking!
If I don't throw it away, I'll die!
No, I can't!
For the sake of gold, I'll definitely take this thing home!
Hey, here he comes again!
The persistent guy!
Huh?
Hehehe, just watch!
Hehehe, it's a great idea, just like Professor Tondemo's idea!
Huh? What's going on?
10 seconds until the self-destruction!
That's the self-destruct device!
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
That's why I said I didn't want to hear Professor Tondemo's invention!
4, 3, 2, 1!
Open!
AHHH!
Senpai!
Ryo-chan!
The Sea Gorilla was self-destructing…
N-no way…
Ryo-chan…
WHY?!
Why?!
WHY!?
WHY?!
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You're safe, right?
Of course!
I'm glad. I was worried.
You got the treasure, but you can't die here.
Then, what about the gold?
I might not get 2 billion, but I'll bring it as much as I can.
I can't believe it. It's a miracle of the sea.
Hey, hey, don't take it without permission. I took this gold with my life.
No way!
This is all mine. Okay?
Let's go home.
It's a happy ending this time.
Yahoo! I'm rich now!
What? That gold was all fake?
Yes. It was just a gold paint.
A few years ago, a ship used for a movie was sunk near there.
The gold and the skull were also small tools for the movie.
No way!
Then, what about my hard work?
What's going to happen?
It's going to be a disaster, Sea Gorilla.
What's going to happen next, Super Beast?
This is it! The submarine engine has been discovered!
We should go back to the sea to capture this thing.
Professor Ezaki, no matter what you think...
Isn't it Ryo-chan?
What?
Super Beast, I'm in a bad mood right now.
Who's the sea? I'm never going to go!
What about us?
No way!
What?
To be continued...
Next Episode
Episode 4
Episode 5
Episode 6
Episode 7
Episode 8
Episode 9
Episode 11
Episode 12
♪ How much do they reflect in your eyes? ♪
♪ After a fight, you always ♪
♪ give me a kiss ♪
♪ You were so dear to me ♪
♪ when I was crying ♪
♪ How much can people get ♪
♪ from something that can't be replaced? ♪
♪ You are me ♪
♪ I am you ♪
♪ That's all I needed to satisfy me ♪
♪ Just by laughing at you ♪
♪ I felt that I was healed ♪
♪ from all the pain ♪
Who the hell are you, Matsukichi?
You're so cold, Ryo.
Don't you remember me?
You're the bad boy from a long time ago.
That's the great youth practice now.
It doesn't seem like it.
Next time on "Work, Matsukichi!"
Thanks for watching!