"Tick! Tick!"
♪ I gaze at that day ♪
♪ Which floats within me ♪
♪ As I pounce on theะ stone ♪
♪ I fly up to my shoes ♪
From the water of the Tunganiposhi
To the Taishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness at Katsushikashiba
I realized that I was stupid
Well, I want something sweet for tea
Well, I'll try it
Ryo-san, you are a great digger
Later
Great luck
It was good
Ryo-san, I'll send you the patrol
Great luck
ryo-san
Ryo-san
I want something sweet
It was in the kitchen. Do you know what a daifuku is?
Huh? I don't know what a daifuku is.
Really?
I really don't know what it is.
What happened?
I kept it in the kitchen. My daifuku is gone.
No, I haven't eaten it.
I don't know either.
That means...
I can't eat it.
Chief, try to say "Ee".
What?
Not "Ee". Say "Ee" like this.
Why would I do that?
Is there a reason why you can't do it?
No, there isn't.
Say "Ee".
I'll crush you. I'll crush you.
The culprit is you, chief!
Chief!
You're so dirty.
You ate the daifuku that the subordinates were looking forward to.
Is that what you're doing?
The chief will take care of all the food in the kitchen.
If you leave a piece of food,
you'll eat it all.
That's the way humanity works.
I can't believe it.
As a human being.
You don't have to say that.
I can't believe it. As a human being.
That's right.
That daifuku is what Reiko bought.
That's right. It's not Ryo's.
I'm so excited.
In the end, you used all the money.
And you have nothing to eat.
That's the usual pattern.
You're so rude.
If I had that daifuku, I could eat it all day.
I could eat it for three days.
But you have nothing to eat.
It was worth 10,000 yen to me.
That's what the部長...
Ah it's the director...
In the end, the manager ate it all.
I thought it was only the director.
I don't know what to believe anymore.
I know.
Daifuku, you have to cheer.
Daifuku ...
I don't know.
After all, this is...
It's not far enough to have three daifuku in one day.
It will not heal my heart.
Usually, the chief always says that he thinks about his subordinates.
But this is completely different.
I wonder if it is okay for someone who thinks about his subordinates to raise his subordinates.
I understand.
I will pay you 10,000 yen for a car.
Really, chief?
Yes.
However, I don't have any cash here.
Why?
It's about you.
If you give me cash, I will use it for fun again.
You can say that.
That's your usual pattern.
Then how can you pay me 10,000 yen?
That's it.
The world's food is free to eat?
I will pay you 10,000 yen for the admission fee.
I can talk to you.
Chief, let's go.
Wait.
Look here.
5 days until the opening.
This is the famous Skyville 50.
It's crowded today.
Everyone is looking for Sky Vikings.
By the way, where is Ryo-tsu?
He is too hungry to walk.
So he said he would come by his motorcycle.
I'm here.
Ryo-tsu's husband.
Ouch.
I'm too hungry.
You are so annoying.
I want to go to the car.
Let's go.
My body has terrible health when I have only water for 5 days.
For the sake of today,
I will eat 10,000 yen for 10,000 yen.
Pay me dearly.
10,000 yen.
Right.
What do you say for 10,000 yen?
I can't pay, but I will pay you 10,000 yen and 635 yen
It would be a small price for a daily meal fee,
What? This isn't enough?
What a shame, Ryotsu.
I said I would give you exactly 10,000 yen.
How disgusting.
Where is the 10,000 yen limit?
Here you go.
Now I can eat the cost of consumption.
I will eat the cost of consumption.
I have it. I have it.
Stop it, you idiot.
It's disgusting.
But you managed to get all these dishes.
I'm so happy.
I've never eaten anything like this.
All the famous dishes from all over the world are on this floor.
There is no time limit.
Please enjoy your meal.
It's delicious.
This looks tasty.
Ryotsu!
Eat the things that look tasty even if you push people away.
This is my skill.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's a disaster!
That's quite a lot.
Of course. It's a waste of time to go get it at this hour.
There's no time limit.
Yeah. If we keep on going, we might get eaten by someone.
It's not a human trick.
Well, let's get going.
Senpai, can you go to the bathroom with me?
What? You're not going alone. You're like a woman.
Please. It's too big and confusing.
Right, Senpai?
Yeah, I know.
No, I sent you here.
Right, Senpai?
I can't help it.
But good things don't go away quickly in the viking world.
I'm your assistant.
Hurry up and do it.
One more plate.
What?
Who is it? It's impossible!
I can't do it.
Hurry up and let all the people in the building escape!
Got it.
Everyone, please calm down and listen.
An emergency has occurred in the building.
An emergency?
We've received a call from the fire station on the 35th floor.
A fire station?
Why is there such a thing?
We're not worried about it right now.
But please think about what you're doing.
Please leave the food as it is and stay calm and evacuate.
It's become a big deal.
Let's cooperate and lead the evacuation.
Everyone, hurry up and do it.
Please act calmly.
Please hurry up and go to the elevator.
Don't rush.
We have time.
Stay calm.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
You're late.
I ate two plates.
Go back.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Let's finish this together.
Thank you all for your help.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Now, this elevator will be closed.
What?
It's a fire station.
I didn't see you and Mr. Honda there.
Yeah, they ran away to Ino market.
If they come, I'll be in trouble.
With the food in front of us?
We can't do this! Run!
Damn it!
Let's get out of here!
Let's!
What?
What's wrong with this building?
It's like a maze.
Senpai, it's this way.
Hurry! The food will be gone!
If it's gone, it's your fault!
You should've prepared for that!
What?
No one's here.
Did everyone leave?
It's true.
Whatever.
It's just a matter of time.
Let's eat!
Yay! We can eat anything!
-Let's eat! -Let's eat!
Come on!
"The
-The
is gone.-
He's nowhere.
So he's still in there.
Man were you there?
Yeah, I did.
Eat more of these expensive things like caviar and foie gras!
Yes, sir.
Don't you think it's a bit disgusting?
That's right.
You're doing an attraction outside, aren't you?
Maybe.
You're so noisy at such a good time for a meal.
Hello?
Ryotsu!
I'm surprised. Are you alright?
What happened to you? You left early.
Listen, Ryotsu. Listen carefully.
A fire broke out on the 35th floor of this building.
The building is on fire!
What?
Wait, Ryotsu.
You're not getting in my way.
You're not lying!
Ryotsu.
I paid 635 yen.
I'll eat a full 100,000 yen bill and go home.
You're going to be surprised.
It's really fire!
You're the ones who are left in the building.
You're the only two left.
Everyone has already evacuated.
I'm scared, Ryotsu.
I'm going to be a yakitori.
Don't be afraid.
Listen to me.
We can't use the elevator anymore.
We're waiting here until we get out of here.
Got it, Ryotsu?
You can't act on your own!
I'm trapped!
Don't be angry, Honda!
This is disgusting!
Wait a minute!
Where are you going, Ryotsu?
Don't leave me!
I'm the one who's leaving!
I'll take care of the fire extinguisher first.
Turn off the fire extinguisher.
Come on, get in here.
In the meantime, I'll have a meal.
You're going to eat again in this state?
I came here to eat a full 100,000 yen.
I paid 635 yen.
I'll eat no matter what!
A live broadcast from the site of the fire.
There are two more people inside.
Oh, I just caught two people.
They're eating!
He's crazy.
Ryotsu, you're eating with a smile on your face.
You're the same as everyone else.
Raoh!
What's going on?
What's that explosion?
The gas station on the second floor exploded.
Why is there such a thing in the building?
I'm so mad at the electrical system.
Damn it!
It's burning! It's burning!
The fire is getting faster and faster.
Eat it quickly!
I can't eat it!
If you eat it, you'll die.
It's running!
The fire is already starting.
Don't make a fuss over it!
We're safe here anyway.
Hey, hey!
calm down calm down
Don't move!
It's not good to eat with a calm mind.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to remember this
No way!
Come on!
Help me, quick!
We'll be done in a few minutes.
We simmered for a good bit.
Not good...
There's no firewood!
Is there anything at the kitchen?
Oh, there's something good.
Honda, bring the soup!
All right, it's a waste of time, but we can save the fire.
Three!
Idiot! That's oil!
I don't care anymore!
Are you still eating?
Hey, Ryotsu, do you hear me?
The rescue helicopter is heading to the roof.
There is a emergency staircase in the kitchen.
You should be able to get out of there.
Go straight ahead!
Oh, no!
I don't want to eat anymore.
If this happens, I'll take the whole thing with me.
Let's leave the food and run away!
Shut up!
Here?
Oh, no! The fire!
What? We're breaking through the barrier!
Let's go!
Wait a minute!
The dessert for the consumption tax...
Let's get out of here!
Are you all all right?
Who is this?
Are you all right?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
I forgot to tell you, but there is a firework show in the roof.
Be careful!
Why are they all here?
Mario Intensifies
Mario Continues
Don't get any closer!
Just shoot there!
Huh?
We've driven all the way to here!
Are we leaving this in there?
Hurry up!
I've had it with this!
Are you going to carry it?
I'm a child.
Cabrio in pocket.
Escalbo in pants.
All right, that's exactly what I need.
100,000 yen!
You're going to jump off like that?
I can't do it.
All right, Honda, go ahead!
Yeah!
What?
You've got to speed it up!
How dare you!!!
I'm in trouble!
I call the shots!
No, stop!
The wash machine is over there.
It's not that tough.
Let's get out of here.
Ryo!
We'll get it.
I'll do it.
I'm stuck.
But it's heavy.
I'll cut it.
Throw away the food.
No, I can't do that.
I can't carry so much food.
You can't be human in a place like this.
Are you going to die for food?
I'll get you!
No!
No, no, no!
I can't!
I'm sorry.
He changed the table cross to a parachute!
As expected of you, Senpai. You're not human!
I'm sorry.
Senpai!
I'm so frustrated.
The Escargot and the Lobster...
I brought them all, but they all got broken.
I haven't even eaten a 10,000 yen bill yet.
I heard that food is more important to him than life.
Please give me money again.
Take me to the Viking.
I don't care, you idiot!
What?
Gunter!
Hey, Shiratori Reiji!
You were impressed by your father,
and became a super poor man, weren't you?
Did you invite Reiko to a date again?
French cuisine, you say?
I'll go with you.
Next time on "Saitoujo Shiratori Race."
I'm counting on you!
Please subscribe to my channel.
Yui
I'm the one who has so much love
I want to run on a bike through the vast desert
I want to be free more than a bird
A lady's dream that changes with the speed of a full moon
I'm sorry, wait for me
The future of the panorama is so bright
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me
Translated by Releska