"Miyako's Room"
When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away.
Those who have no money, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I hope you'll be able to do something about them.
When you have no job,
make your room bright and look away.
Those who have no money, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
Look at the red clouds.
I hope you'll be able to do something about them.
I know, I know, I know.
If you know, then come to me quietly!
If you don't know, then follow me!
If you don't know, then follow me carefully!
"Giri and Ninjo's Little Hexing"
Caw, Caw, Caw!!
Go Go Go!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear?
This is the place we first blocked, so I'm telling you to go somewhere else.
What?
It's a lie.
I've been staying here for three days.
I just went to the bathroom in the afternoon.
I just liked it for a moment.
Fuku-e and the others got on it.
What? That newspaper was not garbage?
What?
That's what he said.
Ryo-tsu.
The park above is wide, so you can go anywhere.
That's right. Why are you so particular about this place?
I can only think that you are being a nuisance.
I've been here since you guys were taking baths.
I've decided that I'll do it here.
No!
What?
Ryo-tsu, you can't.
Give up here and go somewhere else.
You're too late.
Take a look!
The flowers are already in bloom.
What's left is...
I'll do anything and everything here.
Danko Soshi!
Yeah!
If you want to do that, I have an idea.
Let me see.
What's he thinking?
There's no doubt it is something bad.
It's not good.
If it's needed support Bul uda.
Stay here until the non- Kate геро lines stand out.
Is he going to run away?
That means he's not having a drink or a snack.
He'll get it delivered here.
Nakagawa!
You're fighting a bad team again, Senpai.
Nakagawa doesn't understand my frustration.
If they make a fuss, I think they'll get through their selfish demands.
So I can't help it.
Anyway, my parents spoiled me and raised me.
I think it's a different story.
I'm at your house.
I got a drink and snacks.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Yeah, it's a usual thing. Don't worry about it.
Senpai, the baby is crying.
Baby?
What are you doing, Dad?
What did you come here for?
Hey, that's not it.
Don't touch Chiyoko with your dirty hands.
Chiyoko is Kinjirou's daughter.
Why is Chiyoko here?
Oh, she gave birth to a baby at your brother's place.
At the wedding of the lawyer's daughter who was taken care of by Kinjirou,
I took care of Chiyoko today.
Where did your mother go?
If your sister-in-law asks for a lunch box of Hanami, she'll be back soon.
You should have gone to the delivery room.
You shouldn't have said that.
Hey, wake up.
Oh, you're so noisy.
I'll be back soon when I deliver the Hanami lunch box to Sasaki-san.
Please take care of Chiyoko for a while.
Huh? Chiyoko?
I see. You took care of her from Kinjirou's place.
It would be a big deal if you took her out and made her catch a cold.
Please take care of her.
Grandma is going out, Chiyoko.
Bye-bye.
Wow, it's so warm.
She was sleeping quietly until a while ago, but I'm sure she's not sick.
It's warm, but not really.
Be strong, Kankichi.
Are you a policeman?
Maybe the blanket is wet.
It's warm.
Kankichi, which one is better?
Whichever is fine, so hurry up and deliver it.
Chiyoko will catch a cold.
That's a big deal.
I've changed my mind about it.
I forgot about that long ago.
And I didn't have to wear this kind of hair in the past.
It's easy to do it now.
You're so stubborn.
Idiot!
Don't use dirty words in front of Chiyoko.
Which one is dirty?
What?
No, I was laughing.
No, I thought she was a parent.
Is she a parent?
She's not a parent.
What?
What's wrong, Chiyoko?
You must have been surprised because the two of you had a fight.
Kankichi.
We're both parents.
Oh, no.
If you don't get along with each other, Chiyoko won't stop crying forever.
I can't help it.
Let's take a break and pretend to be friends.
What?
You're laughing too, Kankichi.
Look, Chiyoko.
Grandpa and Kankichi are close.
You're treated differently than when I was a kid.
I don't know if I should punch a bad kid like you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know who you're talking about.
What?
You have to raise a girl carefully.
He's serious.
It's too hot and too cold.
Here, Chiyoko, it's your meal.
Oh, my God.
He's a bad uncle.
Here, I made you a meal.
So, it's not that spicy.
You're going to be a great meal.
It's more important to keep up your English with Kinjirou and Keigo-san.
I'll teach you how to play the violin, and how to make tea or flowers.
Okay, Chiyoko?
Your grandchild is funny, isn't it?
He was a child who liked to drink sake and was famous for fighting, but he'snym on the other hand.
He's his first child, so I know he wouldn't hurt.
He'll hurt.
I thought you were a cute kid.
Senpai.
I was raised by someone who was so sweet.
Come on.
Is there something wrong?
I'm just thinking about it.
You're quick-witted, Senpai.
It's said that the soul of a honeybee is up to 100.
From now on, you have to be sure that you don't do anything bad.
Hey, Kakichi. What are you going to do?
It's okay. I'm not as sweet as my grandpa.
I'm not as sweet as my grandpa.
Senpai, you don't know what you're talking about when you say that at the end of the day.
I'm going to be quick-witted.
You can't say that.
You're being so sweet even though you're a baby.
I'm going to be quick-witted.
It's cute.
It's so cute that it's hard to make sense of.
How was it? Was it fun, Chiyoko?
It was fun, wasn't it?
Damn.
It's a pity that I was beaten like a baby.
I hope you don't have to resist.
Senpai, I've always been telling you to leave it to cute things.
Well, I'm going to go back to the dressing room.
If you're going to say that, leave it to long things.
Sorry for calling you while I was sleeping.
Oh, you should show your face to Hanami.
I'm going over there at five.
Yes.
But are you okay, senpai?
Your father is alone.
I'm going to go home by myself.
Even if it's just a little, I'm sure your mother will come back by then.
Listen to me, Yone-san.
I ate all the food I had secretly for the sake of time.
That's a story I've heard somewhere.
Tenryu, originally, it was my money.
No matter what you use, you can't complain about it.
You should apologize honestly here.
What are you going to do about your promise to your grandchild?
Chiyoko?
I promised my grandchild to buy him a bicycle.
You two talk a lot.
Well, it's about time.
It's not just that, Yone-san.
Is there anything else?
Yes.
It's about time.
Nineoe!
Damn it! I miscalculated the wind!
Is everyone okay?
Are you okay?
Are the enemies still fighting?
Aren't you stupid?
Don't stand behind me!
Oh, this year's also going to be good.
Ladies, please open the door.
What are you doing, old man?
Don't you have a cell phone?
I don't have such a thing.
I have a TV remote control.
I can't use it to my satisfaction.
That's right, Chiyoko.
I told you I'd be back soon.
Oh, it's been two or three hours.
Kankichi, you have work, don't you?
I'll take care of Chiyoko, so you can go.
I'm worried about my father alone, so I can't go.
Mom, please wait a minute.
It's my father.
Sen-dagi's Matsuda.
Hey, hey.
Masa.
Long time no see.
Oh, no, nothing at all.
All right.
That's a terrible story.
Are you doing it again?
Yes, that's an urgent matter.
I really want to join it.
I'm sorry.
What's Sendagi no Matsu?
An old friend of mine.
I owe him a life a long time ago.
You owe him a life?
Ouch!
Kankichi was about the age of Chiyoko.
I was a bit too young,
so I had a fight with a street kid.
Take this!
Take it!
Sorry.
What's your name?
That was Sendagi no Matsu.
I've never heard of that.
I was just making you worry.
I never told Yone about it.
I heard that Sendagi no Matsu is now involved in a dangerous story.
A dangerous story?
So that call was to ask for help from your father?
Yes.
Really?
He owes you a life.
If I go, I'll be sorry if I don't.
I'm sorry.
Even your cute granddaughter
might never let go of your love.
I can't live with that...
That's right.
You're getting old,
and so you have to jump into the fire.
I owe you one thing.
Honestly,
this is a long time ago.
It's a personal hice.
What?
When did you become so unreasonable!?
Beg your pardon!
I told you that I'm not going!
Ouch!
Look, I put it on you and you fell asleep.
Hey, where are you going with that?
If you measure the size of a person, you can measure the size of a man.
Chiyoko, forgive my stupid grandpa.
I wanted to see your bride.
Are you serious?
Dad, Chiyoko, time!
Wait, dad!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Don't worry.
I was so excited that I suddenly felt better.
When I see Chiyoko's face, I feel determined.
That's why I can't get over it.
I'm just thinking that form is crazy because it can't be moved.
I know you are reliable.
Wow, this is nice.
He is great.
Hey, he is cute, isn't he?
Yeah, he is.
Thanks.
Next Episode
those girls are out of their minds!
Danco Shishu!
We're gonna win!
Yeah!
Once we talk, we will.
If you talk.
Let's go!
Formation X!
Watch out, Grandpa!
Alright,
just like imposters,
let's do this!
Oh Старый,
you guys really again up here,
If Senpai doesn't come, I'm afraid I'll be out of my mind.
That's why I'm so desperate.
What? You can't come?
No, Senpai.
I'm going.
I'm going, so you guys have to hold on a little longer.
Go, Kankichi.
Huh?
You have an important job to protect the citizens.
You can't let me waste my time instead of chasing you.
Is he that dangerous?
That Sendaki Matsu needs help.
He's a big deal.
Huh?
I'll leave Chiyoko to you.
Come back soon, Kankichi.
Senpai!
Senpai, please come back soon!
Damn it!
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I got involved in a fight with my husband.
Huh?
Chiyoko?
You!
What are you doing with your blood?
Where did you go?
Wait, man!
What are you going to do with your mother?
Are you going to leave her alone?
Yone...
You're going to leave her alone and go after her?
Yone should understand.
I know.
I have to go.
She's been taking care of me for years.
She'll laugh at my last selfishness.
Don't joke!
I won't forgive her even if my mother forgives me.
If she leaves me alone, I'll never forgive myself.
Chiyoko, take care of your parents.
Dad, the locker is open.
What?
Kankichi!
That's the right side.
You're a good-for-nothing.
You can't replace me.
I can't replace you.
Dad, you're worried about Chiyoko.
What?
What is it?
You're waiting for me, aren't you?
You have your own fight, don't you?
Kankichi!
What?
Senpai!
Ryotsu!
SOS!
What?
Ah!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Honda.
Forgive me, Bulbosakonji.
This is the only parent high school that one can become.
Let's go clean up, Dad.
Kankichi...
Kankichi
Good luck!
After all it was a deal.
Huh? Ueno's forest is a man's grave.
Ueno? Sakura? Is this Ueno Park?
Yeah.
What a nuisance!
I thought I could drink under that cherry tree for the first time in a long time.
You're pathetic.
Masan!
Oh, Ginji. So you came.
I'll return your old gratitude.
Who's your opponent?
Who is it?
This person is Sendagi no Matsu.
Senpai, you came after all.
Honda, tell them it's a foul to scratch with your nails.
I can't get it with the tactics of the Kisei.
You guys did a good job.
It can't be helped.
Sendagi no Matsu's enemy,
that is, our...
enemy!
You're so persistent.
Why don't you give up?
A dangerous story about the source of life being involved in the story of the flower viewing.
Well, it was good that we both sacrificed our lives.
Masu.
This is Kankichi of Segaru.
This is the first child of this child.
Please take good care of him.
Oh, is that so?
Don't mess with me!
Hey, Chiyoko, you were surprised.
Look at this!
Baby?
Really?
Cute. Whose baby?
Is it...
No, it's my brother Kinjiro's baby.
That's right. It's cute.
What does it mean?
May I hug you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hmm.
There's no helping it.
I'll let you see the flowers together here with Chiyoko-chan.
Oh!
Yes!
Cheers!
Oh!
What a good thing.
I was hugged by a pretty sister.
Oh!
It's an old grandpa's tatami shop.
Oh yeah.
If you leave it to me, I'll replace the tatami mats of the White House with new ones every day!
Really?
As long as there are tatami mats in the White House!
Well, if there's a day like this...
You!
Ah, that's good.
Chiyoko is safe.
You're worried, aren't you?
If we go back, there's no one else here.
I got a call from the office and I put it on Senpai's phone, but it didn't connect.
I thought I might be able to get her here.
Hmm...
Geez, you're so bored of taking Chinomigo around, aren't you?
Mm, geez!
What's wrong?
I wanted to show Chiyoko the first cherry blossoms I'd ever seen!
No, I shouldn't have.
Hey, do you want me to give you a ride?
Oh, well...
I'm sorry.
Mmm...
You won't see Chiyoko around for a moment.
Chiyoko, I'm sorry.
Also...
It's okay.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take you to Senpai's home town again.
No, don't go there, Senpai!
Senpai!
I walked
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a proud face
A blue aunt above your eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
Everyone, everyone
I can meet everyone
Let's go!
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Why did I draw this?
Moreover, the president has been announced only today
I'm sitting in the studio
The inside is non-cooperative
The temple is inactive
I have to erase the graffiti quickly
It will be a big deal
Next time, erase the graffiti
Thank you
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!