Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you watch TV, ♪
♪ make sure to keep your room bright and keep your distance! ♪
♪ Hello, and goodbye. ♪
♪ If you live just a night, you'll be home soon. ♪
♪ Don't panic. ♪
♪ In this small town, ♪
♪ where are you going? ♪
♪ Hurry up and turn around. ♪
♪ Maybe, ♪
♪ there's someone better than me. ♪
♪ If you're here, ♪
♪ let me hear it. ♪
♪ Let me hear it all night. ♪
♪ I don't hate waiting. ♪
♪ Because I'm a Kameza woman. ♪
♪ I don't want to lose. ♪
♪ I'm a Ginza woman. ♪
♪ I've loved you for a thousand years. ♪
♪ I'm a Kameza woman. ♪
Stradivari! The Great Chaser
Stradivari! The Great Chase
The Great Chase
Here it is!
The world's best violin magician, Michelangelo Gandini, has arrived!
Gandini is the first to arrive as part of the world tour.
Is this Reiko's teacher?
Yes, he has been teaching personal lessons for 7 years since he was 5 years old in Paris.
He taught personal lessons for 7 years.
He is very popular.
I am surprised that there is such a person who is interested in violin in Japan.
There are many young fans of classical music.
I can only hear the lullaby.
He always smiles like this, but his lessons were tough.
He is always busy with 4 hours a day.
Oh, he is invited to today's party.
Is that so?
Actually, I also know him.
He will attend this party.
Our company will be a power for him next time.
It is a 100-person party, right?
Only 100 people from Japan are invited, but two people from our restaurant will also attend.
It seems that only very close people except the staff are invited.
Of course, there will be something that you can't eat often.
All right!
Take me with you.
I will give you an invitation.
Thank you very much for coming!
You can dive into this place even the Kurobeukuu dates.
I'm okay with it, but please wear a backstable and tie.
Please do not make a fuss.
I know.
Do not treat me as a child.
6 hours later.
The 2nd day.
Finished!
10 hours.
Please go home.
The End
I'm so happy!
That was a wonderful performance, Ryo-chan!
If you don't use that famous Stradivarius like your own body,
you won't be able to make that sound!
If you eat too much, your stomach will stick out.
What are you talking about?
It's Stradivarius!
It's about the violin that you have!
Is that Stradivarius that amazing?
It's Stradivarius!
It's the world's best instrument!
If you use Stradivarius,
if you use Stradivarius,
it's worth 300 million yen, right?
What?
That's too much, Ryo-chan!
Does that Dodecadene cost 300 million yen?
It's Stradivarius!
From the 17th century to the 18th century,
in the Cremona region of Italy,
Antonio Stradivarius was the most famous violinist
in the world!
Antonio Stradivarius is the most famous violinist
I don't know anyone who's not interested in violin.
But no matter how good the instrument is,
it's a treasure if you don't have the skills
Mr. Gandini is the world's best.
Hm,
you're a different person from us.
You're a different person from us.
Oh,
I'm sorry.
Reiko-kun!
Mr. Gandini!
You've grown so big!
Please let me down!
You were this small when I taught you.
No, it wasn't like that.
You're a generous teacher.
Hm? Are you friends?
Yes.
I'm Nakagawa.
My father often hears about you.
Oh, Mr. Ryuichiro.
Nice to meet you.
And this is...
My senpai.
Oh, senpai! Nice to meet you!
N-No!
I'm not a senpai!
Well, whatever.
Ugh, I ate too much.
Senpai, you ate too much.
Hey, Ryo-chan, Kei-chan!
I'm in trouble.
Mr. Gandini wants to see you in Japan.
You're in trouble?
But you have a lot of schedules.
That's right. What should I do?
I don't know.
I thought the world we live in was completely different.
But I can talk to you.
All right! I'll let you go!
What? Let you go?
Don't panic.
That's strange.
I heard a voice.
What are you going to do, senpai?
Don't be afraid!
I'll go to the elevator at once!
Yes!
Now! Let's go!
Senpai!
Nakagawa, open the door!
All right, it went well.
But what are we going to do now?
If you want to see the lower town, you have to go to Asakusa!
You can find this place at Asakusa.
It's near Asakusa, right?
Yes.
Eh?
Where?
Ah, is that so?
I'll take you to Bamu-jutsu.
I knew this place before I got here.
He's so loud, president!
Uh... Manager, are you listening to something?
When I realized, he was already gone.
He didn't go back to the hotel room, either.
Oh no! We have to hurry and find the Tokyo Beast!
If anything happens, it'll be bad!
Yes, sir!
Oh, this Tsukudani is the best!
What an interesting foreigner!
I can taste the taste of a girl's Tsukudani.
This foreigner is a good boy!
Of course not!
A girl's Tsukudani? Is this a girl's Tsukudani?
Oh, no, no!
A girl is a girl!
An old girl is a old woman!
Okay?
Oh, yes!
I'm scared because you're pretty good at this.
Mr. G, are you here?
What? You're the three brothers from the G-san Comic Band, aren't you?
Oh, you guys are doing music, too?
Everyone, come over here and let's drink!
Oh, that's great, Mr. G!
I'll get in your way, Mr. G.
Oh, good! Come on, come on!
Here, Gomi!
I don't know what "resistance" is.
♪ The boy's shoes ♪
♪ Geku-gui ♪
♪ Sleepy ♪
♪ My favorite kimono ♪
♪ Geku-gui ♪
♪ Chokirou ♪
♪ In the same place ♪
♪ Choki Choki Chokin ga dale suki ♪
♪ Chokimone ga dale suki chakarimono ♪
♪ San poo ♪
♪ Chi-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa ♪
♪ Chokimone ga dale suki chakarimono ♪
♪ Gakkarui Genkimono ♪
♪ Daikittou Please Gokorokkirou ♪
All three will be together!
♪ Jakken03 Kyoudai ♪
Bravo! Bravo!
He's kinda happy with that.
Oh, this is the best part!
It's like a child.
"I'm so happy!"
"Yay! I'm hungry!"
"I'm hungry!"
"The world's best violinist..."
"I want to play the guitar!"
"This is no more."
"To be able to fit into the atmosphere of a town like this..."
"Here, here..."
"Mmm... It's morning..."
"Oh no! I have work in Osaka today!"
"Hey, wake up! Gusuke! Wake up!"
"I'm still sleepy..."
"Wake up! If you're late, you'll never be able to speak again!"
"Hey, we won't make it in time!"
"Hurry, hurry!"
"Hey, Reiko, last night was fun!"
"Yes, but teacher, is today's concert okay?"
"Hahaha, don't worry about it!"
"What's wrong?"
"No, this isn't my violin!"
"What?!"
"Huh?!"
"What?!
"What?! It's not a 300 million yen Miso Hibari!"
"It's a Stradivarius, senpai!"
"Oh, I get it, I get it!"
"So, is it really wrong? Where's the difference?"
"The Stradivarius is the same as my body!"
"I can tell right away!"
"But, the difference is..."
"The three Janken brothers, Pakichi-san,"
"Mistakenly brought the Stradivarius!"
"Oh, no! I have to do something!"
"Hey, wake up, dad! Wake up!"
"Hmm, I'm sorry."
"It's not about the sake. Do you know where the two old ladies went?"
"Hmm, hmm..."
"I think they have work in Osaka today."
"Osaka?!" "Osaka?!"
"I have to get it back quickly!"
"The concert starts at 4 o'clock!"
"Don't worry! I'll get it back for sure!"
"Let's go!" "Yes!"
"Ah, damn it! I'm late!"
"What should we do, Ryo-chan?"
"Nakagawa, it's a helicopter!"
"Call a helicopter!" "Yes!"
"We're counting on you, senpai!"
"Ryo-chan, please!"
"Hm!"
"We're going to catch the Shinkansen!" "Yes!"
"Yes!"
"Ah, damn it! I'm late! I'm late!"
"Ah, damn it! I'm late!"
"Okay, then let's go to the venue with Master Gandini!"
"Okay, then let's go to the venue with Master Gandini!" "Yes!"
"I'll be waiting for you!"
"Alright! There!"
"Let's go!"
"Yes!"
"I'll be waiting for you!"
"Easy! Slowly!"
"Slowly down!"
"Hmph!"
"I'll be waiting for you!"
"Damn, the river is in the way!"
"Huh?"
"Aaah!"
"Alright!"
"Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!"
"Damn!"
"Aaah!"
"Aaaaah!"
"Hmph!"
"I'm falling, Maruken!"
"Huh?"
"Ah, it hurts!"
"Hey, good job, Gipper!"
"Wake up!"
"Damn, I can't wake up because I'm so sleepy!"
"Hmm..."
"Aaah! Hey, it's me, Paki..."
"Aaaah!"
"Ugh, it's almost time..."
"Well, I'm relieved."
"The teacher came back and..."
"If you're going to the teacher's place, you should tell him that."
He's trying to improve his concentration before the concert.
That's right. Please be quiet.
Yes, sir. We will head over there.
We don't have much time left.
I wonder if Ryo-chan will make it in time.
Hi-Hai-Hai...
Rebay!
Yeah!
Yes, sir!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Aaaaah!
Ouch!
Alright, you're doing well today.
Next time, we'll go higher.
Alright, leave it to me.
Aaaaah!
That's the Stradivarius!
What are you doing?
What's wrong, Kuga?
Why are you so quiet?
N-Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Then, until the day we meet again,
Rock, paper, scissors!
Huh? What's wrong?
The sound is strange.
I think it's broken.
I think there's a workshop nearby.
Let's take a look.
Aaaaah!
Where did it go?
Amazing.
It's been an hour since we started.
That's right.
For the time being, we can't listen to the teacher's performance live.
What's Ryo-chan doing?
It's not calm to wait quietly.
I think it's not having fun yet.
But, even so, it's too good.
Being able to be balanced even at a time like this.
Yeah.
Shit,
where the hell did they go?
I found you!
Hey!
Buncha keeper!
You think they'll come back?
That's the only lot that I got this month.
It's been a long time since I came to the festival.
Haru, look at this number of violins.
Huh?
The violin boom is good on the second day of Gandhi's reign.
But if there's a business like this, it won't end in a year.
Well, that's what the owner says.
Don't say that. Look at it.
I won't.
I don't know much about part-time jobs.
The owner is also going out.
I see.
The sound is different than usual.
Did I get hit by a
I finally caught up.
Why?
Isn't it Kankichi?
You guys, that violin!
It's a mess!
I didn't know which one was which.
What's wrong, Kankichi?
You're in such a hurry.
It's not like this.
I'm not in a hurry.
It's 300 million yen!
What happened to 300 million yen?
You guys made a mistake in the violin you brought.
You guys are this.
That violin is worth 300 million yen.
It's a Stradivarius.
What did you say?
Stradivarius?
Which one is that?
Is there anyone who knows?
It's impossible.
Huh?
Just looking at it doesn't change my violin.
I don't know.
You'll know by the sound.
It's impossible for us to hear it.
Kankichi!
What do we do?
We don't have time anymore!
It's time for the concert.
Sensei.
Sensei, it's about time.
That's...
It's a little inconvenient...
Sensei, that's...
Sensei!
You're not sleeping?
What are you doing?
Reiko, isn't it time for the concert?
But the Stradivarius...
Yes?
Oh, Sensei!
Is it from Ryo?
Where are you now?
Where is the Stradivarius?
The Stradivarius has returned!
Yes!
Anyway, come outside!
Eh? Outside?
Sensei, come outside!
Outside?
Eh?
Where is the Stradivarius?
Huh?
Look!
Nagaga! Reiko!
There should be a Stradivarius in here!
Oh!
The Stradivarius...
Where is the Stradivarius?
Saio, where are you!
You're looking for the Stradivarius from all over!
If we check everything, it'll take us a lot longer.
It can't be helped!
I don't know what to do.
Sensei...
Everyone's waiting for my performance.
But from inside...
?
Hey, hey! You're an amateur, so you don't have to be so lazy to choose!
Hmph...
Thank you for waiting.
We will now begin the violin solo concert by Michelangelo Gandini, the magician of the violin.
I can't believe I chose Stradivarius! My journey is over!
Stradivarius
This is...
Stradivarius!
Do you understand?
There's no doubt about it.
Stradivarius
Teacher, that was a wonderful performance!
Indeed!
I was able to hear the world's best Stradivarius sound.
But you just randomly picked the violin.
You knew it so well.
It was a coincidence.
A coincidence.
After a glance, the teacher understood.
Because Stradivarius is a part of the teacher's body.
Reiko-kun, Mr.Nakagawa, Senpai, thank you for everything.
I'll come back next year. Ciao!
See you!
Senpai! I'm looking forward to a girl's violin!
He said a girl's violin, not a girl's violin.
Take care!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ If you carry your luggage ♩
♪ both your hands will be free ♩
♪ If you can support someone with your hands ♩
♪ I wonder how wonderful it is ♩
♪ It's such a great feeling. ♩
♪ This is what I want to give you. ♩
♪ It's so great. ♩
♪ It's my great feeling. ♩
Oii! who do you think you are?
Why does it look like me?
Why are you so fast?
And why are there so many of you?
Next time, "SF Aliens' Revenge"
Why? Tell us!