Baby Yumi
Lash on a nude that floats in the river
After kicking up a love stone, it goes up to the feet
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I used to do
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
Katsushika Kameari
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn
It's strangely gentle
From the water fountain of Tongari-boshi
The sunset falls to the Kaishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
Katsushika and Shibamata
I'm happy again
I'm going to cry
I realized
Because I'm an idiot
I don't know how to end this
I was happy
But I can't get past it
I everyone watched me
Like a rager
My friends will have to come here
Hold me
Should I be an adultrains
I don't understand
That's why here is also I am running around
You said it was briskly, didn't you think you were already sober?
Oh, we're almost done this year.
Oh, shabu shabu shabu shabu.
Good work!
Ryo-sama, please go home.
That was perfect. Let's all eat Toshikoshi Soba.
Oh, I've been waiting.
Nakagawa, let's eat Toshikoshi Soba.
Yes.
Itadakimasu!
Oh, that old man is really good.
That's Tanaka-san.
I think I'll be able to get old this year, too.
Ryo-sama, what will you be doing this New Year?
Every year, the new year party is held at the chief's house.
I'm going to be there for a year.
The new year party is canceled.
What did you say?
The chief is going to the hot spring until the third day of the new year.
I went there yesterday.
Damn it! You ran away!
Next year, you won't be able to get a year's worth of nutrition.
You're going to keep it from me!
The New Year without Ryo-sama is the best!
It's the best New Year with no Ryosu!
I'm going to be great!
Hey, chief!
Don't you think you're the only one who wants to have a good idea?
Where did he go to the hot spring?
I think he said Nikko.
Okay, I'm going to look for Nikko's inn to destroy it!
N...Nyu...
Senpai, don't imitate me!
Hey, get away, Nakagawa!
Our kintons and katsunoko have been turned into a travel item.
How can I forgive you?
If you act like that to your subordinates,
I'll let the chief know what will happen.
Let go!
Ryo!
If you don't mind, can you come to my house?
What? You have a new year party at Maria's house?
Yes.
It's a new year party for the new year,
which will be held at my father's dojo.
If you don't mind.
Really?
Yes.
My mother is a cooking researcher,
so I think you'll like it.
Oh, you're talking about Kyoko.
Would you like to join us?
Are we allowed to join?
Yes.
Can I join you?
I thought there was a new year party at the chief's house,
so I couldn't make plans for the New Year.
Oh, me too.
Okay, let's go.
Tomorrow's new year party will be at my father's dojo.
Let's have a feast!
So, I'm getting ready to join you.
Okay.
Then, don't forget to invite me to a new year party.
which will be held at Kyoko's home.
I have a new year party plan?
Hyosuke, you'll be joining me.
Yes, I have a new year party.
I'm ready to join the new year party at vale of peoples.
I will soon join the new year party.
That's great!
You'll starve to death if you don't climb up there.
What's going on with these pillars?
There are 1,990.
Yes, I think you can train yourself with just climbing up.
It's pavement.
There's a barracks. It's really not safe.
Hey, hey!
Are you okay?
But it's...
I'm thirsty.
They're all drunk and asleep.
What kind of camp are they in?
I'm sorry.
It's the Hondara Constitution.
Ush! Ush! Ush! Ush!
What?
They're all doing a good job.
Ush! Ush! Ush! Ush!
You're the iron coach!
You're back!
I'm the iron coach!
I'm the iron ripper!
You're always so persistent.
I'm not the iron coach!
I'm Ryo Tsukankichi!
What?
What do you mean?
Get ready!
Ouch!
Uwa!
Maria!
I won't forgive anyone who does violence to Ryo!
Yaw!
You're not doing it right!
Ush!
Ouch!
Now, who's next?
Chief, this woman is quite good.
It doesn't matter.
We'll all get on the same side and get our asses kicked!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Chief!
No matter how many times you get on my back,
I'll get you!
I'm not the one who can win!
You're so bold, ero-gappa!
She's not a woman.
She's a woman.
But she's the son of my daughter, Asato Ai!
She's the son of my daughter, Asato Ai!
What?!
This is the master's daughter, Ai?!
She became a woman in less than a year.
What a stupid woman.
Is that really Ai?
I can't believe it.
She's so beautiful.
Even if she's a stupid son,
I'm glad she's back to her father.
No, Chief.
I invited everyone to the New Year party.
What?
That's right, Ban-chan.
I'm here to eat some simple food.
You're here to eat some simple food?
You idiot!
I won't let you get away!
Chief!
Are you okay?!
You guys!
Leave Ai alone and go home!
This is not a party!
Please, Dad.
I came all the way here.
Please don't do anything bad.
I'm so sorry.
Wait.
If you think about it,
you're my son, aren't you?
Please, Dad.
P-Papa?
You're so mean to me.
I'm so sorry.
Stop it!
I'll forgive you.
Really?
Dad?
Instead of making you come to the New Year party,
I'll treat you like other monks.
Okay?
What?!
Damn it!
Why do you wear this mask
to learn all these things?
I just want to eat your food!
It's like we're in a camp.
I wish we could have the New Year party at the Chief's house.
I should have changed.
You changed?
Let's start training right away.
First of all,
you will run up and down the platform 30 times.
What?
After that, you will jump up and down the platform one more time.
No way!
No problem!
Let's go!
It's impossible to run up and down the platform 30 times like this.
I can't do it anymore.
Senior, it's too hard to get to the table.
I feel like I was tricked by Maria.
Everyone, you don't have to go down.
What?
What do you mean?
That's fine.
20 times 28, 20 times 9, 30 times.
If you use the first step three times, you will be back.
Is that possible?
What do you mean?
It's the Hondara sword.
Then, what's the meaning of the rabbit jump?
You haven't trained at all.
It's the Hondara sword.
Ouch!
My leg is full of beans.
Damn it, Hondara.
You're imitating Ikkyu-san.
Did you call me?
I'm here.
Elgappa, you're a liar.
If you're frustrated, come on.
I'll beat you up.
Ryo.
You idiot, there's a hole.
And it's full of dog poop.
Now you're a dog.
Don't imitate me like a kid.
There's always a hole in our Hondara sword.
A hole?
Shugo!
Hondara sword muscle strengthening training.
Ready!
Yes.
There are two iron bars on each side.
Two?
You're not going to use that bar, are you?
That's right.
It's called the iron bar training.
Start!
Yes.
I used two iron bars.
So what are you going to do?
I'll use two iron bars.
Yes.
Then you'll have to dry the laundry.
It doesn't make sense to use iron bars.
It's a Hondara sword.
You're still too young to be surprised.
Next is the ultimate of the Hondara sword style,
Sorry if I die.
Hell's Kampu Training.
Start!
Yes!
Now you'll be naked in the flapping wind.
Enter the hot spring.
Then...
Hey! Drink!
Where's hell? That's heaven!
There's always a way out.
Don't mess with me!
I don't need a way out!
You're the one who's here to play!
I'm dying...
Ouch!
What the hell are you doing?!
You idiot! You almost died!
It's a dead end!
Are you okay, Jyo-sama?
I'm...
Asato Ai.
You're talking to me?
I'll give you a kick one day, I'm waiting for you, Daizaimon Kaze...
Daizaimon Kaze...
You know me, Ai?
Daizaimon Kaze... I heard it somewhere...
What's with this wind?
Daizaimon Kaze...
Let's go, Daizo...
Let's go?
Yes.
Urgh!
♪ ♪
T-this exaggerated wind backed me up!!
Aaaah!?
It w-when is it...
No wind with the fan!
Who are you!?
Am I a true warrior...
...Kaze!
Teizaimon!
What!?
You!?
Kaze!
Where is Asatoya!?
-The End-
Where is Asato Ai?
Damn you! Are you trying to make a scene?
We are your opponents!
You useless bastards!
What?
What are you talking about?
I won't forgive you!
-The End-
How's that? Open the road!
You suddenly set off a fire...
W-wait! I can't let you go!
Hehehe...
It's dangerous if you get close to me.
Now, who is it?
Who wants to be a sun dweller?
Stop it!
-The End-
Is he a human pop?
No!
-The End-
Don't be rude!
I am a self-dueling master!
Self-dueling?
-The End-
I see! I remember!
That face!
He's the man who fought Ai in the martial arts tournament!
That's right!
I won't forget.
It was at the finals of the world championship three years ago.
Asatomi Ure and I fought against the world's best fighter, Zao Kagu.
-The End-
Ai! You're not the same level as you were before!
Use the Hon-Dara sword!
But...
Hmm?
What's going on?
-The End-
Shut up!
What are you doing?
Use the Monkey Slash!
-The End-
What?
The wall...
What?!
-The End-
Knockout!
The winner is Ai Asato!
Alright!
Good job!
I still remember the humiliation of that time.
For three years, I've been practicing hard for my life.
And when I was about to fail,
I saw a photo of Asato, changed my position, and started training.
You know, you usually put a photo of your lover in a rocket.
Shut up! I'll show you the success!
I'll show you Asato's light upper blow!
Like this!
Oh, no!
You see? The secret of the Jiko-ryu!
The Shirasagi's Sword!
I'll give you a good technique.
The first Shuriken is not that weak, is it?
Shut up!
I don't have any means to defeat the strongest Asato.
Now, Asato! Where are you?
I'm here!
Move!
Where is Asato?
Wait!
Yes?
Where is Asato?
Asato!
I'm here.
What are you doing? Move!
Asato!
I said I'm here!
You're being persistent.
Asato! Asato!
Huh?
Beautiful!
What is it, Agatha?
Yes?
Is there anyone who comes in through the door?
What?
Oh, no! I'm going to faint!
Oh, no...
Hey, Kyoko!
Oh, Ryo-tsu!
Hello! Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
I hope this year will be a good year for you.
Me too.
Hey, Daidaimon!
The Asato Ai you're looking for is this guy!
Don't mess with me!
This is...
a new sword!
What?
Don't do anything bad to Ryo-sama!
This wonderful sword...
No way!
Is that really Asato Ai?
Is that the real Asato?
Yes.
Asato Ai fell in love with a steel coach a year ago and became a woman.
Ouch!
Now...
You're in for a big hit!
No way!
How could this happen?
Is anything just fine?
...
Is three years of training a waste?
Ah!
This is too much harmonious for me.
I trained for three years in the mountains.
That's part of the game, isn't it?
So, where are you going?
Oh, you!
Everyone!
It was just the right timing.
We've prepared some food.
Oh, we've been waiting!
It's the Shishi-Nabe your mother made.
Senpai, we finally get to eat!
Yeah, we forgot about it thanks to that guy,
but we're here to eat some New Year's food.
Itadakimasu!
This Shishi-Nabe contains wild chrysanthemums that were caught in this mountain.
It's fresh and delicious!
It's the taste of a food researcher.
There's a lot of them, so please eat more and more.
The meat is better than the chrysanthemum.
The meat is the best!
Hey, let go of my knife!
I love meat too!
Let go!
You old man, eat some vegetables!
What are you talking about?
This is the same situation as last year's New Year's party.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I told you to let go of me!
Ryo-sama, are you okay?
Father?
It's his fault.
He should know how to be a little more considerate.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry for bringing you here, Banji.
Banji, you're really...
Hey, eat this!
What?
The chrysanthemum!
I'll see what you can do with this.
Give me back the hot pot!
What?
Wait!
Okay!
Wait, Banji!
Wait!
Oh, my God.
I knew it.
I'll have to wait.
Wait!
Why is he always like this?
I wonder if those two are crazy.
Asato!
W-what about you?
I've become a woman, too.
Let's fight fair and square, Asato.
No, that's disgusting.
I'm not going to let go of three years of training.
Come on, get on with it!
You said the chrysanthemum wasn't good for you, didn't you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
What are you going to do?
If it gets dirty, clean it up.
Of course, right?
I got it.
Get out of here!
Banji!
You wasted a pot.
Yes.
You can have another pot in the future.
Wait!
I did it, too.
If it gets dirty, then clean it up.
Y-Yes...
I didn't forgive you.
How cruel.
Stop!
Wait!
Hey, you!
Stop it!
Ryo!
Maria!
Gorilla Eyebrow!
You can't run away!
Asato, it's a match!
You're persistent! Stop it!
Stop it!
I refuse!
What?
Ryo, you're in danger!
Oh, no!
It's dangerous!
It's going to collapse!
What's going on?
If we knock down the pillar,
the tower will collapse!
What's going on?
We made such a railing!
I don't need such a place!
The End
"My Love in the Sky"
There are rumors that I am a woman who can't fall in love.
But there are so many things I want to do.
I...
I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be free like a bird
A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a telescope
Love heart, I'm sorry, wait
The future of the panorama is a dazzling light
You understand, right? I'm sorry, wait
I want to be free like a bird