Greatest
When you watch TV, light up the room and look away.
"The Greatest Movie"
The rich guy, come to me!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky.
White clouds.
I'm sure it will be somehow.
"The Greatest Movie"
I have no work.
Follow me!
A voice?
A voice!
Come to me!
Uh, uh, uh.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
"The Greatest Movie"
The rich guy!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Come with me!
World Cup
The world's greatest sports event, World Cup Soccer, has finally arrived in Japan!
The second match of the World Cup, the police league vs. soccer competition semi-final,
is the victory of Team A of Katsushika, by a V goal!
As expected, you have come out, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
As the opponent of the final,
there is no other chance!
You are washing your hair and waiting, aren't you, Komachi?
That's right!
The final next week will be between Team B of Katsushika, led by Komachi Ono,
and Team A of Katsushika, led by Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
We have a good news here.
It's a sudden news, but the winning team of this tournament
will be given the ticket to the World Cup final!
What?
Did you say something strange?
No, I just said that I will give the ticket to the World Cup final.
The ticket to the World Cup final?
Ticket!
What? Are you that excited?
Speaking of World Cup tickets, they are super platinum papers!
You can't get them easily in Nakagawa.
There are hundreds of millions of people who want them!
It's such a big deal!
I will definitely get the ticket to the World Cup final!
Machikado Soccer 2000 people!
Finally, the day of the World Cup final,
the day of the World Cup final,
has come!
Team A of Katsushika, led by Ryo-tsu Kankichi, has arrived!
What?
What? That is...
No way! No way!
They are...
No way!
They are the players who are playing in the South American Pro League!
They have been disqualified from the qualifying round,
and the top players of the country who couldn't participate in the World Cup are here!
Don't misunderstand me.
They are the people who came to Katsushika as the police officers.
Well, they might have a little desire for soccer.
Team B of Katsushika has arrived!
They have come.
They didn't know they would lose.
What?
Oh, my!
They are the players who are playing in the European Pro League!
What?
They are the players who came to Katsushika as the police officers.
They might be able to play soccer, but...
They called us because they thought something like this might happen.
Now, we have the same power.
Damn it!
Reiko's work...
Both teams have come to the World Cup final to participate in the Super Cooperative Sets!
Wait!
What?
I'm afraid it's not the same!
They are the players who have made the same mistake.
Team B is going to compete in the Super Cooperative Sets!
I want you to play soccer.
OK.
I'm ready.
We're ready.
I'm ready to go.
I'm ready.
All right!
Let's go!
-Let's go! -Let's go!
I'm ready!
-I'm ready! -I'm ready!
That's right!
But...
By the way, the sixth grand was empty.
Really?
Isn't it too small?
Look at that.
It's the seventh grand.
If you put them together, it's as big as a normal soccer field.
No way, Ryotsu...
That's right. I'm going to use these two grand to play.
What?
That's ridiculous, Ryo-chan.
There's a road in between.
I can't play.
I don't care if you give up the game.
The ticket will be ours.
I didn't say no to anyone.
Well, that's decided.
The grand finale of the World Cup Memorial Police Station vs. Soccer is about to begin.
Let's go!
Team Ryotsu!
Aim for the sixth grand and run at once!
I'm not going to pass here.
You can't stop me!
It's a long shot!
Team Komachi wins the game!
The game has just begun!
The same attack pattern again?
It was so close!
Oh!
The same attack pattern again?
Damn it!
Go, Honda!
But...
Honda is blocked by the red light and can't move forward!
I was saved!
It's the worst timing!
It's hot!
No!
It hurts.
It's a fierce fight!
The signal is changing!
Everyone, get out of the main hall!
Where's the ball?
Don't leave the ball!
I did it!
It's impossible to play here.
Let's stop it.
I agree.
What about the match?
Of course, we win!
But we have one point.
Right?
I'm not joking!
The match has just begun.
We should play until the end!
Yes!
But there is no place.
But the old people played soccer without a ground, right?
They played on TV the other day.
It was the time of soccer to kick the ball from town to town.
Then, let's play soccer in town.
What?
No, no!
If we do that, the people of town will be in trouble.
Chief, you often say that we should value tradition and respect the culture of tradition, right?
Then, shouldn't we respect the tradition of soccer?
The tradition of soccer is the street soccer.
Then, can we call it the host country of the World Cup without accepting it?
Yes, we can.
Of course, we should be careful not to bother the people of town.
But the more important thing is to play street soccer here and show the world how Japan respects the tradition of soccer.
Yes!
I feel like I'm being fooled.
I hope we win with our ability.
Yes!
The match is over!
In the final of the Soccer Tournament against the Police Office, a venue has been changed again.
The goal of the Komachi team is the square in front of the station.
The goal of the Ryotsu team is the third neighborhood park.
The whole city will be a soccer field.
Here we go.
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Take this!
Oh no! The roadside!
Here it comes!
Take this!
The roadside in the town is hard to move in the crowd of 10 people!
What's going on?
The soccer pro is confused in the town of Tokyo!
Did you find it?
It looks like it's lost.
This place is like a garden for Ryo-chan.
Damn it, Ryo-chan!
Leave it to me!
No one's following me.
Alright, I'll go to the goal as soon as possible!
I found it, Ryo-chan!
What?
I won't let you do as you want!
Komachi!
A player is on the roof!
What?
It's a goal!
Everyone, go to the roof!
Europe's best soccer team!
Let's make a good pass!
Stop it, anyone!
The front line!
It's a big one, Sakonji!
Another kid?
Komachi!
Don't push me!
This is like a pinball!
I won't be defeated!
Naga! Pass!
Offside!
What, you say?
We got a defense goal on the north-eastern island, so we have to pass now.
Look, no one's following you...
There's really a gap!
That's right.
Who's that?
I'm sorry, this is a repair cost.
What kind of organization are you?
Keeper 1 vs 1.
A perfect chance!
No, I can't score if I keep it up!
Komachi, shoot!
I got it!
It's enough!
Sorry, I made a mistake with the ball.
It's dirty!
The ball is going to the bargain shop!
Don't stop me!
Oh, no!
It's in the manhole!
You're running away!
Where's the ball?
I got it!
Wait!
Now!
I got it!
What are you doing, Ryo?
Senior, the first half is over, and it's already half time.
Huh?
I was whining many times, but you were in the basement, so you couldn't hear me.
No way.
I've been through a lot to get here, but no one's chasing me on the street.
You're an idiot!
Huh?
Oh, no!
What?
Let me go in.
Aren't you here to do anything for me?
You should go to that bar for 19 days!
You should!
Why?
Come on, it's too early!
I'll take your time.
Are you on your way to the bar?
Yes!
Is this a bar?
I'm gonna get you!
The ball is flying toward the top right corner!
Team Komachi, second point!
I won't let you do that!
The goal is unreachable!
It's unfair to move the goal!
Yeah, yeah.
What are you talking about?
It's a natural courtesy to move the goal in street soccer.
What do you mean, courtesy?
What do you mean courtesy?
Street soccer is a place where residents live.
Of course, there are people who work normally.
For those people, the goal must always be moved.
It's possible to say that.
On the contrary, it's common sense to move the goal in street soccer.
It's a matter of course.
But then, the goal area and penalty area...
Ignore it!
Then,
this goal is alive, right?
Pass!
OK!
No!
Move the goal!
Alright!
Wait for it!
The goal of Team 4 is moving!
Team Komachi is chasing!
Wait!
Komachi, over there!
The enemy is tired. It's your chance!
That's it!
It's inoculated, not it?
And then it's in!
It returns!
One point!
The enemy is out!
My team's goal!
Goal!
Team Ryotsu finally caught up with the same score!
It was an awesome match.
I can't say it's soccer anymore
Female 1: I can't say it's soccer anymore.
Run!
Stop!
The intense battle continues!
World Cup Commemoration!
Police Station vs. Soccer World Cup Final!
Which team will win?
It doesn't matter.
Hurry up and finish!
I told you not to bother the people of that town!
Oh, no!
That was close!
That's it.
I have to go!
Oh, no!
That was close!
I have to go!
Stop!
It's over.
I can't believe you.
It's been a while.
Hi, Bobby and Ryo!
O-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L-L
J-Joby!!
Why are you here?
Using the holiday,
I came to Japan with my friends.
I heard that Bobby will play soccer.
So, I came to cheer him up.
Hmm...
Nick!
Ryo!
Give me that!
Go away!
All right!
Hey!
What?
What's this room?
Where are we?
Damn it!
Where is the ball?
There is no place to play!
Here it is!
Wait!
Wait, Senpai!
This way?
Yes.
It's quite lively.
I wonder if the Olympics have begun.
Ryo!
What's that?
He's playing the Matsuri!
Senpai!
What's going on?
We're playing the World Cup Memorial Big Soccer Matsuri!
Please turn around!
What?
Senpai!
I won't let you!
You!
Get out of here!
My back is big, too!
I won't lose!
The World Cup Memorial Police Station vs. Soccer Tournament is now over!
They have entered the long-term game of the V-goal method!
They're not letting go!
The ball is coming!
Both teams are playing the fierce Tsubateri!
Don't come near me!
Go away!
Don't come near me, either!
I'll beat you to death!
The player in this position can't get used to this additional power!
Go away!
You're obviously an otaku of the soccer world, aren't you?!
That's...
No way!
It's the World Cup match venue!
Senpai, please turn around!
Komachi, stop!
Stop! Stop!
No! I can't hear anything!
Throw it!
Where's the ball?
Ryotsu, the ball!
I got it, Gonji!
Oh, no!
I'll finish you off!
Run over there!
Don't be so stubborn!
Take this, my cross-eyed shoot!
Goal! Goal! Goal!
I did it!
I... I lost...
I won the V-goal!
The winner of the World Cup match,
the police station vs. the soccer tournament,
is...
the Ryotsu team!
Ryotsu! Ryotsu! Ryotsu!
We did it!
The World Cup ticket is ours!
Ryotsu!
Here, captain!
I got you!
We won!
Give me the ticket!
Ryotsu, you bastard!
This is it!
This is what I wanted!
Hi, Ryo!
Higurashi!
Why is Higurashi here?
I guess Higurashi only wakes up once every four years, right?
Yet...
Why do we think so?
Why are you so angry?
Because...
Well...
I'm just astonished.
I'm going to ask while he's sitting at the end of the line...
etsu is going to come...
looks like there'll be a demise!
He's got good things to do!
But I can't wait to win!
If I do it well,
he'll be a valuable champion for me!
I have to do something to win the Tour of Japan, right?
His goal,
and my goal is to win the Tour of Japan...
and some of the tournaments will be held.
I see.
That's why they play soccer in Japan.
It's so exciting.
It's like the World Cup.
It's not like the World Cup.
It's the real World Cup.
O-re!
Giga!
The 2002 World Cup is being held.
O-re!
2002?
Not 2004?
How long?
I haven't slept for two years.
You woke me up.
I don't know. I don't know anything.
Ryota!
The World Cup ticket...
No way! No way! No way!
Wow!
Gyokumon!
Don't come near me.
Nobody'll hit you!
Gyokumon! Gyokumon!
G-ge-get away! Get away!
Just, please do something!
YOSHIMA!
You're too much!
Ryozu! You're the one!
I'm not the one who's been running around the church!
Speaking of the past, it's your fault!
No, no, no!
I'm sick of soccer!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Hey, hey!
I don't know how many picks you've received so far...
You've locked the door too much!
You can't get in there, so you can't help it!
Besides, what are you going to protect by locking the door so much?
Next time, "The Man Who Locked Too Much"!
Don't miss it!
Thank you for watching!