Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kick the pebbles and fly to the top ♪
♪ I laughed at the
♪
Take this!
What a splendid Nishikigori!
You know what?
I like the part where there's a little pearl in the water.
Yeah, it's very beautiful.
These three colors are also very colorful.
Which one?
Hey, stop it! The water is dirty!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha!
It's all right now.
We've eliminated the bacteria.
That's it for the pet boom.
Excuse me.
You've become so obsessed with Nishikigori,
it's like a kid, don't you think?
I can't help it.
Since he was a child,
I've raised him with all my heart and soul.
Really?
I thought everyone thought Nishikigori was the same.
But this way of looking at it,
it's become a different kind of pattern.
Right?
One bite of Nishikigori,
Even if you say Nishikigoi, there are both Japanese and German words.
German words?
Japan has improved the way they speak, and has made their Nishikigoi beautiful.
But in Asia, America, and Europe, there are Nishikigoi-like people.
I called everyone here today to see this Nishikigoi.
Why did you have to do that?
What do you mean?
A clumsy person like you wouldn't know, but look!
That guy has a 53 cm long body, and he's planning to appear in the Himpyoukai next time.
Himpyoukai? The Nishikigoi?
Yeah. He hasn't been in the competition for years.
Just by joining, he's a great honor for the Nishikigoi fans.
Huh?
The pattern changes as you grow, but this is a good place to settle down.
It's a three-color male body.
What? Why you?
Ryo, do you know?
Of course I do.
I'm the one who takes care of 88 Nishikigoi that are living in Matoi's house.
You do?
You're good at raising them, aren't you?
Well, it's important to create an environment for the Nishikigoi, such as water and land.
Right, President?
Yes, that's right.
Go swim with everyone over there, Koijiro.
Koijiro?
Yeah.
I named them Daijirou.
They're like my children.
Yeah.
President, this pond has a lot of trees and grass, so it's easy to accumulate garbage.
You have to drain and drain the water.
What?
The bad water flow of the pond causes diseases such as angry insects and caterpillars.
I'm surprised.
I didn't know you were so familiar with the law.
Hypertension occurs when the temperature suddenly drops.
If you mix the salt with about 1% of the water temperature, it will recover.
I see.
I think you can win the championship with that love.
That's right.
President, you're confident, aren't you?
Well, I think I'm going to have a good time, but I'm worried that my wife and I will be on a trip for the next four days.
Instead of doing nothing at the marriage ceremony, what should I do in the meantime?
Then why don't you take over our pet management center?
We'll take care of the water.
We'll check everything from the water to the water.
Oh, is that so?
The management fee is 50,000 yen a day, which is a little expensive.
50,000 yen?
Just looking at the care of love for a day?
I can't change the money, so I'll leave it to you.
B.
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
You're shouting.
That's not true.
Leave it to me.
I'll take care of it for 30,000 a day.
No, I'll take care of it for 10,000 a day.
You?
What?
But I'm raising two baby geese from a female bird.
That's not true.
Of course, I'm the top breeder of two geese.
I'm going to make money by saying something like that.
The color of my eyes has changed since I heard that 50,000 yen a day.
You have to have love for love.
Oh, that's true.
A man in love with love.
Me, I'm the same.
All right.
I'm counting on you to buy it, Ryotsu.
Leave it to me.
10,000 yen a day.
And four horses.
Well then, I'll ask you to buy it, too.
I wanted to get on a ship.
Ah, you want to go by plane.
Well, then I will fly to the sky as if I was on a boat.
Hahaha.
Butt.
I'm not kidding. I'm counting on you.
See you.
Well, thank you.
Have a good trip!
I'll give you a souvenir.
Just by feeding you, you'll make 10,000 yen a day.
Eat up!
Koichiro! Koikichi! Koihime!
Koita!
I'm bored.
I'll try to play games to get rid of my boredom.
Everyone, gather around!
Alright! Let's see who can fly higher!
I'll do this for the best!
I can't believe you can tell by his voice.
Oh, Koichiro.
He's different from the others and smart.
I'll try to play a game.
Ready? One, two, three!
Alright, next up is the Waku-guri!
Alright!
If I put this into practice, I might be able to make some money.
The Waku-guri
Where will it go?
Eh?
Wait up...
Te!
That's dangerous! Don't move!
Alright, just like that.
Takeya!
Are you alright?
Wait, that truck!
Wait, wait, wait!
I can't catch up with him because there aren't many traffic lights!
I'm going to borrow you!
Wait, Koichiro!
Are you alright, Koichiro?
I'm so tired!
Koijiro! Koijiro! Come back! Koijiro!
Koijiro!
Eh? Koijiro is...
Shh! You're going to get rejected by Reiko.
But what are you going to do?
That Koi is the one you especially cherished, right?
The one you're going to give to the Golden Thread Embroidery?
That's why I'm in trouble.
Every 100 Koi is different.
I can't let you fool me.
Listen to me.
Eh?
The fish robot developed by Nakagawa Electro Club?
Shh!
This is Koijiro's photo.
He made a latex-like outer side...
...and put the mecha inside.
What are you two talking about?
Nothing.
It's just a man and woman's talk.
Right, Nakagawa?
Eh?
Yes.
Let's talk more over there.
Right, Nakagawa?
I'm glad.
His movements are real, and his motor is small.
He's the same as a real one.
Fish don't have expressions.
But tomorrow's competition...
He'll be eliminated in the qualifying round.
See ya.
Next time, we'll get back.
I'd love to!
Kaede!
While we wait, I forgot...
He doesn't answer my phone!
Come on.
Stop it!
I've been worried about Kaede lately.
Is he not in good condition?
How old is he?
I don't know either.
Where's he?
I'll go search with him.
What?
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
If it's a group that has crossed the line, they may be discovered as fake.
It would be nice if they could drop the preliminary round as soon as possible.
Ryotsu! Nakagawa!
We did it! The preliminary round is passed!
What did you say?
Oh, what? Is it bad to have passed the preliminary round?
No, it's not that bad. It was good.
Huh? That's strange.
It suddenly stopped working.
Koijiro! What's wrong, Koijiro? Koijiro!
The battery is out, senpai.
What did you say?
Um, I'm sorry.
What are you going to do, Ryotsu?
Nakagawa!
Koijiro!
Leave it to me!
Koijiro...
Hey, this is going to cut the battery soon.
Senpai, hurry up!
Hey, I know. I'm going to modify it a little.
Oh, Koijiro... Koijiro...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, oh!
Koijiro is fine as it is.
Kiyoko!
Oh, Koijiro...
It's all good now!
We did it! Koijiro is left as the final candidate!
If we win this time, no one will be able to fool us anymore!
Oh, this is wonderful!
It's not only elegant and beautiful, but also makes you feel active and healthy.
I-is that so?
It's a little too energetic, isn't it?
No, it's a dynamic and dynamic feeling that has never been before.
It's fresh.
But you're too fat.
You may not know this, but this volume is excellent.
No, but...
Why are you so stubborn?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Hmm?
Everyone, there is no dependence, right?
No, there isn't.
It's decided.
The winner is No. 52, Taisho Sanshoku.
What?
Koizuro is the winner!
Senpai...
This is an unexpected situation.
What is it?
The battery is dead.
There was an impossible modification.
Oh, I see!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Hmm...
The battery is dead.
What?
What's going on?
What's going on, Ryotsu?
Hey, wait a moment!
What?
A robot? What happened to Koichiro?
He's living happily in the middle of nature.
Idiot!
Damn it! Will it end like this?
If this continues, it'll be a return match with Nishikigoi!
The commercial will continue after this!
What happened to Ryotsu? He's been resting.
He's not sick.
I heard he started something again.
He must be making money.
Whatever. I don't know what he's doing, but if I don't see his face, I'll come back and wake him up!
It's cold!
Huh?
Why is Nishikigoi in the bath?
What are you doing, kid?
That's terrible, senpai.
Ryo's bath is forbidden for a while.
That's so unbiased!
What did you start?
Nishikigoi's pet. It's good because it sells at a high price.
Well, look.
Look at this turtle.
From this turtle, the new pattern, size, and strength of the Nishikigoi will be born.
Nishikigoi?
Hehehe.
Good. Good. It's going well.
It's fast to get bigger.
If you take a bath, you don't need to take a bath. You can keep a high temperature.
It has grown well with various products and artificial offspring.
But isn't this bathroom a little small?
I'll give you a hand.
Make a bath in the bath.
As expected, it's fast to do.
24 hours of unmarried and unmarried,
I'll make you more and more various products and artificial offspring and create a perfect Nishikigoi.
Then I'm rich.
Ahahahaha.
That's right.
Let's add ocean water, hormone liquid, and an insect drink.
Hehehe.
What?
Ryotsu completed the love of the new species?
Yes.
It seems that it is a new species that is over 1 meter long.
There is a grand presentation today.
Oh.
I can't believe it.
In such a short period of time.
If money is involved, the power of the senior will be infinite.
I see.
It's amazing.
Everyone, we have a great guest today.
It was the idea of ​​human beings, and it was finally born.
It seems to be Odawara.
Oh, that's amazing.
It's too much.
It's hot.
What the.
I've never seen such a powerful three colors before.
No, it's different from the Taisho three colors and the Showa three colors.
One, two, four colors! It's not three colors!
That's right! This is the miracle I created in the world of the unknown.
It's called the Ryotsu four colors.
It's too narrow!
Senpai! It seems that orders from all over the world are running out!
Don't panic. I knew this would happen.
It's too narrow here.
I'll keep adding more!
One cup of Kouhai will produce 100,000 eggs.
The four colors of Ryotsu have a great reproduction power.
I'm not saying that I'm a thief, but this Kouhai is really like a senpai.
I finally got the success story.
You did it, senpai.
These 300 are from Florida.
These 500 are from Germany.
Let's export more and more!
This is Europe. This is India.
Middle East, Russia, South America, China, Australia!
This studied as a
What's going on?
A tree has a great reproductive power.
Sumidagawa river has been occupied.
This plant is called the Ryotsu four colors.
For the sake of the
The four colors are growing.
What's going on, Senpai?
I have a bad feeling about this.
The Seine River is filled with four colors.
In the UK, Nessie is being chased by four colors and is running away.
We will show you the latest footage from the Amazon River.
These are the four colors chasing the Piranha.
What's going on?
The four colors are tough and have great reproduction.
They grow to 50cm in 3 days.
How long do they live?
Around 5 years.
No, the average lifespan of the Nishiki is 70 years.
70 years?
If they keep growing...
...they'll die.
I don't want to imagine it.
Koijiro...
Koijiro!
Koijirou! You came back so soon!
Koijirou!
Not only in the Pacific Ocean and the Atlantic Ocean,
but also in the South Pacific Ocean and the Arctic Ocean,
a large force of four different lands was confirmed.
But, a voice is crossing the sea...
It's flying like a flying fish!
By the way, Tobio is also a junior.
According to the information from the artificial satellite,
these groups are moving to Japan one day.
Why to Japan?
No way...
No way... Senpai!
They were both defeated by Sake.
Well, then...
Sake will return to his hometown...
Kameari...
He will come back!
Oh? Who do you think it is?
It's Yoko from the tobacco shop!
She is the junior high school student
and a womanizer!
I've become a good wife!
I've been mistaken!
I remember!
The exhaust pipe from that time!
Next time, "A little while ago, the exhaust pipe!"
See you!
Kameari