Seller's Record
As I stare at the daydreams floating inなかがわ
I take off my love rock and jump to the foot
To how far I can go
I wonder if I can go
So I'd save money
I was just anhad it
I was laughed at
Somewhere we don't feel better
Katsushika, Kameari I have a bad cough
♪ The cityscape that never changes is so gentle ♪
♪ From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi ♪
♪ The sun goes down to the Taishakuten ♪
♪ Tomorrow will end like this ♪
♪ I realized that I'm an idiot because I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I'm an idiot because I lost my happiness again ♪
Wow, there are so many people!
As expected of the Motor Festival.
But, who is the person that sent us the invitation?
That's right. Ryo-chan, who doesn't have a car, might not be very close to us.
I have a car, too.
Countach, Mustang, King Tiger, and...
Aren't they all plastic models?
Anyway, let's get inside.
♪ The cityscape that never changes is so gentle ♪
♪ The sun goes down to the Taishakuten ♪
The encaniejings are still on.
We won't have a restaurant with a big family.
Ouch!
You're driving so badly!
I can't believe it!
I knew it. Cafe au lait smells like art.
I know the man.
Eizaki Korosuke.
Professor Eizaki!
He's making such a fuss again.
I'll show you how to get out of here.
Bonjour, Monsieur Nakagawa.
How are you?
Mademoiselle Raikou.
Hey!
You're a man who knows everything!
You're a mountain gorilla.
Who's a gorilla?
Are you from Beijing?
No!
I'm Japanese!
That's a French joke with Esprit.
You know what?
The ancient Cro-Magnon people
went south in 1868
and were discovered in France.
France is a country of history and art.
Hey!
You're so hot!
What's with that outfit?
Dracula?
No.
This is the royal thief
that France has created.
Alcène Lupin!
Lupin?
In the Middle East,
there's a royal thief called the Mouse Kid.
What the hell are you doing?
Lupin is not a vulgar pronunciation.
It's "Lupin"!
Isn't that "France Pan"?
Oui.
In France, this pan is used for fighting.
That's ridiculous.
Anyway, Nakagawa-kun, Miss,
are you still riding a Ferrari or a Porsche?
Y-Yes.
Well,
you can be a French car.
Citroën, Renault, Peugeot...
There's love and art in the French car!
It's totally different from the other day.
Jaguar and T-Time
were all over the UK.
What?
France is the country
that is full of the scent of Europe.
Professor, when is France?
I've been teaching in Sorbonne University
for two weeks.
You've been in France for only two weeks?
Even so,
the flow of the world is still in my ears.
The mountain pass of Montmartre
where all the painters from all over the world gather.
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
And then I sit in a cafe
and say this way:
"Mademoiselle,
I'm a silver plate."
Shut up!
You just have to admit that
the place where you came in
when you fell off the stairs
was all for nothing!
Damn!
-Neg-! -Senpai, please stop!
It would be terrible if we had a duel again like this!
I know, but I don't feel like fighting anymore.
It's so stupid.
By the way, professor, who gave you this invitation?
Wimsh, exactly. I invited you.
My invention is also on display at this show.
And that's...
Nare-da!
What's that?
Ladies and gentlemen, the 21st century is the era of tanks.
And so, I developed a revolutionary tank machine, the All-Aimed.
You're just playing with tanks, aren't you?
You!
Do you know why Napoleon attacked Russia?
I don't know!
I don't know, either!
Then, you amateurs, keep quiet!
Even though it looks like this, it's not just a tank machine!
It detects the car body with a top lens,
and analyzes the car's dirt by computer.
It sprays water and special detergent from 50 places to remove the dirt.
And it can move anywhere with a caterpillar!
In other words, this robot, Zenjiro-kun, is a moving tank machine with brains!
Oh, amazing machine!
I see.
It can move by itself, so it can finish the tank machine by just parking it.
Is it really that good?
Then, let's try it out.
Zenjiro-kun, start the tank machine course.
The switch has been turned on.
It detects the car body and returns the tank machine.
All you have to do is blow it with the AdWord Merit Pipe.
Oh, my God!
Oh, it's Horo!
Then, it's an open car.
I forgot to put Horo's stopper on.
Check complete.
I'm washing it.
The tank machine is starting to discharge.
Help!
Oh, my eyes!
What a terrible guy.
This is not the time to say such things.
We have to help him quickly.
It's terrible.
The work is finished.
Hey, old man, are you all right?
The detergent is melted and I can't see well.
Are you all right?
Can I make it up to him?
Hey, look!
No...
This was the first time I had another coffee at a cafe.
It's not the first time to be filled with water...
Did you understand?
Just like this, you can clean your room and clothes at the same time.
I showed him that I can do it.
Ugh...
You're talking about your stupidity of hating the bucket again!
Under the sky of Paris, the Seine flows.
That chanson I heard on Champs-Élysées was his.
You bastard!
Sen-Senpai!
Huh?
Uwaaah!
♪ Cargo, transport, analysis, start! ♪
♪ Search, end, work, start! ♪
Uwaaah!
Let go of me!
Hey!
Uwaaah!
Senpai!
Alright!
Uwaaah!
Stop it!
Professor, please turn off the remote control!
Hm?
Oh, this one.
Uwaaah!
It seems it's broken.
No way!
Then how about Zenjudo?
He's moving on his own.
Huh?
You don't have to be surprised.
That's another amazing thing.
Uwaaah!
♪ Water washing, end, work, start! ♪
♪ Search, start, work, start! ♪
So he can't stop it?
Uwaaah!
♪ Work, end, work, end! ♪
Ryo!
Sen-Senpai!
Uwaaah!
No! Ryo, you're so shiny!
I didn't like it!
Then we start again!
Haaah!
Uwaaah!
♪ Water washing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing! ♪
♪ Water washing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing, stabbing! ♪
Uwaaah!
♪ lebih, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Take your time, play! Play your game! Play your game! Play your game! Play your game! Play your game! ♪
Uwaaah!
What's wrong?
I love the beautiful sea.
I want to go anywhere, anytime, anywhere.
If you want to, there's nothing you can't do.
Leave it to me, I'll change it.
He's totally in a good mood.
I guess I'll have to turn off the power.
Ryo!
What's wrong with him?
Get up!
He's doing a good job!
It's probably useless.
Zenjido has a self-defense system.
Why would he do that?
In the future, even if it's a machine, it has to protect itself.
Where's the big one?
Let go!
Don't let go!
Stop it!
Ryo, do your best!
Senpai, hold on!
It's a useless resistance.
You're a genius!
Senpai!
Ryo!
Why are you so weak?
It's a perfect defense system, isn't it?
Don't brag about it. Do something!
Dreadhawk!
Tch!
Stop it!
You're too kind!
You can't fight like that!
I don't want to!
Stop it!
Wow!
That's my name.
Hey!
So, what is this?
I found it!
Can't you let us do it?
It can't be helped.
It's right now.
What are you talking about?
Nobody can stop us!
That's why we're destroying it!
Wash it! Wash it!
Hey! We're getting water out!
It seems they're going to wash the whole venue.
That's not right!
What a disaster!
The venue is running out of water!
Wash it! Wash it! Wash it!
Wash it!
We need to do something!
Professor!
Where did you go?
Wash it! Wash it! Wash it!
Wash it! Wash it!
The war is over.
We've done it again.
I can't believe it.
How was it?
We're doing an earthquake search just for this moment.
You did it anyway.
Haha.
It was not my invention.
There's nothing like that.
So he's not the most dangerous person?
That's right! There's one more invention left at the second meeting.
Hey, Reiko Nakagawa, we're going home.
If you keep being with him, you'll lose your life.
Senpai!
That's too bad. It's a new virtual game.
A new virtual game?
Then I'll leave Gorilla-kun to you.
Wait!
This is not a game. Let me play it!
This is it!
You said this is it. Is this all you have?
That's right.
But we can't play without a car and a screen.
Don't worry.
Try wearing a helmet.
I don't think it's dangerous.
Throw it away.
Hold the steering wheel.
What is this?
The screen is in the shield!
Try pushing the steering wheel forward.
Like this?
It's running!
This is amazing!
This helmet is a virtual reality goggles!
That's right.
This is the only one in the world.
It's a compact virtual reality drive game!
I'll turn the engine all the way to the top!
Wow!
It's like a real one with stereo headphones built in.
This is pretty good.
Simulation development is a specialty of teachers.
Then show me the example.
The example?
Come on, hurry up!
What?
Come on!
I got a hairpin all of a sudden!
Just you wait.
This is a replacement for all the manuals we used in the past!
It's the current showroom!
What is this?
T-that's it!
Can't you fill it with bubbles!?
You're not really building a showroom.
Give it to me!
No, it's okay.
Don't try that!
Don't you know?
You could've put something.
Wait a minute.
I don't have any!
No?
How did it go?
The lap time for the 4th lap has increased.
I don't know what's going on outside.
This is not good.
If you connect the lines, you can race with 6 people at the same time.
Don't get close to me.
It's amazing when you line up.
It's kind of dangerous.
Let's go!
Go!
It crashed suddenly.
It's dangerous.
It doesn't look like a race.
It's a group of perverts.
It's great, isn't it?
It looks interesting, but it looks dangerous.
It's a problem.
There is no car body.
I'm glad I noticed that.
Everyone notices.
This is what I developed.
There are two F1 machines.
Is this real?
Of course.
A man who is particular about real things, Korosuke Ezaki.
By joining the engine, Zenkai, and the real F1 machine,
we can achieve the ultimate virtual reality.
If you accelerate, the virtual video will also speed up.
If you spin or crash, you will be thrown out of the car.
In other words, only I, a real F1 racer, can perfectly handle this.
Then, let's compete with me.
You'd better stop.
You're as skilled as Shoemaker or Ezaki Korosuke.
Are you going to face me?
If you fail, you're not going to go to America.
I will win.
You have to be more gorgeous than me,
Let's see who will win.
No way.
I can't beat you.
The even weight can't beat you,
I'm sure you can win.
I'm sure.
The next day
It's spinning!
It's very powerful!
What kind of driving is it?
I think it's going to the audience seat!
It may be killing 4 or 5 people.
It's a very fast car.
Okay, we'll make a difference in this straight line!
It really started to run!
It's a lot of power!
Me too!
Both of them are not aware of Zenkai-kun's fault!
Let's chase after them!
It's a very fast car!
Don't let go, Kei-chan!
I know!
It's very powerful!
It's like it's really running!
It's a very fast car!
Oh no, it's coming!
It's the red light!
The ground especial corner!
Why is it making a noise?
It's one of the best cars in the world!
It's a high-speed corner!
brrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
I have a bad feeling!
How long it will last?
Maybe..
...when the battery runs out or when the game's over..
Oh!
Now it's the crossroads!
Arrrh! It's still a curvy road!
I-I can't go!
It's stuck in the sand-trap!
We're stuck in a trap!
The stop light was on the way down.
The train's coming!
It's the god of death!
If it's not a game, neither of us can do it!
Hey, Tsukoryo!
I think we're almost there.
Let's do this!
Let's get out of here!
Wow! That was super fast!
We're going to win!
What was that?
Well...
This is bad!
The race is over!
We're in the race track!
We're in the fourth corner of the track and are about to enter the straight line.
The battle is...
Whoa! It's the F1!
There are two F1 machines running!
What happened?
This is...
They're still running!
What's going to happen?
They're doing a great job, but...
Is the goal too close?
Whoa! It's a great virtual!
There's a horse running in the race track!
The race track is running smoothly!
How do you like it?
But I remember making a simulation.
What?
Don't let the goal be too close!
No!
No, that's not true!
Huh?
- It's moving! X3 - - I
am victorious! - What are you talking about? I am victorious!
Amazing!
It's a real battle!
Perfect!
What's going on?
The game is over, but it's still a race!
Hey, this isn't virtual!
They're back in reality!
The audience has been
Well, I'll go with this.
Dan!
Hey!
Don't run away!
Oh, nice!
Silver!
Blah!
What a face, Chief!
Look at those gyoza flowers!
Do these flowers cost so much of a price?
Fine!
I'll raise enough flowers for you!
There's so much to do at the back garden!
Look at the goldfish!
I'll be meeting you on Funtou Harasakaryo!
See you there!
"Minecraft"
I'm glad to hear that.