LoneWolf
"When watching TV, turn the room on to make it bright, and try to look away."
"I can't see!"
"Who's here?"
"These two are the only people in " "To
the ones who have no money, come to me!" "I
have no money, but now I'm worried."
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
You know, don't you? You know, don't you?
If you know, then just keep quiet and follow me!
Momoderela
The famous work, Momoderela
Cheers!
Ah, Senpai.
What are you doing here all the time?
You're doing an old man home visit every year, right?
I was discussing what to do for the play.
A play for the old man?
You do that every year? I didn't know that.
I'm a volunteer.
I don't know you, but I invited you.
I'm not going to cooperate with you.
You're a man of money, after all.
Of course.
A multi-talented professional who can sing, dance, and laugh like me
can't do it for free.
What's this picture?
Momotaro and Cinderella?
I didn't expect him to do a play like this at an old man's home.
You're not going to do it for free, are you?
Don't interrupt me.
I thought I'd say something as an entertainer.
Other than us, the children in the nearby kindergarten will participate in the play.
So we're playing a play that's easy for both the elderly and children to understand.
But there's no Momotaro or Cinderella.
There's no such thing.
The fairy tale is educational, and last year's Kaguya was a big success.
What's good about education?
I think it's just a bad influence on children.
Especially this Momotaro.
What?
Momotaro is a classic Japanese fairy tale.
It's too unrealistic for human beings to be born from a peach.
Even if the seed of a peach changes suddenly, it will never become human.
If the seed changes into a human, Yaoya won't stop being noisy.
Yaoya!
Momotaro is a mythological fairy tale.
Let's say there's a human in the peach.
Cut the peach into two.
Do you understand?
Um...
Then, should I cut it?
The knife will hit the peach.
No!
So, the peach inside...
When you cut it, you have to stick it on the side.
It's normal to not think that much.
Seriously.
That's not true.
Basically, there are too many contradictions in this story.
First, a large peach flows from the side of the head to the side.
That's true, but...
Don't you think so?
No.
Momotaro is inside the peach.
It's unnatural for it to float.
It's natural.
It's natural to roll around the bottom of the river.
I'm sure there was air inside the peach.
Then let's say it's floating again.
The baby inside is this big, and the size of the peach is this big.
It's creepy when you say it in real life.
Usually, when such a big peach flows,
"Ryohei! Peach, peach, peach!"
First of all, you'll be surprised.
You'll never think of eating it at home.
Well, I guess so.
Let's say you gave it to your grandma and brought it home to eat.
But you'll eat the fruit after lunch, right?
Usually, yes.
You might forget about it and rot away.
It's an old story, so it's convenient to talk about it.
So you don't have to be born from a peach,
just pick it up at the shrine and it's fine, right?
Then let's call Momotaro.
Momotaro won't become Momotaro.
I picked it up in the peach season,
so I named it Momotaro.
I can make a lot of things.
And this demon taizhi.
He suddenly goes to attack Onigashima.
He attacks the demon and takes the treasure and goes home.
He's doing the same thing as the robbers.
Even if the demon is a bad guy,
if he does this now,
Momotaro and his friends will be arrested for sure.
Furthermore, the liars are the liars.
The liars?
What are the liars?
I think it's a monkey and...
A dog.
A rat.
I don't think they're useful for animals like pets.
The monkey scratched, the dog bit him,
and the rat poked his eye and killed the demon.
The enemy is a terrible demon like Chief Ohara.
Are you kidding me?
You'll get beaten up by a flower bud.
That's true.
If I were Momotaro,
I would never take such a weak person.
I would definitely take him.
First, the lion.
Then the tiger.
Then the grizzly.
This is Chief Ohara.
Hey, don't!
Don't come near me!
Senior!
Ryo-chan!
Bebe-chan!
You're not supposed to use me for your image.
Damn it, what the hell are you doing here?
The boss is coming for us again.
So the chief can be a monkey, a dog, or a pig.
But you can't really be a chief
Komachi, if you're a monkey,
do you think you'll be a chief?
What?
I don't want to be a goldfish.
I know!
Yeah?
Go and kill the demons.
You might die,
but you can't be a chief with a goldfish alone.
You've got to have money.
Yeah, right.
Or a diamond, or a trademark.
Home for two hours.
I'd like a new motorcycle.
I don't know about the rich Nakagane and Reiko, but that's the character.
Oh, it's Volvo.
Ryo-tsu, let's meet up for the survival game next week.
I came to the right place.
If you were Momotaro, what would you do if you got on this demon island and exterminated the demons?
First, change Momotaro's costume.
Costume?
Set up the best flag in Japan, wear this flashy outfit, and attack the enemy right away.
Immediately find the demons and meet them at the return point.
If this is the case, I will attack at night.
The ship is also a landing destination.
Of course, only in the best clothes.
As expected of the former Green Belly.
So, do you land from the back of the island?
It's naive.
Maybe there...
It's a minefield.
I see.
Then how do you attack?
You land here and here.
First, use the shield instead of the flag.
Drop the main gun and destroy the enemy's main camp.
Then, even if the dog is a dog, release Doberman at once.
In addition, put the gorilla inside the castle, not the monkey.
This triple attack will shake the enemy's forces.
Take the treasure there and run away.
This is the "Island Storm Strategy."
Wonderful, Bulba.
There is no such old-fashioned story.
After all, it's better to make Cinderella.
You can give dreams to children and the elderly.
I'm not kidding.
Where in Cinderella can I give you a dream?
That's because Cinderella is beautiful.
Among the dozens of beautiful women, I was in the eyes of the prince.
I'm in the eyes of the prince.
If you're ugly, you can't even draw a flower.
You should be angry.
Why are you pointing at us?
Do you mean we're ugly?
Well, don't get excited.
For example, if you like Cinderella's hard-working appearance before she transforms, it's true love.
Choose a bad sister.
If you choose a bad sister and marry her to change you, this is true love.
Cinderella has solved the lesson that only beautiful women can be happy in the world.
How can you say that you have a dream?
And this is also full of lies.
When the magic was over 12 o'clock, the dress and the carriage were gone.
Why didn't the glass shoes disappear?
If you say so, it's true.
That's true.
If you give up the room and leave the glass shoes, the size of the shoes should be 24 cm.
If you look all over the country, there should be 50,000 women with the same size of feet.
Cinderella alone is not realistic at all.
You're complaining too much.
Then what kind of play should we do?
Okay.
Then I'll write a script that combines Momotaro and Cinderella.
What?
This is definitely better.
The About a Most recorder
♪ I'm gonna cry, cry, cry, cry ♪
Ryo-tsu, Kankichi, what are you doing?
I'm making the costumes, but the script isn't finished, so I can't act.
Hey, sorry, sorry. The script's finally done.
Everyone, remember the lines right away!
Ladies and gentlemen, and otossan, okkasan.
Next up is a super old story by Broadway's Matsuo, delivered by the Katsushika family.
"Momoterela, Hajimari Hajimari!"
Momoterela, I've never heard of it.
Me neither.
Once upon a time, there lived an old man and an old woman.
What's with this face? It's all about makeup.
Why am I an old woman?
I'm an old woman, after all.
Hey, don't say that!
One day, the old man was on his way to the mountains.
The old woman went to the river to wash.
While the old woman was washing in the river,
a huge peach came down, and...
"Donbraco, donbraco," right?
Ouch!
It came down from the sky.
That can't be true!
Ouch!
There were also four.
That sounds like a peach.
But weren't there only one peach?
She said, "Momoterela," so there were four!
So the old woman brought her the peach to her home.
Then the old man...
Oh, this is a beautiful peach.
Let's cut it and eat!
Grandpa?
An unbelievable scene happened,
Suddenly, the heartless old man...
...sneezed.
That's all I have to do.
Old man! Come back!
The old woman ran away with four babies.
But she couldn't help raising the babies.
The old woman gave birth to her own breasts and gave them to the babies.
You can't do that in front of people.
Excuse me.
The old woman had a lot of wrinkles, so her breasts didn't come out.
What are you talking about?
Then you have to give her a name.
First of all, you're so cool, so you should be called DiCaprio.
That's a good name.
But you didn't give her a good name, so you gave birth to her breasts.
That's all.
You gave birth to a baby boy, called Pteranodon.
His names are Momotarou, Momojiro, Momoe, and Momoko.
The little boys grew up quickly, and Momotarou became a childlike boy.
"H jap, jap!"
Momoko grew into a beautiful daughter of a working man.
Momojiro became a mathman.
They all left the house.
Uwaaaah!
I'm home.
Big news! Big news!
What's wrong, Momoe?
Tonight, a swimming competition for women will be held at the castle, led by the prince.
What?
If the prince sees me there, I might become a bride.
Oh!
Prince, you're not talking about Japan, are you?
In this age of globalization, there's no such thing as just Japan.
It's global.
Oh, this is...
Huh? Grandma, why did you suddenly turn young?
I'm a beautiful girl who's in fashion now.
Eh? And why doesn't Momoko have a swimsuit?
I'm poor, so I could only buy two swimsuits.
It's because you're beautiful, isn't it?
Actually, Grandma...
I was jealous of the beautiful Momoko, and I bullied her.
She's such a bad girl.
It's your script, isn't it?
Anyway, I'm going to catch the prince's heart with this nice body.
Yeah!
Hey, what's wrong with Momotaro?
Ah, Momotaro...
Momotaro was taken by a turtle who saved him, and he went to the Ryubu Castle to get a leave of absence.
Long ago, long ago, Momotaro...
A turtle came to help a turtle...
That's Ureshima Taro, isn't it?
That's Momotaro, so it's fine.
Oh no, it's my turn...
Oh, it's a pity that I'm the only one who's free...
Hey, hey, you poor girl.
Ah, you...
What are you doing?
Entering the lower position on your own!
By the way, what are you?
Don't suddenly put in the ad-lib.
Huh? I'm a street-walking lover.
Momoko, do you want to join the swimming competition with girls?
Yes!
Then I will grant your wish.
"Mahariku Maharita"
A pumpkin will become a horse and a mouse will become a mouse.
One, two, three!
"Mahariku Maharita"
I want to be a glass bikini.
One, two, three!
Wow!
Thank you! Thank you!
Momoko, you must return at 12 o'clock.
I understand.
The magic will dissolve and return to the original "Boro".
No, the glass bikini will become transparent.
Stop it!
I'm kidding.
You see, it's a problem if you don't make it in time for the last train.
Momoko entered the castle to find the prince.
I'm the prince of this country,
looking for a bride.
So I gathered a young girl
and decided to open a swimming competition full of girls.
"Ushiyoshi Ushiyoshi Ushiyoshi!"
I don't want to play this kind of role.
Ouch!
Hey, "derai"
I played your best role.
Do it properly!
I got it!
"Uchiyoshi Ushiyoshi Ushiyoshi Ushiyoshi!"
Aikiba, let's start!
This is good!
Who should I choose?
That girl!
Marry me!
Come on, come on, you're a man!
You're a man, not a man!
What?
Momoko is going to go home at midnight
and she's going to drop the glass bra.
She'll look for a girl who suits her
and finally find Momoko.
Is that right?
I don't like this!
We can't just drop the bra!
That's right!
And we're so jealous of her
that we're going to be demons
and take her home.
Why are we the ones
who have to hold the swimming competition
when there are so many women?
Hey, hey, hey, wait!
Let's go home!
It's starting to get really crazy.
By the way, what's wrong with Momotaro?
Nakagawa! Terai!
I'm counting on you!
♪ Momotaro from long ago ♪
♪ I'm the best Momotaro in Japan ♪
♪ I came back from Ryugu Castle ♪
♪ I'm the best Momotaro ♪
All right!
Kennon!
I sandwiches!
Momotaro!
I'm sorry for being so cool, but it's hard to continue this play.
It's finally my turn.
Help me!
I won't let you run away!
It's finally a battle!
This year's play is unexpected and interesting!
What?
Maybe everyone...
Is everyone enjoying this play?
What's with this music?
Oh no!
I might have called Captain Bakuryuu with a real radio with this equipment!
Target found!
Prepare to launch the missile!
Stop!
Fire!
The End
This year's play is impressive!
Amazing!
Another Orio 2!
You did it on purpose!
Orio 2!
What are you doing?
This year's play is really fun!
It's fun!
End!
Go on!
Next!
End!
The End
I'm telling you the facts!
Everything I know!
What's wrong, senpai?
I'm all wet.
The brakes are broken.
The bike broke into one part.
You should change your clothes.
I'm all wet.
I'm sorry!
Wait a minute.
I'm counting on you.
Even if something happens, we can't go out.
We can't just wear the equipment naked.
What? A monk? Are you copying?
That's right.
You don't need a copy machine or fax to go to the temple, do you?
If you have such extra money, you can pay it back.
Even if you tell me, you should tell the chief.
A massage machine is more useful.
I was surprised.
I was copied.
What a disgusting composition.
But this is interesting.
Let's try a lot of things.
Ryu, let me iron it.
Oh, no!
What are you doing?
No, it's a misunderstanding.
It's a little experiment.
I don't know.
I'm in trouble.
I was treated as a pervert.
Of course.
But what are you doing?
I just played.
I found an interesting game.
Use the chief's photo.
Expand this and match it with the copy I just copied.
The chief's full picture is completed.
Isn't it interesting?
That's too much, senior.
That chief...
The chief is here?
I have a phone call.
It's in the book.
Don't scare me!
It's the manuscript I forgot yesterday.
Please send it to the library immediately.
But it's become a convenient era.
Mr. Ohara's essays in the library
are very popular.
I also put in effort to write.
Is the director's manuscript
in the copy machine?
I think so.
Director's manuscript?
It's an essay I wrote on the theme of
Japanese art.
I can't believe it!
What's the copy paper
there?
It's the director's manuscript.
Move!
As I thought.
No. If I send something like this!
It will be in the book.
I will get it!
It's the power.
I can't send it.
It seems that the copy
has already been sent.
Idiot!
I didn't notice because the cover was on the back.
I tried to explore this work a little.
The manuscript has arrived.
That's good.
I've been sent pictures one after another.
Will this be posted?
Yaaay!
ah
the summer of this year has arrived
it has come it has come
my voice keeps on singing
in the southern wind
I praise my large chest
like the father's piece
at this height
ah
the summer of this year has arrived
it has come it has come
♪ ♪
Wooo ha ha ha ha ha!
-Naigisabe- Poro poro!
-Olebri! -Poro poro!
Motu!
Heroes of Tejiru
What? Dera is a healing type?
Plus, it has a healing ability 30 times greater than a dolphin!
This is it! It's truly a healing type.
You can't use this guy.
I don't have a choice.
Alright, I'll take care of it.
Next time, "Take care of it and get rich!"
Please watch!
♪ Over there is Kameari! ♪
♪ Ah, I'm sure it's Kameari! ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town! ♪
Thank you!