"I'd love to see you myレミィ indiru."
Turn on the room light and watch TV when watching TV!
If you don't have enough money for anything, come over here!
We don't have any money, but we're worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
It'll all be alright eventually
Come to me, you jobless one
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red moon is burning
It'll all be alright eventually
I know, I know, I know
If you know, then keep quiet and follow me
The face of the red-winged one
Dyed in red
It's hot. I feel like I'm going to die.
This heat is really not good.
I'll take a break for a bit.
Here, 210 yen for two.
Wait a minute.
Where's the money?
Here you are.
Thanks.
Senpai!
What's wrong?
Shit! I bought ice cream!
That's probably one of the reasons.
Mirror building?
It's suddenly increased recently.
It reflects the sun's light and lights up the place where it usually shines, so the temperature doesn't go down.
Thanks to that, my room is also bright.
It's a terrible situation.
It's like a sauna.
It's so hot even though I'm closing the curtains.
This is the cause.
There's a mirror building in front of us!
Yeah. Thanks to that, the sun is shining on dozens of people.
It's like the sun is shining on the sun.
This is terrible.
I don't need a double-decker.
This is like a nuisance.
Senpai, my head is getting numb.
Ouch! It's a heat stroke!
It's dangerous to enter the room during the day.
Don't you have a cooler?
I don't have one.
It's just cheap for a chicken.
I don't have one that costs as much as a cooler.
Hey, Hojo.
It's the day off today.
Oh, yes.
I'm going to the library.
Let's go back to the office.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Hojo's not sweating at all.
What?
By the way,
it's a great temperature inside here in the mirror building.
He shouldn't be sweating.
That bastard.
Could it be...
Here you go, Hojo!
Seriously.
Wow.
Wow, it's so cool.
It's like heaven.
Oh, I'm sweating.
I knew it.
Hojo, you're hiding the cooler, aren't you?
What proof do you have?
This coolness is proof.
It's because I'm turning the fan.
Just turning the fan won't make you this cool.
Or is it because of the cooling function?
The fan has some function.
What's that?
And the hot pot.
In summer, the only place where you can eat hot pot is a house with a cooler.
What?
Find it thoroughly.
Yes, sir.
I found it.
It's a cooler.
The outdoor unit is being disguised as a orange box.
I see.
If it was a cooler, everyone would be in pain.
But that cooler is...
I... I sent it from the country.
I didn't need it at home.
Why is it set up secretly to avoid people's eyes?
When people find out there's a cooler,
everyone will go to the room and live a peaceful life.
That's what I thought!
Kikuri.
Are you still a policeman?
I thought you were a policeman.
What?
As a police officer, you must always think about public interest.
But you are prioritizing your own interests now.
You have no right to call yourself a police officer!
So,
we will use this room.
What?
Ouch!
You want to play another game?
Of course!
I can't sweat even if I move my body this much.
Cooler is so cool.
Cooler is so comfortable.
You can't live like this alone, Hojo.
What?
Ho...
Wow, it's so cool.
There's a cooler in Hojo's room.
Really?
There was a rumor that there was a cooler in Hojo's room.
Well...
Who are you?
Please give us some coolness.
Here! Here!
Is this the room with the cooler?
Hey!
Hey, wait a minute!
Don't come in so much!
Wait!
Hey, you're in the way!
Ah! So painful!
This is not a game.
It doesn't make sense if there are so many humans in the cooler.
But there's only this room with the cooler.
Can I have all of this air duct?
Eh? No problem.
What are you doing, man?
Hmm...
I'm sending the coolers to other rooms.
What?
Alright.
Switch it on.
Whoa, it's so cool in here!
I did it!
Yay!
You did it, man!
Really?
Oh, um...
What?
If you block that source,
there won't be any cold air in this room.
Your Majesty, the spirits of this place must be distributed fairly among the people of Ryo.
I see.
But you have already monopolized the spirits for several days.
So you don't have any for the rest of your life.
How long is the rest of my life?
It's about six months.
It's winter, isn't it?
It's your own choice, you idiot!
Take care of this remote control.
Don't play with the switch on your own.
Senpai, are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's better to feel a little hot for him.
It's hot.
It's cool.
It's very comfortable.
It's about time...
That bastard stopped the cooler!
Hey, what are you doing?
That's what...
He stopped it suddenly...
What's going on, senpai?
It's hot.
Be strong.
You're the only one who can rely on it.
You did it!
Oh!
The cooler...
Covering everything with just one cooler was reckless
Damn it
No good, it's not cool even in the shade
I need a cooler
What was that?
What?
Ryo-san
What's this cooler?
The customer bought a new cooler and took it away
It's a waste, we can still use it
Really?
Alright, I'll take all of them
All of them?
Ryo-san, you really got a lot of coolers?
Yeah
Wow
Please install it in my room too
Me too! Me too!
Of course, I'll install it
However, the installation fee is 10,000 yen per unit
Of course, we don't want to volunteer
If you don't like it, you have to put up with it
I don't like it
I'll pay you
Please understand
knew we were going to meet at the end
I knew it
Good for you
I think you'll be able to play games with confidence
Wow
It's wonderful
It's cool!
Cool!
Well, it's different from having a cooler.
I also had a temporary income.
From today, I will be able to live comfortably.
Motion is still going.
What's wrong?
Grandma, what's wrong?
Is it a break-out?
It seems so.
Damn it.
The power cable broke.
Is it because everyone turned on the coolers?
The old coolers had a lot of electricity.
I don't know.
I'm going to call an electrician.
But it might take time to repair.
What?
Then, why don't you use a cooler?
Give me the money back.
I know.
I swear.
What?
How much?
How much does it cost per case?
Purchase.
What?
It's still the same as before.
I have no idea.
I can't afford it.
It's more like water thaniplane.
Yes.
It seems to me that you've done something great.
It's like a sports toy.
A sports toy?
Yes.
I think I can remember things.
I see! So that's how it was!
What?
Hehehe...
I'll use you from now on, for the revenge you've put us through!
I'll make you pay for it!
At this company, we're currently studying solar panels used for solar power.
What's that?
A lot of nico-nico from Katsushika.
Wow, that's a lot of solar energy!
It's a perfect place for a solar panel test.
Right? Leave it to me!
I'll test your new products!
Power on!
Wow, the needles are working at once!
Amazing!
That's a lot of power!
Alright! Let's turn on the coolers in the room!
Yes!
Alright!
Next!
It's alright! We still have plenty of power!
I see!
Now we're done with the heat of summer!
Hahahahahahaha
Awww, that's aРelly nice.
It's cooler than my apartment.
Right?
In these cold temperatures, it's the coldest.
I don't sweat even when I work out.
Just a real...
But there's enough power in here.
So no need to force the cooler.
It's okay to make the cooler the strongest.
How about you move in?
Oh, I'll think about it.
He's still a tough guy.
I'm so sad that I have to go back to this fucking hot country.
Shit...
I have something prepared for you.
What is it?
It's a cooler suit made of the leftover cooler.
The cooling comes out of the back of the cooler,
and the hose is used to enter the suit and cool the body.
But it looks hot.
The machine on the back looks heavy.
It's true that this is heavy.
It's an old-fashioned cooler, so it can't be helped.
I'm sweating just standing up.
Wait.
I'll make it today.
Oh, I'm sweating for a moment.
No matter how much you move, you'll never sweat.
You look sick.
It's too heavy to load the battery, but it's long enough.
Take a walk over there.
Wow, it's so sunny, but it's not hot at all.
It's too cold.
I have to raise the temperature.
I can't do it.
I can't reach it.
It's cold.
What?
I'll be back in a hurry.
I'm dying of cold.
Please turn off the switch.
Let's go.
There was a problem with the position of the switch.
This time it will be fine.
Hmm?
Perfect.
Then I'll walk over there for a while.
What are you doing, Ryo?
What?
It's a little experiment.
Hmm?
Hmm.
This is pretty good.
The heat outside is like a lie.
Hmm?
It's getting a little hot.
Let's do it today.
Now I can sweat for a moment.
I'll pull it out in a moment.
I'll pull it out.
I can't do it.
What's going on?
Huh?
I'm back.
It's fluttering.
Did something happen?
I'm dying of heat.
What?
Oh, the cord.
I can't do it.
Don't pull the cord out and pull it out.
Is that so?
Wait a minute.
I'll recover it now.
What?
It's rules.
I'll make you cry.
Are you all right, Bulba?
Hey.
It's hell.
I saw the nature.
It is dangerous to walk with the power cord.
It's too dangerous to walk with a cord.
It's better to have a battery.
The more we sell, the more electricity we have.
It's a waste if we don't use it.
Then how about we actually sell it?
What?
I think the power generated by solar power will be bought by the power company.
Really?
Yay!
It's from the power company.
Oh, there are 200,000 too.
That's a lot of money.
No, we can't let it go like this.
We need to give more power.
Give more power?
We used the power of that mirror building.
That's why we got this much power.
There's no way we can do anything else.
That's right.
There's a limit to the amount of solar power we can use.
Then we just have to collect the light.
What?
We need to collect the power of this place.
That's right.
We have to start the power of this place.
We need to start the power of this place.
It's that guy.
This angle, I think.
I saw it.
It's Does it work?
It's a success.
The power generated is rising.
Hojo, are you there?
What?
I saw you.
You're not reading a book.
Help me.
What?
What is it?
Gather the light!
Help everyone who is left in the dorm!
Huh?
Ah, it's hot.
Why are you even asking me?
Hey, Hatta.
Alright, alright.
No, it won't come out.
If we don't contact them quickly, it will be a big problem.
Today at 1:45 PM.
In other words, the light reflected on the mirror building around the dorm will be concentrated in the Nico Nico dorm,
and it will instantly become an incredible high temperature.
No one will come to Ryo's phone,
and if this happens, I have no choice but to fly directly to the site.
Prepare the helicopter immediately!
Yes!
Now the power generation is even better!
What is that?
This should be enough.
It's really hot.
I'll go back to my room.
This...
This is gathering the light!
How can it be?
If it's like this, it's ridiculous!
Stop it, Senpai!
This is the only place where the air is rising so much!
What is he doing?
The temperature is rising more and more!
There's not even a minute left!
Are you sure?
Senpai, please stop it already!
President, I can't do this!
I have no time!
No, this doesn't work!
He's getting more tired!!
It's going too fast!
You can't get out of bed until you return!
Don't go back!
We don't have much time left!
Senpai!
I can't do it anymore.
I'm leaving!
Too much light!
The amount of "nico-nico" has...
... melted!
Welcome!
Please come in!
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
Yes!
Would you like a California Maki?
No California Maki!
We're not in America!
I'm sorry!
Well...
Um...
I'm sorry!
Welcome!
Then...
Kushi-age, Kaki-age, Katsu-age,
What is it?
Age-age?
What do you recommend?
Be careful with Katsu-age!
Huh?
Is it a gag from my father?
Yes!
I'm sorry!
I don't get it.
Huh?
Really?
Welcome!
Summer vacation is coming to an end.
Why can't Lemon take me anywhere?
What? He'll take me to a different place?
And I'll meet a real ninja?
Yay! Lemon has always admired ninjas!
Next time, "Lemon will become a ninja of the 9-1-1!"
Don't miss it!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a Kameari ♪
♪ Come on everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!