Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset floating on the river
and fly to the place where I found my love
I laughed the
Like the nice sound of the good energy somewhere
meets the putst
and even the evil blond
The cityscape is a bit gentle
Theará
The symposiums were hung by the слыш pushing the window
There is the
The Master.
What the
what's the matter?
Zarwell.
The memories of the "Yatai"!
How is it?
Oh, Reiko-kun, it looks good on you.
Chief...
Is this fine?
Is something wrong?
No, it's just...
Kei-chan, the kimono of a man should be closed lower.
I did what you told me to do!
By the way, I can't see Ryo-san running to the fire.
Ryo-chan is going to pick up Lemon-chan.
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, cute!
Yeah, it looks good on you.
Really?
That's the spirit of the Edo area!
Is that so?
There are many people, so don't get separated.
Yeah!
Alright, let's go!
If we don't hurry, we'll miss the shrine maiden!
Wait, Ryo-chan!
I'm going!
Even though it's a secret, be careful not to get drunk or fight.
Yes!
That's good.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Nice!
How is it?
It's quite good.
Eh, don't you also feel dizzy because you wanted to get up?
No, I'm playing Lemon's role.
Or so you might say...
I can see that you're holding back.
Kankichi!
What?
I want to hit that big taiko, Lemon!
Me?
Okay, leave it to me!
Hey, let me hit this one too!
Oh, Ryo-san, that's good.
Don't hesitate.
Okay, here, Lemon.
Don't hesitate, just hit it as hard as you can.
Yeah!
Good, good!
That's the way!
You're on the right rhythm!
You're a real adult.
Goldfish scooping, huh?
Okay, that's it!
Lemon, let's go get some goldfish!
And then we'll go and get some dolls!
Senpai, you're really good.
Let's go!
Goldfish scooping is all about spirit!
Now we have a lot!
How's that?
Please, don't bother!
It's gonna break!
Yeah!
It's gonna be great!
Don't underestimate a innocent police officer!
I'm here!
I'm sorry!
Here it is!
So much!
I feel like I've forgotten something.
Oh, no! What did I do?
Lemon!
Hey, Lemon!
Where are you? Lemon!
Lemon!
What's wrong, senpai?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Didn't you see Lemon?
Lemon was looking at candy craftsman Nessie.
I saw him at the cotton candy shop.
I see.
Lemon!
Huh?
There he is!
Lemon!
Huh?
No, no.
Lemon!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Maybe it's Kan-chan.
What?
It's Miharu!
You were at a candy shop with that maiden old lady?
Yes, it's been a while.
To meet her at this place.
Lemon!
"I'm so happy!"
"It's over!"
"What's this, Kankichi?"
"Are you here to see the festival?"
"Well, after class, I can go to the shrine!"
"Hey!"
"Oh, well..."
"I'm so happy!"
"We're starting the child shrine!"
"Come on!"
"Yes!"
"Oh!"
"Hurry up! Hurry up!"
"We need to find the best spot!"
"Yeah!"
"Yari! You're the best!"
"I'm the best!"
"Hey, that's great!"
"Oh, Bunta and Akira from Tonorimochi!"
"But... The HISA is at first..."
"Oh,53!
"Hey, Yari...
Let's go!
You're really something!
Yeah!
It's hot!
All right, Chinkichi!
chinkichi!
It's an attack from God Wind!
What?!
Yeah!
Go!
That's it.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I told you not to carry the mikoshi to the fight!
You are not allowed to carry mikoshi!
It's boring that mikoshi is not allowed to be carried even though tomorrow is the real festival.
What, you can just sneak it in and carry it.
What?
It's strange.
There are always yakisoba and okonomiyaki stalls there.
Oh, from Miharu's grandmother.
Maybe something happened to her.
I think we should go to the back of this shrine.
Let's go!
Yeah!
No, grandma, you have to sleep.
When I hear that festival, my body starts moving on its own.
Didn't I tell you not to move?
I'm fine for a bit.
What's wrong?
What?
I'm so sick of this.
Grandma!
Hey, what's wrong?
Let me go.
I have to go to the shop.
You can't do that.
Otherwise, I may not be able to get the place.
Is that what that gorilla is saying?
I don't care about the place.
He will take care of all festivals around here.
I prefer to find a place for myself.
I always thought the best idea was to leave the shop,
but I didn't have time to do that.
That's what makes us lovable.
You're right.
Good.
We'll do it instead.
What?
If we do it, we can do it.
As promised, we'll show the shop.
Okay?
All right.
What a nice idea!
I will help you, too.
Grandma, rest in peace and rest.
You two.
You guys...
I won't forgive you for your half-hearted work.
I'm counting on you for today's Yoimiya and tomorrow's Honmiya.
Leave it to me!
Thank you, Kanchan, Ton-chan, and Chinkichi-kun.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, everything's ready.
We've turned on the lights, and we've prepared the propane.
Then let's start cooking. First, let's prepare the Okonomiyaki flour and vegetables.
Miharu-chan, prepare the packs and the chopsticks.
Okay.
Ton-pei, light the fire. Let's start with the yakisoba.
Chinkichi, use the fire to lure the customers in.
Okay!
Fire!
The fire is too strong!
No, no, no! Don't drink the water!
"The highest mountain in the Akagi Mountains,
couldn't be separated from the cute, innocent you guys!"
Don't stay there…
Kankichi, the Okonomiyaki became a monkfish.
I was too indecisive.
Today, I'll use the flour…
Ebonhe
Yeah it looks pretty good!
Now here we go!
Yeah!
Welcome!
Ah, Sanba!
Why do you guys have to be doing this!
It's not that important! Something happened!
Huh?
Huh? I don't know what it is, but it's a pretty cheap restaurant.
Kan-chan.
Shut up. You're in my way. Go home!
What's with you? We're trying to buy it for you.
That's right! We're customers!
Customers are gods.
You're so sweet. Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Three yakisoba, please. I'll serve you.
Good.
Here you go.
You did it, Kankichi.
You're in my way.
It's a special yakisoba with red pepper and red pepper paste.
Hey, you guys.
What the hell is this?
A bearded gorilla.
The End
This is where Mrs. Tomei's yakisoba should be.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, yeah. Who are you going to refuse to open a shop?
Kankichi.
I'm going to help the shop with Mrs. Tomei.
What?
Sorry.
Don't be so rude.
I'm not rude.
I'm going to beat up the bearded gorilla.
There's no need for a bearded gorilla.
I'm sorry, bearded...
No, Kankichi.
What's wrong? Are you drunk?
Yeah.
It's true.
It's like Mrs. Tomei and her granddaughter are there.
Oh.
My grandmother can't go out of the shop.
I can't go out of the shop.
So I open the shop as an extension of this.
I can't go out of the shop, so I can't go in.
The problem is that we're not thinking of giving up.
That's why I'll only open the shop.
I can't.
Well, you old man.
If you don't go out of the shop, I'll break the whole house down.
Because, there are no shortage of young people in the school.
Yes, but...
What are you talking about?
I'm running the shop instead of you.
What?
Do you understand what you're saying?
Oh, I see.
But it's not a child's play. It's not a play.
We're not playing.
No matter what you say, I won't get out of here.
Me too.
Big brother.
You're a good boy.
I'll let you go today.
But if you're in trouble, be ready.
I'm about to puke.
Thank you, Kan-chan, Ton-chan, and Chinkichi.
What? I'm not scared of a hedgehog.
Kan-chan.
What?
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm just a little nervous.
Yeah.
You're so noisy.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
I thought it would be easier.
It was all about failure at first.
What? It's a big deal for the first time.
That's right. Tomorrow is the real night.
I'll do my best from morning.
You can rest in peace.
Yeah.
It was so cool.
What will happen to the stall if that happens?
It's been a while since we've been here.
We'll protect it!
Are you serious, Kankichi?
What if the storm blows up the stall?
We'll be out of business!
Shut up!
Why, grandma?
You don't have to go that far.
Just a little bit is enough.
We're going to do it.
I don't want to just sit around and do nothing.
Tan-chan!
Me too! Me too!
Kankichi!
Tan-chan!
Tan-chan, what's wrong?
Do you want to go?
Yes.
Peek-a-boo!
I did it!
I'm going to tie the firewood to the tree with this string!
Hang in there!
Alright!
Ugh!
We're going to be fine for a while!
We have to be patient until morning!
We can't sleep!
Y-Yeah!
We're going to be blown off!
Yeah!
It's our stall!
Ewww!
Ugh!
My seat!
Damn!
It's no good!
The other stalls will be blown off!
Ugh!
What should we do?
If other stalls get blown off, this won't be a festival!
And we can't protect all of the stalls on our own!
Ugh!
What should I do? Damn! What should I do?
Who is it? What are you doing there?
You guys...
Higun... Gorilla...
If we get kicked out of the store, we won't be able to hold the festival anymore!
Gather the ropes and tie the people in the store together!
Gather as many young people as you can!
Yes sir!
Oh, and...
Take off your kappa.
Yes sir!
Damn, you've seen it all.
Let's go, you guys.
Come on, do your best!
Huh?
Tomorrow is the festival too.
Yeah!
Ah, bubor.
I see...
You really did it, right?
Thank you.
I did it too, did I not?
Yeah!
We did our best.
Watch out!!
Yes sir!
What are you doing?
That happened?
Kan-chan was very manly at that time.
I don't think about it later.
I don't need to do this.
I'm always at the station.
Come and play with me sometimes.
Yes.
Bye bye.
Lemon, lemon.
Kankichi!
What?
Kankichi, you were here.
I looked for you.
You're right, Ryu-chan.
It was a lot of people.
I said I was looking for you.
You're right.
You're really good to me.
I mean, I'm better than you.
But it was fun.
The festival.
I see.
Here we go.
Kan-chan's children.
It's like her.
Really.
When she's doing that, she's like Ryu-chan's child.
You're right.
Okay, Lemon.
You can make your own cotton candy over there.
Want to go?
Really, Kankichi?
Okay, let's go.
Yeah.
*
10 games, 10 games, I'll write down my thoughts and then go to sleep
I always wear sandals, always have scandals, don't worry
Don't worry
I play the Kooner every day
Every day
I threw my boredom away in the end-of-the-year book
I'm an idiot with no sense of purpose
I'm innocent, I'm poor, that's a piece of cake
Right?
I just do what I want, whatever I want
One lightning strike and a smoke from under my head
If I run and run away, it's right on the camera
It's perfect
On a flower- flavored head
A mass-produced typhoon
I'll find my way back
libro.com
10 games, 10 games, I'll write my thoughts and then go to sleep
forward leaving reward
Working classroom
for work
I'm feeling dizzy
and dozing off
in the other room
Mr. and Mrs. Yan, Mr. Yan
Mr. and Mrs. Yan
we're all
ografi
got
our checkered
checkered
Pocala
and our
super sixty-five
調介
"Ha Ha"
The club president
started to dance?
I'm so embarrassed
It doesn't suit me!
What, you're a temple?
What, Borubo and Sahonji too?
Wait a minute!
There's something wrong with this!
Alright! I'll join too!
Next time on Dance! Dance! Dance!
Don't miss it!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, Kitto Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!