『Hana Re Te Mite Ne...』
中川に浮かぶある日を めがけて Nakagawa ni ukabu aru hi o megakete Bright and sunny by the Nav biliary
When I kicked the tree, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if it's going to be a good time to save money
I was laughed at that it was just a tree
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are only thorns and thorns
There is no one bad day
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of the Tongari-boshi
The sun sets to the Taishakuten
Tomorrow will end tomorrow
tomorrow will end tomorrow
I'm not happy
I lost my happiness
And I realized
I'm an idiot
A man of love, Ryo-tsu Kankichi
People call me the love-hunt
I was popular since I was a child
But what's wrong?
When I came with recent girls
I didn't know my charm
If I think about the stories I heard
I think I'm different
I'm a woman
I'm a man
I'm the first man I don't want to marry
I'm the number one
10 years in a row
I think there's a woman
who understands my wonderfulness
somewhere
Burn, the island of love
The island of love
To the sea
To other people
The island of love
Isn't it grand?
Wait a bit
Wait a minute. Why do I have to go to Hokkaido?
There is a girl I know in Hokkaido.
Let's meet up.
When I showed you the photo, you seemed to like it.
I said I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
So I thought I'd see you before you changed your mind.
There is an important meeting tomorrow, so you should go first.
I understand. I'm going to Hokkaido.
I'll pay you back if you give me a flight ticket.
If I can get a 3-day leave and get money back...
What is it, Chief?
Don't tell me you want to pay back the ticket.
No, I don't want to. I don't want to do that.
Listen, Ryotsu.
I'll come to the meeting as soon as the meeting is over.
If you don't go to Hokkaido, what will happen to me?
That's a threat, isn't it?
Then I won't see you.
You idiot!
You're getting old, and if you don't have savings, you don't have a home.
You liked me and sent me a ticket to Hokkaido.
I won't do this again!
I understand.
If only we could meet a little.
That's fine.
You're a woman I like at first sight.
And what kind of woman is she?
That's right.
Her style is like that of Fujiwara Nori.
Oh, the one with the nice body?
Her hairstyle is like that of Ina Mori Izumo.
That's amazing!
That's a misunderstanding.
No, wait a minute.
What about her face?
Face?
It's hard to say, but to put it bluntly...
To put it bluntly?
Shimura Kento and Hanako Yamada were split by two.
And they couldn't sleep at night.
And I thought that Nagagawa came to pick me up in the morning.
But I'm stuck in a seat.
Both the chief and Nagagawa do not trust him at all.
I'm so suspicious.
Where do I get in?
You idiot!
Be careful!
I'm sorry.
I saw him somewhere.
He's a man with a good sense of taste.
"Akimoto"
Huh? What's wrong?
It's pretty warm.
I thought it'd be colder this season.
Lord Ryochi!
Do you need anything from me?
Actually...
What? You switched the flight tickets?
I bumped into the cartoonist Akimoto in Haneda's lobby.
In Haneda?
Oh, that's right.
So this isn't Hokkaido?
It's Kagoshima.
Kagoshima?
Anyway, please return to Haneda with the return flight.
You're kidding me!
I took a three-day leave.
I'm going back to Haneda and go to Hokkaido.
Thank you.
If you don't return, you'll be in trouble for a whole day!
Even if you say that...
All right! I'll talk to the cartoonist Akimoto.
Thank you for your help.
Oh.
Are you Akimoto?
Yes.
I have to go to Okinoerabujima for an interview, so please come back soon.
Okinoerabujima?
It's an island between Amami Oshima and Okinawa.
Oh.
The locals should be waiting for me.
Then I'll go there and interview you.
So you go to Sapporo instead of me and meet me.
That's ridiculous.
I'm a good man.
Shut up!
I decided that, so do it!
See you!
I've talked to him.
I'm going to Okinoerabujima.
Really?
Yes.
Take me to the plane to Okinoerabujima.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Chief Ohara!
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
I just got a call from the dad of Ryo-chan's fiancé at the exit.
He said he wanted to take the plane he was planning to take.
What? Ryo-chan did go to Haneda this morning, didn't he?
Yes, he took me there by car. There's no doubt about it.
If he's not sleeping, where is he?
I thought he was a famous manga artist, so I thought he was a more difficult person.
But he's a pretty mean person.
Chief, wait a minute.
What?
Stop! Stop!
What's wrong, Chief?
Who are you?
I don't want to. Ryo... No, I mean, I'm Akimoto Osamu.
I'm Akimoto Sensei.
You!
This is terrible! You're going to make me sleep!
You should've told me in Sapporo!
Why do I have to marry you instead of you?
You!
Wait a minute.
What?
What's going on?
You!
It's hot. My throat is dry. I'm dying.
Water... Rain?
I'm going home.
Why is it raining in the desert?
Hey!
You idiot! What are you doing?
I'm sorry!
I didn't know you were in such a place!
Shut up! You're drunk!
What's wrong, Hiroshi?
Ritsuo?
Hiroshiro?
Thats...
I know you and Ritsuo!
Ritsuo?
Ritsuo-san?
I have a dozen of them.
Ryoichi-san, are you sure?
It's the first time I've met you, and you're carrying all your stuff.
I was just sleeping.
Yuriko-sensei, this old man tried to hit me earlier.
Hey, what are you saying, Boku-chan?
But it's great to be able to educate children in this kind of nature.
Is that so?
It's wonderful.
The kids in Tokyo are so naive, they can't do anything about it.
The children on the island are cute.
The children in Tokyo are cute.
15 minutes by ship from Elabujima.
That's quite close, isn't it?
But there are only 3 ships a day.
The last one is the evening return.
This is the elementary school I teach.
It's a really small school.
Yuriko-sensei is back!
Yuriko sensei!
I'm back!
Everyone's so cute!
Yuriko sensei, who's this?
It's like a gorilla!
It's rude to meet you for the first time.
This is Ryotsu-san, who brought us the marble and coral for the school.
Let's greet him.
Hello!
As expected of Yuriko sensei, you're polite and polite.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, but can you take this to the science room?
Yes, yes, I understand.
Then, Shinji-kun, Hiromi-chan, please.
Yes!
This is the science room.
I can't do it.
I'm in trouble.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
Oh, this is a little stiff.
You have to fix it.
Hey, bring the nails and tongs.
Yes!
Just a little bit.
You don't have to do that.
I'll fix it, I'm good at it.
I'll fix it soon.
This school is a mess.
By the way, I'll fix it all.
You do your own work!
Is that okay?
I'm sorry.
Then I'll be in the office.
Hey, Yuriko sensei, are you still a single child?
Yeah.
I see.
I see...
Your luck is back now.
I've been waiting for you!
You idiot!
I said get out of here!
Get out!
Ah, wait, no, I said get out!
Okay, now this is perfect.
Wow, it's perfect!
It's only a few hours away.
I can't thank you enough.
Don't thank me.
Oh, no! The last flight to Erav Island has left.
Yeah, the inn will stop at Minshikun, so don't worry.
But there's no such facility on this island.
What a perverse place.
If you don't mind, can you come to my house?
It's a small place.
No, I can't go to a single single woman's house.
I can sleep in the school's bathroom.
Please let me treat you to dinner.
What? Dinner?
This is about me?
Oh, but...
Oh, I'm so weak.
It hurts!
I was really happy, but I was embarrassed.
Shut up!
Don't tease me!
Wait!
I'm not going to sleep!
Hey!
So you fixed all the doors in the school's bathroom, right?
That's right, Mrs. Ryotsu.
You're very clever, Mr. Ryotsu.
Well, I'm not that clever.
I didn't think I'd live with an old lady from the gym in the school's bathroom.
You're so good at talking.
What happened, Mr. Ryotsu?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
More importantly, are there only you and Mrs. Ryotsu in the school's bathroom?
I used to have five of them, but now there are only two of them.
A new teacher is coming from Kagoshima, but...
It's not easy.
It must be hard for you two to clean up the classroom.
All right, I'll help you tomorrow.
What?
The classroom's bed and chair are broken.
If possible, you should repaint the classroom's paint.
Besides, I can't teach you how to study, but I can teach you how to do the gym.
But, Mr. Ryotsu, you're a police officer, right?
Is that okay?
It's fine.
My boss is always bullying me.
Sometimes I want to live in the rich nature.
I see.
Then I'll count on you, Ms. Yuriko.
But...
It's fine.
You're like your ex-boyfriend.
You have a new love for him.
Ms. Yuriko!
Yes, thank you.
I have something to do early tomorrow, so I'll get some rest.
Then, Mr. Ryotsu, I'll leave it to you tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
You must be tired today.
There's a futon in the next room, so please take a rest.
Oh, okay.
Um, Ms. Yuriko, are you from this island?
No, I'm from Nagasaki.
Why did you come to this island?
Well...
I like children.
Then, you must have a elementary school in Nagasaki.
Why did you come to such a strange island?
Because there was something I didn't like about Nagasaki.
You mean him?
Yes.
He's different from Mr. Ryotsu.
He's not friendly or manly.
I'm not friendly or manly.
I'm manly, after all.
Once you decide something, you have to do it no matter what.
That's right.
I'm going to make a test problem, so please take a rest.
Oh, really?
Then, good night.
Damn it.
I can't sleep well when I think that Ms. Yuriko is next to me.
She's a good woman.
If I could marry her...
But, Ms. Yuriko is a true Japanese.
I want my child to be able to play baseball team.
What's wrong?
I had a bad dream.
Oh, my.
I want my child to be like Ms. Yuriko.
Okinoe Love Island?
Why are you there?
I'm not going to be long if you talk to me.
Idiot!
I'm not your father.
You're so mean to me.
I think I might get married.
What?
I met the ideal woman.
Really?
Yes.
Anyway, don't worry.
Bye.
Hey!
Damn it.
What's wrong?
Ryotsu's ideal woman appeared.
I think I might get married.
What?
Everyone, I have a very good news today.
Mr. Ryotsu, who fixed the school gate yesterday, will help me today.
What?
I'm looking forward to it.
Peace, peace.
Mr. Ryotsu, is the teacher of the high school good?
Leave it to me.
Come on, get out of here.
But I have to change my clothes.
Come on, run.
I'm a grand master.
I knew it.
Mr. Kuriko, you're different from a man.
Really.
It'll be a great help.
Alright, I'll give you a test.
Ichiro!
Good job!
Hiroshi!
That's mean.
Everyone, be careful now.
Some people think that studying won't help them, but...
That's right! Life is fun because it can be done.
What's important in life is that you can do whatever you decide to do.
That's my policy.
So, that's all for today.
-Yuki-sensei. -Yuriko-sensei.
You've gotten used to the children.
Did you hear that?
I love children too, so I've become a hot-tempered child.
How long will you stay on this island?
How long?
If it's okay with you, I'll stay forever.
I'll stop being a police officer and become a teacher.
That's great.
Great?
Yuriko-sensei.
This is definitely Yuriko-sensei's...
...punishment.
It might be the greatest confession from a girl.
Yuriko-sensei, I've got a delivery.
Delivery?
Yuriko-sensei wants to stay with me forever.
Alright, let's make a confession.
I love you! Please marry me!
No, I don't want to, Ryotsu-san.
I'm over 50 years old.
But if you're serious about it, you should think about it.
Yuriko-sensei is...
Yuriko-sensei.
What's wrong?
You seem to be crying.
What is it?
I can't make up my mind.
I'm sorry for making you sad.
I'm in Kagoshima City now.
My parents won't let me marry you.
So I left home yesterday.
I want to see you right away.
And we can talk.
Don't cry.
Did I cry out of happiness?
We're going back to Tokyo?
You said you would stay here forever.
It's fun being a teacher.
But I think I love to be a police officer.
I think the people in the police force worry about that too.
Yuriko-sensei, the typhoon is coming, and the ship is damaged.
I'm sick of it.
I guess we shouldn't do it today.
If a man says something, he must do it no matter what.
I've taught the kids that.
Boss, are you sure we can swim to Kagoshima?
I'm confident.
We'll reach Satamisaki in 20 hours.
We can return to Tokyo by train from Kagoshima.
But it's too dangerous.
We don't know where we'll be in this storm.
Don't worry.
Besides, Ms. Yuriko,
you should care about your children's happiness,
but also yours.
Mr. Ryotsu...
Could it be that letter...
Sorry, I read it.
Mr. Ryotsu, I...
I...
I'm sorry.
Listen to Ms. Yuriko!
Okay?
Yeah.
Goodbye!
Mr. Ryotsu
Thanks to Mr. Ryotsu,
I was able to start over again with him.
He also came here
and he'll teach us the script with us.
Thank you so much.
I sincerely wish you happiness.
From Yuriko
Senpai, it seems like you were dumped.
Even so, where on earth did you go?
That idiot.
Why, why is it Hong Kong even though I swam for ten days without drinking or eating?
You're already in love, aren't you?
Idiot!
If it's you, then I'd rather wake up.
Even if it's a boring story,
I want to make the whole body hot.
I want to see my friends.
I definitely want to be loved.
I don't want everyone to hate me.
I feel like we're melting.
I definitely want to be loved.
For some reason, love is just cowardly.
Don't hide everything about being strong.
Wow!
You're really a crazy professor!
This time, it's the Air Police!
And what's with this plane?
It's not a surprise human contest.
You don't have to fly with this.
Next time, "The Crazy Air Police".
That's why I said I don't want to!