" horseshoe"
Once you see the television,
bright the room to watch them away from you.
The people without money, come to me!
I don't know either, but I feel worried
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
I'm sure it'll be okay
You know it, right? You know it, you know it!
If you know it, then shut up and follow me!
The End
Thank you for watching!
Next time, I'll be back with a more interesting story.
Let's go home.
Okay.
What do you want?
Well...
Kankichi said he'd use your mail.
No, it's not that.
Please take this.
Okay.
I have a lemon on my phone.
That's not a normal phone.
You can type with the voice.
What do you mean?
You can just talk to it.
That's convenient.
But I can't get an answer from Lemon.
I have the same phone, but I'll try it.
Mail.
What is it?
Oh, you're talking.
Yes, well...
To Lemon Ghiboshi.
Okay.
What's the title?
Oh.
Test.
Here's the content.
Hello, Lemon-san.
That's really convenient.
Send.
I sent a mail.
Oh.
Please say "mail" on your phone.
Mail.
Wow, it's all hiragana.
I thought it would be easy to send a mail.
Yeah.
And thank you.
I'll use it carefully.
Yeah.
Lemon's Parenting Diving Machine
Cute.
You've grown up so much.
Yeah, it's been six months.
You look like Matoi-chan.
I look like Lemon-chan.
We're sisters.
Yeah.
Hey, you.
Good Прек Acting Books.
Pretty good.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
I've never seen you before.
This is...
àn Vaccination D kr.
I don't know.
This is what I am all about.
Oh, it's all about you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
If I meet her like she does, we get to talk.
Do you want to leave?
Fine.
Hey!
差ね or fucking Verse 3 and all that so it's not okay stop.
You're letting a little boy enter your house?
I can't help it.
When I get a bit of a salary, I come to get sushi.
I'm working at the restaurant on my own.
I'm sure Ryo-chan Kichi is going to do something.
Shut up!
I'm a relative of the Gibon family!
Don't interrupt me about your family!
Hmph!
Yeah.
Well, well.
Hey, Matoi.
Can you come out in the magazine?
What?
My friend is an editor at a baby magazine.
She's looking for cute babies.
It's not a big deal.
Really?
I think she'll be happy.
Wow!
Ahaha!
You're already in the entertainment world!
I'm not!
I'm just taking pictures of baby magazines.
This is a corner where you introduce babies.
No, I don't understand.
Idols are getting younger and younger.
Momos' little sister's little sister.
Well, I'm sorry for being the other little sister.
Oh, well.
I'm sorry.
You, too.
Then, please.
Well, Mika.
You, too.
Mika.
Oh!
There you are!
You've gotten better, Lemon!
The baby drinks the air with you.
It must be hard to put it out.
It's hard to say.
Lemon didn't really make a big difference.
That's not true.
It's true.
Because I'm the one who held Lemon.
Don't be so angry, Lemon.
Lemon was a baby 3 or 4 years ago.
I was, too.
Did Kankichi have a baby?
Yes.
Look, it's Lemon's album.
Which one?
Don't look at it because it's embarrassing.
It's an album that's a little embarrassing.
Which one?
Is this Lemon?
It's cute.
It was a baby who didn't cry at all.
It's the same as now.
Are you praising that?
This is another Lemon.
It's like a baby.
You're wrong about a parent and a child.
If it's an orange, it's a perfect parent and child.
It's okay.
Lemon will take care of the oranges.
I'm sorry.
Put a baby in a bottle.
It's time for the interview.
Yeah.
I'm nervous.
You're okay.
We're with you, so we'll do it.
Oh, here they come.
Wow! Out of the blue?
Hmm?
Hey, Ryotsu-kun!
Hey, DENKYOKU SPARK! Are you editing for a magazine?
No way! I just passed by.
Oh, so you're with Plus too.
Plus says he's helping out, so I'd like to say hello.
Seriously, what are you up to?
Are you friends with Lemon?
Ah, hello, everyone!
I'm DENKYOKU Plus's father, Spark.
What kind of person are you?
Let me introduce you. I'm the fake inventor of Chitomachi.
Hey!
I'm kidding. I'm the president of Super Electronics.
Oh, the president.
How many craftsmen do you have?
Seven, including the branch store.
That's a lot of money. You need to make it more reasonable.
My company is developing sushi robots.
Hey, are you selling the product?
I'm just giving you some examples.
This is a sushi robot. It has 50 wheels per minute.
You really need to be a good man to make sushi.
For people like that, we developed a humanoid robot.
What? I didn't know there was such a weird humanoid robot before.
It's not like that. It's this kind of robot.
Oh, you have a good face like a craftsman.
What's more,
What?
You can do a job for five people by yourself.
Five people is fine, but the appearance is too SFX-chic.
Originally, the machine was a machine, but it was too machine-like, so it was made human-like with artificial skin.
Don't do it! It's even more creepy.
What else do you have?
How about a knife-cutting robot?
It's a speed of one in 30 seconds.
So don't make it a humanoid.
And the sea-shaped resin machine.
It's a robot that can handle even the business language.
That's what makes it humanoid. It's creepy.
That's what makes it more impactful.
Um, I have a visitor.
My name is Miwa from Baby's Life.
I'm glad to meet you today.
Ah, hello, hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Spark, the electric pole.
Hey, it has nothing to do with you.
No, it's just for my baby.
I've brought you a useful item for your baby.
How about it? Would you like to see it?
Um, I want to take a picture of Mikai.
Yes.
No, I didn't expect that.
A piece of garden in a bag.
Nice.
Cute.
Awesome.
Eh?
Ah!
Um, could you not get in the way?
I'm not going to get in the way.
I'm going to show you how to walk around the garden.
I think it's a good idea to take a picture of it.
In the garden?
It'll get dirty.
Don't worry.
I have a safety walker I developed.
It's a revolutionary system that doesn't get dirty even in the garden.
It's a doll.
It looks like a hamster ball.
Even if it's inside the house, it can't go outside on its own.
Even if it's in the house, it can't fall off the veranda.
It's certainly safe.
It's safe even if your mother calls you for a long time.
But how can I put such a big thing in the room?
That's right.
If it's too big to get out, you can't put it in.
It certainly won't fit.
What if it falls on the slope?
It's too dangerous.
If it's really safe, you don't use dolls.
Well, what's next?
Hey, don't cheat!
Apolo-kun!
Apolo-kun?
Doesn't it look like the artificial intelligence robot we made somewhere?
That's rude.
This is not a robot.
It's a baby suit for babies.
But it's still an unfinished product.
Unfinished?
There are no babies who can take tests.
Of course!
So, let's explain the functions with the improved Apolo-kun beta.
Why me?
I heard that babies these days can't do HiHi well.
Yes, there is a tendency like that.
That's right!
With this Apolo-kun,
HiHi can be easily controlled.
Oh!
It's a structure that forces the correct HiHi movement with a power motor.
Furthermore,
in this way,
it can guide the correct way of walking.
The correct way of bowing.
Ah!
Furthermore,
the correct way of bowing.
Captain, nice shot!
As expected, a single player is different.
Once again,
the correct way of bowing when a boss is angry.
Captain, thank you for the meal.
I'm sorry.
Could you give me half of the salary?
Salaryman!
I feel terrible.
It's not good to forcefully let him do it.
Hmm.
Apolo-kun is indecisive.
So, the next item is.
Oh!
Don't say that!
Did you come to the product monitor?
Damn,
thanks to Spark,
I've spent a lot of time.
I'll take Mikan for a walk today.
I have to go to the store to prepare, so I can't go today.
I'm sorry, orange.
Then I'll take you to the lemon.
Oh, lemon, are you okay?
Yup!
It's not good to be exposed to the outside, so I'll be back in 30 minutes.
Okay, I'll go.
Be careful.
Yup!
That's how Lemon becomes a little sister.
But I'm still worried.
Kankichi, follow me so I won't be found by Lemon.
Roger that.
This phone has a lost mode, so you can see where Lemon is in one shot.
Okay.
Here it comes!
Ah, Plus!
Um, um...
I'm sorry about earlier.
Huh?
Isn't it Plus?
Didn't you go home with Spark?
I remember it was your father and you said it was not his father.
You're so cute, aren't you?
Yeah, you're just like Lemon.
You can have a conversation if it's not through mail, right?
No, it's just...
Why did you say sorry earlier?
Oh, that was because my father made a big fuss...
But I don't feel bad.
He's a good father with good children's feelings.
Look, even this new Hyper Land Cell,
it's dangerous for children to go outside.
This phone too...
Something wrong with your phone?
Well...
I can't talk to Lemon-san well,
so my father...
Anyway, about the baby,
my father thought about it for my father's sake
and invented it for the baby.
What are you doing, Plus?
You were talking nicely,
but now you're quiet?
This...
Hyper Land Cell, activate!
Wait, Plus!
This is the power of the new Hyper Land Cell!
K-Kankichi!
Sir!
Huh? Senpai?
I got it, I'll go help him right away.
Ryo-chan, did you do something again?
Anyway, I'll go to the hospital right away,
so please take care of the rest.
I can understand how Minomushi feels.
Senpai!
Are you okay?
Thanks to you.
I was wondering what would happen.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it was you.
But why was Kankichi there?
Huh?
No, it was just a coincidence, a coincidence.
Right, Mika...
Huh?
Your face is a little red.
What?
Mikan!
Really?
Well, I'm a little hot.
What should I do? What should I do?
All right.
Anyway, let's hurry home.
Lemon, follow me.
Okay.
I'll take care of the doctor.
Oh, Plus, I'm counting on you.
Plus...
Lemon, let's go!
Okay.
Oh, Dad?
Huh? Mikan-chan is sick?
That's bad.
All right.
There's a doctor robot that's just right for you.
His name is Akahie-kun.
Yeah.
You're a fool, Dad!
The thermometer!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Mikan has fever.
Where's the doctor?
Plus is calling him right now.
It's Lemon's fault.
Matoi told me to come home right away.
What should I do?
It's okay.
Everyone's with Mika.
You don't have to worry about anything.
Take care.
I put on some ointment.
Oh, what did the doctor say?
He said he had a cold.
There were a lot of people here today.
You must be tired.
I should give them some medicine.
Yeah.
You've done a good job.
Plus.
Um...
How about Lemon?
If it's Lemon, it's Kikyo and Mikan's business.
Kankichi!
Leave Mikan to Mom and Grandma.
You help out at the store.
Yeah, I got it.
Leave it to me.
Plus, you go home...
Huh?
What should Lemon do?
Put some ice in this ice pillow.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Yeah. We're going to cool the heat of the oranges with ice.
That's right. Let's fold the lemon.
Yeah.
Then, Lemon. I'll leave this to you.
When you put the ice in, bring the ice pillow.
Okay.
Then, Naemon...
But...
Let's fold it, Naemon.
Huh?
That's enough.
Put it under the orange's head.
Got it.
It's okay.
I'm sleeping with the doctor's medicine.
Then let's go now.
You two are tired, aren't you?
Let's put in some hot cocoa.
Y-yes. Thank you.
Lemon is here a little longer.
It's okay.
Lemon...
Okay.
Don't worry about it.
Lemon... I...
I'm sorry, Plus.
But I want to be by your side alone.
Ah...
Then let's go.
I'll get you some drinks later.
Yes.
Man, it's tough every time the party's over.
But, I can manage drinking alone,
so this is a good job.
Bus, are you still there?
I can't go back like this.
I made Mikan branches catch a cold.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry about that. I'm sorry.
I'm not.
If that's the case, I have a responsibility.
That's right.
Hey, that's not the case in this kind of situation.
Oh, yes.
Well, I'm sure you feel the responsibility.
That's right.
Alright. Let's cheer Lemon up.
Come on, Kakichi!
Idiot!
If you enter the room like a lump of gold,
your orange illness will get worse!
Come here!
Damn it!
You called me like a lump of gold.
That's what I said.
Hurry up and come in.
Plus, you'll catch a cold too.
Yeah.
What's with everyone gathered?
Let's leave him alone for now.
So that Lemon doesn't feel bad.
That's right.
That might be the best thing.
I'm sorry, Mikan.
It's because of Lemon that I've caught a cold.
I'm sorry.
Mikan,
I'm not going to do anything.
She's always been like this...
Mikan...
Thank you, Onee-chan.
Mikan! How are you feeling?
Oh, the fever's gone down!
I'm glad you're well, Mikan. I'm really glad.
What's wrong, Nemo?
Mikan's crying. I'm sure she's hungry.
Kankichi, call Mom over.
Okay, I got it!
Hey, Milk! Milk!
Hey, shut up! Don't run around the house!
Oh, Geppert!
Mikan woke up and she wants some milk!
I know that.
She's just gotten a little cold.
Look! Everyone's breakfast is ready!
Oh, good job, you three.
What a great teamwork.
You're so full.
Nemo, you did a great job.
You're a great sister.
It's all thanks to Kankichi and Plus.
I can't help it.
What are you doing?
I don't know what Kankichi is doing, but don't talk so much.
You're so annoying!
I'm gonna kill you!
Stop it! It's the same thing every time!
I'm not gonna do it! I'm gonna kill you!
You're so rude!
Stop it!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm getting a fever.
I might have caught a cold.
I'll catch a cold.
I'm sorry, but I have a bad feeling about this.
What?
You don't believe me?
You're gonna admit it yourself?
Damn it!
I'm so frustrated.
Mika, you're so annoying!
Stop it!
Why, how come?
Why?
Your eyebrows look like black dessae.
You can run fast in your sandals.
Why?
You're always putting your arm around him.
Why, why?
Even though it's a mess, everyone adores it
It doesn't matter, but
The title of this anime is so long
This is Katsushikaku, Kameyari Koenmae, first appearance
Why, why?
Everyone, together!
Listen, Honda!
Men always forget the two letters of ambition
But we can't forget it!
From today to tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow
We always have the ambition to become the best!
So Honda, let's sell curry in this fire truck together!
Next time, "Men have ambitions!"
Please watch!
There is a Kameyari over there
There must be a Kameyari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel and give it a high rating!