English Translation:
A starry sky blooms on the inner palette
I kick the stone, then the shoes fly off
I wonder if I should go to the gym I was saving up for
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are only patsushika and Kameari
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn is strangely kind
Please give me that
From the drain of the
Tungari Boshi
to Taishakuten
the sunset falls
Why does tomorrow end like this
Katsushika and Shibamata
People often say they only lose
But I didn't mean that
So stupid
Matsutake guard, guests!
Fantastic!!
Delicious! This is the paradise of this world!
Hey, Ichidou!
Z Пон let's fight!
Connection!
Look! It's Kyoto's best-selling Matsutake!
One kilogram, 100,000 yen!
It smells pretty good.
Mmm, it really does.
So this is the scent of Matsutake!
It's Canada's imported Matsutake, but it's one kilogram, 8,000 yen.
It's cheap.
Speaking of the best-selling Matsutake of the autumn season,
it's the one that's eaten first in the spring.
You guys should be grateful for just looking at it.
I'll cook a Matsutake of one kilogram, 100,000 yen from now on.
While I was coming here, I saw the people lining up in the yard.
We all came here to taste the roasted Matsutake.
It seems that there are also imported Matsutake from Europe.
Yeah.
Thanks to that, we citizens can easily enjoy the Matsutake.
Actually, I'd like to go to Binchotan,
but at this time, it's like an imported product.
I'll just use gas.
So, from now on, I'll cook a Matsutake of one kilogram, 100,000 yen
at Binchotan!
Everyone, I'll serve the scent of Matsutake for free
in exchange for your little delay.
Matsutake!
Shut up!
I'll go!
Think that the scent alone is not enough!
Wow, what a great scent!
Be careful not to burn yourself.
Okay.
Yum!
Yam!
Here it is.
Um, sir?
Can I bring some home?
I feel bad for the family if I eat alone.
Oh, that's fine.
You're a family man, aren't you?
Really?
Yeah.
Well, shall we eat?
Let's eat!
Hey! It's a shiitake!
Ryotsu!
No way! Why?
There's so much shiitake!
Don't mix it!
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
Did you bring some shiitake too?
Uh...
I don't know what's going on.
Chief Ohara bought some for us.
He bought some for Mr. Kanada.
Mr. Kanada?
Here, Ryotsu.
Let's eat while it's hot.
Wait!
What's wrong, Su-senpai?
I'm not kidding!
Don't be with the chief's stingy milkman!
Stingy?
My shiitake costs 100,000 yen a kilo!
I'll buy it!
It's the best thing I've ever had!
100,000 yen a kilo?
That's right!
It's different from what the poor people eat!
Then, why don't you choose the shiitake you bought yourself?
What do you mean by that?
I don't know which shiitake costs 100,000 yen!
It looks similar, but it smells completely different.
You bought a high-priced shiitake, so you have a good taste in price, don't you?
Right, Ryotsu?
Uh...
You have to eat it quickly, or it'll cool down.
I'll eat it.
Hey, Reiko!
Oh, this is...
Huh?
Sorry, Ryotsu.
What do you mean by sorry?
The chief asked me to eat your shiitake!
Don't say that.
You brought it here on purpose because you wanted to eat it with everyone, didn't you?
Huh?
Uh...
That's...
Oh, that's right.
Huh?
Nagagawa, you!
As expected, high-priced shiitakes have a different scent.
Really?
It's delicious.
Right?
Hey!
You're eating my shiitake!
If you don't eat it quickly, you'll lose your senior's share.
I know!
Uh...
Is it a domestic product or a imported product?
Which one is the best?
All right!
This one!
Hmm?
Oh, my!
The inside of my mouth is full of it.
Oh!
Mr. Kanata, you look delicious, too.
You can eat imported products, too, can't you?
Damn it.
This time...
Oh, my!
This is the real one!
Wait for the imported one, Ryo-chan.
If this goes on like this, I'll get hit by a lot of bad shiitakes!
I can't taste it anymore!
Mr. Ryo.
You're a good boy.
You only eat imported products.
I don't even know what it tastes like, but I do shopping without knowing the taste of it.
Give it back!
Give me back my 100,000 yen!
Yoshinori-chan, what are you looking at?
opinion
Mr. Matsutake is a living corpse.
Mr. Matsutake has a 10-ienie omelet.
International Food has a 10-ienie omelet.
Oharabuchi has a 10-ienie omelet.
He's been living like that for more than four hours!
Hmm...
I feel sorry for him.
Don't be reduce.
He has eaten a lot of your shiitakes, Ryo-chan.
I know, but...
I have one, chief. It's a special for Ryo.
Ryo's?
"Aki no Kouraku ni Matsutake Gari"
I was thinking of going with my family, but I got a lot of matsutake earlier.
Besides, I thought this was for Ryo.
That's right. If you're a senior, you might be able to get back as much as we ate.
So if Ryo's mood gets better, it'll be cheap, right?
I guess so.
That's right. If you keep this up, you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
You have two hours. We'll take them all!
Ryo!
Leave it to me.
Mr. Ryo!
I don't care if it's a mountain or a river, my bike is worth a thousand dollars!
All right, that's what I'm talking about. Let's do it!
It seems like you're in a good mood. That's good, chief.
Let's go to the Matsutake Gari course, Mr. Ohara.
I'm Matsukichi Takeyama, the owner of this area.
Yes, please.
Well, let's go.
Hey, you! Get off the bike from here!
Get off!
What?
I got it.
What's wrong with this guy? He's got a strange customer.
Hey, old man. What's the Matsutake Mountain season right?
Well, I started it to sell my land.
Oh?
Matsuri.
I met him because he didn't have any customers.
I'll give him the land I've been waiting for.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Huh?
The land is worth three hectares of land that was put on the rope.
That's a lot.
Now, the rights of this Akamatsu forest, which can harvest a lot of matsutake, is only 150,000 yen.
It's a good deal to come here every season.
So, if you can get more than 150,000 matsutake, you can make a profit.
But, I don't see any important matsutake.
No, it's not like that.
Last year, I got a lot of matsutake on the mountain next to me and it was on the newspaper.
It's almost a million yen.
A million?
What?
What's this?
Is this true?
Is it really a million?
It depends on the area and age, but no matter how little it is, it's double the amount of the lent.
Chief!
Let's stop hunting matsutake and do it here.
But 150,000 yen is a big budget over.
You heard what I said, right?
150,000 yen paid will be at least 300,000 yen and come back.
I hate such a gamble.
Huh?
Even though it's a chance to make money, Chief Maihon!
Good!
Chief, how is your grandson Daisuke doing?
Daisuke?
Daisuke must be happy.
If he runs around the mountain with his grandfather.
I see.
This is a contract.
Just sign and pay contract and it's okay.
Ah ...
I'd better think more about it first.
You still say that, eh?
Shut up!
Idiot.
What are you saying, idiot?
Senpai, don't you think 150,000 yen is too cheap for such a size?
It's not sure if there's any matsutake.
Huh?
Then, we just need to have more than 150,000 yen worth of matsutake, right?
The root of the red pine is the point where the matsutake is put in.
All right!
Hey, Ryosu! What are you doing?
You know what I mean, right? The smell is important! The smell!
Senpai, you're not a dog!
Oh!
There it is!
Oh, as expected of Ryosu!
You're really good at this!
Chief, I'll find 150,000 yen worth of matsutake right away!
Although the imported ones and the domestic ones were not able to be separated,
do you know the smell of the matsutake itself?
When you make money, you will develop a superhuman ability.
All right! I'll use this to get more matsutake!
No way!
Then, I'll sign the contract.
Oh, yeah.
Sir, are the matsutake on the cliff included in the contract?
Yeah, they're included.
Hmph! No matter where you look, there's no matsutake around here.
Here, Chief! Sign it quickly!
You can write your name here.
Here.
Chief, sign the contract right away.
Huh?
But I really can't gamble!
Yes, you're right!
Forget about this!
Oh, no!
Hey!
Ryosu!
Hey! Is this okay?
Don't you say you're my brother!
How did it go, Koichi?
Oh?
Now we have a deal.
I see.
It's full of matsutake.
I didn't know the top of the cliff was Akamatsu-bayashi.
Nobody was bothering me, so I grew up like this.
This is like digging a gold mine.
You did it, senpai.
Ryo-tsu, I had a good shopping thanks to you.
No, it's a little bit of oil.
Please call me Matsutake Hunter Ryo-tsu.
If there was such a place, I wouldn't have lent it.
Banjai! Banjai! Banjai!
Matsutake Mountain Banjai!
A thief came to my Matsutake Mountain.
Is it Matsutake Mountain that Ryo-chan said you had found?
That place is in the newspaper and TV.
The thief was the thief.
I was told to come.
Yes, Kameari Park...
Oh, Ryo?
Did you see the newspaper?
I came here early in the morning because I couldn't stay.
It's terrible.
I brought a lot of matsutake mushrooms.
Ryo?
Boss, please rest assured.
I'm going to harvest them all now!
Wait!
I promised Hiromi and the others that I'd bring them to the matsutake hunting this holiday.
I love them unless they're properly grown...
Grandpa said I was lying.
It's okay, Boss!
The new matsutake will come out by the next holiday!
Really?
Alright.
Protect the matsutake from the thieves.
Then you can do as much as you like.
Really?
As much as you like matsutake?
Yes.
Relax.
I'll protect it.
I got it.
Leave it to me.
I bought some food, Boss.
Then I'll protect the matsutake no matter what.
Here.
I have to do this much.
Boss!
The matsutake on the west side was stolen by the cats!
Here it is.
It was stolen?
It was stole!
Let's go!
You're a thief, Boss!
What do you mean, sir!
Let's go!
You are entirely innocent!
They're not some thieves.
Let's run away!
Let the police show up.
Let's go!
Wait...
Listen up, Osogi!
Retreat!
Damn it!
The next day
Senpai, I've brought all the members from Nakagawa Prefecture.
Alright!
General, I'm the commander of Ryotsu!
Uh, uh, isn't that a bit too much?
This is just right!
Listen carefully! The purpose of the operation is to protect Matsutake!
In other words, we must not put intruders on the cliff!
Based on this line, we will form the Matsutake Defense Sword!
All members, with all your strength, let's support them!
Yes sir!
It's a rather strong defense.
I heard that there are a lot of pretty good Matsutake.
We can put them on the cliff, right?
This is it! Act No.1!
The third group, quickly capture the target!
Roger!
The tenth person?
We can leave the chief's Matsutake alone.
Of course! There's no one who can break through this defense!
Ah!
I don't know, I don't know.
I can't believe it!
He's guarding so seriously!
Looks like there's a professional with a strong arm.
Damn! What a persistent thief!
The C-24 infrared camera caught the culprit!
Huh?
Give it to me!
What? What a stinky thief!
Oh!
Yes, Matsutake Defense Force.
Senpai, I'm Chief Ohara.
What?
Oh, ah, Ryotsu.
How's Matsutake doing?
Has he grown up?
Yes, of course, Chief.
Tomorrow, Hiromi and Daisuke will go hunting Matsutake.
Please take care of him.
See you!
Tomorrow...
I'll re-plan the plan!
I can't let any of you steal Matsutake!
It's a battle of force!
Please...
Stupid!
I can tell from your movement!
Take this!
Now get down!
Finally someone has helped me out, bastard!
Prepare yourselves!
Let's go!
Hey, Senpai! Where's the defense switch?
W-what's going on?
Senpai!
Let's get this guy out of here!
Roger.
Wait a minute! Are you going to kill me?
Fire! Fire!
You idiot! You idiot!
That's... wrong.
Mr. Tsuchiya, stop the attack!
You're too late!
Damn it! It's like a thunderclap!
It can't be helped. I'll go back upstairs...
You thief!
Get up!
You stole my matsutake!
You're the thief?
You're the one who stole my matsutake.
What?
I just took back my own matsutake!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who stole my matsutake!
I'm coming!
Stop it!
This is terrible.
I'm a thief.
The right thing to do now is to get back.
I did it!
Did I do it?
I just didn't get to protect my matutake.
Don't get so angry!
Roger!
You're the one who stole my matsutake!
I'm going to protect the pine tree.
I see.
It's your job.
Idiot!
You should bury yourself in the pine tree.
And become a pot of oil.
At least, you can kill the enemy.
See you.
Are you leaving, chief?
I'm going to die.
I'm not going to die.
Maria.
What happened to the pine tree?
Since when did it become a real woman?
Maria is here, too.
I didn't know you were a clone human.
Next time, "Hondara Prefecture is in danger."
Please watch it.
The girl who plays the role of the enemy.
I can't fall in love.
Rumor says so.
There are so many things I want to do.
I want to try the love.
I want to ride a bike in the vast desert.
I want to be a lady
With the speed of a full moon
I change into a lady's dream
Love heart
I'm sorry, wait
The future of the panorama
The dazzling light that shines
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait