Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I looked up at the sunset floating on the river bank
And I jumped to the top of the pebble stone
I laughed and said "It's still as it was"
There are only the good things in the world
But the bad things are the only reason
The cityscape doesn't change
It's so kind
Because the crows are crying, the birds are singing
Are the yakitori and hobari here?
From the water tower of Tongari-boshi
To Taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end as well
But I'm happy again
I lost it and I realized
Because I'm a fool
"The Exhaustion of Two-Man-Botch"
I think I'll spin it
I'm so sorry
It's all just a dream
In the future, I hope
"Death of Fun"
I'm going to take a break for a bit.
*Titanic*
*Punch!*
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Damn it...
I forgot to set it up myself...
Well, at least it was perfectly wake up...
This is because the boss...
You idiot! I'm so late that if I'm late tomorrow, I'll be fired!
I haven't taken a bath in a while, so I'll take a shower.
Reiko-san, good morning!
Good morning!
I just got a call. Mr. Terai said he's taking a break from the cold.
Yeah, he was so lazy last night.
Oh, so today it's just you and Ryo-chan.
What?
What about Mr. Ohara and Ms. Nakagawa?
Ms. Nakagawa said she was going to Europe for a break.
Oh, I see.
Mr. Ohara said he'd be at the wedding.
So he's always with that gorilla guy, right?
That's what it means.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous to be with such a wild, erotic middle-aged gorilla.
That's right.
We're going to the station to cheer him up.
Don't worry about it.
Ryo-chan and I are friends who are more than just friends.
But...
It's really okay.
See you later.
Let's see.
Uh...
Um...
New underwear.
Okay.
This shirt has the least dirt on it.
Oh, crap!
I'm going to be late again!
Hurry up!
Eh?
Ryo, what are you doing?
Shh! The chief is in the back room.
Ryo, didn't you say yesterday that the chief was off at the wedding?
Really?
Geez, I'm not listening to people.
I'm in a hurry. I'm going to go to bed.
No, Ryo. There are only two of us today.
There's Nakagawa and Terai.
Kei is in Europe, and Terai is off in the wind.
Huh? Then, there are only two of us today?
Huh?
Ryo and Reiko are alone?
Well, Reiko doesn't seem to care about that gorilla guy, so I don't think she's worried.
Reiko might be, but her opponent is Ryo Tsukan Kishi.
Oh, bon appétit.
Reiko's not good.
Maria!!
Ouch!
What's wrong, Reiko?
My eyelashes are stuck in her eyes.
Oh, well. Look. I'll take a look.
Okay, open your eyes.
Please be gentle.
Just like me.
Huh? Oh! That hurts!
I got it.
Ryo-chan, it hurts!
Sorry, sorry, Reiko.
Don't be so rough.
I'm sorry. I'm nervous.
Then, I'll do it again.
Ryo-sama!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't think you had eyelashes on you.
You're misunderstanding.
Why did you come to the station?
That's...
I got it.
Komachi-chan and the others must have been upset.
If Ryo-chan and I are alone, nothing will happen.
Right, Ryo-chan?
Of course.
Ryo-sama, don't be so suspicious.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Ryo-sama, please forgive me.
I understand. Go home.
Ryo-sama, you hate me, don't you?
No, no, no.
You have your job, don't you?
Yes, but...
I'm sure you won't be able to work if you're with me.
That's right.
If Maria-chan is there, I can't help it.
I understand.
I believe in you, Ryo-chan.
It's not me.
Then I'm leaving.
All right.
All right, it's done.
I'll go patrol to kill time.
Oh, no!
Ryo-chan, what's wrong?
The old man at the station
Oh, no, no, no.
I came to pay the debt.
Ryo-chan, please get me back.
Ryo-chan is in trouble.
Do something yourself.
It's a pinch until the payday.
I'm in trouble.
Ryo-san, where is Ryo-san?
What?
Oh, oh, oh.
You can't hide it.
I heard from Komatsu-chan.
I heard that Ryo-san and Kimu are alone today.
Komatsu-chan is unnecessary.
Ryo-chan didn't go to patrol just now.
You don't seem to be calm, Reiko-san.
It's not like that.
The locker is suspicious.
I don't think I can enter a place like that.
That's true.
I want to say that.
But if Ryo-san can be cornered, he can do anything.
It's strange.
I thought it was here.
The rest is in the back room.
Ryo-san, it's useless to hide.
Today, I'll pay for the accumulated money.
Damn it.
I'll pay for it.
Haha.
That's right.
I'll pay for the accumulated money.
I went out for patrol.
After Ryo-chan comes back,
I'll tell you that I'll pay.
You went home.
Go out.
I want to go out, but I can't.
I can't go out in this outfit.
I'll help you.
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of you, Ryo-chan.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You have to be patient.
Don't pull my face.
Ouch.
I'm out.
Thank you, Reiko.
What's with the outfit?
My body can't go back to normal.
But I can move.
See? See? See?
I can't even go to the toilet in this outfit.
The most troublesome thing is that I can't put my pants down even when I go to the bathroom.
What should I do, Reiko?
That's right.
We have to get it back somehow.
What if we pour hot water?
Freeze-dry method!
You can move your feet, right?
Only the tip of my feet.
Did you hook your feet?
Yeah.
You can't let go.
Huh?
I got it.
I'm glad. I can grab your chin.
I tickled you.
What are you going to do, Reiko?
Be patient.
I'm dying.
It's okay, Ryo-chan.
I don't know what you mean.
Zangief.
Thanks to you, I'm back to normal.
Ryo-chan.
Huh?
Ryo-chan, you're the best.
What are you doing to Reiko-san?
Huh?
This isn't right.
You're not doing it right.
You're a pervert.
That's all we have for today.
If I hadn't done it at the last moment, Ryo-chan wouldn't have been in this Everyone was
in my hands.
Everyone must have felt the same way you feel.
Come on.
That's okay.
You're a pervert.
I can't let you hook your feet.
Fat.
Thanks to you guys, Maria will get a kick in the ass!
And the old man from the plastic shop will pay for the debt!
It's all a mess!
What? It's your fault, right?
That's right! You're doing too much bad things!
What did you say?!
Ryo-chan, hold it, hold it.
You two came here to eat together, right?
That's right!
Well then, let's eat!
Okay!
It's so good!
Ryo-chan, why don't you come over here and eat?
Hey, kid, a gorilla man is fine.
But your lunch is going to be bad!
Leave it alone! I'm just like you guys!
Ryo-san!
Huh?
Oh, Junpei!
Ryo-san, this is bad!
What's going on?
I said, this is bad! Come here!
Okay, I understand, I understand.
You two, go to your rooms.
What?!
I'll take care of it.
Ryo-chan, be careful!
Ryo-san!
Ryo-san, you too.
Be careful!
Hardest of the best, Ryo-san!
It's okay. It's all good.
If you pay the latest attention and put the Итак in comparison fast,
the problem will be solved right away.
Right, Ryo-tsukan Kichi?
You did it!
Yup, we did it!
I did it!
Ryo!
You did it!
The airplane is safe!
No, it won't move.
The engine is gone.
Junpei, get me a tool box.
Okay!
Alright! It's done!
That's it!
Yes!
The engine is safe!
Here, Junpei.
Thank you, Ryo!
The next day
Here, have some tea.
Thank you.
Junpei and the others were very happy.
It's good.
The tea after a job is delicious.
What's this?
Is there something on my face?
Did I keep moving around with this?
Don't worry.
No one will laugh at you.
I won't forget the heart of a child forever.
No, I like Ryo, who is still a child forever.
Don't tease me.
What's this?
Could it be...
Who are you?
Hi! It's been a long time, super poor guy.
Hey, Junpei.
Who are you?
Hum, hum, hum.
I'm rude, me, me.
Even if you say that, do you know Reiko?
I can't remember that, either.
Miss Reiko, it's me.
I'm super rich shiratori, Reiji.
Oh!
I'm so glad you can remember me.
No, it's...
It's all over here.
What?
Hey, why would you do that?
You can't get me out, so you're completely forgotten!
Hey, hey, calm down! Who are you talking to, Shiratorina?
No, don't be mean, Super-poor-man, Reiko-san!
That's why I said call me Super!
It's been a while.
But you were moved by your father and became a super-poor-man, weren't you?
I was moved by my father and came back as a super-poor-man.
What a sweet father. So, what do you want today?
That's a good question, Super-poor-man.
I know, so don't point at me!
Just a moment!
What's this flower?
It doesn't feel like the season. Did you pick it up in Porsche?
You're so detailed.
Don't worry about the small things.
Anyway, Reiko-san, since you came back as a super-poor-man, I'll have you as my wife.
I should have said no to that before.
That's not true!
I can see that you're not serious.
You'll be my wife. This is fate.
R-Ryo-chan...
Hey, Reiko, you don't like it, do you?
Besides, stop this!
It stinks and I can't stand it!
What? What are you talking about?
You're the biggest flower in the world!
Shiratori-san, I'm sorry to say this, but you're too late.
I know, it stinks too.
I'm engaged.
You're joking again!
I'm serious.
Then, who's the one you're engaged to?
That's...
That's me!
What?
Oh, no!
Well, that's how it is.
Shiratori-kun, you're really late.
We were just talking about where to go on our honeymoon.
Right, honey?
Yes, darling?
H-Honey?
D-Darling?
I guess Europe is better.
The whole world is the same.
I knew it.
Hmm...
No, it's definitely strange.
What?
What do you mean?
If you think about it, well, not necessarily.
Even if the world and heaven turn around,
Reiko-san won't fall for a super-villain, super-poor, super-short-and-super-long-term gorilla man like you.
I-I can't do that.
That's even more suspicious.
What?
Then, why don't you show me the proof?
Proof?
If you're engaged, why don't you give me a big kiss right here in front of me?
What?
Not a kiss on the cheek.
A mouth-to-mouth kiss.
Zzz...
You're always in front of me.
If you're engaged, you should be able to do it.
Now, I'll take a picture of the proof.
Why don't you do it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
I can do it.
Eh?
Re-Reiko...
Y-Yes, you can do it!
Look closely!
Sorry, Reiko.
Please bend over for a while.
Re-Reiko?
H-Hey, here I go.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
B-Bunny...
Oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ahh!
Hey, hey, Tamma!
Excuse me, I'm calling Papa.
Hello, it's Reiji.
Huh?
The company went bankrupt?
That means the super rich will fall out again?
Ah, Shiratori-san, you shouldn't be in a place like this.
That's right, it's the most important thing in Shiratori-ken.
Uh, I understand, Papa, I'll go there right away.
That means I'll be rude.
Papa!
Hey, hey!
What are you going to do with this flower?
Huh?
Ah...
Ah, it stinks!
Huh?
Hey, Reiko.
If I hadn't been contacted by Shiratori's father, would you really have kissed him?
No, no!
Yeah, I know. It's a joke, right?
Yeah, I guess.
Ah, it's over.
There were so many things happening today.
Yeah, there were so many. I'm so tired.
That's right, Ryo. How about having a meal together sometime?
Oh, that's great. But me...
It's okay. It's my treat.
Yari, what's with the wind?
It's nothing.
Well, it's okay. It's just a big welcome.
Mr. Ryo!
Oh, Honda. What's wrong?
Senpai!
Yeah, what's going on?
What's going on?
Nana-chan isn't answering my calls.
It seems like I'm being dumped.
Yeah, that's too much.
She doesn't even reply to my emails.
It's over.
Hey, you!
Sorry. I'm gonna hang out with Honda tonight.
Honda, I'll listen to your story.
Oh, Senpai.
Come on, hang in there.
There's your treat.
Here.
Wow, you're so pretty.
Why don't you also get some drinks with me?
That...
Hey!
What?
Why are you drinking too much?
I'll get you a drink.
Good.
Why are you drinking too much?
Hey, come on.
I found some.
I thought I wouldn't need it, but I found a weird takoyaki shop.
Next time, a fierce battle in front of the station.
Thank you.
There's a wall over there.
Oh, there must be a wall.
Everyone, come to our town.
Thank you!