Translated by Thaury
Swandering the river seen end-to-end in the sun
I tear off the love stone and fly down to the invited building
From the water tank of a pointed hat
To the taishakuten, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
Katsushika, Shibamata, I lost my happiness
I realized, I'm such an idiot
This is the escape room in front of Kameari Park.
I see. This is the rumored...
Escape Room
Escape Room, in front of Kameari Park.
Is that it?
The escape room is the basis of police activities.
It's a very important job.
It prevents crime...
Of course, it prevents crime.
The crime rate of the criminal by interrogating the police is higher than expected.
Police School, Daishiten, 777th Street.
Newspaper, Newspaper, Newspaper.
I'll introduce you.
I'm Miyaji, your student.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
After graduating from Tojo University,
Miyaji entered the police school with the best grades.
He's a top student with a good education.
Amazing.
Tojo University is a prestigious school, isn't it?
He's a candidate for the future executive.
He's Terai, the secretary of our escape room.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
I don't know anything.
Even if I had any questions, I wouldn't ask you.
What?
Please be gentle, Miyaji.
Those two are Nakagawa and Reiko.
Nice to meet you.
It's an honor to have a good student like you.
What?
Police School, Daishiten, 124th Street.
Police officers are required to wear uniforms.
They're not required to wear uniforms.
They're not allowed to wear uniforms.
Nakagawa.
I see.
I have permission, but...
It's boring to wear uniforms.
20 centimeters above the knee.
Too short.
Yellow and pink uniforms are not allowed.
Chief Ohara.
What?
Do you know what they say about this escape room in the police school?
No.
The escape room in front of Kameyari Park is the first place to have a bag.
A
The chief's management ability is also problematic.
The first step in my field experience is why this is an escape room.
I have to measure the thread of the upper part of the body.
I will create the training schedule myself.
Please feel free to do it.
Ms. Terada, please lend me the map of the patrol area.
Oh, yes.
Um...
I'm... I'm a monk.
Hello.
Actually, it was a difficult training.
It's only one day today.
It's going to be a long day.
Yeah!
100km/h deck morning!
With a brilliant technique!
Here I come!
Yeah!
Oh, oh!
Good morning!
Ryo!
Oh, no!
I've been riding my bike since this morning!
Finally, I can ride this bike!
Cornering is my life!
You! My important data has been leaked!
What?
You're wearing the uniform of the police, but...
Police school, page 125,
Support for the officer's uniform wearing duty.
Who's the one who's violating the rules of sandals and no underwear?
Me?
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi, and you're Daru!
Good morning, Ryo-tsu.
You're in a good mood this morning, too.
What's with this mouthy guy?
I'm Miyaji, an intern.
An intern?
I'm Ryo-tsu Junsacho.
I'm going to appoint you as the director of Miyaji's army for the day.
What?
What's the director's duty, chief?
You're going to patrol with Miyaji.
Good for you, Ryo-tsu.
Chief, I can do it by myself.
That's the chief's order, Miyaji.
What page was the uniform's rule?
Page 572, rule 17.
I'm going to obey my boss's orders.
Damn it.
Today is the day Virtual Fantasy X will join the arcade.
I can do as much as I want if I can fool the intern.
All right, let's hurry!
Follow me, intern!
Ryo-tsu!
Don't be late, intern!
There's no skateboard in the main equipment department of the foreign police!
Are you okay, chief?
You left Miyaji to your senior.
Ryo-tsu of the physical side and Miyaji of the brain side.
It may be surprising to combine different personalities for a high effect.
Chief, you've done a good job paying your debts.
Humph!
Huh?
"The Subway Shop"
Ten minutes before the game starts...
I'm the first one to enter the coin in the new game machine.
Ryo-tsu!
Yeah?
The default patrol course is not working.
It's fine.
But the first place to pass the Kameari elementary, junior high, and high school, and the Tatsushika area is the official course.
What are you going to do if you go to such an uninteresting place?
My patrol is decided to be a game, pachinko, and plum.
Then, isn't it a tour of the amusement park?
Please return to the official course.
If you don't like it, you can leave it to the two of you.
You go over there, and I'll go over here.
Two hours later, we'll meet at the exhaust.
Bye!
Wait a minute.
Please wait.
Page 843.
Newbie training, number 20.
You must be on duty during patrol training.
I knew it.
Get out of the way.
Are you going to disobey the director's orders?
Are you going to give up my directorial responsibility?
This will be the first reason for the Virtual Fantasy X to be taken away by someone else.
I understand.
All right.
I will adopt the official course.
What?
I'll just go around somewhere.
No abnormalities near the Kaeyari Elementary School.
Hey!
You always carry such a thing?
Yes.
Because of this, I always got the top grades from university to the police school.
But even if you're smart, you can't be a police officer.
In fact, it's a hindrance to your education.
What?
What a police officer needs is more than knowledge,
but more than the ability to make a decision and act.
A ability to make a decision?
Mr. Ryotsu!
Where are you going, Mr. Ryotsu?!
This is the ability to make a decision! Remember that!
Parora! Parora! Parora!
That's it!
Mr. Ryotsu!
We're running out of time.
We only have 3 minutes left.
When the shutters open and we jump in at the same time, we win.
This guy's fast!
Alright, I'll suggest you to give the police officer a skateboard.
30 seconds to go!
It opened.
I'm excited.
Virtual Fantasy X!
Go!
I won! I'm in first place!
So this is Virtual Fantasy X!
Mr. Ryotsu!
Why do you know?
I can't think of anything else other than your words!
I'm in first place!
I'm out~!
Take this!
I won!
Hey, hey, don't go!
Oh...!
How could you do that to me!
It's because of you that I violated the rules of your programbirds at the start of the Competition.
Don't keep that secret from me!
Well...
I see.
What are you doing?
That was awesome!
You wanted to play that game until you ran away with me, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Of course, it was for the patrol.
What?
30 minutes to the escape room.
The patrol should be efficient and be in the back.
If you don't hurry to the next place, you won't be able to do everything in time.
Don't be stupid.
It's a professional to climb mountains with a direct feeling.
If you decide here, you'll be able to do it.
That's the secret of the patrol.
I'll stay here for about an hour.
I've never heard of such a gamble patrol.
Come on!
Let's go!
Just do it once.
I can't.
No suspicious vehicle.
No.
No problem.
Just leave it to me.
All transfer from headquarters to the game center in front of the station.
Arrest Maruhio of Ryoga Station Arashi.
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
Ryoga Station Arashi.
As I said, if you stay here, you'll be the first trainee.
You're so lucky, Miyaji.
You didn't do this crime?
Huh?
Oh, of course I did.
My sense of smell as a patrol chief is sensitive to the smell of crime.
The smell of crime.
Shut up.
I'm on it.
Chance.
Listen.
This is not something you can get by studying a little.
Hmm?
My sense of smell is getting more and more.
This way? This way?
This way.
All right.
Let's go, Miyaji.
Yes.
Here?
That's right.
It smells good.
There's something in this store.
Where is it?
!
It's here.
Miyaji!
You haven't left yet?
Well, I'm sure I'll arrive at the spot tomorrow at about 3 a.m.
Now, you're going to block the entrance because you're going to be wagon service.
Well...
Even if you're like this, my sharp senses are always catching up with the situation around me.
Hey, didn't you think the man who just left was acting strange?
Eh?
Miyaji, try to identify that man.
Oh!
The crime rate of the criminal, according to the questions asked during the patrol, is...
More expensive than expected!
Yes!
Ichimatsu!
Hehehehe...
Excuse me, but...
What is your job?
Hello? What is your job?
Job?
I'm asking about your job.
Huh? Your job?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Eh? What is it?
Stop it!
What are you doing?
I don't know! I just asked about my job, and all of a sudden...
What a pathetic trainee!
Didn't you do judo?
I'm on the third team, but...
What?
Your third team is better than that!
Hey, old man!
You're lying!
What a pathetic trainee is!
Look at this!
Sometimes, it may be more swaying than judo!
Swaving.
Swaving?
And, when the opponent is panting...
Swaing!
Give him a good hand!
There! There! There!
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
We are not getting paid for it!
You got it, Miyaji?
I think this is a will.
Will? You?
I was fired from a company I worked for for 30 years!
I'm sorry for being so rude earlier.
It's okay. Don't think too much.
It's good to be alive.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Let me go!
Cheer up!
Are you sure you're okay with that?
I'm fine with your energy.
He found out about one incident in an hour and saved one life.
Maybe he's a good cop.
By the way, what is a ristora?
Is it a rare animal?
It's different.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm hungry now.
The next day
This dango is always delicious.
Sorry, Ryo.
I'm sorry to ask you to do this.
Thank you.
I'm glad we happened to pass by.
It was a flood after the rain.
What a coincidence.
I came to eat dango.
That's the work of the shakum.
You have to do it right.
What?
I've been wrong about one thing.
You're too smart.
You don't have enough experience.
So it's just right to work three times as hard as you.
Well, do it right.
If you do it, you can do it.
I can't move anymore.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm sorry.
Ryo, this is a bath.
If you don't mind, I'll use it.
Oh, Miyaji.
The warm hearts of the residents have returned.
Can I get something like that from the civil servants?
Don't waste the kind heart of people.
In the next few days,
In the bath!
Yay!
Good bath!
Are you okay, Ryo?
Mr. Ryo, go to the bathroom while you're working.
That's fine.
You're dirty with the dump cleaning, too.
It's disgusting.
That's right.
I've already washed the mud.
Let's go back to patrol.
Yeah, I got it.
Then, before that.
Huh?
Let me back off.
What?
The contract is 300 pages.
I will obey your orders.
It's 572 pages.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Wow, it's refreshing.
You know what?
If you just go around the patrol course of the century, you won't be able to get there.
I don't know if I look like I'm playing all the time.
It's really helpful to the residents, isn't it?
And then you're working at a game center or a pachinko.
That's why.
That's to look at the world from different angles.
Oh?
Weight scale.
Let's see how much it is.
Oh, it's the plastic model.
But I can't make it in a place like this.
Don't make it too big.
It'll get in the way.
I'm sorry.
When it's done, show me how it's done.
Let's see.
What's this?
What's wrong?
It's glue.
You put it here and...
I can't take it off.
It's instant glue.
What?
Do something.
Yes.
What are you doing?
It's a cart.
We need to get back on patrol.
What's wrong?
My knees are stuck.
What?
The dump truck is coming in.
We need to hurry.
It's a paddock.
What?
I need to hurry.
No way.
It's a
You're right.
This is awful.
We can't push it any further anymore.
Let's go.
Ready?
Alright, let's change direction!
Huh? How?
Hang on!
You have to move your center of gravity!
Go! Go!
Hey! You too, shake your butt!
Do you want to die?
Ugh...
Let's do it again, okay?
One, two...
Change!
Is it okay?
Yes!
Hehe!
Look, it's the same as skateboarding!
Alright!
That was useful for me again!
Ryo-san! Behind!
Huh?
Oh no! It's a boundary!
Now, let's change the ring.
Yeah!
Huh?
Alright!
Three, two, one!
Yes!
Ah!
Good luck!
Virgin Road in that form...
Amen!
We did it!
We're out on the national road!
We finally stopped!
Isn't it embarrassing to be in a town like this?
It can't be helped!
You and I can't walk!
Huh?
It's a highway!
Ah!
It's a road!
It's an artificial road!
You're kidding, Miyaji!
It's a waterway!
We can't use this scale!
Idiot!
If we let it go here,
we'll have to use a huge number of people and taxes!
Huh?
That's why we have to do a quick search of the street!
I got it!
All right, let's go!
Ah, a car!
No!
What are you doing?
Give me the bike I just told you!
No!
Ah!
All right, I'm on the gas!
Yes!
Okay, it's a truck!
All right!
Ah, Honey!
I'm on the gas!
All right, let's change the route!
I'm going to shake my butt!
Yes!
One, two, three!
Ah, crap!
I shook my butt too much!
Ryo, the car!
Yes!
Ah!
You, kid!
Now, everyone is still the police!
I'm sorry, but please follow the bike ahead!
Oh, you're Ryo from the park's exit, right?
Yes!
All right, leave it to me!
Thank you for your cooperation!
All right, everyone!
We're going to stop at the intersection!
Ryo!
Yes?
My legs are about to fall off!
What?
Ah!
I'm back!
I-I'm coming this way!
Ah!
Hey, hey!
Be quiet!
I'm still the police!
Ah!
You did it!
Where's Ryo?
Ah!
Hey, Gifu!
I-I'm so sorry!
Ah!
I-I'm in the b-base!
Oh, the bank produção is in trouble!
The president's office is sure.
What? The president's office?
Miyaji!
I have a lot of money!
Idiot!
You don't have any money!
Yeah!
I'm going to the bank with Miyaji!
The news that a naked editor with a heavy weight has appeared
has been leaked to the Katsushika office.
I'm going to the Shimasu Shogunate today!
It's the constitution!
No way!
Miyaji was also naked and shivering!
Ryo, at times like this,
your daily trust is what counts!
That's right, senpai!
You're so heartless!
The constitution is terrible!
Heartless! Heartless! Heartless!
In order to save the crumbling toy factory,
I made a figure that can move 40 places in the whole body!
Alright! I'll sell it, sell it, sell it,
and make a fortune!
Everyone, please buy it for me!
Next episode: New product doll on sale!
Would you please?
I'm rumored to be a woman who can't fall in love
But there's a mountain of things I want to do
Me
I want to ride in the vast desert on a motorcycle
I want to be more free than a bird
The lady's dream changes with the speed of a full moon
I'm sorry, wait for me
I'm going to dive into the future of the panorama
You understand, right?
I'm sorry, wait for me