♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Te-te-te-te-re-mi-ro-mi-ru to-ki-wa ♪
♪ He-ya-wa-ga-ru-kushitte ♪
♪ Hanare-te-mi-te-nee ♪
Subtitled by C.R.
♪ Nakagawa ni ukabu ♪
♪ Anu hi wo megakete ♪
When I kicked the love stone, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I was saving
I laughed at the fact that it was still a baby
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win
I have a cold and a cold, but I can't change a single nightmare
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the water tank of the Tungari hat
The sun goes down to the Taishakuten
Tomorrow, I'll wear a hat
It's over
If I win, I'll be happy again
I lost it and realized
I'm an idiot
That's what happened while I was taking a break
Well, it's always like that
Senpai, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Finally, it's a room
You can see no. 2 or no. 3 in Tokyo
I'll be satisfied this time
Is it an old movie theater, Ryo-chan?
Yes, not mine
When I was a kid, the movie was just as good as it can be
At that time, the movie theaters in Japan had several stars
But I remember this Orion's hadn't
Check this out
Asakusa Rock
Asakusa Rock, a movie theater and industrial area that has built the era of Japanese photography through Meiji and Showa.
Since the opening of the electric theater in Meiji in 30, as the first movie theater in Japan,
many theaters have opened up like a flash.
When I was a child, movies were the golden age.
In this era when TV was not yet so popular, movies were truly the kings of entertainment.
This is a story of memories of that time with me and this Orion.
Don't be so rude, Kichi!
It's already the beginning!
I made it!
The brakes are not working!
If you pay for the movie tickets, you can't buy ice cream inside.
Let's use the same ticket.
Excuse me, one small ticket, please.
Yes.
Here you are.
Hey, wait a minute.
Why are you wearing a coat in summer?
I'm cold.
Then what's this inside?
Oh, no!
No, you're not!
There's no gap in the lower part.
I thought there was another one.
Where is it?
Oh, there it is!
Oh, it's here.
You're a jerk.
What?
Oh, no!
Ouch!
What are you doing to the customers?
You're wasting the ticket fee.
Where are the customers?
I have no choice.
I'll pay the bill.
Kichi!
Of course.
I can't buy ice cream anymore.
It's okay.
I have seven tickets.
Seven tickets?
Damn it!
It's so cool inside.
This is the only place with a cooler.
It's crowded.
It's like a stand-in.
That's why I should have come earlier.
I'll look for an empty seat.
You guys go to the right.
Okay.
It's crowded, after all.
It's not empty at all.
Yeah, not even one.
How about over there?
No, it's not open.
I can't help it.
Let's look at the front.
It's easier to sit down.
Yeah.
It's hard to see, but it's powerful.
It's heavy.
Huh?
I didn't know you liked movies so much.
What?
There were no TV games back then,
and there were a lot of houses without TV.
All kinds of kids went to the movie theater.
And when it comes to movie theaters,
Ramune's bottle is the best.
What?
What is that?
Ramune's bottle has a B-ball in it.
You break that and take it out.
But why a movie theater?
Movie theaters are usually in the low end.
The rolling bottles come in front.
You put it in your feet like this.
When the kids were young,
they all broke their bottles when they got bored of movies.
What?
Are they doing it while they're filming?
Yeah.
When adults notice it,
they quit for a while,
but it starts again soon.
And then the movie theater finally gave them a prize.
After that, they stopped breaking them,
but even the smart guy who brought them
to the bottles that were falling on the street came out.
He's your senior, isn't he?
Yeah.
Anyway,
he was saying that he had the best memory.
Yeah.
That was one day of the time
when children were like that.
What?
Oh, lord!
Ramune!
Isn't that great?
Who is it?
There is no one here.
Go for it, lord.
Almost there.
I'm back, Samurai Kintaro.
What?
Kintaro!
Kintaro on the left!
Ah!
Kintaro on the right!
Damn it!
It was almost done!
Don't do anything stupid!
Hey!
You're in my way!
I can't see!
Damn it!
Let go of me!
It's all his fault!
What the hell did you do?
No!
Hey!
You're here again!
You're so annoying!
This way!
Take this!
Three, four!
No!
Six, seven!
You're like a mouse!
Six!
Yes!
Eight!
Six, seven!
Oh, my God!
- Hey! - Don't get our asses kicked!
No!
Hold it right there!
Hey!
What's going on?
It's all your fault!
I can't let anyone who doesn't watch movies come to the theater.
Get out of here.
What?
What's up, Hikaru?
Dad.
Huh? Kankichi-kun Kane?
Huh?
The guy from Tsukudaniya, Gin-san.
Why do you know my name?
You've been watching movies with Gin-san since you were little, right?
I remember you.
How about it?
Shall we go see it?
What?
Are you sure?
It's your first time in a movie theater, right?
Dad.
Don't say that.
It's a movie with a lot of people.
This is the movie theater.
Wow!
You can shoot with this machine?
It's so hot.
The lamp heat of the movie theater is so high.
I'm heating it with this carbon duct, but it's still hot.
Summer is a hell of a heat.
Why are there two of the same machine?
I cut the film.
Switch?
Yes.
Kintaro-san.
It's about time.
Can you say that?
Watch it from here.
Yes.
You have to go.
I can see the screen.
It's like a special seat.
Watch it.
The mark is on the right end of the screen.
It's a disaster.
It's true.
Switch with the second mark.
Oh, now this one is moving.
Oh, it was like this.
It takes about 13 minutes to shoot in one film.
It takes about 7 hours.
Hey, Hikaru, roll this.
Then, this is one film.
Don't touch it.
Are you kidding me?
But, it's amazing.
You're still a junior high school student, right?
I'm still a half-person.
I help the children during summer vacation.
If you let me do it, I can do it, too.
That's right.
Hm?
Oh.
You're late.
It's about time for the next film.
The next film?
I'm holding a film in a few pieces.
What?
I'll shift the screening time in order, and take the finished film to the next movie theater.
Oh, it'll be hard if you don't make it in time.
Yes.
I'll have to wait for the audience in the middle of the movie.
Oh, here it comes.
I'll go get the film, so please take care of the rest.
Yes.
Oh, the film's broken.
What?
Oh, the fire.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
The audience is starting to fight.
Don't you know what I'm doing?
You have to connect the film quickly.
I'll do that later.
What?
Don't let the audience wait for you.
Okay.
That's good.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm glad.
The background scenes will make the dialogue go well.
It's hard, isn't it?
You have to do that?
Not at all.
I love movies.
There are a lot of people who are struggling in a place we don't know.
Yes.
But we're just watching them.
Dad.
Yes?
Why did you put them in the movie theater?
They like movies.
If they like movies, they want to see the movie theater.
But...
What?
That's strange.
The directors should have gone home.
Is there still someone in there?
You guys.
I was going to clean up the bottle I spilled earlier.
I'm sorry I made a fuss.
Hikaru.
This is how we got along with Hikaru.
Next time, the young man will become a star.
The End
So we went to Orion Island.
Did you go to see the movie every day?
Of course, I just went in from the back door.
I talked to Hikaru about movies every day.
I like Tokijiro Kutsukage of Raizo.
I also liked Hiraio Saburo.
Kikuchi is good at historical stories.
I've been coming to the hut since I was three.
I came every day, so I remembered the lines.
Oh, this is next week.
But the works change every week, so it's hard.
You have to remember the title properly.
This is called a sewing machine.
See, the movement is like a sewing machine that sends a thread.
It's true.
The volume is 2 seconds per second.
It's a 24-frame movie.
So the movie machine is showing the movie while blinking 24 times per second.
Wow.
What is your dream?
I want to be a film director.
I don't have a qualification as a film director yet, so I can only do a little.
But I want to get a qualification and enter a film company.
And my dream is to be a director.
What? A film director?
Yes.
I want to make a film in a movie theater all over Japan.
Wow.
A director can only be a smart person.
Yes.
My father said that if you go to a good university, you will be a good student.
A film director?
Yo! Start!
I have a big dream for me who is living a normal life.
I'm not old at all.
But Hikaru is a man who has always been a grown-up.
When the summer vacation was coming to an end, a big thing happened.
You don't say?
You are going to do a film?
Yes.
I suddenly got a fever this morning.
If I asked a doctor to come ...
No, you will be ill.
It's almost the first screening time.
Well, if you call for help, it's okay.
I'll do it on my own.
You?
Yes.
But you are ...
I understand, father.
You'll be safe for a while.
But, teacher, today is the first day...
Father, I'll do it for you.
S-silly. I'm still a criminal.
It's okay, father. Leave it to me.
I can't help it. I'll ask the doctor for help.
Yes.
Anyway, let's see what's going on.
Hikaru, we heard what you said.
We'll help you.
Thank you.
There are already a lot of customers.
It's time for the screening.
Hikaru.
Then, Kankichi, ring the buzzer.
Yes.
This one.
Tonpei, turn off the lights.
Roger.
Turn off the lights.
Chinkichi, open the curtain.
I'll be waiting.
Turn off the light on the screen.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Now, let's go.
Yes.
Let's go.
Okay.
Ta-da, let's go.
This is it.
Let's go.
It's good.
I'm ready to go.
Rensui, ready.
The End
That way!
Don't just watch movies!
Get the film back!
I'm in trouble.
What's wrong, Hikaru?
The sequel isn't here yet.
What? There's only one more?
Yeah.
It went well, but if the rest of the film didn't come...
I'll go on the way.
Kankichi!
It's the usual order, but the film's already here.
I'll go on the way.
This is the last reel.
If the film doesn't arrive in 13 minutes,
the movie will be cut in the best part.
Then the movie will be cut in the worst part.
What? 20 minutes ago?
Yeah.
If the movie goes on for 5 minutes,
the film won't arrive in Orion Island.
What's happening?
The End
Where did it go?
No way...
Are you okay?
It looks like the leg bone is broken.
The ambulance is here!
Old man!
It came from Orion Island. Where's the film?
You're in the way!
Everyone's waiting!
Old man, where's the film?
Please...
Leave it to me, old man!
Hey, what time is it now?
It's past 10:05.
We're not done yet!
Only 5 minutes left.
Episode 2: "Ne Efendimiz"
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Sorry, sorry!
Oh yeah, the Sandlot....
No way!
It's a mattoon this time!
Damn it! It took too long to get back!
It's a curve again!
Here! Here!
Now it's construction time!
I can't stop!
The film!
Wait! Wait for me!
I really don't have time!
The mud man?
No! I don't have time!
We don't have a minute left.
What's he doing?
What's up with Kankichi?
The mud man is going to end up in a good place!
Hikaru!
The mud man!
It's me!
Kankichi! Where's the film?
Here!
Hikaru! Take this!
Thank you, Kankichi!
It's a sign!
We made it!
It's okay.
Good~
Haha~
In the end, Aesaki was automated and he lost his qualification as a film master.
Since that, he doesn't get along with Hikaru anymore.
What happened to him after that?
He became the director.
He is still doing well in his paprika.
Also,
- Well, let's go, senpai. - Huh? Where?
Where? The last screening of "Orionza", right, Ryo-chan?
That's right.
Thank you very much for coming to the last screening of "Orionza".
The movie we're going to watch today is a nostalgic movie that was decided by everyone's request.
Please enjoy the movie until the end.
Huh? Huh?
I love movies.
Te-ten is decided, then the flicker is picketed, then the movement is heaped,
then everything is combined, then a great power is flying.
Here's the last energy like a dream, for everyone.
Tomorrow, tomorrow
♪ Believe in the future, draw the universe, and stand on the ground ♩
♪ The planet with the turtle will change the world ♩
♪ This is good, right? ♩
♪ There is no excuse! ♩
It's here! The ghost of Urajima Taro!
What? It's alive?
Then take it to Ryugu Castle!
Wait a minute, grandpa!
I'm not a real turtle,
and I don't know where Ryugu Castle is!
Next time, "The Return of the Turtle"!
Thank you!