"Tekken"
When you're watching TV
Make sure you make the room light and stay away!
Hey, Ryo, you want to do fortune-telling again?
This time, it's about the fortune-telling of animals!
I told you that fortune-telling is all over the place!
What exactly is a fortune-telling of animals?
It's about the marriage of a young man named Koala, a monkey, and a girl named Mihara Junko!
No, Ryo! This is not a fortune-telling of animals, but a fortune-telling of gods!
Ryo, who was born on March 3rd, is a god of Kamakura!
He's proud of his average height even when he's hit by rain or wind!
If it's a god, then it's Kamakura, right?
We're all the same, right?
After the rain, as if someone was calling me
I walked back and forth, holding my mother's hand
I felt something strange at that time
So I'll give you a new tile!
I only walked through the dark side
Everyone was a child once, but they all forgot
A politician with a big-faced face and a blue aunt on top of his/her eyes
Turn and look at that corner
To everyone, to everyone!
I can meet you there
There's a turtle over there
Oh, there's a turtle for sure
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Drink the haji and get a part-time job!
Did you have fun, Daisuke?
Yes!
I see
Here you are
Oh, this is Ohara-san
Yamada-san
A part-time job?
I'm sorry to be embarrassing, but I was fired
So I can't find a job
Here you are
So you knew the manager?
I was shocked. I think he's the same age as me
So I was shocked. I think he's the same age as me
There's a saying that a part-time job is not easy
Well, he wasn't depressed, that's good
You should be careful too
If you're fired that young
You'll have to make a way to Ibarani
Don't be stupid!
You'll be the best in the country
You're a good person
It's okay
It's fine. Even if it is, I can live no matter what I do.
Because I'm like a part-time job for the police.
Idiot! Are you proud of that?
Mr. Omari, the suspicious guy who sneaked into the building...
Huh?
The culprit found out that there was a continuous storm of buildings during the execution.
Thank you all for your cooperation.
Thank you for your cooperation.
So, Chief, let's go to the library.
Ryotsu, why do you have to go to the library?
There's no other way. They say they're paying for the patrol car.
It's better to wait for the patrol car.
No, it's better for us to go to the library.
It's a bonus.
Please wait a minute, Chief.
What? What's wrong?
I peed.
What? You're not a child, so be patient.
No! I'll leak!
I'll do it in this park.
Ryotsu, wait!
I can't help it.
Sir, please hurry up.
Don't be in a hurry. You'll be in charge of the car for a while.
Take a good breath now.
Sir, there's no good air in a place like this.
That's right.
Is this a toilet?
I'm sorry, Ryotsu.
Hey, wait!
Oh, no!
Wait!
Ryotsu!
I'm sorry!
Sir, this!
Damn it! If you let me go here, I'll get a bonus.
But I'll be in trouble!
Wait a minute!
Hey, wait!
What?!
What are you doing?
Sakuya!
Wait!
You'll be in trouble if you do this!
ah!
Oh, Ryotsu's not here!
Wait!
Come on!
No! No! No!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
You idiot! You want to burn me alive?
You can do both, but it's your responsibility as a director, Ohara-kun!
I'm sorry. What should I say?
I don't want to hear anything!
You're fired! You're fired!
I'm fired?
Chief, the time has come when you should be afraid.
Chief, are you also fired?
You idiot! You too!
Huh? I knew it.
I never thought I'd be fired.
Chief, you can't just keep sighing.
If you do this, you have to find your own way to live.
A way to live?
Yes.
You can work part-time or do anything to earn money for your living.
I-I see. Ryo-kun, do you have a good part-time job?
Yes.
Chief, do you have any special skills?
Special skills?
Well, I have a master's degree, a master's degree, a sword skills...
You can't have special skills like that.
You need to be a high-ranking officer or use a computer.
You don't have any special skills.
I can't have that.
But I have a career as a police officer for 34 years...
That's useless!
What?
You can't have a license to handle dangerous objects or a cooking license.
What would you need to get a fire-fighting license?
What would you need to be a fireman or an instructor?
There's no need for that.
You have to have some knowledge of paarthing.
You can also make an assistant.
If you have enough experience, you can make hats.
If you can handle it, you can also make cookies.
You have to be good at cooking and they'll be able to eat spagetti in your appetite!
What?
You really can't do basic means!
At this age, it's tough to find it.
No, Ryo-kun.
I have to protect my own life, too.
I'm counting on you, Ryotsu.
Hmm. It's not good to be asked by a former boss.
Former...? I'm counting on you.
You can't refuse a former boss' request.
Former?
Well, if I'm with you, it'll be fine.
Let's look for a part-time job together.
I'm counting on you. You're the only one I can count on.
Leave it to me.
I'm counting on you.
Hahaha.
Welcome. How are the fries?
Hmm. They're a bit hard.
You don't look happy.
There are a lot of young people around here, so you must be hostile.
N-No, I'm not.
What do you mean?
I hate young people.
I'm in trouble. There are only young customers.
That's right.
I'm not angry, I'm not in trouble, I don't think anything.
The rule is basic.
Can you do it?
It's all right.
Look, this is not a store for old-timers.
Hey, I'll order.
Yes, I'm home.
Welcome. We have an easy-to-see menu here.
I don't need it.
Just a shake and cheeseburger, please.
Yes, one shake and one cheeseburger.
Would you like fries with it?
I said I don't need it.
That's what I said, right? Hurry up.
Here's your shake and cheeseburger.
It's 380 yen.
That Ryotsu doesn't get hungry easily.
It's a perfect match.
Thank you very much.
Please take it easy.
You put up with it well.
Because fast food is a lot of fun with a smile.
Usually, I kick that guy, but it's for the money.
It's amazing that the share is for the money.
It's for living.
Welcome.
Now you try it.
Smile, smile.
Welcome.
Here's an easy menu.
Why? Are you an old man?
I get mad when I see an old man.
What?
Don't get angry.
What are you doing?
You're a bad old man.
I feel bad.
What?
I can't help it.
Shut up.
You be quiet.
You?
I can't help it.
You're right.
Smile.
Stop laughing.
I'll give you a cute little guy.
You don't know how to talk.
Wait a minute.
I'll teach you something called courtesy.
You stupid.
You're too fast.
You need to act.
I'm serious.
Stop right there, kid.
What are you doing?
The cost?
Each color's different.
Just one.
So, you're making me laugh?
Get out of the way and get out of my way.
I can't hear you.
No, you can't hear me.
It's a part-time job, so please do it as the manual says.
I got it.
Listen, no matter what kind of guy comes, don't get angry.
I'm hungry.
Welcome.
Here.
I'm hungry.
You guys.
You think it's okay to eat something that you can't see?
What?
Shut up.
I'm hungry.
You should pay when you go out.
You idiots.
You're just like you.
You're pretending not to see.
But you're a man.
What?
Listen, you idiot.
Do you have any respect for your family?
You've got a strong temper.
So, you want to be fired again.
After all they fired a kid.
What's going on in this country.
I can feel the worst.
It's impossible for the head of the company to be a customer.
Yeah.
So I've found something that suits you.
It's a daily wage, so you'll have the feeling that you're working.
What do you think, chief?
You don't have to be careful with this book.
Well, I guess.
What are you doing, old man? You're so annoying.
Ah, sorry.
Clean up that early and bring the money over there.
Y-yes, sir.
Chief, please be careful with your foot.
I-I'm fine.
No, I'm not.
I'll rest for a bit.
Again?
Well, it can't be helped.
Then let's put it down here.
Be careful.
Lucky, lunch time!
Th-thanks.
Chief, this won't last a day for just half a day.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Hey, didn't you have my lunch there?
I left mine there, too.
Huh?
You're putting a lock here?
No, it's illegal.
But the chief will be fired one after another.
If you say no, I'll say no.
Good luck, sir.
Hey, what are you doing?
Huh?
No filling up.
All right.
Come with us to the police station.
Well, um, you know.
No, no.
We're from the police department.
I was just collecting the loot.
Collecting?
Chief, run away!
Hey, get in the car!
Chief, get out of the car!
Hey!
Oh, come on!
I don't want to live like this anymore.
I never thought my part-time job would be this hard.
That was a good bath. I'm finally tired.
Thank you for your hard work today.
You seem to be tired lately, but please don't overdo it.
It's not easy for you to be sick.
I'll try my best.
It's my duty to support my family no matter how hard it is.
You have to be patient this time.
I'm your former boss, so I'm doing my best.
Former boss...
This is really the last part-time job.
I'm afraid of heights.
Don't look down.
Please wipe the windows properly.
No, I'm scared.
It's too scary.
It's for living.
If you don't want to, I don't want to.
Get out of the way.
No.
Don't mess with me.
Stop it.
Don't push me in a place like this.
Who are you?
Don't step on the switch.
Ryotsu, stop.
Down, down.
Down?
You're going too far.
Up, up.
What are you talking about?
Stop.
Good.
Here.
Down slowly.
Stop.
Ryotsu, look.
What?
Look.
It's him.
The one who left the building in the storm.
That bastard.
What?
What are you going to do, Ryotsu?
Let's break through the window and get in.
Idiot.
The windows at such a high place are all thick and double.
If you hit with a hammer, you can only get cracks.
And if the glass shards fall down, it's bad.
Let's climb up and step inside for now.
Roger.
Good.
Okay.
Captain, hurry.
Oh, this must be the worst floor, Captain.
What?
What? This is the 80th floor, so it's probably 30 floors below.
All right, let's go 50 floors.
Roger.
But you saved me on Sunday.
It's easy to find the culprit without anyone.
Ryo-chan, you go there.
Roger.
Wrong.
Did you find it?
It's not this floor.
All right, let's go one floor below.
Hey, is this floor all office?
That's right.
What about a private room like a law firm or a president's office?
Private room?
I think it's two or three floors below.
All right, wait.
Yes, sir.
It's two or three floors below.
Good luck, sir.
I'm coming first.
Please come after me.
Ooh.
Oh.
I'm going to heave a good night's sleep, so get some rest.
Pack the bags and go to the bedroom.
Wait up!
Are you okay, chief?
I'm fine.
Go down.
Roger that.
Damn, down.
Alright, we're here.
Damn, we're down!
Wait, are we really down?
Huh?
I can't do this...
I'll never let you get away with this!
Prepare yourself!
Wait!
Kanishiro!
You did it, Ryotsu.
Yes, sir!
Thank you for your help in arresting the culprit.
You're the one who...
You're in my way.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Ohara, you're a great man.
I didn't know you were following the culprit while you were working part-time during the probation period.
Well, how should I say it?
The long-standing reputation as a policeman has led to the arrest of the culprit.
What did you just say, sir?
The probation period?
That's right. Congratulations.
From tomorrow on,
you'll be the head of the police force.
Then, I'll be the head of the police force.
Who said that?
I won't let a policeman like you go.
Oh, thank you very much.
That's great, sir.
Let's work hard together as policemen.
Ryotsu...
I see.
At that time, I knew that being a policeman was my job.
I'm glad I became a policeman.
So, you didn't come to the police station.
And Ryo-chan and the chief.
Well...
So, the young men's dislike for the chief is a little better, isn't it?
That's right.
I have to understand their way of thinking.
They don't always pretend to be watching.
They're doing pretty well as a team.
Their appearance is good and so are their ways of thinking.
You guys!
What?
Huh?
Don't you have to throw away your empty cans in the trash?
Hey, wait!
This is why young people these days are not good at this!
♪ The train is coming ♪
♪ I'm sleeping on my dad's back ♪
♪ This week, too ♪
♪ I'm doing my best ♪
♪ The sound of the gong is also good ♪
♪ I'm holding the bucket in one hand ♪
♪ But the hot soup bowl is so hot ♪
♪ The annoyance of the remaining work ♪
♪ I'm annoyed, so I'll clear it up ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ If you take a hot shower ♪
♪ I'll recover my health with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ On Monday ♪
♪ Monday ♪
Profiler from the main office?
Is profiling the latest investigation method
that analyzes the psychology of the culprit
and divides the number of criminals?
I understand that,
but why don't we dress like this?
Next time on "The Girl Manga DECA"
Thank you for watching!