The End
When you watch TV
Keep your room bright and keep your distance
It's like someone's calling
After the rain
You look back
And walk
Give your hand to your mom
The strange feeling I felt
At that time
So I walked
Of the arcade
And saw
Who was it?
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgot
A politician with a big face
And a blue aunt in her eyes
Turn around
That corner
You can see everyone
There's a wall there
Come on, everyone
To our town
Thank you!
Friendship Wings
It's not fair!
J.A.T.
This is the union business
Thank you for your service
recyclable
Coast ME
Rent
As well as
With various
E-sports
I'm going home for my friend's wedding.
I didn't know that.
We will arrive at Haneda Airport soon.
Captain, the wheels are not working.
What?
One more time.
No, they're not working.
Stop landing. Increase the altitude.
What? It started to rise again.
What happened?
What? It doesn't fly at all.
It's strange. I made it according to the design.
The main wing is in bad position.
Ryo-san.
Let me see.
Look, the center of gravity is too forward.
What?
The angle of the wings doesn't change.
What? Is that so?
The position of the wings is important for airplanes.
The wings are the life of the airplane.
Do you know why airplanes fly?
I don't know.
They fly because they fly.
By changing the angle of the wings to the energy of the wind,
the aircraft becomes powerful and powerful.
Ryo-san, you're amazing.
You know everything.
That's the acceptance of a best friend in elementary school.
I see.
But it's amazing that a best friend knows that in elementary school.
Yes.
That's Takashi.
He said he wanted to be a pilot in the future.
He liked airplanes so much.
I see.
When I was the same age as you,
the airplane contest hosted by the model company was held every month.
I participated in it often.
Do you know Bentendo Island,
in the middle of Ueno's Shinobazu Lake?
Yes.
The contest was a competition to fly an airplane to Bentendo Island,
but it was a tough one because if you failed on the way,
you would fall into the lake.
Go, Stargo!
Go!
Number 21 failed.
Damn it!
Next is number 22.
All right.
Kankichi, do your best for us.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Good direction.
Good wind direction.
Go, Hindenburg!
Ouch!
Number 22 failed.
What?
You can't even reach the lake.
That's strange.
What's wrong with it?
Isn't it all?
I'm sorry.
It seems that everyone failed.
It's impossible to fly to Bentendo Island.
Wow!
And I'm running out of electricity.
Wow…
Whose's it?
Adults make it, right?
That's number 24 from Lindbergh.
Number 24?
Yes.
Huh?
I can't believe it.
It's like a child like us.
The winner is Takashi Asahina of Lindbergh.
The airplane is amazing.
Incredible.
Hey,
if you like,
If you like, can you teach me how to make it?
Please!
Sure.
Yay!
For a model airplane, the wings are important.
Wings are the life of an airplane.
Oh...
Do you know why an airplane flies?
No...
Maybe it flies because it flies.
By changing the angle of the wings to the energy of the wind,
the aircraft will have the strength and the power to fly.
Power?
It's hard to say.
Airflow is a property that lowers the air pressure when the speed of the current increases.
The reason why you put paper on the wings is to increase the pressure.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
I don't understand.
In other words...
I brought my first good friend, Kankichi.
You're stupid.
Don't say that.
I could have given you a snack.
Thank you, auntie.
Oh, auntie.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
I'm not your auntie.
Don't laugh like that.
It's disgusting.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
You're a good kid.
You're a smart kid.
Oh, my.
What are you talking about?
You're stupid.
Takashi, you're in the same elementary school as us,
but you know difficult things very well.
My dream is to become a pilot.
A pilot?
That's cool.
It'll be fun.
Oh?
¡Oh, man!
What's that sparkling thing?
¿What can it be?
Isn't it a Ramen?
Takashi?
Do you not know what a Ramen is?
Ramen?
Then I'll teach you how to do it.
Put the Ramen on you and walk.
You'll get the back-igaed Ramen.
Hey, it sounds amazing.
It'll take three years.
You're so powerful.
And among the menkoro, this silver photo is called "silver face" and it's expensive.
Kankichi has 200 silver faces.
It's the man's medal.
Kankichi, you're good.
Well, in Asakusa, Kankichi is the strongest.
I've been doing it for 10 hours and I've even removed the bones on my shoulders.
You're noisy.
It's a very difficult game.
Can you teach me?
Sure.
Huh? I can't do it.
You have to step on the axis.
Like this?
You have to be strong.
For example, when you remember being scolded, you say, "Daddy, you're an idiot!"
Ouch!
What did you say?
It's dangerous to say it out loud.
So you have to shout it out in your mind and hit the menkoro.
I got it.
Daddy's...
Idiot!
I did it!
I did it, Kankichi!
Good job, Takashi!
Since then, we've been in different schools, but Takashi and I met every day and he opened the menkoro and the plane for us.
I can't do it again.
All right! I got it!
Ouch!
All right, your turn, Takashi.
I knew I can't play the real game!
I don't want to get your menkoro anymore...
Don't worry about it.
Takashi, don't give up on your menko winning.
Remember! You'll definitely win if you # sigma # win!
I got it, Kankichi!
Remember! You'll definitely win if you # Tamara # win!
We can win!
Alright!
BABALO!
You idiot!
We did it!
Hey!
Come to my house next time.
It's the first night market near the lighthouse.
Eh?
Can I go?
Yeah.
Alright!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Oh!
Here!
Look!
It's a candy shop.
It's not the house of the minister.
Welcome!
Ah...
Hello!
Please come in.
Let's go to my room.
Oh,
Thank you for the tea.
We'll bring tea later.
Okay.
It's beautiful.
It's elegant.
It's different from my mother.
What's wrong?
Come on.
Yeah.
Wow!
It's amazing.
Takashi's room is full of airplanes.
My dad is a pilot.
Eh?
A pilot?
That's why he's famous as a pilot.
That's amazing.
Here.
Here's your tea.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, I want coffee.
How about sugar?
Yes.
It's my first time to drink coffee.
I'll have 10 cups.
We'll have 10 cups, too.
10 cups?
Dad,
they're Asakusa's friends.
They talked about us before.
it's you guys.
We're here.
Dad,
are you leaving already?
Yeah.
This flight to Europe will be longer.
Cool.
It's Europe.
Europe?
Where is Europe?
I know it's Harappa.
Have a good time.
Thank you.
Go.
Dad,
previously on TV,
you said you knew everyome.
Just like dad.
Almost like a home drama in the United States.
Did something happen?
No.
It's the first time I've seen my dad
tie up his tie to go to work.
My father,
no,
he looks like a dod blade.
Mine, too.
Mine is the clay one.
Your place is
just a far away place in Asakusa.
It's so nice.
Not at all.
It's just old and old.
All three of us are drinking.
That's all we do when we're on leave.
Well, then, take your time.
Thank you.
Takashi's so nice.
He has such a beautiful mother and a cool father.
I envy him.
I envy Kanchi and the others.
I envy the two of them.
Huh?
Oh, right. Let's play some games.
Wow, there's a lot of games.
Which one should we play?
What about the time-lapse train game?
What's so funny about that?
Chinkichi is a railroad maniac.
Hey, let's play just once. It's fun.
You play it alone.
What? You want me to wear a tie?
Do you have a fever?
No.
My father wants me to wear a tie like Takashi.
Can you cook with a tie?
You idiot!
Hey, wait.
Hey, Kanchi. I brought you some coffee.
As expected! This is American style.
Here.
Huh?
Mom, don't drink it.
Don't drink it.
Drink it in a cup with a handle.
I don't have anything like that.
It's the same as anything if you get hungry.
Hmm.
No.
This father is so far from America.
What?
You want me to take a pilot's license now?
Don't you dare lie down!
Hey, you!
What are you thinking?
If you have time to think about that,
learn how to make a chowchin.
You won't make it in time for the order.
Damn it!
What?
The next person is him?
It's cooler if you go out by car.
You idiot!
Ouch!
Where do you get such money?
You idiot!
I can't do it either.
My father can't talk either.
All three of them are stubborn fathers.
I really envy Takashi.
A car that's expensive for a nice house.
A cool dad who's as beautiful as a beautiful woman.
Isn't that great?
Not at all.
My dad is not at home at work.
I envy Kanchi and his parents who are always with him.
You're so noisy.
Yeah.
My parents...
They don't seem to get along very well.
No way!
My parents...
They fight a lot recently.
I don't care if they don't live in a good house.
I don't care if they don't have a car that's expensive.
I just want my mom and dad to get along.
Don't worry.
My mom and dad are fighting every day.
My mom and dad?
My mom too.
It's okay.
Takashi's parents will get along soon.
I guess.
They're adults.
Yeah.
It's okay.
It's much better now.
Really?
Takashi praised me.
Great!
Okay.
I'll give you the flight this month.
You'll fall into the pond.
What?
But I think it's going to be a good flight.
Okay.
I'll fly you to the movie theater next week.
Stop it, Kanchi.
Next week?
I'm looking forward to it.
You don't like being with your family that much?
Stop it.
You'll always have to do your job.
Which is more important?
Your family or your job?
Even if you have to fly, you'll still be the pilot's wife.
Or should I say your wife?
You should marry the plane.
Shut up.
You're so late.
The movie's about to start.
Hey.
You should've thrown it before we left.
It's starting.
Yeah.
Let's wait inside.
Takashi finally got here.
Did he go to school?
Let's give him the pamphlets.
Takashi was looking forward to the movie.
Huh?
Takashi's house is...
It's pitch black.
That's strange.
It's not showing at all.
There's no car either.
Are you the Kankichi brothers?
Yeah, but...
The kids of Asahina-san are holding this thing.
Oh! Takashi's plane!
Thank you!
Oh! That letter is here.
Uncle, where's Takashi and the gang?
They left.
Their parents got divorced.
What? Divorced?
But they left with their mother now.
They'll probably go back home.
No way.
Why are they keeping it from us?
Kankichi, Tonpei, Chinkichi, please forgive me for leaving you in silence.
The two months I spent with you were so much fun.
Ueno 22:20, Aomori 20th!
Maybe it's this train!
22:00?
We have 5 minutes left!
No! It will take 10 minutes from here to Ueno Station! We won't make it!
No! We can still make it!
What?
We can't make it!
The 22:20 Aomori special train will depart soon.
Please get in and wait for us.
Kankichi, we can't make it! We won't make it!
But the direction is different!
I'm going to go home! Wait for me!
Kankichi! What are you thinking about?
It's okay if I'm not here, Takashi.
Okay, Mama.
It just started.
We can't make it!
Hey!
What are you doing? The train is...
We can't make it! We won't make it!
Besides, where are we going?
Ueno station is over there!
Just follow me!
I was so happy!
Why?
Why did we get divorced?
Kankichi!
I don't know!
The world of adults!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Goodbye.
The train will depart.
I understand. It's Nippori.
The train might pass through here.
What time is it now?
10:05 a.m.
That's it! That train!
Help me!
It's silver!
Did they go to pick this up?
What should we do with this?
Takashi, you gave me the most important plane.
You gave me a plane. Now it's my turn!
Throw it at the train!
Take my treasure!
What? Snow?
A shining god is flying!
No way!
Kankichi and the others!
Let's fly the plane together again!
Let's make it to the end!
You were on board, Takahashi.
I was.
I'm glad to see you.
The End
Amazing!
Thank you, Ryo!
Ryo, did Takahashi become a pilot?
I don't know.
But I believe that he will.
He will realize his dream and fly the world.
Ryo, this is bad!
Reiko and Nakagawa are on the plane!
Everyone, the plane is about to land.
Please follow the instructions of the crew.
Everyone, please calm down!
There is no point in making a fuss here.
Let's believe in the captain here!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Don't give up!
If you think you can hide it, you will definitely win!
Kankichi, I won't give up!
Take this!
Let's go for a little opppression!
Let's go, Takahashi!
Still, we'll take it easy here.
Hey.
Are you before us?
Whoa!
How precious!
We are one and only.
Let's go!
So, where does this plane go?
What?
Captain, we did it! We did it!
Reiko!
Nakagawa!
Hey!
Ryo!
Senpai! Terai!
You're safe!
Thanks to you, we were saved.
That's great.
It's all thanks to Captain's calm control.
It's Captain!
Kankichi!
T-Takashi!
Let's go, Kankichi.
Get off the bus!
Hey!
Go!
Me!
If you don't make it, it's too dangerous!
Good!
Move it!
It's dangerous!
I'm not scared with you!
You're my best friend from the first episode!
Keeper, keeper, it's time to save the world.
I'm sorry I'm your darling.
Where are you going?
Come on!
Please, stop.
Razor!
♪ It's so smooth and smooth ♪
♪ Even the frustration that's been left behind ♪
♪ Let's get rid of it with "Iraniran" ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ If you go through the hot shower ♪
♪ Get well with a safe pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ Every Monday ♪
Oh, "Denyoku Plus"! Long time no see!
I'm going to the amusement park with my father.
I thought he was your father, so I thought he was a good guy.
He's a very decent guy.
No, he's not!
Hey, you should do something about this father!
Next time on "The Hyper President's Family Service"!
Thank you for watching!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's definitely a turtle over there ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪