Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I wonder if I went to the taiko that I jockeyed ♪
♪ I laughed at the fact that it was still a joke ♪
♪ There is only a reason to be angry wherever you are ♪
♪ The cityscape that doesn't change even if you have one evil intention is kinder than the world ♪
♪ Because the crows are crying, the sun is already setting ♪
♪ The yakitori is overflowing, the beer is overflowing ♪
♪ From the tap of the dongari hat ♪
♪ The sunset falls to the taishakuten ♪
♪ It will end tomorrow as well ♪
♪ I laughed at the fact that it was still a joke ♪
♪ I lost my happiness ♪
♪ I realized that I was a fool ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
THE RACING PEOPLE
TO TAPE
Well, well. I haven't been in a very good mood lately.
The tea I got from after one job has weer good.
Yes, chief.
Hideyo, your legs are shaking.
You can't do this, Hideyo.
You're lacking in exercise.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Next is the abdominal exercise.
One, two, one, two, one, two, three, four...
Dad, your body is stiff.
I'm trying my best.
I'm doing it.
But I'm sick.
If you do it, you can do it.
Ryo.
No.
Not "no".
You were selling oil here again.
No, it's not.
It's a patrol in the park.
Ryo, it's painful.
Yes.
So what happened, chief?
It's the autumn of sports.
Well, actually...
Daisuke's sports day?
In my school, the students and the subordinates are divided into red and white groups and participate in the competition.
We'll win.
Ryo, come and see us.
I said it well, Daisuke.
That's the spirit.
So the chief himself trains his wife and grandchildren.
It's a wonderful family love.
Oh, I want to cry.
You're saying something like that on purpose.
You who can only move with money can understand.
I'm being called.
All right.
Next, dash to that slide.
Repeat five times.
Ready.
All right, Daisuke.
Go.
Don't lose, dad.
Goal.
Just a little more.
Go for it.
Goal.
All right.
Second.
Goal.
All right.
Good.
Wait, wait.
Good job.
Goal.
All right, forget it.
Damn it.
Dad, are you okay?
Hideyo.
Are you all right?
Well, let me see.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
I can't get it.
Ryozu, let him play.
All right.
Yeah.
I don't think they can play tomorrow.
If you rest tonight...
If you force yourself, you'll be late for your treatment.
Hideo-kun, don't worry. I'll do something about it.
What? I'm going out instead?
Daisuke is working so hard. There's no way you can leave him alone.
Hideo-kun can't go out. You're the only one who's got time and energy.
It's for Daisuke.
But...
Ryo-chan, please go out.
You're always the only one who's got time and energy.
Wait a minute.
You're suddenly telling me that.
I have a schedule.
I'm sure Sunday is full of schedules.
I have to work until 5:00 a.m. and TV until 12:00 p.m.
Monkey.
You want that, don't you?
No, I don't.
Then I'll be like a money-grubber.
Oh, yeah.
Then...
Oh, I'm bored.
I'm bored of the day.
I'm bored of my schedule.
It's too early.
It's a trick to make money.
Whatever happens, we'll definitely make Daisuke's red group win.
Leave it to me.
It's cheap.
If you lose, I'll double it and give it back to you.
It's okay.
Then I have to get ready for tomorrow and get ready to go out.
I'll excuse myself today.
That's the silver.
I'm not in a good mood.
Are you really okay?
Well, the one who can beat Senpai with physical strength is Hiroshi, but there are not many people.
That's for sure.
Honda, I'm going again.
But Senpai, are you okay?
I'm exercising.
I see.
The opponent is a young man with a lack of exercise.
That's what I'm going to be.
That's right.
If you don't bring an Olympic player, you won't beat Senpai.
Next.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Now, my motto is to deepen the bond between parents and children.
Therefore, I would like everyone in the family to participate in the competition.
Ryo-chan? What happened?
It's late.
That idiot.
He is late for such an important time.
That's him.
Ryo-kun.
Mr. Honda?
What's wrong?
We've been drinking together since last night.
We've been drinking since last night.
What?!
I fell asleep in the middle of it, but Senpai kept drinking until just a while ago.
My head hurts!
Are you okay with this?
Senpai, wait a minute!
Senpai, wake up! Senpai!
Ryo-chan, wake up!
You can't do that!
I can't drink anymore.
I'm freezing! What am I going to do?!
Are you awake, idiot?!
Chief!
Senpai, it's a sports day!
A sports day?
It's Daisuke-kun's sports day. It's about to start.
Ah, I see.
Don't be so stubborn, Ryo-chan.
We're going to have a 100-meter-long competition soon.
Senpai, can you run?
I'm fine.
Let's see...
This is fine. Don't worry. It's a perfect hand.
The first event is a 100-meter-long race.
The competitors will gather at the first gate.
All right! Leave it to me!
Ryo-chan, are you really okay?
Easy, easy.
Uh, I was in the red team.
I've seen that before.
Huh? Isn't that Tsuruta, a player from the J-League?
What?
That's right. He's the Japanese representative, Tsuruta.
Why is there such a guy?
You're surprised too soon. Look over there.
Huh?
It's Hayami Shunsuke of the Olympics.
What? Is there a 100-meter Japanese record holder?
Yes. He's a father of a freshman. He's a famous student.
Damn it. I've never seen such a strong opponent.
Is there a famous person in the red team?
There is. Look!
Ah, thank you. I can't do anything alone.
Haku-san, Minamiyama of the Japanese Academy.
Jambaraya, the composer.
Uh, and the professor of the university.
I won't be a full power!
Hmm, this is really bad if I don't get serious.
The 100-meter race is about to start.
I hope the strong opponent is not the opponent.
He's a little weak, Ryo-san.
Ready!
Now, the first group has started.
Tsuruta has already jumped out.
He's pulled out the other players in a flash.
Tsuruta is already in the straight line.
Goal!
Tsuruta is in first place, as expected.
How is his record?
He's got 10.09 seconds!
In a non-eventual participation race in elementary school, he suddenly got 10 seconds.
He's finally a senior.
Ryo-san, do your best!
Now, Hayami, the Japanese record holder, is in this group.
Will he be able to break the record of Tsuruta earlier?
About the position...
Same group, huh?
Ready!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Good job!
Hayami started lightly, but he was caught in a flash.
Oh, no!
Is this a human or a gorilla?
Hayami is chasing a player with a fierce momentum.
Damn it!
Fukie Takagawa is racing!
Oh, no!
Why is he so furious?
It's the gorilla again!
No, a general faster than Hayami caught up with him!
That's a great dead heat!
Goal!
Hayami, the first shot!
Oh...
That was close, wasn't it?
Idiot!
Don't be silly, Ryo-tsu!
Hm...
I can't stand this anymore...
I can't wait.
Wow, what a record!
It's a record for Japan!
Hayami has updated his own record!
I see!
Then I'm not a 9 second record, either.
You're kidding me!
Awesome!
Stand in position!
Ready!
Nice, Daisuke!
Daisuke!
Go, Grandpa!
-Yay! -Good job, Daisuke!
-Good job, Mom! -Good job!
-You practiced a lot. -Yeah!
Ryotsu, why don't you learn from Daisuke?
Next is the hammer throw competition.
Okay, I got it next.
That was close!
He fell on the 85-meter line.
The white team's Mizobuchi had only one meter left!
What? That Olympic Mizobuchi?
Why are there so many Olympic and pro athletes?
I don't believe this!
Episode 1: The
He was 28 points behind.
Daisuke won the first place, so do something about it, Ryotsu.
Even if I say that, it's the opponent's opponent no matter how hard I try.
Do something about it.
I won't let you lose, Ryotsu.
No way!
Next is the sand draw by FUKEI.
The sand draw is my specialty.
Now...
What?
There's a sumo wrestler!
The red team is...
I knew it.
Listen.
There are two sumo wrestlers.
If you do it properly, you won't win.
So...
FUKEI versus the sand draw.
Which will win, the red team or the white team?
The white team with the sumo wrestler is the winner?
That's right!
Yes!
The red team!
This is the red team's victory!
It's here.
Wow!
I won, I won, I won, I won!
It's a bit hard.
Ryosan is amazing, mom.
I can count on you.
Yeah.
I'll leave it to you.
I've got this!
I'll give you a box with the bet!
Well, give me the box on it.
Let me take a look and look at it.
Give him a little more patience.
Oh, I can't wait to see the odds.
You won't win this time!
You're too calm right now.
I'm down!
I can't do this!
You're doing it wrong!
I've got this!
For you, alcohol is the same as gasoline.
For you, alcohol is more like water than gasoline.
Now, water. It's real.
Drink this.
The first program of the afternoon is
"The Big Ball Rolls by Fukuoka".
Ready!
Oh! Red team is so fast!
White team is pulling them away!
Red team is pulling them back quickly.
Goal! Red team wins!
Next is "The Ball Rolls by Kei".
Ready!
It's you!
I won't lose!
What?
I can take it off.
It's glued with instant adhesive.
And this is garlic.
What?
I got you!
It's the payback I had just had!
Dang you!
What?
It's a shrimp!
You did it! It brought me down again!
You really are Ryo-chan!
You really are like a senior.
You're so dirty as usual.
Next is "The Ball Rolls by Kei".
Huh? It's the Kokaiki Jido!
Huh? They're collecting stamps for the Yamanote Line?
One signal machine? That's impossible!
I-It's impossible! I want to borrow a car!
No way!
The Red Team and the White Team have only 10 points left!
Two more games.
With this 800m relay, if the parents win with two or three players, they can turn the tables.
But Senpai, if you say relay...
The opponents are Hayami and Tsuruta.
They're the best players.
Compared to that, this team is...
So it's them after all.
What should we do, Senpai?
Hmm...
Now, there are two more games left.
First up is the non-competitive relay.
So the first one is Tsuruta.
That means Hayami is the anchor.
Get to the edge!
Huh?
Ryo-san, do your best!
Ryo-tsu!
Ready!
Start!
Tops off have Tsuruta from the White Team!
Ryo-tsu from the Red Team is also right behind them!
The Red Team is in the lead!
Yay!
The White Team is also in the lead, with a 1st place baton!
But he got through in a flash!
The White Team's third player has the baton!
The Red Team has finally gotten the baton!
I've calculated all this.
Change.
What?
The third-class of the White Team is leaving the Red Team!
Hey, Red!
Don't run around!
The fourth-class of the White Team is doing a button-touch!
The Red Team is finally doing a button-touch!
The White Team is definitely at the top!
Oh, the fourth-class of the Red Team is fast!
They took the top back in no time!
They're widening the gap!
That's...
It looks like Ryo-chan.
The Red Team is doing a button-touch!
The fifth-class of the White Team is 200 meters ahead!
Can they make it?
The Red Team is only half way through!
Oh, they're falling!
Meanwhile, the White Team is at the top!
Poor thing...
The White Team is leading the Red Team!
It's the last spurt!
Let's fly!
The red team is doing a button-touch!
What's going on?
The White Team is flying to the top!
The red team is doing a great job!
Ryo-chan's doing a good job, too!
Go, Ryo-chan!
The Red Team is doing a great job!
They've broken the gap!
The red team is finally doing a button-touch!
I'm exhausted...
I'm so thirsty!
Ouch!
Stop!
My back hurts!
Ryo-chan!
Are you alright?
Yes.
I-I-I'm fine...
The last race is the triplets...
Ryo-san, you can't do it!
What's with this?
Ryo-tsu-san, don't overdo it.
You've done a good job.
It's finally the last triplets race.
The players will be gathered at the entrance gate A...
Yeah, it's the last race!
I'm going out.
What?
Where are your legs?
It's not perfect, but I'll do my best for Daisuke.
Papa...
Listen, Daisuke.
The triplets aren't going to run alone.
Help Papa, okay?
Okay!
Okay, you two.
Do your best.
Daisuke, do your best!
Okay!
Ryo-san, I'll do my best!
Okay, well said!
Ready!
Now, the last race.
The triplets start!
Daisuke, do your best!
You!
Daisuke, go!
Go!
You're the best!
Daisuke, you're the best!
Ryo-san, you're the best!
You're the best!
Then you'll get a chance to run a lot.
Daisuke, you're the best!
You're the best!
C'mon, guys!
One, two, three!
Go!
I know!
I'm sorry, dad! I-I'm fine!
I-I'm fine!
Oh, Hideo-kun!
The No.1 in the Red Team suddenly speeds down!
He's going to be overtaken one by one!
Hold on, dad!
Daisuke, don't give up!
That's right! I'll reverse it!
The No.1 in the White Team is in first place!
And the No.2 in the White Team is also in first place!
He's a little far away, but the No.2 in the Red Team is also in first place!
Something happened on the way, but the No.1 in the Red Team is also running desperately!
Dad, don't push yourself too hard! Let's stop!
Daisuke, don't give up!
The goal is just a little further!
Let's run to the end with the power of the two of us!
Yeah! I got it!
Daisuke! Just a little more!
You can do it! Last Spurs!
Daisuke! You can do it!
Now, the No.1 in the Red Team hasn't given up, and he's finally reached the goal!
Daisuke, you're great!
You didn't give up and ran to the end!
Yeah! Dad did a good job, too!
This guy is...
.
. . .
. . . . . . . . . . .
. . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
.
Um, um, that 10,000 yen is...
I don't mind that.
But I have a favor to ask.
Huh?
Come to my sister Sakura's sports event.
You'll win this time.
101, 102, 103, 104, 100...
This is an international kindergarten, so it's an international tournament.
There's a world record holder.
What's this?
The head is at a wedding.
Nagagawa is in Europe.
Terai is sick.
Today I'm alone with Reiko.
Hey, Maria!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
There's no way Reiko and I are alone.
Next time, "Two-person Exhibition."
Thank you for watching!