Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating on the river ♪
♪ Flying to the corner of the pebble ♪
♪ I wonder if I'm going to the taiko that I used to jog ♪
♪ I laughed at the fact that I was still a child ♪
♪ Even if you're doing well somewhere, it's only for the sake of winning ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes even if you have a bad temper is kinder than the night ♪
♪ Because the crows are crying, the sun is already setting ♪
♪ The yakitori is running wild ♪
♪ The beer is running wild ♪
♪ The
♪
♪ ♪
Nakagawa Ryuichiro
The father of Nakagawa Keiichi
The world's best group enterprise
The president of Nakagawa Concern
The catchphrase, "I can work 72 hours!"
He is a super businessman.
I have a meal.
Come and eat!
DECO judgement
Actually, I didn't buy it from your company.
I bought from your company.
There are other companies.
Let's wait 15 seconds.
Okay.
I'll sell it at the price you offer.
Thank you.
I'll send you the details from Nakagawa Secure.
See you.
President, you look tired.
You should take a break.
We have 7 minutes until the end of the day.
Yes.
What's the next schedule?
We meet with Mikimatsu Nakagawa in 2 minutes.
After that,
you will get some sleep for 5 minutes.
Ah, the old man in Hawaii?
Yes.
After the storm, we will talk on the phone with the French president.
After arriving at Heathrow Airport,
we will have a lunch with the members of the English Chamber of Commerce.
After that,
we will meet with Mikimatsu.
But this is the upper part of the Atlantic Ocean.
Hello!
Hey!
Hey, Ryuuichiro!
Oh.
Mikimatsu-sama, we apologize.
I'll come back now.
No, it's fine.
5 years ago, when I promised to give you a date,
I was going to show her off.
But she dumped me.
So I don't have anything special.
I haven't seen her in a long time.
I'm satisfied with just seeing your face.
You can go to sleep now.
Yes, thank you very much.
See you again, Yuichiro!
No! I slept so much!
Where is Mr. Mijimatsu?
He went home 2 minutes ago.
What?!
I can work 72 hours a day, but I can't believe I made such a mistake!
Nakagawa Family's Home Corruption
What?! You're going to quit being a police officer?!
What's the meaning of this, Nakagawa?!
My father suddenly said he was retiring as president of the Nakagawa Group,
so I was appointed as his successor.
Why does that father who loves work more than the meals he eats at the restaurant?
My father, who used to say, "I can work 72 hours a day,"
has been working for 71 hours a day.
I slept for 55 minutes.
My father, who is strict with others, decided to retire because he had to be strict with himself.
What?!
Only 5 minutes?!
Nakagawa, so you're really going to quit being a police officer?!
Yes. I thought I had to follow my father's footsteps one day,
but I didn't know it was so soon.
I still have a lot of things to do as a police officer, so I'm very confused.
Nakagawa!
What are you talking about?!
Is there anyone who would refuse to be the president of the Nakagawa Group,
which has a net profit of over 100 trillion yen?!
Ryo-chan, do you want me to quit being a police officer?
No! I don't want you to quit, either.
But as a distant relative,
I've always thought that Nakagawa is the right successor to the Nakagawa Group.
When did you become a Nakagawa relative?
I don't like it, Bucchan.
This is how I and Nakagawa are related.
Huh?!
My younger brother Kinjiro's wife's mother's father's younger brother's husband
is the son of Nakagawa's uncle's younger brother's daughter.
I-I don't get it...
Anyway!
I believe that Nakagawa is the only man who can become the leader of the Nakagawa Group
and rebuild the world economy!
Sen-Senpai!
Did you buy me that much?!
Of course!
I'm going to do anything to make you the president!
That's right! From today onwards, I'll be your secretary!
Senpai!
Nakagawa!
Say something!
Ryo-chan, aren't you thinking of something weird again?
You're so rude!
I don't know if you're thinking of such a thing!
Look closely!
Ryo!
What are you going to do with the police job?
Of course, I'm going to quit.
Is that really okay?
Yes.
Nakagawa, let's go!
Y-Yes!
I'll become the vice president when I become the president of the Nakagawa Group!
Alright, Nakagawa, let's go! Are you ready?
Y-Yes!
Then, are you really not going to get your retirement back?
Yes.
I think you're the only one who can make the big Nakagawa Group.
Since you said you're going to quit,
I don't have anything to say to you.
But you're still young,
so there's no way you can do your job.
That's not true!
Oh, you're here.
Keiichi!
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hello.
Oh, it's Ryo-chan.
Who is this man?
He's Keiichi's superior.
No, I quit the police job.
Here you are.
I'm going to be the vice president of the Nakagawa Group.
What do you mean by vice president?
Keiichi hasn't been appointed as the president yet.
I'm going to tell you the truth.
The current president has appointed Nakagawa as his successor.
Then I'll ask you this.
Keiichi,
are you really going to be able to do your father's job?
Well...
I can!
Then,
try to be the president for 72 hours.
If you can do that,
I'll accept you as the president of the Nakagawa Group.
I understand.
Senpai,
72 hours is too much.
What are you going to do with your weakness?
I'll do something about it!
Keiichi,
you can do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Y... Yes.
Wake up!
Nakagawa, wake up!
What time do you think it is?
Senpai?
Eh?
It's still before dawn.
Senpai, it's still 5:30!
Shut up!
Open it!
Senpai,
I'm going to change my clothes.
Please wait a moment.
Oh, come on!
Change your clothes in the car!
No way!
Have a seat.
All right.
You have to wear this until you get to the airport.
What?
That much?
We've arrived in Washington.
We have a breakfast meeting with the president.
You're going to the White House?
That's right.
Excuse me.
What?
I just got a call.
The landing is delayed because of the confusion at Washington International Airport.
What?
I won't be able to attend the next meeting in Los Angeles.
Are you going to go with that hand?
I'll go with my own hands.
Senpai, let's not do this.
Don't you dare say that!
Hey!
You can do it!
Yes!
I'm drowning!
I have to go further!
Darn it!
I ended up in the water.
Senpai, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Wait, don't shoot! Nakagawa, say something!
Y-Yes!
I'm Nakagawa Keiichi, and I'm going to be having breakfast with the President.
He's my secretary, and he's not suspicious.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Mr. Ryuichiro's son, huh. I'm glad to meet you.
Me too. It's an honor to meet you.
President, I'd like to ask you about the water that's on the side of the Rocky National Park,
which the Nakagawa Group is going to be selling.
Oh, the water that's going to be selling as Rocky's delicious water.
Of course, yes!
Thank you very much.
Now then, let's go have breakfast.
Yes.
Wow, looks delicious!
Nakagawa, stop right there!
Look! You went over 10 minutes with that trouble just now.
No way! I haven't even had a bite yet!
You're a jerk!
If you're eating, you won't make it to the next meeting in Los Angeles!
Come on, let's go!
Well then, President, I'll be going now.
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, he's just like Ryuichiro, he's a super businessman!
Thank you. That was a very good deal.
Nakagawa, this way!
Oh, Senpai!
What's wrong? Are you going down the emergency exit?
No! The next meeting is at the building next door.
It's faster to go from here.
I left a rope here, so you can cross here.
Eh? You cross by rope?
You're a former police officer, you can do it.
It's so high!
It's faster to go down the elevator, after all.
If you're a bloodthirsty person, you can do it!
Yes!
You're a lifesaver.
Are you really going to do it?
Yes!
Hey, you!
Ouch!
I wish I could've become a fireman!
Okay, this place went well too.
Now, the next meeting is in Japan.
Huh.
Oh no!
Nakagawa! Let's eat in 3 minutes!
Ugh, you killed me.
Slurp, slurp, slurp, slurp.
Ha!
I knew you were going to rush.
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
You haven't eaten!
I'm too hungry to eat.
The next meeting is in France.
You have to eat to strengthen your body.
Senpai, enjoy your meal.
Well, I'm sorry.
What are you going to do about me?
Eat up!
"Merc..."
"Merci..."
"Merc..." "Okay! The contract is done!"
"Merc..."
"Nagagawa! Sign it!"
"S-Sign it?"
"That's right! Sign it in the contract!"
"I'm sorry."
"Here, sign it."
"Oh... sign it..."
"That's right. Sign it there."
"Okay."
"Yes, that's okay."
"Send 1 million tons of sake."
"Go back to Hell. Next is China."
"Okay."
"Sign it."
"Okay, the contract is done! Next is Kenya."
"Are we still going?"
"Of course! What are we going to do with this much money?"
"We can't be the leader of the Nagagawa Group!"
"S-Senpai, we're done."
"Okay, get on the helicopter first."
"Nagagawa! Go back to headquarters and report the progress."
"Okay."
"Hey, Nagagawa! Don't sleep!"
"Y-Yes, sir."
"Be strong! It's only been 50 hours!"
"We're here, Nagagawa."
"Sleep in the conference room. I'll take you there."
"That's it."
"It seems that Keiichi-kun still can't do it."
"If this continues, we'll have to gather the top members of the Nagagawa Group and decide who will be the successor."
"Yes."
"The meeting place is in Tokyo."
"Some of you will be the candidates."
"Let's list the candidates."
"Hey, wait!"
"Don't give up just because you failed once!"
"Give Nagagawa another chance!"
"But..."
"If you're the candidate, it's fine."
"Hmm."
"Okay, I won't fail next time."
"What? You can't use the runway?"
"Are you stupid?"
"I'm sorry."
"I'm out of money today."
"You can't be stupid!"
"You just want the washing alone!"
"You can't be stupid."
"He's here!"
"Hey!"
"What?"
"How could you?"
"The
"What?"
"Why would you anything?"
"What the hell do you mean?"
Wow!
It's been 20 years since I've been to Japan.
Well then, shall we open a meeting to choose the successor of Ryuichiro?
I thought that Keiichi would be good, but it seems that he is still a weakling.
It seems that he was a weakling.
For the time being, as a result of talking with everyone here, five people have been chosen as candidates.
Introduce yourself from Eichi.
I'm Eichi Nakagawa, the head of Nakagawa Business Administration.
I'm in charge of the first-hand trading.
I'm Juichi Nakagawa, the vice-tower of the Nakagawa Bank.
I'm Nakagawa Kofu, the vice-tower of the Nakagawa Bank.
Hi! I'm Tsurumatsu, the grandson of Miki Masaji, and I'm playing in Hawaii.
Nice to meet you!
That's great, Tsurumatsu!
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa, a local official in Tokyo.
Please take care of me.
That's great, Nakagawa!
Ryuichiro, you're going to choose from these five people, how are you going to decide?
Can't you choose one of me?
How about that, everyone?
Then, as the president, you must pursue profits for the employees and their families.
I'll give these five people one million yen each.
One million yen!
You will compete to see how much you can earn with that one million yen a day.
You can do it however you want.
I understand.
I'll do my best.
I'll double it to two million yen.
Aloha!
I'll do my best.
The Chinese spring market went down by five dollars.
It's a buy.
The oil price in Hokkaido is moving.
Alright, it's time to sell.
The euro-to-dollar market is rising.
For now, buy about ten million euros.
Ahahaha!
I won again!
I'm going to increase!
It's my last chance!
Aloha!
Well!
The germs from the hot market of Naftak are all throbbing.
Buy 50 million yen!
Alright, run away.
That's it!
Run!
Hey, Sanba.
Sanba, get out of here!
I'm lost again.
Even though I bet ten million yen!
Senpai!
We already lost 9.9 billion! What are we going to do?
We still have the final race!
If we do this, we'll be aiming for a super big hole!
Nakagawa, Ichikabachika's 181 points!
Buy one billion! It'll be double!
Eh? Is it okay to buy such a big hole?
It's okay!
Leave the strong man of Dotanba to Ryo Tsukankichi!
Yes, I understand. Please!
Let's announce the winners!
First place, Tsurubatsu! 3.5 billion!
Second place, Eiichi! 3.12 billion!
Third place, Baron! 2.5 billion!
Fourth place...
Even so, the fifth place will be eliminated.
Fourth place, Keiichi! 2.0 billion!
11th place, 199 billion.
It's only a billion difference!
So 11th place is disqualified.
Next is Keiichi.
Next is the main office building in Tokyo!
This way.
Boss, stop working and play with me.
S-Sorry. P-Please get off.
A boss shouldn't lose to a secretary's charm.
Nakagawa is not that kind of person.
This way.
Boss, buy a leather coat.
It's a bit expensive.
Please.
Okay. Let's go!
That idiot.
As expected of Mikimatsu's grandson.
Tsurubatsu took out the beauty secretary, so he couldn't try the next person.
It can't be helped. Since Tsurubatsu is disqualified, next.
Ready!
One, two, Tsk!
And once back to the stage.
Tsk!
I'm just a passing mongrel!
Keiichi, what are you doing?
Keiichi is disqualified.
You and Keiichi will have to challenge your last challenge.
As the president, you have to overcome any kind of hardship and reach the top of the world.
And then, the next battle will be...
...Everest!
I'm getting further and further away from the top.
Everest is certainly the top of the world, but...
...the guy who grew up in Hawaii, Tsurumasu, gave up before he could climb it.
My son climbed Everest once in his student days.
Maybe it was a good idea to challenge him.
I will try to crush anyone who climbs to the top by 5:00 p.m.
I'm just a passing Everest mongrel!
I'll roll this stone...
What the...
Help me!
Baron!
I...I heard my senior's voice...
It stopped.
Baron!
There are only three minutes left.
Nakagawa, are you okay?
Is that the top?
Two more minutes!
Two more minutes?
Yes.
Nakagawa, hang in there!
Almost there!
Who are you?
I'm Everest mongrel.
One minute left!
30 seconds left!
Nakagawa, hang in there!
Sen...Senpai...
10 meters left!
Hang in there!
Yes!
Nakagawa, hang in there!
10 seconds left!
5 seconds left!
4 seconds!
3 seconds!
2 seconds!
1 second!
All!
Just 5 seconds!
You did it, Nakagawa!
Sen...Senpai...
Well done!
Now you're the president and I'm the vice president!
Eh?
Keiichi!
Good job!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry for climbing up, but I found out that my clock was 5 minutes late.
What?
In other words, I was working 72 hours a day!
So I'm withdrawing the president's retirement declaration!
What happens to Nakagawa?
Keep being a policeman!
Don't mess with me!
My hard work so far is nothing!
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry, but I'm going to have a business trip, so I'll be rude to you!
Keiichi!
See you in a few years!
Hey!
Wait!
Sounds like your father.
But now I can continue being a policeman.
Nakagawa!
You're back!
Yes.
I look forward to working with you again.
By the way, where's Ryo-chan?
Here.
Who?
Me again!
Oh, this is Ryo-san, a distant relative of Nakagawa.
Do you need anything?
So, I was wondering if it would be okay to go back to the police station.
You don't have a seat anymore.
Nakagawa!
You can use that seat every day!
I see...
Hey, chief!
Please forgive me!
Idiot!
If you want to go back like that,
you'll have to work there for a while!
No!
It's raining like someone's calling me.
But I didn't have to go out yet!
I'll be back!
Akino-san...
Thanks!
Take this.
Here's a lot of soldiers...
Well,
Thanks.
Take care.
Hey, what is this?
That's a old będzie!
I've got to use this.
I'm sure that Kameari will be there!
Come on, everyone!
To our town!
Oh!
Mai-chan!
There is Kameari!
Oh!
I'm sure that Kameari will be there!
Come on, everyone!
To our town!
Thank you!
Oh, no!
I've been caught by the shop's gang!
They forced me to work part-time and tried to pay the debt!
That's so mean!
And why?
Why is Shiratori the partner of the part-time job?
Next time on Ryotsu vs. Shiratori
Part-time job is a big mess!
Thank you for watching!
There is Kameari!
Oh, I'm sure that Kameari will be there!
Come on, everyone!
To our town!
Thank you!