OPEN SUBS
♪ When watching TV, look out the window and look away. ♪
♪ At the end of the rainy season, as if someone's calling you, ♪
I walked while looking back at the afternoon after the rain
I reached out to my mom
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black side of the Akegai Tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
Politicians with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
Everyone, everyone can see
There is a wall there
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Senpai, good morning
You're early today
I was studying Chinese at night to respond to international society
It was a little late, I arrived as it is
It's amazing, right?
What's amazing?
Marjan, Marjan
I see
Anyway, I sleep there
What is this future map?
It's the completion schedule for the Nakagawa Island plan
To overcome the 21st century in which international competition is getting more and more intense
Now at the Nakagawa Group, one-third of Tokyo Bay is full
and gather the main building of the group.
Oh, as expected of the world's best, Konzen Nagagawa.
It's not easy to do.
Of course, each company is connected online,
and it will be a global communication base
that can be accessed by satellite communication and light fiber overseas.
Since each building is connected by monorail and aerial road,
it will activate the interaction within the group and make the work smoother.
I see.
But isn't it inconvenient to commute?
Odaiba is now only available by car and Yurikamome,
so it's quite inconvenient.
I don't worry about that.
Before Nakagawa Island is completed,
I plan to run a non-stop linear subway from Tokyo, Yokohama, Chiba, and my house.
That's great!
How about you try to go from Kameyari?
That's a good idea.
I'll tell the project team.
Oh, that's great!
The bus arrives at the station and is barely safe.
Good morning, Mr. Terai!
Oh, good morning.
You always arrive 15 minutes before, Mr. Terai.
You're late.
Well, I actually bought a house.
I was supposed to go to work today.
What?
The house is the story of the time you were a real estate agent about two years ago?
Yes, after that, I looked at various properties and finally decided on one.
I thought I had given up completely,
I thought he was a good man, but he's been looking for two years.
He's a very dedicated man.
That's normal when you're looking for a house.
Oh, Chief!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Ryotsu, when you're looking for a house, you have to be careful,
and look for it until you're convinced.
If you decide to buy it lightly,
you'll end up crying later.
I don't have to be a good man.
So, Terae-san, what is the next house?
What's the next house?
Well, while I was looking for a cheap house,
I went to the back.
It's either Chiba or Saitama, right?
Anyway, the budget...
Where is it after all? Tell us clearly.
You probably don't know, but the nearest station is Kokkyougaoka.
Kokkyougaoka? I've never heard of such a station.
Is that definitely Japan?
Excuse me, but it's a range that can be used for commuting.
That's why you were late.
I was a little late.
It's because of the bad weather.
It takes three and a half hours.
Three and a half hours?
But the area is 220 square meters,
and there's one person per family,
and there are 20 rooms in the living room.
That's a lot of money.
If you don't mind,
please come with us on the next day.
We'll welcome you.
Oh, we'll have free lunch.
I agree.
If you want to drive, let's all come.
Well, then I'll...
But...
I can't drive.
There's a place I can't pass on the way.
What?
Don't worry.
The train is passing by.
I'll write a map now.
If I get lost on the way, I won't be able to go back.
That place is...
I don't think he's living in the city of Fuji.
Hmm, there's still an SL running.
Oh, that's nice.
It's nice to feel good.
It reminds me of the French garden landscape.
How long will it take?
Wait a minute.
The station we just passed is at the end of the Gaoka.
Next is the Kusoto Bridge.
We'll change trains there.
I see.
It should take three and a half hours.
Anyway, the land was 500 yen.
500 yen?
I bought 200,
but I heard that if you buy 10, you get one.
I heard that if you buy 10, you get one.
That's 220.
What kind of real estate did he buy?
I'm here.
It's a station that's different from a toilet.
That's amazing.
There's no convenience store or house in front of the station.
There should be a bus stop in front of the station.
Senpai, isn't that the one?
What?
This is a trace of a wild animal.
What time is the next bus?
It's 5:05 p.m., so it'll be in about two hours.
What?
Wait for two hours?
I've exchanged the things I came here for.
I didn't expect to see a wooden bus running at this time.
It's better than the bus that comes out of the TOTORO.
Check it out.
There's a used car center.
It's a pretty big used car center.
Business is about to start here in this rural area.
Why is it written with name and address.
Director, everyone, thanks for coming.
Boss, did you buy the whole journey?
We will have to buy a car to live here.
Now, everyone get on!
Now, everyone get on.
I'm going to the supermarket.
It takes 30 minutes to go to the supermarket.
And 1 hour to get to the nearest bus stop.
It's not one bus per family, it's one bus per person.
It's a long way.
Is the bus that has the name on it for commuting?
It's impossible to use a bicycle.
All the employees are using cars.
Then we should go to the station by car.
It's hard to go to the station.
There's no gas bill.
There's a used car center here.
You can buy one for 5000 yen.
What? Is it that cheap?
It's like a bicycle.
Yes, that's why the bus stop is not a local bicycle.
It's a local car park.
It's more amazing than Tokyo.
We're here.
It's a big and nice house.
It's the best environment to raise children.
Yes, it is.
It's green and the air is good.
It's embarrassing.
It's a small house.
It's really big.
It feels like we're all alone in the Pacific.
Let's go inside.
Hello.
What's this?
It's a time-lapse ticket.
If you give me one, I can only invest.
Invest?
Here you are.
It's nice.
It's a pretty girl.
You're so proud of yourself.
It's a calm and spacious house.
I like this place too.
Please have a seat.
Now the lord is also a master.
He's the lord of the city.
It's a big house.
From now on, we'll live together alone.
Sorry for making you come all the way from far away.
It's perfect for this place.
Ryo.
Thank you, madam.
I'm coming.
This is our moving party.
You don't have to be so careful.
I told you I didn't have to be careful.
Hey, don't say that.
You don't have to hit me.
Here's your tea.
Hello.
Oh, you're the kids.
You look like a monk.
Especially your brother.
I'm your older brother, Eitaro.
I'm your younger brother, Bisaku.
Hello.
How are the kids doing in school?
Are you driving?
Elementary school is close.
It's only 10 minutes away.
Oh.
Let's play baseball in the yard.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
You're the best match for kids.
Sorry.
I'll be serious next time.
Here we go.
The yard is too small.
And it's too big.
How about we play in the school yard?
What?
In the school yard?
It's only 10 minutes away.
But...
We should stop.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Oh, that's the school yard.
It's closer than I thought.
Ryo, it's time to grab the rope.
It's not so far.
It's narrow.
What do you mean narrow?
Oh, no.
What is this hill?
Are you OK, Ryo?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
He said I should stop.
That may be 10 minutes,
but it takes an hour to get back.
It takes an hour to get back.
Just you see!
You're a real jerk. You moved to such a terrible place.
That's strange. I paid this month.
What's wrong?
I'm here to collect the tax.
I paid the house tax, but the staff is here again.
I'll ask the staff.
Hello, sir. I'm Kanetori, the manager of this district.
I'm not the boss. But I heard your wife paid.
This is the receipt.
Excuse me.
This is the amount of the next house.
We haven't received it yet.
What? What does that mean?
Let me explain on the map.
This district is made by filling the river. The river is in the area of the prefecture.
This house is just on the border.
This is 52% of our prefecture, and the other 48% is the other prefecture.
Oh, really?
I'll tell you in detail.
This is what it looks like.
This is how it looks like.
The children are completely in my prefecture.
The bedroom is like this.
By the way, is the master sleeping on the right side of the bed? Or is it the left side?
It's the right side.
So the master is in the next prefecture, and the wife is sleeping in my prefecture.
I see.
What's this?
The kitchen, the bathroom, the bathroom, the children's room on the second floor, and half of the bedroom.
Besides, one-third of the current one is my prefecture, and the other two-thirds, half of the bedroom, and the guest room are in the other prefecture.
The phone bill is in the other prefecture, isn't it?
The gas and water bill are in this prefecture.
Chief, what should we do?
We should immediately ask the real estate agency.
What's going on?
What the hell?
We were about to hit it!
I just saw a gorilla and I made a mistake.
I didn't know there was a human population here.
It was a field last year.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Are you okay, Ryo-chan?
We were about to attack the second class.
The real estate agency said this place is in the Kinryoku prefecture.
That's strange.
It's true. It's in the Kinryoku prefecture.
Be careful.
The Kinryoku prefecture is the prefecture next to it, so it's fine if it's on this side.
Hey, John. Come here.
It's dangerous!
Hey, you guys, stop it!
This is Kinryoku!
I thought it was a perfect point.
The population has risen.
Hey, wait a minute!
What a place!
It's the real estate agency's car!
What?
How are you, sir?
It's a wonderful environment, isn't it?
This land is worth 500 yen.
Hey, real estate agency!
Geek!
I saw it somewhere.
What are you talking about?
I'm the head of the Nikoniko real estate agency.
I've never seen you.
I never saw you.
I got it!
You're a...
As expected, you're Hanyu, the real estate agent of the hens!
No, he was pretending.
Hey, Hanyu, you were just lying and making that man buy a house.
Please stop it, you're so rude!
Shut up!
The whole area is Kinryoku!
Didn't I say that?
I didn't say anything like that.
But the contract is over.
I'll pay you later.
-You're complaining... -Shut up!
The hunter fired his gun and we were about to die!
Hey, give me a thousand more sticks to keep the flow going!
That's ridiculous.
Then, sir, this is Hanyu...
No, stop it! I'll give you a thousand more sticks!
I don't need anything else!
That's great, Mr. Terai.
If we can get a thousand more sticks around here, the hunter won't be scared.
Sure.
Wait a minute.
Hey, come here.
I heard you were selling Toho for 10 minutes to elementary school.
That's the intersection of the school.
It's true that it takes 10 minutes to get there, but it takes an hour to get home.
This is a fraud, isn't it?
And you said that the subway would open in two years.
That's also a fraud, isn't it?
Sir, this is...
Don't interfere with business!
I'm not a demon.
And if you sell me a thousand more sticks, I'll let you go.
If you want to buy it, I don't mind buying a thousand or two thousand sticks.
I see. Then I'll buy two thousand sticks for a single stick.
Here's your cash.
That's not...
If you don't want to...
Sir!
All right! I'll sell it!
All right. I'll let you make the rest of the money.
Nakagawa, come here!
What is it, sir?
Nakagawa Island Project.
Stop the Tokyo Bay and do it here.
What?
If you move the Nakagawa Group to this border hill, this countryside can turn into a great city.
Do it!
Even if you say that suddenly...
Rather than building the Tokyo Bay, it's much cheaper to use this 500-yen pot of land.
But...
You suddenly said that. Ryo, you're thinking of something strange again, aren't you?
Don't say that.
I'm...
I'm thinking about the happiness of my colleague's wife.
My happiness?
Nakagawa Group, move here.
Nakagawa Railway will definitely create a new route, so it will be much better for transportation.
Well, that's what I think.
Then the three and a half hours of commuting will be reduced, and there will be a lot of supermarkets and convenience stores.
Children will also be able to go back to elementary school without going through such a dangerous slope.
I see.
Nakagawa, do it!
Even if you say that, I understand.
But I cannot change my plan.
Senpai, please create a simulation to persuade the members of the Nakagawa Group.
Hmm...
Okay, leave it to me!
Ryo has been resting for a long time since then, but what's wrong?
Good morning!
Ryo, what have you been doing for three days without any money?
What?
It's a simulation!
You...
Well, well, I made a great CG, so please take a look.
Everyone, put it on.
What is this?
I put it in the CG and made it possible to see it in virtual reality.
Virtual reality?
It's virtual reality.
You can experience it in real time.
I see.
Anyway, put it on.
Okay, here I go.
Oh, isn't that Kameari Station?
What do you mean?
There's no zero-line platform at Kameari Station.
Nakagawa Railway was able to get on it.
Wow, isn't that the Giniya Motor Car?
It's 600 kilometers per hour, so you can get to the border hill in 5 minutes.
Now, get on!
Oh, that was quick.
The station name has changed.
It's stupid to say the border hill.
We changed it from Beverly Hills to the border hill.
The monorail is connected to the house of the guest, but we're taking the helicopter.
I'm impressed by this virtual reality.
The virtual reality?
That's...
Yeah, it's the building army of the Nakagawa Group.
Oh, it's my house!
Your house is right in front of the monorail station, so it takes 30 minutes to get to Kameari.
You can save up to 3 hours.
That's good, isn't it, Terai-san?
But there's no rice paddies or rice paddies, so the environment is...
What?
You're talking about luxury.
In front of a station in such a great city, the land will naturally rise.
That's true, but...
One grain will cost you 3 million yen.
3 million yen?
Your land is 1,000 grains that you took from Hanyu, so it's 1220 grains, so it's 36.6 million yen.
That's...
Look at that.
Departments, banks, schools, hospitals, etc. are connected to the central highway, so you don't need a car.
What a great city.
Even between each building, you can go freely without getting wet in the rain.
Then let's go to the observatory of the Nagagawa Group main building.
There's a factory, too.
Nagagawa Group has many customers from abroad.
I think the management team will be okay with this.
I want to move, too.
But this looks like you live in the city.
I don't think so.
Don't be so luxurious.
I'm doing this for your convenience.
Ryotsu, what's up with the gang of facilities in the stadium?
That's...
It's all gambling.
After all, we need facilities to survive.
You're making a city of your own choice.
No, it's not that.
I don't like it.
There's an edge zone next to the stadium.
What?
Why do we have a branch?
We thought it would be fun to move here.
Idiot!
What are you thinking?
It's too bad for the environment of children.
I don't like it.
You should go there once in a while.
I'm a wife.
The gambling, the edge zone, and the branch are all cool.
I'll erase them later.
What's that?
What was it?
It's strange that the first floor in the middle of the city is empty.
Hello.
What?
Ryotsu, I brought the land contract.
Please sign and return it.
Land contract?
I bought 2,000 barrels for 1 yen.
Idiot! Don't say that!
Give it to me!
That land is your land.
What are you talking about?
It's terrible, Ryo.
I refuse this selfish transfer plan.
No way!
I put all my money into making this CD.
Shut up!
You are...
Wait, you idiot!
What are you thinking?
Damn it!
I thought it was a good opportunity.
Humans should live a life of their own.
Why are you so frustrated?
You're really angry.
What?
You don't have enough calcium?
Shut up!
You're doing unnecessary work.
I'm getting angry again.
Next time, "Send it with calcium!"
Please watch it.
Please subscribe to my channel.