Come on, let's go!
Next is this turtle!
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
The white clouds
It'll be all right
You know what to do, right?
If you know what to do, just come to me!
I'll be right back!
Hey, turtle!
What are you doing!
Cheer up!
It's Kankichi!
What the hell is going on?
You're imitating a thief like this!
I've already seen that you're a thief, Kankichi!
Hey, there's a deep reason for this!
Deep reason?
Do you know a TV show called "Tetsujin Baka Ichidai"?
Yeah, it's a show where macho men who show off their strength compete to the limit.
I watch it often with my grandma.
And when I applied, I won.
You won!
Oh, that's great!
Maybe Kankichi can win.
Right? Tomorrow is the real show.
But I haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
I can't get any strength.
Even if I asked the chief, no one would lend me a meal.
I can't help it.
Even so...
I'm really sorry!
But if I win tomorrow's TV show, my family will invite me to Hawaii.
Yeah!
If you let me eat sushi, I'll definitely win and take all the Ghibosh family to Hawaii.
I'm talking about you, so why don't you take me with you and make money later?
I won't do that.
I'm always taken care of by everyone here.
I just want you to welcome the New Year in Hawaii.
But I want to go to Hawaii.
Me too.
Mom wants to go too.
Well, if you can go for free.
Don't be fooled by everyone.
I'm a man of the Ryotsuke family.
There must be something behind me.
No, no.
Sometimes you have to believe me.
I can't believe you just by looking at what you do every day.
That's right.
How about making a branch shop for Chokanda Sushi in Hawaii?
What?
Branch shop in Hawaii?
Yeah, I think you'll definitely win sushi here.
I see.
I'm sure you can really win.
Yeah.
As long as I'm hungry, it's easy.
Alright, I got it.
Thank you.
Yes.
Make him eat sushi.
Okay, Mom.
Yay!
I did it!
Let's eat!
You're really full.
You must be really hungry.
I ate a lot of sushi here, but it's still delicious.
It's delicious.
You're gonna win for sure.
Leave it to me.
Hey, last battle, this arm wrestling.
It's going to be serious.
Both have won over 2000 times.
Both have won, and they have great records.
Don't lose!
Just a little more!
The enemies are resilient.
Do your best, Kankichi!
Hey!
Oh! Kanaka is finally down!
The number is 2,009 times!
The winner is Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
Yay!
That's a lot!
He's an idiot, but he has a lot of stamina!
It's all thanks to my sushi!
A new iron idiot has been born!
His name is Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
He's got a Hawaii trip!
Everyone, let's watch!
The first place is Hawaii!
He's a great person!
I'm not saying he's bad, but there are quite a few rich people who are trying to spend New Year overseas.
Huh? That's a producer and staff of an iron idiot.
Yo! What are you doing here?
Oh, Ryo-tsu-san.
What?
Of course, I'm going to Hawaii with all the champions and my family.
Look.
Huh?
W-What?
Wasn't my family the only ones who went to Hawaii?
Oh, come on.
Didn't I tell you that there was a TV show about an iron idiot who was against his family?
What?
I didn't hear that!
I told you at the beginning of the show.
Didn't you hear me properly?
Huh?
I-Is that so?
Anyway, please do your best with the help of your family.
It's a waste.
I can't tell everyone just because I said it.
If I did...
Look!
As I thought, there's a reason behind it.
Yes.
Did you go to Hawaii to compete in the first place in New Year's Eve and make such an iron idiot race for this old man?
You idiot!
I hate you!
I guess it's supposed to be so.
I have to participate in the race all alone.
Hey, Takahashi!
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
I just go.
It's the first time to travel abroad with your family.
It's my first time seeing a fish.
That's right.
But you can take off your belt.
Sorry.
Kanchi, is everything really free?
Of course.
We're going to have an indoor meal from now on.
The main dish is meat, and I'll ask for chicken or beef.
I'll ask for whatever you like.
I prefer fish.
Don't be selfish.
This is what beginners of overseas travel are.
Everyone, please announce your schedule after you arrive in Hawaii.
Oh, no.
Yes, yes.
Pay attention to this.
What is it, Kanchi?
Everyone is a beginner of overseas travel, so I'll explain the rescue equipment.
That's what Mr. Stewardess explained to us earlier.
No, it's a matter of life and death, so it's a matter of life and death.
All right.
I'm explaining right now, so please be quiet.
Yes, sir.
I see.
I can't help but feel I'm in a hurry.
That's right.
Huh?
What?
You can hear music.
What are you doing?
Wow, it's Hawaiian.
Isn't it lovely?
Nice.
I've been able to trick it.
Great.
I can see the sea.
I can see the sea!
The wife and husband are in this room.
Here's the key.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
Grandma and Lemon are in room 703 next door.
Here you are.
Hey!
Hey, what about me?
You will be staying in this room 704 with me.
Why are you with me?
I'm with you!
Wow!
What a beautiful view!
Damn it.
It's the same room as Grandma's.
I don't want to stay in it.
I'm a little busy.
Let's decide the location.
I'm going there now.
I've rented three cell phones.
If you need anything, contact me.
I understand.
See you.
Bye-bye, Kankichi!
I'll be back by dinner.
From now on, it's going to be tough!
Hey, everyone, pay attention!
The first-class passengers will start off on their bikes.
We're leaving by bicycle!
Huh? My family won't come!
Everyone's sick...
Then, is it dangerous?
No, I'll do everything by myself!
Eh? Are you sure?
It's a harsh race where you have to ride a bicycle and a water bike!
It's fine!
But what will you get if you win?
Well then, everyone!
Please do your best to get the prize money of 100 million yen!
Wow!
What? 100 million yen?
In addition, we have prepared a very luxurious prize for the families up to the third place!
Is what you're saying true?
Yes, of course.
100 million yen?
All right! I'll definitely win!
Now, the start of Hawaii, where one iron man is the king!
The third place champion, No. 30 Ryosu Kanki!
Let's hurry and go!
Polly idol!
Well, what's the matter?
Oh, is it Kanki?
I don't know how to use the safety box, though.
Ah?
I can't pay the cash!
Oh, I got it! I'll be right there!
The course is different!
Oh! No. 30 Ryotsu, who is the lead, has left the course for some reason!
It says here, you know!
I don't understand.
I don't know.
You have to put in the number of the secret code.
It doesn't matter how many you put in.
Even if you tell me.
There are phone numbers and date of birth.
What is the number of the store?
It's 8810.
That's all.
That's good.
When you want to open it, press the number.
I got it.
Is it a hotel?
It's a very long way.
Now, the second race.
It's a race.
The second runner's family is touched.
The players who rode the oaf on a bicycle.
They are all very tired.
Oh, my.
Ryoji, who was out of the course while running the top, is back.
He joined the second race.
It's the second time.
I will lead all of you in one go.
What are you doing?
Kanki-Kichi.
The TV paid for.
I want to put it back.
I got it. It'll be quick.
I got the oaf on the bikes.
Pay mode is paid movie.
If I do this, I'll go back to my normal channel.
Can't you see this guy?
Oh, it's an historical drama, isn't it?
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
I've only stayed in a hotel, so I don't know anything about hotels.
Read the explanation.
It's written in Japanese.
I'll be late for 20 minutes.
All right, if this is how it is...
What?
Kankichi, the historical drama in Hawaii is also in Japanese.
Huh?
Kankichi, where did you go?
It costs 100 million yen.
I'll pay you back!
Oh, Ryoichi is the best!
Ryoichi is the best!
He's entering the third race, the marathon!
He's the best without a replacement!
What a strength!
Again? What's going on?
Kankichi, come here.
I found a good store, so I'll decide.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it too early to buy anything?
That's a pretty good property.
Grandma, you don't speak English, do you?
You're the same!
Anyway, don't make a contract yet.
I'm going over there now, so tell me where you want to go.
Huh?
Okay, I got it.
Whoa!
Ryoichi is the best!
He came here and he's down!
Yeah.
It's tough.
He's the only one out of all 30 groups
who's been participating alone.
He's been cycling, swimming, and running.
He's been doing this all by himself.
I guess he's almost exhausted!
Hm?
All right, I'm done charging!
What kind of man is he?
He came back in just 20 seconds!
Huh?
What's going on, Ryoichi?
He suddenly started going backwards!
But, English?
What should I do?
Oh, right.
There's supposed to be a company in Hawaii called Nakagawa Group.
I'm going to ask the employee there.
This contract is good, right?
Yeah, it's a very good property.
I'm glad I found it.
I see.
Grandma, you can leave the rest to the people in Nakagawa.
Sorry for the trouble.
Yeah, that's fine.
Then I'm going.
I'm going.
He's a busy guy coming all the way to Hawaii.
Well, he's giving me a nice job.
So, he's doing a pretty good job.
He's doing a very good job.
All right.
Then, Light, come here.
Light, come here.
Light a hug.
He's good!
How did I get through the secret sciences race of the first day?
The marathon had 75 points,
the swimming gave 100 points in the top,
and the bike gained 0 points as the fastest.
Which makes it the fifth!
Wow, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I'm going to be like this for three days.
Ah, I'm going to die.
Wow, it's delicious.
Sometimes meat dishes are good.
Oh, what's wrong with you, Kankichi?
You love steak, don't you?
You don't have an appetite.
No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I don't want to die if the competition goes on for three days.
I'm going to put in an option from tomorrow.
I need to get more strength.
All right! I'm going to eat!
Wow, Kankichi!
You don't have to eat like that.
Shopping and a cruise to the Western City.
The Hanauma Bay One-Day Course.
Are we going to this today?
If you come to Hawaii, it's an optional tour.
I have to enjoy the tour.
It will cost money, but if I win, I'll be able to do something.
Thank you for waiting.
Look, the shopkeeper is here to pick us up.
Please take care of everyone.
Yes, everyone, please get on the bus.
Can't Kankichi go?
Yeah, I have some business today.
Oh, it's boring.
Have fun!
Hmm, I can't be called out today.
I had better put in an option from the beginning.
Now, let's find out how they can get on a train or a train from Hawaii!
The second day's first activity is sky-diving.
Diving from an area of 1,000 meters above sea level,
how can you get off near the top of that surface?
The center is 100 points.
It's scary.
The flying order is,
Let's start with the top family from yesterday!
Oh, the fifth start.
But I'm good at diving.
I'll get my sense back from yesterday.
Well then, everyone,
let's get this party started!
All right! I'm in good shape!
I'm in good shape!
He's not just a simple transformation.
He's wearing the moon's energy on his back!
Seri's stick is in the dark.
If it's a sky incident, I'll leave it to you.
The master of the moon,
Moon Dekka!
I'm here!
Same goes for Venus Dekka.
Hey!
Why are you guys showing up?
The special detective department is on a holiday in Hawaii
for the New Year's Eve.
The special detective department is on a holiday in Hawaii for the New Year's Eve.
And they're asking the TV department to get in the way of you guys!
What?
You guys don't show up for nothing because you're special, do you?
Moonlight Power!
Reca!
What's that?
Let me explain.
By transforming Moon Dekka into Rosa Ogawa,
you can cause a huge, intense wind to blow.
Oh!
Moon Dekka!
You're so澄!
Oh!
Moon Dekka!
K겠지만!
They're really something!
What?
It's the first time you needed to go on a tour,
but you called us!
What's the matter?
You were fooled by your hunting experience after you shopped?
Okay!
I'll tell you!
Hey! Moonlight!
Please, send me to that direction!
What? You're too cocky to tell me the direction!
Fine, I'll do as you say.
Venus!
Roger!
Oh!
Mars!
I told you the fishing was wrong!
No, no, no.
I can't understand Japanese at all.
I hope Kankichi won't come soon.
Hey!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
K-Kankichi!
Kankichi!
Don't underestimate a Japanese tourist!
I-I'm sorry! I'll be back!
What? You can speak Japanese!
Let me see.
Here, here, here.
See you later!
He's not as good as always.
Why is he a parachute?
He's like 007.
Now, each player will be sent to the goal as follows.
Good job!
But you landed pretty far, so you get 0 points.
Damn it!
What's the next race?
The second race for today is long board racing on the Oaf Island!
Well, I'm good at surfing.
That's my style!
Ready, start!
Fuck!
You're so annoying!
No, no, no.
What?
Can we go back there?
They're just for show.
"Taking her own life"
Now, here comes the first challenge, Life-Saver!
Please save the drowning beauty, and aim for the goal with two people!
"I'm going to save the drowning beauty!"
In short, we just have to save the girl!
Alright, it's your turn! Grab on!
"I'm going to save the drowning beauty!"
Sitting down and paddling is tough!
I'll go on the wave, so when I'm on the wave, grab on my back!
"Okay!"
"I'm going to save the drowning beauty!"
I'll go on the wave, so when I'm on the wave, grab on my back!
There she goes!
Ready, go!
Grab on, now!
"I'm going to save the drowning beauty!"
"Yeah!"
Yippee-ki-ki-ki!
This kind of feels a little extravagant!
"I'm going to save the drowning beauty!"
That was so lovely!
I want to show Kankichi too!
Dear, thank you for your hard work for a long time.
You've been working hard for a long time. Thank you.
No, thank you for giving me such a wonderful trip.
It's another gift for your gratitude.
What is it?
Open it.
Such an expensive thing.
Which one?
It suits you very well.
Dear, thank you for your hard work.
Hey, did you see that pendant just now?
A big ruby with a diamond on it.
A $100,000 is a ridiculous treasure.
My heart is pounding after a long time.
I wonder what kind of treasure it is.
Wait a minute.
Google.
What are you guys?
Don't talk.
You have a long umbrella on your back.
Come with me.
Yay!
I'm the president!
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
Are you
love the sea and protect justice?
Who called you, Poseidon?
I'm going to lock you up in a tank.
If it's an ocean case, let me handle it.
I'm sorry.
The first one is the one who can get the cutout!
Dolphin Dekka!
Are you here to get in the way of the race too?
I'm on a part-time job during my New Year's holiday.
Again?
What? I'm free to get in the way now!
Kankichi, something bad happened!
Something bad happened in the cruiser!
What? I got it! I'll be right there!
Get in!
Dolphin Dekka!
I'm sorry, but can you take care of this girl for me?
I'm counting on you!
Hey, wait a minute, Ryotsu!
Hey...
What?
Yes, I was suddenly shot from behind.
I didn't see her face.
What did Kankichi say?
He said he'd be here soon.
How did he say he'd be here?
Aloha!
We're waiting!
Kankichi!
What has happened to you?
Kankichi!?
Kankichi!
What happened to me!?
Why?
I didn't see you.
I thought I could see you.
Look, I saw you!
I'm saying my name.
That means you're Kankichi.
Kankichi, you're Kankichi!
The Hiroshimaены of the group.
The Hiroshimaens?
Listen, I've been hit.
Kankichi…
I don't think so.
I see. Did the culprit run away?
We were on the deck the whole time, but nothing like that happened.
That means the culprit is still on this ship.
Does that make sense?
Then the culprit must have been caught.
What?
While I was coming, I contacted the coastal guard, so he should be coming soon.
Oh, here he comes!
Hey, here he is!
Hey, this is bad. What should we do?
What? They're not looking at us.
If we hide the pendant somewhere, we'll be able to do it.
I see.
All we have to do is leave the rest to the coastal guard.
Kankichi.
Yes?
I want to pee.
Oh, well, that can't be helped.
Here, here.
Kankichi, bring it for me.
Huh?
This is too much of an excuse to be called into the back room.
Hm.
"Oke."
Ah, wait a minute.
Hey, let me take a look.
Here, here, here!
What are you doing?
Ochiai.
*Sneeze*
Hankichi!
Hey, Raymond. You're still up?
Yeah.
I fell asleep.
Thanks.
No, I have to go back soon.
Hurry up!
Hankichi!
All right.
Oh, yeah!
You did a great job, Dolphin Dagger.
Yeah!
Now, the second game of today.
The longboard is the end of the O.A.F.T.O. half-way race.
The players who have safely rescued the beauty
are now in the goal.
Thank you for your hard work.
But you're in the first place, so you get zero points.
What?
I did it!
I'm in third place.
All right.
I'll be in the top position all day today.
What is the third race?
Now, the last race of today is
a physical strength match!
Animal Onbunmaru-son!
Please carry these cute animals
and complete the goal of O.A.F.T.O.!
Wow!
Ryoichi has carried an elephant!
Just by carrying an elephant,
the elephant will be added 100 points.
Furthermore, if you can reach the top,
you will get 100 points.
A total of 200 points will be added.
I'll be in the top position all at once!
You go first!
Wait, you bastard!
You!
Hey!
You shouldn't be eating that!
You!
What?
You're feeding animals
and making them rampage!
Who's doing this?
You!
You are!
I'm not just a piece of junk!
When an accident occurs on the land,
I can solve everything with a single piece of bread!
I, the King of Bread,
am here today!
I, the King of Bread, am here today!
Are you in the race, too?
I'll give this to the elephant!
What?
Hey, Cube!
See?
Yaw!
Don't let it get away!
Hey!
Don't eat though!
Eh...
Oh?
Hello?
What's up?
Did you find the criminal?
After all, we didn't find him
and were released.
So?
What do you want to?
I thought about taking a photo of Hawaii
You should come with us!
You what?
I don't have to go!
I don't care if I can't do it!
Lemon really wants to go with you.
Or what?
Is there any reason why you can't come here?
No, no, that's not true.
Okay! I'll be there soon!
Oh, damn it!
So I'm going to go out of the course for a bit!
Wait! I won't let you!
If you want to go, you have to compete with me first.
I'm not going to go! I'm going to do a U-turn!
No problem!
Now, let's have a serious match.
What?
I don't have time to play with you!
Let's go!
It's going to be a long ride.
Kankichi, you're really late.
You don't know the photos here, do you?
K-Kankichi!
I'm sorry!
The road is a little...
Wait for me, Konji!
Kankichi, the rides are different every time you come!
This time, it's a fake card!
It's amazing!
I know.
Your face is so pale.
Are you all right?
I see.
Okay, then, I'll take it.
Hey, smile!
Here!
Cheese!
Don't call me!
What time is he going to Hawaii?
I don't know
Hawaii is held in Oahu Island
Family vs. family, an iron man and a fool in Hawaii
The second day's final race, the animal on-board marathon is also the end
Only number 30 Ryozu Kankichi is left
It seems that the arrival is quite late
Will this be dangerous?
It seems to be dangerous
I don't know
What is it?
It's here!
This is a good picture
Camera on standby
Please continue the broadcast
Everyone, please take a look
Number 30 Ryozu Kankichi is back with an elephant
Ryozu Kankichi participated in this race alone without his family's request
Please watch
What an iron man and a fool
He does not let go of the elephant he carries
One step, another step and he is approaching the goal
Ryozu Kankichi received applause and support from the gallery
Now, Kato's goal
Somehow, I got only 100 points for the elephant
Now I'm in Ryozu-san's hotel
It was Kankichi
Kankichi, what happened to you?
It's just a futile
I heard that some residents in the family were sleeping
What table?
I heard that your family members are sleeping in their beds after losing their health.
What? What are you talking about?
Hey, Matoi.
You're awake.
What's this place?
Don't worry. It's a hotel room.
I see.
Kankichi, why didn't you tell me?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Don't be silly.
I heard all the stories from the producer who was a stupid iron man.
Geku...
What about Lemon and Gepard?
They're all going to see a fire dance show.
Then you're the only one who knows the story.
You're such an idiot who works hard alone until you get this far.
Idiots are born stupid.
If you say a word, I'll join you.
No, you're in charge of your own business.
I'm just a little bit more interested.
I have a lot of work to do for my family.
I just wanted you to enjoy your Hawaii trip.
Really, you said something that didn't make sense.
But I've revised it a little bit.
I'll be participating in the race tomorrow.
I can't help it if you get caught.
Actually, I thought I was at my limit by myself.
I'm sorry. Please.
Huh?
What?
Huh?!
Huh??
What?
Gepard, no!
You mischievous girl!
Grandma!
No!
Please help me!
Wait!
Oh, I wonder if I'll be fine if she's that good.
Matoi!
Did something happen to Kankichi?
Hmm? Hmm...
So, if Grandma finds out about the race, it'll be a big deal, right?
I see. So that's what happened. I'm sorry for doubting you.
Ahaha! Don't worry about it at all. But, you really like Kankichi, don't you?
Everyone is looking at the bad side of Kankichi, so they don't know the good side of Kankichi.
That's right. But, this is a secret for everyone.
I see!
Today, we're going to tour the city.
What's up? Matoi, you're not going, either?
Yeah, it's a little windy.
Kankichi, if you do anything strange to Matoi, I'm sorry.
That's why, it's a misunderstanding.
Don't worry. Matoi is stronger than Kankichi.
If something happens, we'll beat him up.
Alright.
Then, it's okay.
That's true.
Hey, put that back!
Then, I'm going.
Hey, have fun.
Grandma, too.
Yeah, sure.
Then, we're going too.
Yeah, leave it to me.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Mahi,!
Hey, get in there, too!
The new Taitai!
I'll give you an opportunity to do a good job, so please be careful while you're relaxing.
Well.
Will you take over the land?
It's okay! I'm good at riding a bike!
The pedal is heavy!
What is it? It hurts!
It's a tire! It's been hit once!
Today is the last day. We have prepared a more harsh trial!
Damn it!
Kankichi! Are you okay to fly so far?
What? I'm ready to crush you like this!
Now, everyone! It's a Kamehameha grand premiere!
The Kamehameha Grand Prix
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
You brat!
But...
This is terrible!
Kankichi is amazing!
He's top at tearing his legs apart!
Okay! I'll reach the goal as I am, and I'll get 100 points for the first race!
The top goal is the Ryotsu Kankichi Team!
Now, both teams have got 100 points!
They've finally come out in the first and second places!
Alright! Next is the 10 km race!
Let's go!
Hey, wait up!
What is it?
I'll let you swim with this for today's performance.
What? Did you give it to Tetsukabuto?
I told you that the final day is prepared for a harsh trial.
Hey, Matoi! Hurry up!
What? I can't swim with this on.
What? Again?
Hello?
Kankichi, I've got a big problem. Lemon has been kidnapped!
What?
It's a relief that you've come all the way here.
Now, miss, shall I give you a stuffed animal?
No!
This one?
Lemon!
What?
Hooray!
Yes, Kanchi, Matoi!
Hey! Speed up!
Yes!
No! If I had such a heavy thing with me...
You don't have time to take it off now!
Now!
What?
Damn it! Take this, Kazuma!
No, wait!
Hey, Kanchi!
I can't catch up!
Gah!
Ah!
I can't do it!
Don't let go!
Okay!
Hey!
They're from the Special Police Department!
Oh, it's Ryozu.
They came to the right place!
Sorry, but I don't have time to push you!
What?
I forgot the time and played too much!
I completely forgot that there was a mission!
Well then, goodbye!
Hey, hey!
Help me!
You can't tell what's going on if you look!
You're an idiot!
Matoi!
Take the bicycle and climb up from there!
What?
Hurry up!
I got it!
What?
Just keep your head on the pedestal and climb up!
No way!
It's okay!
Sorry!
Kankichi!
Hey!
Gah!
Why the bicycle?
If you don't have this, they'll be here!
Kankichi!
Get in!
Yeah!
Now, miss!
There's no one to help you anymore!
Get that stuffed animal over here!
No!
Don't come any closer!
What?
What's wrong?
Kankichi!
Matoi!
No way!
I was supposed to fall down, but...
Don't think you can escape from me!
I can't get out of this narrow tunnel!
Hey!
I need you to hold me tight!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What?
Kankichi!
Raymond help me right now!
Well!
The enemy is hitting us!
It's our turn!
Oh!
The tunnel!
Hey!
Stop the car!
Quiet!
I said stop the car!
Hey!
I'm going to kill you!
You scum! Go home!
Ah! I was on that cruiser yesterday!
What? So you two are the perpetrators of the jewel robbery?
That's right. I hid a pendant inside this kid's stuffed animal.
What? What did you say? You hid a pendant inside this kid's stuffed animal?
And then you took a lemon...
Damn you! You brought in a kid like this!
I will never forgive you!
Kouki!
You idiot!
The sword is one more thing.
Kouki!
Hey, kid!
Lemon!
Give me the stuffed animal!
No! This stuffed animal is the treasure that Yuzu, who went to Kyoto to train, bought for Lemon for the first time with his salary!
Lemon! I'm going to give you the stuffed animal!
No!
No way!
It's no use!
You can't take it!
No way!
I'll take it!
Kouki!
Thanks to wearing this armor, I'm saved!
Lemon, run!
Kouki!
Matoi! Lemon!
Huh?
Damn it!
Uwaaaaaaah!
You bastard!
You always do bad things to Lemon, you bastard!
How about this, chas!
Today,
I'll make you pay for this!
Kankichi!
Lemon!
Kankichi! Lemon!
You were scared, right? You did your best!
I was sure you would help me!
I see!
Alright! Leave the culprit to them,
and get ready!
We're going back to the race!
If we do now, we'll be in time for the last race!
Yeah!
The end!
The winner is the Suzukidan team!
Congratulations!
Damn!
The danger of being in the lead was so strong,
that they ended up in 3rd place!
That was a bit disappointing!
Well, it can't be helped!
There were accidents too!
Kankichi!
You two did a great job!
Everyone, I heard everything!
Thank you so much for helping Lemon!
Even so, he's still a watery guy.
He kept the race a secret!
No, I'm just
going to have everyone I'm taking care of
enjoy my trip to Hawaii!
I'm just going to have everyone I'm taking care of enjoy my trip to Hawaii!
Ryoichi-san, well done!
Oh, Producer!
That was close!
If there was no danger in the middle,
I would have won for sure!
Oh, I lost 100 million yen!
100 million yen?
What is 100 million yen?
The prize money for this race!
If you win, you get 100 million yen!
Kankichi!
You didn't say anything like that!
I didn't say anything like that!
What? You said something cool,
but you actually meant that!
No, no, no!
Everyone, you see,
there should be a luxury prize until third place!
Yes, that's right!
A world tour with the family!
A world tour?
Did you hear that? It's amazing!
Everyone, it's a world tour!
You did it, Kankichi!
That was big!
I did it!
What do you think?
I'll do it when I have the chance!
However, this is free for the next project!
For everyone,
you will have to do
a family-based iron man race
while going around the world!
What?
Are you going to do this race again?
While going around the world?
Yes!
Kankichi!
Are you going to let us do that race?
What?
No, no, that's not what I mean!
We're almost at the end of the Shogatsu!
Damn it!
I hate the iron man race so much!
The End
I'm sorry!
Yes!
Why, why,
why, why,
why is it that
We are Tetsu and Tomo!
So?
Yes.
♪ Even though I'm wearing sandals, I can run fast, why? ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ Ryo always has his arms around me, why? ♪
♪ Even though I'm in a hurry, I'm loved by everyone, why? ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ It doesn't matter, but ♪
♪ Bon Bon Bon Bon ♪
♪ The title of this anime is ♪
♪ So... ♪
♪ So long... ♪
♪ I wonder why ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ I wonder why? ♪
♪ I wonder why? Why? ♪
♪ I wonder why? Why? Why? ♪