Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I looked up at the sunset floating on the river
I kicked the pebble and flew to the end
I wonder if I'm going to the taiko that I jockeyed
I laughed at the fact that it was still a joke
No matter how much I cheer up, it's just for fun
The cityscape that never changes even when I'm moaning is tender
The crow is crying, so the hat is shaking
I'm a yakitori hobari
From the
I don't think anyone will be happy if I show them my hobbies, like weddings and family articles.
I think it's useless to make it because it's just me who's on it.
Thanks to you, I've been getting a lot of return every month.
I've read you guys, and you're young and fresh.
I want you to make a Getsuhika that the writers will be happy to read.
Are we going to make it?
Yes, I hope you can accept it.
Sounds fun. Let's do it.
Okay, I understand.
Please accept it.
It's the first renewal, so I'd like to have a flashy special.
Then why don't you do a special about Nakagawa, the number one handsome man who wants to marry in the book?
That's good.
And the special about Ryo-tsu Kankichi, the number one man who doesn't want to marry for 20 years.
That's good. If you bring those two, everyone will pay attention to them.
Then I'll write Nakagawa-san's article.
Wait a minute. I'll be in charge of Nakagawa-san's article, so you should be in charge of Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
No way!
It can't be helped. Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, let's do it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Yeah!
Why isn't it working?
Don't be disappointed.
I'm gonna make it.
If it's a man's article, you can write it as much as you want.
Then I'll explain the worst part of Ryo-tsu Kankichi thoroughly.
I can't stand this smell.
I thought it was a miserable meal for a week until the payday.
I'll eat a decent meal for the first time in a week.
The sixth day.
I'll eat all you want!
I can't eat!
You're here!
The seventh day.
I'm sorry that I'm late.
On the third day, I was able to announce that it was a she-eating meal.
I got it!
A stolen cat!
Wait!
I got it!
Damn cat!
Give me back my cat!
Ow!
I got it!
You bastard!
Wait!
Damn it!
I killed the last one!
You're the worst!
Come on!
I can't believe you're still here!
Hey,
This is bad!
Look at this!
You're the number one man
Ryo Tsukankichi is so mean!
Who took this photo?
That guy is Ryotsu-san?
Looks like a elephant.
Who are they?
They are new members of this year's spring.
Hey, hey! Don't talk to each other!
Ah, they're here!
They're looking at me like I'm looking at something dirty.
They disappeared in an instant.
Damn! They're the ones who are going to do this!
What's up with you?
Don't be so nosy! You're the one who started this!
It's not me!
Hey!
I'm in charge of this, and you're in charge of Naoko!
Naoko? Damn you!
Hey, Naoko!
Oh, Ryotsu Kankichi.
You put this picture on the wall and made me draw a bow!
What are you so excited about?
You just made me do what I wanted to do.
You're the one who's been doing the worst things all day.
Even so, it's cowardly to hide it!
And it's a violation of privacy!
I'll blow it up!
Stop it! Let go!
It's not me, Senpai.
Chief? Director?
Idiot!
You don't have to yell like that!
I don't care if you yell. What's the matter?
Do you need my explanation?
Well, it's about the violation of privacy!
But that picture!
You knew that I wasn't allowed to do it, so you ate the bow of the park!
Well, I was just worried about the amount I would pay.
Who says "you"?
You hussy!
I'll lick you!
Listen! Don't be so harmony!
Come here!
You've been lecturing me for 3 hours.
Damn it.
This is all Naoko's fault.
If this continues, I'll revenge for her!
Osaki, good job!
Senpai, why do I have to do this?
Don't complain. Let's go!
I'm very excited!
Hey!
And this guy was working at a store that looked so nice.
No way, even if it's a lot, it's not.
No, there's no doubt about it.
Okay, I'll take a decisive picture.
Senpai, even if it's a lot, it's impossible.
This is the only way to get in.
You wait here.
It's definitely impossible.
I'm sorry.
It hasn't started yet.
Well, it's not that.
I saw the flyer for hiring a staff member.
You're kidding, right?
Yes, it's super serious.
This is not a monster house.
Look in the mirror and come out.
No, don't eat.
What?
Thank you.
Let's go, Honda.
What's wrong?
It's a rental video.
I came to return the video I borrowed.
What?
You're in a confusing place.
Hi, John.
Hi, Naoko.
Good evening. How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
You look very close.
I thought you were a man,
but you're dating such a foreigner.
I'm going to a cafe.
Let's go, Honda.
Yes.
A Naba eel entering the station.
Hey, give me that toy.
What?
Welcome.
There it is.
Coffee.
Yes, please.
How would you like your coffee?
With sugar and cream, please.
How many spoonfuls of sugar do you like?
One, please.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Here you are.
How would you like your coffee?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I wonder if it's okay, senpai.
Yes, according to the weekly weather forecast,
we'll keep an eye on you.
Please, one more.
Thank you for waiting.
Delicious.
See you again next week.
Bye.
What's that?
That was a quick answer.
Thank you.
Hey, you.
What?
Well, you and Naoko are...
How about...
Well, um...
Please speak in Japanese.
What? You can speak Japanese?
What's your relationship with Naoko?
I'm a teacher and student of English.
What?
Senpai, what's going on?
I was just having an English lesson.
Oh, you were learning English.
That's surprising.
Damn it, Naoko.
He's got some weakness.
I'll catch you.
Bye, Sensei.
Really?
Ahh, you really quote me.
Are you sure?
Bye, Naoko.
That little punk said you should get泡.
What's surprises, right?
I can do it when I'm serious.
Why don't you wear the shoes when you go out?
Tell me when you're free.
No, I'm free...
If he's a man, he'll be mistaken for a stalker.
I think this one is more suspicious.
Don't talk nonsense. Let's go.
I think he woke up from the sailor suit the other day.
Where are you going?
I think he's going back to the village because his family said it was Yokohama.
Let's stop this coolness.
What are you laughing at?
That's the seat of the elderly.
Young people, stand up. That's healthier.
Yes.
Young people these days don't get on it, do they?
In the ship.
Chieze.
Hayako, cheese.
They are waiting for us.
Senior, don't talk like that because it's gross.
What did you say?
Someone is coming.
What?
What? You were dating that little boy?
He seems to have a serious heart.
What?
You're already breaking up?
What a girl.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Seriously?
What?
Jolly.
I'm counting on you.
Mamoru!
Why are you standing here?
Come on, let's go home.
Let go of me.
Mamoru!
Mamoru has been being possessed by you all this time,
and he's been bothering you.
It has nothing to do with you.
She's a very good woman.
Now,
you two can leave now.
If you don't leave, I'll have to pay you back.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Come here.
I said, let go of me!
Don't be so quiet.
I'll listen to you in a quiet place.
Somehow,
Kumoyuki is getting suspicious.
Yeah.
It's pretty cute when you look at it.
If you don't want to get hurt by that face,
go home now.
Do you two know who I am?
I'm a police officer.
I'm scared of the police,
so I won't be pulled by them.
He's a good guy,
but he's not a good match for me.
This is bad.
Senpai,
let's go help them.
Wait.
Stop it.
Mamoru.
What are you doing to the leader?
I asked you to get rid of him,
but you didn't say anything about violence.
Shut up!
Mamoru.
Are you okay?
What are you doing to your brother?
Brother?
You said he was your brother.
Mamoru,
I've never heard of a police officer's sister.
You're so funny.
I'll beat you up
with my siblings.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
We're just passing girls.
This is disgusting.
Why are you so rude?
If you give violence to your brother,
they won't keep quiet.
Something weird is coming.
Hey,
beat them up.
Yes sir.
This one.
You're strong.
Damn it.
Brother.
Don't look at me.
If you approach more,
I'll beat you.
Nice.
Oops.
Brother.
Relax.
Fuck.
Keep this in mind.
Ryo, Tsukankichi, let's thank him for now.
Eh? How did you know?
Senpai, take it easy.
Oh, no.
By the way, why are you guys here?
That's...
Oh, right, there was a cosplay party nearby.
Right, Hayako?
Y-You're right.
You guys...
You're so...
You have a hobby?
Hey, why are you guys involved with them?
I'm the one who wants to know that.
I was trying to get Mizuki out of that group.
Mizuki?
Kimura Mizuki.
Ah, the one who used to come to our house a lot.
Last year,
Ryo's parents got divorced,
and he became a thug.
I thought he wouldn't come to high school anymore,
so I was hanging out with them.
So I was trying to get him out of the group,
pretending to be a friend.
If that's the case,
why didn't you tell us honestly?
Mom was worried too.
Well, well.
Mamoru-kun, you like that Mizuki kid, right?
I-I'm not like that.
He's a good guy.
I've liked animals and flowers since I was a kid.
Then why didn't you tell him
to quit directly?
I did. But...
Shut up.
You're going to be with that kind of people.
You can't do that.
I don't understand how he feels.
Just leave me alone!
Mizuki!
Mizuki...
That's why I
wanted to understand how he feels.
So you joined the group.
What a good brother.
He's still a kid.
Okay, Mamoru. Can you get well?
A man has to get well
for the sake of his loved ones.
Sometimes, you have to work hard for them.
I'm asking you
if you have the courage.
I do.
Okay. Then leave the rest to me.
Jo-Johnny!
Jim, don't worry.
I'm not here to beat you up again.
Mamoru wants to fight you directly.
What?
Are you stupid?
Mamoru can't beat Johnny.
That's not true. I've tried.
I can't beat him.
You're so stubborn.
I have a condition.
If Mamoru wins,
I want to get rid of him
from your group.
Okay?
That's not a joke. Why would I...
Shut up!
If I win,
I'll run around Yokohama
naked.
Ryotsu...
That's funny. I'll take that challenge.
That's not funny.
What's wrong?
You're already asleep?
Not yet.
You can't do that.
He never fought with anyone.
Hang in there, Naoko.
If you go out here,
everything will be over.
I'll finish you off.
Why? Why would you do such a stupid thing?
I'm doing this
for the sake of our promise.
Promise?
When we were in elementary school.
I'm thinking of becoming an animal doctor
when I grow up.
Mizuki likes animals,
so she'll be able to do it.
Really?
Really.
Thank you, Mamoru.
I'll definitely become one.
I'll cheer for you. It's a promise.
Promise?
To make Mizuki realize
her old dreams.
That's it.
I'm not done yet.
You...
It's not over yet.
What the hell is this?
This is really bad.
It's fine. You win.
Mizuki!
You have freedom.
Do whatever you want.
Let's go.
Mamoru!
Mamoru, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
Ryozu.
What?
I...
You won.
You're a man among men.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be so harsh,
but you can't be so harsh on me.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I've already checked you out. You're a pretty good sister.
I don't want to.
Senpai!
Senpai, I'm in trouble!
What's wrong?
Look at this.
What is this?
Nana-chan will look at you with a strange look. What are you doing?
Naoko!
What is this, senpai?
Naoko! What is this?
Here's the camera. You must have forgotten it in Yokohama.
Let's go, Komachi.
Yeah.
See you.
Hey, wait!
Damn it! Remember this! I'll definitely take a picture of you in a embarrassing way!
I'm a girl who's called by someone.
You're a crazy girl!
You're a crazy girl~!
I'm gonna take this.
Well, that's the way it is.
Well, that's how it is.
This is a miracle!
Teruha~!
Kuroutsuka!
I don't want you to go!
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
Politicians with a big face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
You can meet everyone
There's a camera over there
There's a camera for sure
Come on, everyone, to our town
There's a camera over there
There's a camera for sure
Come on, everyone, to our town
Thank you!