Legend ofougou
When you watch TV, turn on the light in your room, and try running away!
Come to me, you without money!
Even if I'm not with you I'm worried
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
It'll be alright somehow
If you're jobless, come to my place
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red clouds
It'll be alright somehow
You got it, right?
You got it, you got it?
If you got it, then shut up and follow me!
Honda Shock!
Yves' Marriage
I did it! I'm so happy!
I'll treat you to anything you want, Honda!
You should pay back your debt sometimes!
Don't be so hard on me!
Oh, stop!
I'll buy you something, Nakagawa!
Hmm, a candy store...
How nostalgic!
I'll buy you some sweets and candy!
Oh, there's strawberry candy, too!
Wow, I remember my childhood!
I used to take Yves to the candy store in my neighborhood!
Oh, dear...
Hehehe...
Hmph, hmph...
He was really shy as a kid, you know
Yeah, that's why when I wasn't around, I didn't go out shopping
It still is, though
Hmph, hmph...
Oh, it's baby color castella!
This is Yves' favorite Kansas candy!
Oh, come on, let's go buy it
Huh, go buy it? No way...
"I don't know."
"I think Eve lives in a university dormitory in Takao.
But I don't know how long it will take her to come back."
"It's okay. She'll be back home in a few days."
"No, that's not the problem."
"She probably can't make friends and is lonely."
"That's..."
"Ahh!"
"Brother..."
"You brought this to me on purpose?"
"Yeah, it's Eve's favorite, right?"
"Thank you."
"Then I'll go get something to drink."
"It's okay, it's okay."
"Because you bought juice with the vending machine before."
"I was surprised and started crying."
"You bought it for me."
"I'll buy it for you."
"Hey, hey."
"Are there any girls who can't buy juice with the vending machine these days?"
"Here you go."
"Thank you."
"There's something weird here."
"I wonder if it's..."
"My brother bought this for me."
"Geez, girls are always so unlikable."
"I think he's worried about me."
"But..."
"Hmm?"
"Eve!"
"What?"
"Wanna play tennis with me?"
"Sorry, but my brother's coming right now."
"Okay, see you later."
"See you later."
"You've changed."
"You couldn't even talk to me before."
"And you didn't even make a loud voice like you do now."
"That's right."
"So you started living in the dormitory after leaving the house?"
"Maybe."
"But..."
"I bought it for you."
"Right."
"Eve, you've always liked orange juice, haven't you?"
"Thank you."
"Have this. This is tea for you."
"Eve looks much older now."
"He must be kidding."
"He's still a little kid."
"Is that so?"
"I'm telling you."
"No, I'm not."
*phone ringing*
Ryo-chan, it's a phone call from a young lady.
From me?
I'll call you back.
Hello, this is Ryo-tsu.
Oh, it's Eve-chan.
I'm sorry I suddenly called you the other day.
By the way, what's wrong?
You suddenly called me.
Huh? Do you have something to tell me?
*phone ringing*
I'm sorry!
I'm late for class.
Oh, it's fine. You're free.
It's really far when you're on the train.
My brother's motorcycle
can catch me up in no time.
What the hell is your brother's secret story about Honda?
There's someone I want to meet.
Huh?
*phone ringing*
Kawasaki-san!
Eve-chan.
I'm Ryo-tsu, your brother's friend.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kawasaki.
Nice to meet you.
Is this the person you want to introduce?
Yes, he's Kawasaki, the head of the second-rate club.
And he's my precious person.
Your precious person...
Huh?
You two are dating?
Yes.
Since half a year ago,
I've been surprised when I heard about Honda.
Really?
So you introduced me first.
Yes.
We're going to get married.
What?
*phone ringing*
I was very familiar with people.
So I couldn't make friends with Ryo even when I moved to Ryo.
*phone ringing*
I couldn't get along with others.
So even after the lecture,
I couldn't go back to Ryo.
But I still think this person is her precious person.
*phone ringing*
I think she is.
No, she's my precious person.
*phone ringing*
We are friends.
We'll always be friends.
*phone ringing*
So that's why you're not interested in me anymore.
But you're both students, right?
No matter how much you do, you get married early.
We're serious.
I asked your parents for an interview.
What?
I've already made a reservation for the wedding.
Are you already talking about that?
Why didn't you let Honda know sooner?
I tried to talk to them many times, but...
Eva!
I bought your favorite Imagawa-yaki for you.
Let's eat it together.
Eva, you like this ice cream, don't you?
Eva!
Looking at your brother's face, it's not very good.
For my brother, she is still a little child.
What a pain.
Father.
Huh?
Hello.
Oh, you're here.
Kawasaki.
What?
Ryo-san is with you?
Is it the engine?
Yeah.
I heard you ride it stupidly.
What?
You're pretty close.
Kawasaki-san, I bought a motorcycle at home.
What?
Does that mean you passed the hard motorcycle test?
Hey, hey, hey, come here.
What?
Ryo-san, what's going on?
What happened?
It's not like you are the one who started it.
you also like your wife, didn't you?
Yes, about it...
Don't worry.
I know it's true.
You also know Michael.
He is the person who invented this game, and he also invented the biome.
Wow, he is smart.
we will open it.
Okay.
Uplift.
What?
Hey, hey, Kawasaki-san!
How's it going, Monkey?
You're happy to have a new brother, right?
Shut up! It doesn't matter!
Actually, I...
I wanted a tough brother like this!
So I'm really happy, really happy!
You're so popular...
Mom really likes you too...
Then the problem is only Honda, huh?
Yes...
Alright! I'll try to talk to him!
I'll see! Leave it to me!
Honda-kun!
Don't scare me, Yosenpai...
I'm going on a patrol from now on...
I know! Well, listen to me...
It's already June...
If you say June in English, it's June...
If you say June, it's June bride...
The wedding bells are ringing everywhere...
The wedding will be held...
Honda, your little sister Eve is also going to get married someday, huh?
What?
Ah! Hey!
Hey, Honda! Don't lose your temper!
Eve is getting married?
Hey, wake up!
That was a joke!
Eve won't get married!
You're right...
Eve is still a kid!
Wedding...
I...
Ah, it's still a long way to go.
Huh? It looks like a boxer just knocked out.
I'll go first!
It's a reaction beyond imagination.
He needs to make a thorough plan.
Eve...
From now on, we'll have a strategy meeting for the marriage announcement strategy against Hayato Honda.
But, Senpai...
What?
It's not good to link the word "marriage" and "Eve," is it?
I don't think I can avoid shock no matter how I tell you.
But if you tell him straight, his heart may stop.
That's why I thought about it.
It's the Honda Kawasaki Friendship Strategy.
Eve will be a friend with Honda before introducing Kawasaki.
For example, when Honda's bike is in trouble while patrolling, Kawasaki will pass by.
What's wrong?
It seems to be broken.
Please let me help you.
Thank you.
First, you become a friend.
Then, you become friends with Honda.
And a few days later, Honda passes by where Kawasaki's bike is broken.
Hey, you're the one from before, aren't you?
This time, it's my turn to help you.
Haha, thank you.
After such a fateful encounter, the two became close.
Love was born someday.
Happily, they became friends.
What?
What will you do if you marry Honda and Kawasaki?
What are you thinking, senpai?
Huh? That's strange.
Anyway, after a fateful encounter, the two become friends.
Yes, it's Otohime.
Otohime will join them and go on a touring together.
Honda says, "I'm glad to have a wonderful girlfriend."
"It'll be good if you have a girl behind you for the next time we go on a touring."
"Is there anyone good?"
No, but there won't be any female acquaintance with Honda.
So Otohime says, "What about bringing Eve?"
Honda may not like it, but somehow Otohime will persuade her.
Finally, Eve will come out.
Yes.
This is how Eve will join the tour.
At first, Honda will worry about her.
But, after many, many times,
Kawasaki and Eve feel it's natural for them to be together.
And they see the love and tell each other that they are dating.
You're not talking about marriage yet, right?
Eve is still a child for him.
Eve must tell him that he has grown up.
How long will it take to get married?
About 10 years.
10 years? Is it that long?
It takes too long no matter how long it takes.
It can't be helped. Honda's nerves are that weak.
Is something wrong with my nerves?
Honda!
What were you talking about?
Nothing.
You were saying my name just now, right?
It's my fault.
You're suspicious.
It's really nothing.
Don't be so grumpy and tell me.
I told you it's nothing.
I don't know how to tell you about Eve's marriage.
I don't know how to tell you about her marriage.
Honda, hang in there!
Excuse me.
Hello.
Oh, no. It's Eve and the others.
I wonder if they're here.
Eve, Kawasaki, what's up today?
Actually, I'm talking about getting married to Eve.
I have to ask Mr. Ryotsu to...
Honda is here. I'll talk to you later.
But...
If you know that you're Eve's fiancee, it'll be a big deal.
Eve's fiancee.
Brother.
Honda, hang in there.
No, Honda. Eve wants to eat konnyaku.
Please, brother.
Please accept my marriage with Eve.
Don't make me even more excited.
Brother.
Eve...
is...
is... is... is...
is... is...
Demonic voice "Yibiru"
Demonic phone call
Our business never stops
It's me
That voice?
I understand, I will call for you now
Demonic phone call
I haven't seen him since morning .
Here he is.
Welcome back !
I thought he might get here some day.
We'll have to get you ready!
The special suit for Mr. Honda ...
is also prepared properly.
Bantou Togo Alliance is back!
Let's go!
We've been chased!
We're in the middle of a program, but I'll tell you the news that just came in.
Right now, a bunch of rioters have suddenly appeared in the entire area of the city,
and they seem to be doing rioting.
The police chief is considering a very careful measure.
Hey, no way!
The sudden appearance of this rioting group is a result of the revival of a person
called a legend among the rioting gang members who are running a battle
when they gather to talk about their relatives.
Big brother!
It's become something ridiculous!
Hey, you!
That's a real one!
What the hell did you do?
I didn't do anything!
This is the kind of thing you do!
There's no way you're involved in this kind of thing!
You're making such a big deal out of it!
Wait a minute!
It's not Mr. Ryozu's fault!
It's me!
You're...
I see, so that's it.
That's why you said it wasn't me!
I'm the one who brought my daughter to life.
I understand how you feel.
However, you shouldn't act like this!
You have to stop this as soon as possible!
It's my responsibility to do this!
I'll stop it no matter what!
Mr. Kawasaki!
Wait up!
You can't involve a person who has nothing to do with this!
He's my brother!
He has nothing to do with this!
But...
Mr. Kawasaki...
Nakagawa!
Get the helicopter!
We'll follow him!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Honda!
Y-You're...
Kawasaki, the fiancé of Ms. Eve!
I-I don't know!
I don't know any fiancé!
Mr. Honda!
You're late, you guys!
W-Wait!
You're too fast!
I love Eve from the bottom of my heart!
I want her to accept marriage!
Eve is still a child!
She can't marry!
Mr. Honda!
Listen to me!
I won't listen to you!
Can you see me, Mr. Honda?!
W-Well...
That's...
Oh, thank you!
I'm going to make this wedding ring!
I'll be the one protecting her from now on!
No!
I wonder what they're trying to do...
Brother...
Mr. Kawasaki...
Denomai
Only the two of us can do it.
You're the first one to follow me up here.
As expected from my little brother.
Mr. Honda.
I'm going to see Asahi today.
Please take care of Eve.
Yes, big brother.
Mr. Kawasaki, big brother.
Eve.
This is a happy occasion.
Yes.
Hey, maids.
You look good.
Eve, show me your wedding ring.
Yes.
Wow, it's cute.
By the way, I was wondering.
Do you know Eve's personality?
Yes, when she rides an elephant, her personality changes.
It's like a new person.
I heard about it a long time ago.
I see.
I hope you know.
I didn't know such a wedding would be held in Japan.
The motto of the wedding is to respond to all needs of the guests.
Wait, I'm running away.
Now, Professor Otsuka, who is the father-in-law's wife, will give you a toast.
Hmm...
It's hot.
Damn it, this is bad!
Really, what's wrong with this?
Asahi is Eve Kawasaki!
I'm going to have a nice chat with you.
This is close!
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- - - - Eve
-chan!
Big brother! I
'm going to be happy! You're going to
be happy, Eve! Of course!
- - - - - - - - - - - - - -
Yeah, it's better than seeing it again
Na na na na na, na na na na na, na na na na
What is this old-fashioned pro-wrestling?
Do you think you can get money with this?
What? You think you can crush it thanks to me?
Alright, I'll make you the best pro-wrestling organization in Japan that I can get money from!
Next time on "Mine only! Katsushika Pro-Wrestling"
Thanks for watching!