"He's not here..."
I have 900 yen left this month.
The crab is popular, so I can't take it out.
Ryo-chan!
But I can't throw away the 7-padded koi.
As a 3-pack, I can be more at ease with the single-handed method.
But...
Ryo-chan!
Ehhh...
What are you doing?
I'm not suddenly.
I've been calling you a few times.
I understand. What's the matter?
What's the matter?
I have a lot of things to do.
Don't let me waste your time.
Yes, yes.
I'm a scary woman when I turn my enemy.
Hello, Ryo-chan.
Again?
Where do you want me to sell land?
Are you looking down on me?
You can't sell anything you don't have, right?
What?
Don't sell anything else.
Thank you very much.
Is it a real estate again?
I think it was yesterday.
I'll enter this month.
It's been a day since I entered the house.
Why are you coming to me?
Isn't it your house in Asakusa?
You can't sell there.
Do you have any other intentions?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Speaking of another land...
I see.
That's it for today.
See you!
Was there an intention?
Yes.
When watching TV, make your room bright.
Stealthily and also you.
Good!
Keep step in.
You do not have to be serious about it.
I mean it.
I don't need to be scary.
Now,
Follow me!
Then,
Yes.
You see?
To buy a new house,
I wonder if I'll be able to do it somehow
I know, I know, I know
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
Follow me!
Hyoutanから10億円
Hurry, Gramateng!
We have to save Matsusako!
Dad, why don't you live?
What are you doing?
I'm going to die!
You're just working from home!
Shut up! What do you want?
My old man who passed away last year
Huh? Tsukuda Island's father?
He's still alive, isn't he?
It's his brother
Oh, you mean Uncle Minokichi
That old man didn't have any land?
He had a lot of land in the past
This used to be Uncle Minokichi's house
But he loved drinking and gambling
He sold his land and everyone else disappeared
That land was left somewhere
What?
And for some reason the real estate company thinks I'm the owner of that land
If we do well, that land might sell for tens of millions
What? Tens of millions?
Uncle Minokichi's luggage is here
I think Yone cleaned it up after the funeral
Mom!
Wait!
Dad, that old man was single all his life
Yeah
If his parents or relatives find out, it'll be a big deal
Dad and I will take care of this
Then we'll be able to split the land
You haven't changed at all since you were a kid
You're against it?
No
Okay
This is the phone I used to use when I was in elementary school
Don't take anything that's boring
I'll take anything that's old
It's an album
Dad was young back then
Of course
It was hard for him to be popular and his mother to be jealous
I can say anything about the past
If you think it's a lie, ask your mom
Come on
Forget it and find out
Where's my land?
Yeah
You guys
Ouch
What have you been doing?
Are you looking for something?
Ouch
We're looking for old clothes
Right?
That's right
The old clothes are cheaper now
Clothes?
It doesn't matter
You can put them back when you're done
-Give it to me. -Okay.
What's with the "what the hell" thing?
If you don't hurry, I'll find out.
I know.
-I found it! -Really?
It's the box that Minokichi-ojisan was taking care of.
Yeah, there's no mistake. The right to use it must be in here.
That's the right to use it.
What's this?
It's Harasetsuko's bromide.
Bromide?
Everything else looks like a movie actress.
It can't be helped. It's a Miha old man.
Huh?
The bottom is filled with love from a woman.
As expected of the playboy, Doraku-ojisan.
A broken watch, a small watch...
It's all useless, but he's taking good care of it.
What's this? A communication book?
It's all soldiers.
Idiot. It's the family.
It's a big book.
Anyway, let's look for the bottom again.
This is...
Land...
Law...
What?
No.
Dad, it's the Land Law.
Really?
Where is the land?
Where?
Kasumi-cho...
That's Azabu.
What?
It's the first land.
It's a big hit, Dad.
Dad, you're right.
Mino-kichi-ojisan is great.
Did you find the
There is also.
It has a house.
No.
The reason I found it is because it tried to me.
I durable enough to be a dad.
No.
Archers don't just bitterly fight to win this battle.
I'm sorry, but I'm not good enough to you.
And in the end, only the middle remained.
Yes.
So, you're saying that Minokichi-jisan sold the land and built a castle?
Well, a small land like that won't cost much.
However, the ten pots are an important point.
This is a project that our first-class construction group is working on.
It's the completion of the Big Hills Mansion.
Huh?
It's crumbling here.
Yes.
If we don't get the land of Lord Ryotsu,
we'll have to make it this way.
I see.
Then, even if we buy ten pots, we might be able to buy them at a higher price.
If we buy this place from another company,
we'll be in trouble.
The president wants to settle this in one fell swoop.
That's right.
Maybe it'll sell for about 50 million yen.
So, the amount we're going to show you is...
The amount is...
We're putting a lot of effort into the Big Hills project.
The amount the president has decided is...
Hmm. How much is it?
3.3 square meters equals 100 million yen.
In short, it's 100 million yen!
What's 100 million yen?
100 million yen!
Please sell the five pots.
I'll sell them! I decided in 0.7 seconds!
Well, I'm sorry I'm late.
Father!
I've been waiting.
Father, please be happy!
That land sold for 100 million yen!
What? Really?
No, it's 100 million...
You just think about real estate,
and don't talk about your family.
Otherwise, you'll change your mind in 0.4 seconds.
Y-Yes.
100 million yen is amazing.
It's not a dream, Kankichi.
Before my father came, I negotiated and raised the price.
I'm glad.
This is the contract.
Please sell them here and here.
Oh, yes.
Wait a minute, father.
I'll check the documents first.
Yeah.
Okay, that's good.
Well, father, sell them here.
It's coming.
And here, too.
Good.
All right, it's settled, right?
Yeah.
Well, well.
Then, please cut 100 million yen into small pieces and bring it to me.
Then I will...
I'll give it to my father.
So don't make any mistakes.
Y-Yes, I know.
All right, then let's go, father.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good, that's good.
Well, I'm a scary man when I turn into an enemy.
Y-Yes.
Thank you very much.
That's good, father.
Yeah, it's true.
He's a really scary man.
He's going to take 900 million yen.
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
Why are you grinning so much?
Oh, me?
Did something good happen to you?
Well, not really.
I've earned 900 million yen.
That says something about them.
The problem is how much money they use.
In this era of ultra-low-minimum wages,
it's not easy to give credit to the bank.
It's a good thing to make everyone happy.
I want to do something big like this.
For example...
This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this!
I'm going to buy everything in this store!
I did it!
No!
It's small!
It's not big at all!
Alright, I'll use it more!
Today is the day of the big day!
All mention cards have been collected.
Hahaha!
I'm going to buy everything to make all the pachinko bags empty!
I'm going to buy them all!
Success!
This will be a good use of about 900 million yen!
I don't have good ways of using money to make you like me, your old friend!
I'm going to go through the moon tonight!
Alright!
Alright, I'll put all the money in the red 99!
Thank you!
Now, how is it?
Red 99!
Yes!
No, black 100!
No, I can't waste it.
I'm glad I thought about it.
I can't even do it myself.
I'm back!
Good work!
No problem.
I'll think of a more reliable way to use it.
The British famous horse, the Dian, is at the auction.
British market?
As expected of the real thing of Salabread.
He has a good face.
Dian? That horse?
Do you know him?
My British friend had an unmatched horse.
He said he wanted a Dian at the next auction.
I see.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that.
But I'm glad I have money.
Because I can buy a horse.
I have money, too.
That's right.
I'll be a horse owner.
Salabread will earn a lot.
That Dian is the descendant of Richard, the master of the Derby.
So, he will make 2 million pounds.
How much is 2 million pounds in Japanese yen?
About 400 million.
If the enemy has 400 million, I can win.
That's right.
Then, 200 million is required.
It can be spent talking with 2 million.
1 million is a lot.
In other words, it's still a lot.
You have a great idea, right?
A good idea.
No way.
Was opened?
Yes.
I directed a voodoo.
We've appeared.
I will show you about this.
The End
I'm fine with this, so use this one billion for your own sake!
You gave me all the money so that Kankichi could be a parent and a child.
I'm very grateful for your blessing, and I'll use this one billion.
What do you mean by one billion?
Don't be surprised!
You've been acting strange since yesterday.
You were grinning and grumbling.
I didn't say anything.
I wouldn't ask you if you didn't want to.
I know. You're going through a lot of trouble, Yone.
Alright.
Hey, Mom.
What?
Do you have anything you want?
A ring or a handbag, anything is fine, so tell me.
I want something.
Yeah, something you want.
Oh, I know. I want a boss who works.
Really?
What is it?
What a good person.
Are you going out?
Yeah, he's not a worker.
Come play with me for a bit.
Oh, I see.
If I use it now, it'll be the money of a homeless man.
I'll share it with you around Ginza.
I'm sorry.
I finally got a chance.
You're awesome, Yoshi.
The best friend.
I love you like my best friend.
You think you're good?
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
I'm just looking forward to it.
You will enjoy eating this hotift, aren't you?
You're welcome.
If you return to Japan, we'll get the code back for you.
You're so funny.
Oh, here they are!
Mr. Nio, say something!
How do you feel about being the world's best member?
Please, say something!
Even as a local civil servant, I've worked dozens of times as much as people.
I've been to the UK to make a long-term dream of becoming a bar owner with the 900 million yen I've saved up.
But there's nothing bad about it.
Is there really nothing bad about it?
Huh, old man?
You're a 900 million-
I don't want to hear that. You're misunderstanding me.
What do you mean? Explain it to me!
No, old man. The land was sold for 100 million yen.
But what happens when you give 100 million yen to an old man who only has 100 million yen?
If he's working hard, it's the same as you.
I thought about how to use the money in front of the Buddhist temple.
I thought about buying a handbag for my mother.
But I ran out of the house.
I didn't have the courage to share it in Ginza.
After all, I was always drinking cold sake in the bar.
You were watching?
So for my father's sake, I took all the money and operated a dream-like asset management.
I'll win the big case for my father.
After all, it's a battle of truth.
It's a battle of truth.
I'm going to get 100 billion yen in prize money.
100 billion yen?
Not only the prize money.
The amount of the commercial, the movie, the CD, the DVD, the DDT.
That much?
Yes, it's a hundred million yen.
That's great.
I'm sure that Nino-Kichi will be impressed with my father's enthusiasm.
Uncle Nino-Kichi.
Well done, Genji.
You're a man who looks up when you buy a horse.
That's why I'm a good brother.
Uncle Nino-Kichi.
Thank you.
As expected of my child, you're big, Kankichi.
You have good muscles.
As you can see, it's a selfish and luxurious horse.
From now on, you will need the money to maintain it.
Can I borrow 100 million yen from my father?
Of course.
Use it without worrying.
Thank you.
Let's bloom a flower together, father.
Okay.
Ryo-chan is the owner.
I can't believe I'm the owner.
Charles lost the auction, but he was very disappointed.
I wonder if that horse is good for Ryo-san.
What?
You don't like it unless it's a hotel?
A luxury four-star hotel that can enjoy the night view of Tokyo.
A one-night suite room for 3 million yen.
I only eat food from the UK.
After all, the horse of memory is different, Kankichi.
Don't mess with me.
Kankichi, stop it.
Let go of me.
You haven't repented yet.
I'll make you a hot pot and eat you.
I said stop it.
This horse will pay you millions of yen.
Be patient.
I can't use the remaining 100 million yen.
I have to make the diamond race as soon as possible.
If you don't let me do it, I'll be in trouble.
Wait for the course at full speed.
Yes.
It's a test, Diane.
If you can't do it, you'll be in trouble.
Do you think you're kidding?
I'm serious.
He's running.
Are you looking down on me?
But he's giving you a good time.
What?
He's not slowing down at all.
He's back.
It's a great speed.
It's a new record.
What?
I did it, Kankichi.
However...
Well done, Diane.
It's a feast.
Where in the world is there a horse that can run on his hind legs?
What?
Kankichi!
That bastard.
The horse racing club in England let him go.
I knew it.
President, I can't ride that horse.
Hey, the race is coming soon.
Someone please hit someone else.
You'll ride it, Kankichi.
Take responsibility for buying such a useless horse for 900 million yen.
I got it.
How was it?
How do you feel about participating in the race yourself?
It's an honor to be able to fight with Aiba, right, Diane?
You bastard.
Well, it's finally the start of today's main race.
And the last one who didn't get in the gate is...
Kankichi, you're going to be in trouble.
Listen, Diane.
If you lose, the food is domestic and it's a waste of vegetables.
What?
The race is starting at the corner.
No, it's a little late.
Oh, Diane is coming.
What are you doing, idiot?
Oh, no.
Diane is going to be in trouble.
Oh, wait a minute.
Senpai.
Ryo-chan, do your best.
The late Diane is still in the lead.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It's a good start.
Kankichi went from the first corner to the first corner.
Diane went up to the 5th place at once.
Good luck.
The lead is Tan-chan.
Next is the SDG, Kamiya, and Diane.
Diane is in the 4th place.
She's going straight through the 4th corner.
Diane is in the 3rd place.
She's going to win.
The 3rd place is Kakeyama.
It was the top.
And Diane was at the top.
Go, Diane.
Go.
What?
Let's go.
Diana suddenly changed her starting position.
All right.
It was the timing that made her break out.
I'm going to go with that any way.
Yay.
That was awesome.
That was fantastic.
Ryo-chan is good.
Ryo-chan.
Are you okay?
You little bastard.
It's not my fault.
That guy...
Charles from back then!
Charles, long time no see!
Oh, Mr. Nakagawa.
So this is the friend who was after Diane?
Yes. Charles was unable to give up Diane, and he came all the way to Japan.
Diane is my horse! I've given him a billion!
I'm going to make millions from now on!
Kankichi, if you don't ride it, you'll lose it.
Sell it!
Yes, yes. Charles says he wants to buy Diane.
I'll sell it if I can make a billion!
Don't laugh! I'm serious!
Kankichi, you should pay the trouble before Ms. Hachida changes her mind.
How about a billion yen?
Oh, no!
Then I'll give you 90 million.
You can't lose any more than this.
8,500 million!
Then I'll give you 80 million!
Damn it, he's looking at other people's feet.
It's a plate of bread. It's a famous dish. Why is it 10,000 yen?
It's because you're not a fool.
Don't keep complaining about your father not doing anything.
It's because you're a horse!
You've made a billion yen!
What?
Why are you two doing this?
Mom, you...
You're about Minokichi's land...
I'm sure he's impressed by the shadow of the grass.
Make a thousand yen with this money.
You idiot.
Hehehe.
Ah, a piece from Hyotan.
A billion yen from Tanabota is a billion yen.
If you say so.
Both Kankichi and I are pawns of the coin again now.
Yeah.
Well, all you need to do is pay the special fee.
Right, Dad?
Yeah, that's right.
You idiot!
Hehehehe...
It was a rainy afternoon, and someone was calling me
I looked back and walked
"Mom, please help me!"
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked the red and black tile
I walked the red and black tile
Everyone was a child at one time, but they all forget
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Look at that corner
Everyone is looking at the blue aunt above their eyes
I can see everyone
Let's go
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Come to our town
Thank you
How about this? This is the helicopter I made
It's called "Shouldercopter"
Even if this is a traffic jam, it will definitely be a big hit
I'm a genius
Let's go
Next episode, "Fly, Shouldercopter"
Thank you for watching