Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats on the inside ♪
♪ I picked up a pebble ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ on the deck of a bike ♪
♪ I laughed like I was on top of a catacomb ♪
♪ Wherever at any time, it's warm ♪
♪ We've been here many times ♪
♪ A ниどくまで ♪
♪ it's kind of you ♪
♪ in any case ♪
♪ When the ferns start to cry ♪
♪ give me another pebble ♪
♪ Even grandpa and grandma ♪
♪ also have that kind of mood ♪
♪ The pond above ♪
♪ has milky water ♪
♪ From tomorrow onward, to the
♩ ♪ From tomorrow onward, to the
We're getting paid half of our salary!
If you're angry, then we won't do anything!
But this time, we don't need to feel that bad.
What?!
The 35th Ryoutsu Kankichi Bonus Education War strategy meeting is about to begin.
Mr. Plumber, this time we don't need to feel bad. What do you mean?
We decided to take a strategy that will definitely recover our debt without wasting our time.
Oh!
What strategy is it?
Teacher, please come in.
Teacher!
I'm here.
T-this person is...
Mr. Plumber Mr. Muu.
He's a professional debt collector.
A professional debt collector?
Your debt recovery rate so far is 10%.
You've never failed.
And the amount of debt you've recovered is not that much.
But even if you're a professional, you can't catch Mr. Ryou alone.
That's right.
Not alone. I have a few excellent subordinates.
Hehehe.
What?
Leave this year's bonus education war to us.
Bonus Education War 8!
I'm back. I went on patrol.
How was the shopping street?
Is there any place to rest?
Plumber, electricity vendor, fish shop, sugar plumber.
Everyone it's open all the time.
UKASHI Yesterday when I was patrolling, there was no shop closed.
What's wrong with that?
Every year around this time, the shop is preparing a bonus.
This is when to prepare for my bonus!
Tap, tap, tap
The
Now that you mention it, it seems so.
But yet, this year there hasn't been any movement at all.
Now then, have you given up on repaying our debt?
Of course not!
Huh?
Ah! You were there!
We talked about it and decided not to do anything special this year.
It's stupid to just chase after Ryo-san and ruin his precious day at the end of the year.
That's why I didn't give up on collecting the debt.
I'll come to Saesoku while I'm delivering.
Pay me well!
Really, you're not going to do the bonus delivery this year?
Yeah.
We...
Yay! Bonus!
I had a lot of things this year, too.
What would I do if I didn't get a bonus?
That's good, Senpai.
All right, I'll immediately lower everything at the bank...
What's wrong, Senpai?
Usually, people from the shopping street should come up with something.
You said you wouldn't do the bonus delivery this year.
That's right, Senpai.
No, but it's about them.
Maybe they're planning something.
Are you crazy? You're suspicious.
Thanks for your thought, Usagi.
I'm sure it'll work out.
...Did you say you were suspicious of the bonus delivery this year?
...What do you mean?
Oh?
Well, as you can tell, I haven't been buying anything lately.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much!
You don't have to watch our movements, Ryo-san.
Yay! Now I can use the bonus without hesitation!
I wonder if it's okay to give them a little debt.
I don't know!
I'm so happy!
I didn't know how long I had to wait for this day.
I'm so glad I came to the police station.
What is this feeling?
I have a terrible feeling.
I didn't expect to get a debt.
It's just a thought.
Let's begin.
Uncle! Uncle!
What?
Give me back my money.
Why do I have to give you back my money?
The shopkeeper asked me to get a debt from Ryo-san.
What are they thinking?
They asked a child like me because they were busy.
Give me back my money.
I'll do it next time.
When?
When I feel like it.
When do you feel like it?
Be still, be quiet!
Give me back my money!
No way!
What do you want?
Uncle won't give me back my money.
"I'm not going to do it."
"What?"
"Are you a professional debt collector?"
"You have to pay back the debt quietly."
"Or I'll cry."
"You can collect more people."
"What do you think of people who are bullying kindergarten children?"
"I understand."
"You just have to pay the debt quietly from the beginning."
"Take this!"
"Damn it!"
"Just in case, I'll use the weapon to take the debt."
"I'm glad I prepared a weapon."
"Target locked on."
"Starting the search."
"They're making fun of the people at the shopping district too."
"They're making fun of the people at the shopping street too."
"I don't like the idea of hiring a kid like me."
"And I don't want to be asked to do things for others."
"I won't give a bonus for getting bullied!"
"You can't do that."
"What?"
"Be sure to pay back the debt!"
"W-What the hell are you doing?"
"My name is Hayate no Jouji, I'm a professional debt collector."
"I'm here to collect money."
"I'm the child's partner from earlier!"
"You can't be with a kid like him."
"This target scope and booster shoes are connected."
Once you lock on the token, it will continue to chase you to the end of hell.
You're already locked on!
Return your debt!
What?!
I'm going!
Robot Nation!
This is my garden!
I'll get caught by that guy!
What?!
I told you! You must not let the token you locked on escape!
What was that just now?!
We're just taking it easy, old man!
As expected of you, big brother! You're so good!
There's no one around here who can beat me!
Get out of here!
What?!
I got pulled out by a bike!
Return your debt!
I got pulled out by a human too!
What the hell?
Thank you for your hard work!
You're good!
You're a stubborn fellow!
That's what it's all about!
You can't run away from me!
Damn it!
That's right!
What the... is this?!
You're going to jump over the river with that momentum?
You're not going to!
Damn it!
You have to do it!
Gadren Kick!
What?!
*Splash*
*Sigh* Good grief.
He was a tough opponent.
Hm?
*Sigh*
*Splash*
What's this?
Hey-!
You're dead!
*Splash*
What the hell!
stan me!
*Splash*
Uwaaah...
If you want to see more, pay me back my debt.
Debt?
Are you also a debt collector?
Thank you.
My name is Sexy Rose.
There's no man who didn't fall for my charm.
Now, pay me back my debt.
The most important thing to me now is...
Please.
Money is more important than charm!
Hey! Wait!
My name is Scissor Hand Paper.
I'm a debt collector.
Oh, what's next?
Watch me show you my skills.
Dog.
Cat.
Bat.
Huh?
And the
It's a fun game, but you have to pay back the debt!
That's foolish.
I want to keep this half...
My name is Parasol Tanaka.
I'm going to captivate you!
Get out of the way!
My name is Mizugay's Mizutayu!
My name is Gengen!
Get out of the way!
My name is...
Shut up!
Damn it! I'm going to the Asakusa Indie Hall!
I wonder if the debt collectors are okay.
They're 100% successful professionals.
No matter how well they do, they won't get away.
Welcome.
Coffee!
Me too.
Thank you.
If the debt comes back, so will my wife.
I'll go home too.
I'm glad you're here.
I should have done this from the beginning.
We didn't have to push Ryo-san around.
Why did the bonus fight start?
At first, we just went to collect the debt together.
But Ryo-san suddenly ran away when it was time to pay.
I see.
I was in a hurry at that time.
I was in a hurry.
Ryo-san was young, but we were young too.
We all ran away.
The old lady at the confectionery was still as energetic as she was running around.
In the evening, I thought I finally caught Ryo-san.
After using up all the bonuses...
I was really hungry at that time.
So from the next time, I started to plan and collect the debt.
That's right.
I did a lot.
I dug a little pit and made a lot of holes.
After I became the president of the confectionery, I made machines and so on.
But in the end, I failed.
You really laugh.
I'm sorry.
From now on, you don't have to do that.
It's a good thing.
It's not good.
It was my duty to collect the debt from Ryo-san.
I'm so frustrated that I have to leave it to them.
Grandpa.
My special move!
How many people are you talking about?
Huh?
Collecting the debt!
You again!
I told you.
I will continue to chase you to the end of hell.
If you do this...
Yes!
What did you do?
It's a special instant adhesive.
I can't follow it.
Don't underestimate me.
Full power!
Ouch!
What a surprise!
Don't come back again!
It seems that I have to go myself.
Don't you get it?
I wouldn't be cool.
Teacher...
It's okay.
Your expectations are not changed.
I meet you again.
I always wait for your customer.
Is it the end?
What?
Coming!
It's working!
I can do that.
You've done well in pursuing my subordinates.
You're the master of debt collection, aren't you?
My name is "Debt Mu".
I hate debt from the bottom of my heart.
What?
My parents had a small shop in Hokkaido.
But the shop was destroyed because of the customer who didn't pay the rent.
I swear to my heart since that day.
I will never let you step on the debt.
Now, pay the debt!
Ah! It's a UFO!
Now!
How cowardly!
Usually, you can't defeat a boss character by yourself.
But you can't defeat a boss character by yourself.
There's no such thing as cowardly people who can't pay the debt.
It's the plumber.
Hello?
Yeah, yeah.
I see.
Ryo-san was caught.
Oh, Ryo-san...
Well, you did a good job.
Thank you very much.
You guys are wrong!
You guys even borrowed the hands of the people who don't know this!
Don't you think it's embarrassing?
That's right.
Don't you think it's embarrassing not to pay the debt forever?
Huh?
I'll pay the debt someday.
But I'm sorry to die this time.
I'm not worried about him.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
You're going to use your cowardly hands again?
I'll show you the true power of my boss character.
Huh?
Now, you want to pay the debt.
You want to pay the debt.
Psychiatry?
Damn! Who's a psychiatrist?
It's useless. You're already in the mood to pay the debt.
You can't help but want to pay the debt.
You'll pay the debt no matter what happens.
You have a debt.
You have to pay the debt.
Of course.
Now, if I count to three, you'll wake up and pay the debt.
One, two, three.
That's right. I have to pay the debt.
I've been in debt for a long time, but I haven't paid it at all.
What a terrible man I was.
I'll pay the debt now.
I've borrowed hundreds of millions so far.
I'll pay the debt to Nakagawa.
I'll pay you back all the bonuses, Nakagawa!
What's going on here?
I think you went to returns from the biggest part of the debt.
So you mean you won't return our debt?
That's...
I'm not kidding.
We hired you.
Let's take responsibility and get my debt back.
I know.
I know! Bring it back!
Let go of my debt!
I'm going to pay you back!
I won't let you go!
What the hell?
I knew this was going to happen.
Those who don't know much about mass production can't get their money from mass production.
We made a mistake by asking them to do this.
But if we do it ourselves...
The cost...
What's the point?
We don't care how much it costs, right?
We're chasing mass production every year not for money.
It's a matter of pride as human beings who do business.
Pride?
We get the money for the products we sell.
Even if it costs a lot of work.
That's the pride of a businessman.
That's a good point, Ma-san.
Pride of a businessman?
It seems we were wrong.
Mr. Deng.
But what about this year's bonus?
Are you going to give up?
What?
There's a way for people who know Ryo very well.
Nakagawa!
I'm going to pay you back now!
What?
I'm going to pay you back as well.
What are you doing here?
I'm sure I was caught by the debtors.
More importantly, where is the sound of the bell?
Where?
Huh?
You just...
I got it!
I did it! I'm so lucky!
Oh no! The trap!
This is good enough.
Ryo, I'm going to pay the debt.
There's no other way.
Stop me!
Don't come near me!
My bonus!
I guess you can't rely on the power of others.
Next year, we'll definitely pay the debt ourselves!
Yeah!
What should I do?
I ate a strange tree that came from the sea,
and I became a rubber human whose body stretched like rubber.
Wait a minute.
My limbs are stretched, and this may be surprisingly useful.
Next time, "Ryo of the Rubber Rubber".
See you!