"The
ない奴は俺んとこへ来い俺もないけど心配するんだ2
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
They'll be alright eventually
You understand, right? You understand, you understand?
If you understand, then quietly follow me!
Ryochi and Komachi are ballin'?
8, 9, 10, you're right.
Well, I'll contact you when you're enrolled.
I feel sorry for the neighbors who can get the latest type of plasma TV at such a low price.
The customers are lucky.
After that, you can run around the sports event and get the prize.
These 100,000 yen are all mine.
Easy peasy!
The police station, the ball, the sports event?
The prize is amazing!
There's even a brand-name product and an overseas trip!
Wow!
Wow, amazing!
Hey, don't you want to go out with everyone?
Four of us, relay?
Komachi!
I'll definitely get Gaultier's wristwatch!
Oh, I already have a competition event, so you can get another relay.
What?
You can't go out now?
What's going on, Maria?
I'm sorry, Ryo.
But, the right triangle can't go out unless it's a man and a woman.
I'm a woman, but my body is a man, so I can't go out!
I've practiced.
I've practiced for two weeks.
But I can't do that now.
Ryo, what's wrong?
Huh?
Reiko!
The heart, the body, and the woman, Reiko!
Come out on the two-man triangle with me!
And win the championship!
What?
Please!
Come out on the two-man triangle with me!
But why is it a two-man triangle, senpai?
It's because it's a hole.
A hole?
I see.
Hey!
Ryo is a newbie!
I can't lose!
Just come out on the two-man triangle!
Oh, it's okay!
I don't know about other things, but at that time you were very strong!
That's why I want to compete against me!
Let's go out!
What?
You just came to support us, Hattori-san!
You're not recophyting me!
If it's a pair-out, it's a fork dance.
If we get serious about it, we can win the championship.
I'm sorry, but I'm already registered for the girls' relay.
Registered? What's that?
Senpai, you haven't registered for the room yet?
If I don't register, I can't go to the sports day.
The deadline for registration is 5 p.m. today.
5 p.m. today?
Then, the registration for the sports day will be...
Stop!
I'll register for the two-person-three-person.
My partner must be registered by the end of the day.
The two-person-three-person is a lottery for the one who wants to be a member.
A lottery?
Why are there so many two-person-three-person-want-to-be-a-member?
Because they're stupid.
They all think the same way.
But now we can't switch to another category.
As there are many want-to-be-a-member, we decided to cast a lottery for the partner.
The partner will be chosen by the lottery draw.
What?
The two-person-three-person-partner will be the one who draws the same lottery as the partner.
I don't have time to find a partner.
What?
Two people in the front row have won, so there are two more groups.
If you don't win the lottery, you won't get anything.
Ready, go.
Yes.
Another one has won.
There's one more group left.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
One more.
You're stretching your arm so fast.
No one'll be zero in the end.
I'm a total loser.
It's about time to get to the end of the game.
Yes.
One for you.
Oh, that was close.
You're a winner?
Simultaneous.
Oh, that's the end of the game.
It's the end of the game.
Come on.
You have to win the first game.
Ah, Komachi! I can't believe we're with you!
I can't do anything with a pervert, pervert, and gorilla!
I can't do anything!
You're right, you grumpy monster!
What's wrong with you?
So you two are in danger, right?
No! I'm telling you to change your partner!
That's right! You don't care if you change with someone else right now!
It's a rule! You're in danger, you grumpy monster!
Stop it!
It's better to join the pervert than to get the watch of Galtier!
You won't be able to do anything.
It's better to be with Komachi while archers.
This is impossible!
Komachi, you can do one pervert.
What do you mean?
Well, we have three answers, so...
We have three perverts in the first round!
That's right!
Well, I have to go now.
Hm?
Who?
Komachi?
Mom, how was your Taiwan trip?
Yeah, I'm cooking with my dad right now.
I want to see your face if you're going to Tokyo.
Sorry, I have something I can't skip on Sunday.
I have something to do.
Komachi, it's your dad.
Dad, please enjoy your trip with mom.
It's a gift from Komachi.
I'll enjoy it with my friends.
Dad, why don't you ask him?
Komachi, what's going on with Ryotsu after that?
Oh, it's Mr. Ryotsu Kankichi.
His eyebrows are thick and his legs are short.
Hey, are you still saying that?
How many times do I have to tell you that I can't do anything with such an amateur?
I was here, Komachi. I looked for you.
Call me.
I'm busy, so don't talk to me.
It's Mr. Ryotsu's voice now.
It's not over yet.
I'm glad, Dad.
I'm relieved, Komachi.
I'll be nice to you two because I won't get in the way.
Mom!
Bye.
I'm out of breath.
Are you the country mothers?
You made a strange mistake again because of you.
Maybe Komachi and I are still in trouble.
You shouldn't have told us.
I was kidding.
You might think we're in trouble, but I'm theutter of a problem.
I'm sorry to listen to you.
But you cannot be.
I'm a body-fattening girl.
A fetishist.
Religiously.
So...
My body is a little overweight.
Come on!
A woman has to be able to understand men she loves more and be with her because of her virtue.
I also notice that you're making trouble for me.
So, what about how many people you're seeing in your life?
I then I'll change all the time.
Damn it!
It hurts!
Hold on!
If you let go in the middle, you'll get a disqualification.
Good.
Don't get too close, Sukibe.
Don't get too close? How are you going to run?
I don't want to be interested in a young man like you!
What did you say?
So, what's your position?
Fine, I'm going to start from the right.
You don't have to say it many times, you know it.
Ready!
It hurts!
What are you doing?
I told you to start from the right!
So, start from the left!
Your right!
I said it's your right!
I thought it was your right foot!
Don't say things that are confusing.
You're so kind!
No!
You're the one who's late!
It's my fault!
Now, I'm going to start from the inside!
Ready!
Start!
Cartier's watch!
Plasma TV!
You're so useless!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ouch!
Cartier!
Damn!
If I'd practiced beforehand, I wouldn't have lost!
It's Komachi's fault.
Give up on my plasma TV!
What a fool you are, Taiko!
This is the preliminary round.
We're second place, so we'll just have to win the finals, Tomma!
You're here, Komachi?
What? We have an hour before the finals, so I can do whatever I want!
We've been checking the flow of the finals, but it's not like we're going to the preliminaries.
Are you sure?
If we keep running like we did earlier, we'll never win.
We won't even get the TV or the clock!
But it's impossible for us to match your pace.
This is the secret weapon that will make that impossible possible.
What?
What is this?
It's the Nini-chan I made last night.
It's the Victory Machine for the 2 of us!
It's a Truth dejar out of Protech!
Truth işin dotaikun ...
Don't offense me!
I, Komachi, will definitely win if the 1 of us can make our 2 in 3 win today!
What? The 2 of us?
It's Victory!
Yes.
Oh, hey, Mom.
Are you already at the airport?
What the ~!
What? What are you doing in that poor place?
Why are you here?
Dad is acting like a fool and says, "This way, this way."
Originally, it was my mom who said that.
Today, today, I'm almost at my father's mercy.
Dad is at his limit of patience.
That's what I'm saying, Komachi.
Don't fight over useless things.
If it's now, it's still...
I'm out of breath.
What's going on?
Today, I gave a gift for a Taiwan trip at my parents' bank.
I gave a gift for a Taiwan trip at my parents' bank.
But instead of Haneda, who is at the airport,
I heard he's at Akabane for some reason.
Hanenoji is the only one who's doing it.
That's what couples are like.
And I'm nervous about a foreign trip that I can't get used to.
I thought I'd pick you up at Tokyo Station.
I'll be right back.
You're going?
Where are you going?
I'm sending you two to Haneda.
Get rid of this weird thing!
What about the final?
Hey, hey!
Hello, it's me, Ryo-tsu.
Oh, Mr. Ryo-tsu.
We couples are no longer allowed.
Please take care of my Komachi.
No, that's not what I mean.
Komachi can't walk right now,
so I'll ask around the station and go to Haneda.
Mr. Ryo-tsu.
I'm glad to see you.
I've been a wife for 25 years.
Couples are strangers after all.
If you're going to be with Komachi,
you'd better think about it.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
That's what I mean, Mr. Ryo-tsu.
What do you mean?
It's time for us to start walking our separate paths.
What?
We're going to walk our separate paths.
Dad, Mom, what are you talking about?
I'm going to Hamamatsu-cho.
Take this off.
I forgot the key.
I won't take it off.
What are you going to do?
How are you going to get it?
It's the wedding ceremony.
You're lost in the red field,
and you're in a divorce.
It's too much.
What?
If this happens, I'll go with you.
You're kidding, right?
I can't go to the final by myself.
If that's the case, I'll go with you,
and the safest way is to come back in a hurry.
You're going with me?
With two people and three people?
Let's go.
I'm Ono, participating in today's Taiwan tour.
Ono.
Ono Shojiro and Ono Masako.
I'm your daughter.
We're busy.
We'd better take the train.
I'll be there.
Please wait a minute for me.
Ready?
Jackson,
Please wait a minute for me.
If you start the car,
you can't stop it этого.
if I start the car,
You can't reverse the car in that speed?
I don't have a pedal in the foot curb.
All I have is the body.
Please give me part of your body.
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move!
It's gonna crash!
It's gonna spin!
Idiot! It's the other way around!
You can't stop it, but you can back it up!
If you don't change the direction, it won't run as it is!
To change the direction, you have to crash into something again!
I have to!
Good job, the direction changed!
It's not good at all!
It's dangerous!
Let me know faster!
This time, it's a pedestrian bridge!
What?!
The uphill is still good.
The problem is downhill!
Help me!
The next is the uphill...
Dad! Dad!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It hurts!
Nakagawa, you're really something!
Congratulations on making it through the first place in the preliminary!
You're the best at the rental competition, aren't you, Terae?
Kei-chan, Terae-san!
Reiko-san!
Everyone, please do your best in the relay!
I'm so excited!
I can't see Komachi-chan and Ryo-chan's two-person triathlon team...
We've been looking for them for a while now, but...
Are they practicing secret training somewhere?
I'll make something weird like this!
I'll bring it here!
I'll set you free!
It's too much trouble to make you do something that big!
It can't be helped!
Even I didn't expect this.
Couldn't you contact your mom?
I don't have a cell phone...
I can't wait for her to contact her.
Hello, Dad?
Did you two bux?
Your Father and Mother broke up!
What?
Hello?
Dad, why don't you take the next train and follow your mom?
Yes, Hamamatsu, not Hamamatsu, Hamamatsu-cho.
We're heading there right now.
Mom, what are you doing?
Yes, Mom. I'm Ryotsu.
Okay, it's fine.
Mom, you go ahead.
Eh?
Did you get off?
Did you get off the train in Okachiba?
But I don't have a cell phone.
I got off the train and I'm calling you this week, Mom.
Get on! Get on!
Don't get off the next train and get off at Hamamatsu-cho!
We're heading there too!
That's what a married couple is like!
Masako!
Masako! Masako!
Dad!
Thank goodness!
Hey, don't stop near the entrance!
It's already late.
The second line door is closing. Keep an eye on it.
Reiko-san!
Yes!
You can do it!
I can see the station, Komachi!
Yay!
The train for Okuno-san and the others is almost here!
Huh?
Hello, Mom!
Hey!
Komachi!
Where are you?
Everyone's looking for you!
Hey!
Komachi, I think she's talking.
Huh?
Hey!
Naoko, I'm sorry!
We'll talk about it later!
Hey!
Where are you?
Dono Shiojiro and Ono Masako!
Komachi!
Kyo-ichi-san!
This way!
Làh!
Dad! Mom!
The reunion is coming!
Dad!
Yeah-
Enjoy it!
You have the best time!
Yay!
Wow!
T Oregon
So this is what you get to catch them.
That's the difference between the father and the mother with all the trouble.
But you Ho almost saw his face before the departure.
If it's good, I never quit.
I haven't finished yet.
Hello? Yes, this is Ono from Taiwan Tour.
I'm sorry, I'll be arriving soon.
I saw you again, you're in a perfect mood. You really look good together.
You're right.
After you return from your trip, you'll meet your parents again.
You don't have to go.
I'm at my limit.
Are you Mr. Ono? This way, this way!
I'm here!
Nice to meet you!
I'm going!
Huh? It's a daughter and a daughter-in-law.
You made it!
Ah, exercise!
Next, we'll do a two-person, three-person final.
The first course, the Shinjuku team.
The second course, the Arakawa team.
The third course, the Setagaya team.
The fourth course, the Suginami team.
The fifth course, the Katsushika team.
Is the fifth course, the Katsushika team, dangerous?
What's wrong, Ryo and the others?
Senpai, you wanted to go out so badly.
Ah, they're here!
Yes, yes, yes.
Ready!
I made it in time, but...
It's not...
It's not like this!
I came all the way here!
Huh? My legs are light!
If it's this...
Here I go!
Yeah!
Wow!
I did it!
President, Ryo did it!
I'm glad, Ohara!
I did it!
Ryo, you're the champion!
Fifth course, the Katsushika team.
Disqualified!
Huh? Why?
I didn't put my feet on the ground, so I'm disqualified!
Disqualified!
Oh, Katsushika!
I'm out of energy!
I was surprised, but...
Disqualified!
and how the moon is shining,
and how the village mayor ordered a wedding.
It's so exciting!
What are you going to do?
I don't know anything!
You explain it yourself!
It's your problem!
It's all your fault!
It seems that there are some good monkeys and dogs around here.
Maybe...
There's no way!
Mr. Honda, when you ride a motorcycle, your personality changes. Why is that?
Why is that?
Why does the sun rise only once every four years? Why is that?
Mr. Nakagawa doesn't lend money to the mass production company,
but he can easily borrow a tank or a fighter.
Why is that?
Mr. Reiko is a rich man,
but he works at a gas station. Why is that?
Why is that?
Damn it!
No matter how many times I do it,
it's the worst day ever!
This fortune-telling that I choose A or B,
no matter how much I pass by,
I end up here!
What the hell is going on?
What's going on?
I have a bad feeling about this day.
Next time,
"The Way of Fate"
See you then!
Next time, "The Way of Fate"