Tea possibilities
When you watch TV
Look at each other in the room, then try to stay away
The day of inner peace floats like a twilight
Look at the radiating sun
How kind of you
From the tapestry of a plump hat
To the taishakuten
The sun is setting
Tomorrow is over already
Why is it over?
If I win, I'll lose happiness again
I noticed, I'm such an idiot
48 hours, a world tour
Are you reading a foreign magazine again?
What kind of magazine is that?
It's a magazine for young women in France
It's for various reasons
I'm just a random person
I'm fine with being dizzy
What do you think, Nakagawa?
Did you say something, senpai?
This is a foreign newspaper
You guys don't seem like you're from the city
Is that so?
Isn't this a great professor?
It's really Professor Ezaki
What's wrong with Professor Ezaki?
He's going to announce something at the university in New York
It's his research
It's not good
What?
It's a train
Really?
I have a bad feeling about this
Everyone fell asleep for a while
See?
Professor Ezaki
How disgusting
I feel bad
I've lived in all the countries in the world
I came to the conclusion that Japan is the most wonderful country in the world
It's true that it's Japanese
You're clearly mistaken
What are you doing?
Don't look at me with that dirty face!
Ouch! What are you doing?
I'm going to sell a train for 100 million yen
1 million yen?
That means
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
. Thank you for always caring and thanking you.
Let's introduce myself.
Please, everyone, thank you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please come this way.
I am the origin of Japanese Wabi-sabi.
The heart of tea is the mother's heart.
If you drink it, you will be alive.
Please enjoy your meal.
Ryuuho!
Please.
Then, I'll enjoy my meal.
Please enjoy your meal.
I need to use the bathroom.
20 million yen!
Please wait!
I'm sorry.
What's in that plastic bag?
I'll check it.
Well, this is...
What's wrong, Ryuuho?
You did something again, didn't you?
I didn't do anything...
Stop cutting my hair!
This is...
...the best salt!
Oh, senpai!
The treasure of the pond!
What?
Don't be so careless.
You're not going to be able to taste it.
What are you talking about?
Look at that!
That's an ordinary voice, not an inborn voice.
What?
Come to think of it...
It's all black.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
You're going to be suspicious.
Don't lie!
Even if I lie, I won't let you fool me.
That's right!
I won't let you fool me!
What?
*Gasp*
Look at this!
*Groan*
Oh! The color's changed!
The pattern's changed from the bottom!
It's exactly as it is. I painted it black and faked it.
Ryo-chan!
*Groan*
As expected of your husband.
I'm so happy that you saw through this trick in one look.
*Groan*
You're being so arrogant. You really didn't know anything.
What are you talking about?
Your husband saw through everything that happened.
*Groan*
Oh! It's black again!
What?
The real thing is...
*Groan*
Here!
Your husband did a great job.
He hid the real thing in advance and painted it in the normal color,
and then let it go into the pond.
*Groan*
That's exactly right, Ojaru!
You knew everything, Ojaru!
Wow! Kiyo did everything.
You're really good at this, Professor.
*Groan*
This old lady is really something.
By the way, everyone, I have something else I'd like to show you.
*Groan*
This is the videotape I'll use when I announce this at the next conference.
If this is announced,
the whole world will pay attention to my theory of learning, Ojaru!
Show this tape to everyone in the audience.
*Groan*
Ezaki Korosuke, stop!
One point!
You're breathing is so scary.
Damn you, you old man.
Watch this.
*Groan*
KINPU HUNTER~ The thoughtless Massacre
Fufu...
Wh-what?
Hey, we wouldn't let anyone announce something like this at the conference, right?
No, no, that's not it!
That's not it either!
That is the wrong tape.
Where did the wrong tape go?!
Master!
Did I misprint the videotapes sent by the young ladies last week?
Oh no!
I sent them myself, open-minded.
*Groan*
At this rate,
Is this a worldwide announcement?
It seems like a very important tape.
You've forgotten to take a look at it.
If I contact you right away,
will you send it to me or will you go get it?
I don't know who sent it.
Is it Haruko, Natsuko, Akiko,
or Fuyuko?
No!
The conference is tomorrow.
There are only 48 hours!
Only 48 hours?
Where do your daughters live?
Haruko is a smuggler in the jungle in Africa.
Natsuko is investigating the location of the submarine at the Bamiuda Sea.
Akiko is currently on a dog-hunting tour of the North Pole.
Fuyuko is... Where is she?
They're all in a terrible place.
What's going on?
If I don't get that tape, I'm done!
What?
Let's go on our own!
Huh?
Please be careful.
For your husband, even if it's in the fire or water...
Professor, I'll take care of the plane.
No!
Thank you!
A world tour?
Sounds fun.
Okay! I'm going too!
You two be careful.
Hey, hey!
It's Keiichi!
Hey, did you hear that?
Is it really that great of a tape?
It's the person who said it, so there's no mistake.
If he takes that tape, he'll make a lot of money on it.
Then we're winners, right, kei?
Let's go.
Wh- what the check!?
Hang in there!
This is the fastest!
It's still too early!
So you're already in Africa?
Africa is wonderful!
Look at these animals!
This is the kingdom of nature!
You guys don't have to fight like that.
Why don't you act like me, and act naturally?
Then you can talk to the lions!
You're lying!
I'm not lying! Look!
That's a cat!
Look! The words are working!
Yes, yes!
You can do this, too!
How's that?
It's a touching moment for both of us!
Thanks to you, Grandma!
I can do this, too!
They're here.
We finally made it.
Here we go!
The owner of the house is having coffee.
This is Africa.
The Kiriman is really good.
It's not the time to drink coffee.
We have to do something!
We have to talk to the lions!
Don't panic.
Be quiet!
It's tea time!
What?
Amazing.
The lion is staring at us.
The owner is really good!
That's why I told you.
Don't panic.
You were just drinking coffee.
What?
It's a car!
You guys!
Catch the last one!
It's me!
It's a surprise to me.
It's too scary.
It's not a secret!
It's época!
Everyone, follow me!
What!
Dah!
Don't!
Oh no!
It's bad! Run!
I won't let you!
I'll kill you!
The prisoners!
Please be careful!
We're arresting them all!
Oh, Mr. Harukojo!
What? That's...
Light coffee is American.
Cute coffee is African.
Dad's video letter?
If that's the case, it was just a picture of Dad.
So it wasn't you...
Then...
What the hell is this place?
Ah! Dad!
So the video letter didn't have anything different on it?
No, it wasn't.
It's a signal!
The sea is the source of all life.
This fantastic ocean...
I want to show it to you and everyone else.
If you're as good as your husband,
you can do anything!
Ho ho ho ho ho ho!
You're just dead!
Ha ha ha ha!
Uwaaah!
Help me!
This is the place!
There's only 12 hours left!
Ha ha ha ha!
I wonder what it is...
Hm?
What is it?
Stop!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
What?
...
A video letter?
I sent it by mistake.
It's an important tape used at the meeting.
I don't have time to read the letters I got, so I brought them all.
That's it!
Damn it!
No!
-Hakuna- -Hakuna-
-Shut up! -Shut up!
Why me?
This guy...
Shut up.
What do you want, big brother?
Help!
How is it, master?
This is also different.
It's Fuyuko's place, but where is she now?
Oh, dad. If it's Fuyuko...
Is she really going to space?
Here. This is it, dad.
I thought it was weird.
This is it. There's no doubt.
Congratulations on the completion of the meeting, master.
But we have to hurry.
We only have three hours until the announcement.
The car is coming.
Keiichi-mon, here you are.
Thank you for your hard work.
From here, we should be able to go to the venue in 30 minutes.
40 minutes left until the announcement.
We're barely in time.
Hey, you have the tape, right?
If you say you lost it after coming this far, it won't be fun.
Don't worry.
I'll put it here.
What was that?
I took the tape!
What did you say?
I'll take this tape!
My world's biggest announcement is...
I'm going to chase that crazy guy!
All right!
Get ready!
Yeah.
I give it a shot!
All right.
Go, go, go!
If you run into a man, he'll cut you!
You'll have to do it yourself!
What you're saying is right.
I'm afraid this won't be a good thing.
Really?
I'm sorry, Master.
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I'm sorry, Master.
I'm sorry.
Drink it up, will ya?
Oh no, it's a traffic jam.
Damn it!
We're going to use that thing!
Huh?
It's the Kiba Police's horse, isn't it?
Alright, Nakagawa!
You're going to have to get the titan to the venue somehow!
Huh?
Ah, Senpai!
Damn it!
Hurry up!
Hey, you thief!
Wait!
Give me the tape!
Bro, they're chasing us with their horses!
Damn it, they're so quiet!
Bro, it's a traffic jam!
Damn it!
We're going to break through!
Stop!
Ah, Grandma!
We're alive!
It's time for us to stop!
W-What's this?
This isn't a circus!
Ah, you guys!
Run!
Hey! Give it back!
Wait!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Shut up and put the blanks back!
I wonder if they'll come after me.
I'm going to go, big brother!
Oh no!
It's heavy!
I'll never let go!
Big brother!
I can't take this anymore!
Hey! What are you sleeping on?
What is this?
It's a bath!
What are you doing?
I'm going to get the tape back!
Why me?
I did it!
My husband!
I got the tape back safely!
What an old lady!
To horrible!
So, now it's the professor Esaki's present.
First, please take a look at the videotape.
Yeah, it's tape we had a lot of trouble with.
Show me what you've got.
I want you to know something.
Who's coming this time?
Right!
G
W-What is this stupid anime?
It has nothing to do with the main subject!
Imperator!
It's an interesting joke!
Bravo!
It's so interesting!
Splendid, sir!
The humor that makes the whole world laugh!
What exactly was our trouble?
Ezaki Korosuke, Japan's best!
Thank you!
Yeah!
Subtitle by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Thanks for watching!
If you like ourYubi videos, please subscribe to our channel!
The final energy
Looking at tomorrow, believing in yesterday
Drawing the universe, standing on the ground
The planet with a turtle is spinning
I wrote a poem
This is good, right?
There's no excuse, right?
Maria
This is Maria.
I've been with Ryo-sama for over a year, but I haven't made any progress at all.
So, when I consulted with Komachi-san, he said that there was no choice but to make a "magnificent reality".
Next time, "Maria's Love Tekken".
Thank you for watching!