Wanderer"
"The Wanderer"
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and look away.
"The Wanderer"
Come to me,
the poor guy.
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky,
and the white clouds.
I'll be able to do something
in the meantime.
"The Wanderer"
I'm not busy,
and I'm worried.
There is no single wasted time.
"The Wanderer"
Come on, follow me!
Meditation! This is the temporary exit!
Alright!
Oh, good morning!
Good morning, Ryo-chan!
Ryo-san, wait a moment!
I'll clean up now!
Senpai!
Don't use my desk without permission!
I'm sorry...
Ryo-chan, what are you doing?
That's right!
Don't you feel sorry for Terai-san?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I feel sorry for him too!
He changed his mind and was aiming for the real thing!
But he got away with it and he's running away!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Oh no! The chair is bent!
Oh, I broke the ornament.
Don't worry about me!
Ryo-chan is self-sufficient!
I can't use this chair anymore.
Give it to me!
This is how you do it!
This is how you fix it!
Oh, then I can't sit.
You're going to the art museum.
I'm getting a tip from my salary next month.
Shut up!
You can't sit like this!
See? It's comfortable to sit.
It's not bad...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Gagu!
This time, the bookshelf...
Oh, no!
Why is there a bookshelf in such a place?
Ouch!
Gagu!
What are you going to do with this, Ryo-chan?
If I do this...
Ouch!
Oh!
This wall is also hard!
Oh, stop it!
I'm going to support you with this!
The window is broken!
There are holes in the roof!
Oh, it's a mouse!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ryo-chan, I'm going to do it!
Get out of here!
Oh!
Ouch!
What's going on?
What?
How could it be?
Huh?
Wow!
Our leader!
What are you guys...
Ah, our leader!
That's...
What is it?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Who the hell is doing this?
Huh?
You again, Ryotsu?
You call this a "mess"?
This is just the way it is.
Idiot!
For some reason, at such an important time...
Important time?
The Headquarters will be here tomorrow morning.
The Headquarters?
The Headquarters's actual investigation, you idiot!
If you tell the Headquarters about this, they'll know.
Don't make that face, Butchon.
It's impossible to change the date of the Headquarters's investigation.
I've become weak.
Leave it to me, Butchon.
By the end of the day, I'll make sure to make sure the Headquarters is as it was.
You think so?
Of course, Butchon.
Anyway, everyone gather here at 8:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Until then, continue your usual work.
Ryotsu, your punishment will be decided at that time.
Wash your head and wait.
But, there's no Headquarters. How can I work here?
Yeah.
Even the idiot there can think about that!
Chief!
The Headquarters will be repaired as it was!
I'll work here too!
I'll make sure to get through this hard time!
Chief!
I can't do this.
The day after tomorrow means the day after tomorrow.
I don't have time!
What's with that cold look?
Everyone has it, doesn't he?
You're so angry that you're going to break the bridge!
No.
Well, I guess you don't do it that often.
Anyway, it's a crisis.
I'm sorry for raising the force of the Nagagawa Group.
I'm going to make a big surprise appearance!
Don't let us down this time.
What?
We decided to take this opportunity to think about whether it's okay to follow Senpai or not.
Don't be so mean, Reiko-chan.
I'll take a look at Ryo-chan's work.
I've been with you for a long time.
Please persuade the two of you.
I have a family I have to protect.
Is that so?
Do it yourself!
I'm not asking you anymore!
We're going back to the office.
Please contact us once the policy is decided.
Chief Ryo-chan.
Oh.
Isn't this my wallet?
Hmm.
We can't let this go to the original until the day after tomorrow.
We can't, Ryo-san.
That's it!
For now, if it's a look for the original,
papercraft or writing, or whatever,
I'm counting on you.
It can't be that kind of thing.
If you do this,
I'll ask you to do the renovation of my dad's store.
Come to think of it,
No, I heard that we should change the building into a new one.
Oh, really, Ryo-san?
My old man in Tsukuda-jima got tired of living in a new house,
so he wanted to build a house on the ground again.
He said that, but he didn't say anything.
Oh, let me do that!
Then...
I'll do my best.
Really?
If I can't get through, the street will be blocked.
Now I have to find a room for the temporary house.
Is it true that he found a property for the temporary house?
It's about Ryo-chan, so it's definitely a bad place.
I thought Ryo-san was going to this area...
Hey, this way!
Here!
Go up the elevator!
Okay!
What?
Wow! It's so big and beautiful!
What's wrong with this place?
My skills are just like this.
Well, relax without hesitation.
It's strange that the temporary house is better.
Ryo-chan, did you do something bad?
I can hear everything!
What?
Ahahaha!
It's such a temporary house.
I thought there must be an property that the real estate company is not even renting.
We rented it for 3000 yen a day.
It's a condition to clean up through the wind.
It's cheap in this room.
As expected, Senpai.
K-chan, if you praise it, it will be on the map again.
It's amazing!
There is a washing machine in the bathroom!
The mirror of the washroom is also large.
There are also things that make a big wind.
It's like a department store!
Compared to the department store, it seems to be a temple for the common people.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, Chief Ohara!
Chief, how is my temporary house?
Please relax slowly.
There is also a sofa with a leather handle.
I can't do that, but...
I'm not worried about you, Chief!
Chief, the repair work of the washroom in front of the park has been done perfectly, so please rest assured.
Oh, I see.
The repair work of the washroom in front of the park is complete.
I'm a man who does it when I do it.
There should be a washroom around here.
Oh?
An announcement that there is a washroom.
Phew, what do you think?
Reiko, can I borrow an tout?
I've got to go to the other side, I'm in pain!
Hayato, there looks to be a problem with the motel service They have at night.
Elder, did you bring all the mulberry?
Was that all, Captain?
Yo-san!
Wasn't the old lady's poem "Shigin no Kai" this weekend?
Keiko!
Did you call me?
It's the last letter of the book!
What?
I said, the last letter!
No, I can't hold it in!
It seems like they haven't had a chance to talk since just now.
I can't calm down when I have more than 60% of the time.
You're right, the work efficiency is getting worse.
Don't be so luxurious!
Forgive me!
Why is the exit on top of the building?
I just wanted to ask the directions!
Did you climb up the stairs?
Check!
The elevator is stopped by regular inspection!
Senpai, this place is really...
It's not suitable for the exit, Ryo-san.
Let's move, Ryo-chan.
Don't say it so easily!
It's been three days since we've found this house...
It's this place!
What did you say?!
Damn it!
I'm not sure if this is the right place to continue, though.
The ratio is close to the original station.
The most important thing is that you only have to pay for the high fever.
It's a super good property.
But senpai.
Ryo-san.
Because, Ryo-chan, this is not a pub.
It's a station size in terms of size.
Certainly the red carpet on the front looks like a stone light.
Kei-chan, you're putting it on your pace.
Yes, yes, yes.
"It's a station size in terms of size"
How about it?
It looks like a station, right?
If you do that, you'll get in the way of the business, Ryo-san.
Do you have permission?
Huh? Ryo-san?
Yo. You're still as energetic as ever.
Oh, Ryo-san.
We're going out soon.
Yeah.
It's a summer vacation.
Okay.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh.
If you're going to give us a vacation,
there's nothing more reassuring than this.
Well then, I'm counting on you.
Ryo-san.
Bye-bye.
Have a good trip.
Take care of your souvenirs.
If that's what you want,
I'll let you use it.
Eh? Kei-chan.
It's until the day after tomorrow.
Until the day after tomorrow.
Since long ago,
I've been called Miyako.
Eh?
Say cheese, please.
Oh, that's not fair.
Here's a beer.
Here's some more.
Shrimp shumai,
I'll be taken away with you,
Pfft.
Bring me the beer.
I can't give you the beer.
lt's a beer!
It's a good place to go to the toilet.
I'm sorry, but please go to the store.
Whatever you want, I'll have beer.
Bring me beer.
I can't bring you beer.
Beer, beer, beer.
Senpai, it's impossible to go to the toilet here.
That's why I told you.
This is bad.
If you don't remove the red carpet on the front, the customers will come in more and more.
Yeah.
It looks delicious.
Ten bottles of beer for the time being.
We are at a tea party.
Well, ten bottles of beer.
I'll take four.
Me too.
Umesawa is here.
Yeah.
What shall i do, Ryo?
Damn.
Yeah.
*Sigh*
The power went out again!
I don't know what's going on.
This is the application problem of the formula that I taught you earlier.
Oh, I see.
Let's make it a solution!
What?
You stole everything!
You said you don't know.
I can't run away anymore.
I think it's better to give up honestly.
I don't know.
You don't know.
Then why do you have my underwear?
*Sigh*
Next to math is English.
Yes.
You stole it!
Be honest!
You don't know.
You don't know!
You liar! You pervert!
You!
You can't concentrate at all with this!
This is not good, I will fail the exam!
You are unreasonable to turn the room
instead of teaching at home, Ryo-chan.
Uhmm...
I thought it was just right
because I didn't have money to go to the prep school
I thought it was just right because I didn't have money to go to the prep school
Hey, stop it!
You're noisy, so the children won't stop crying!
Ugh...
KOUMYOU
Pardon me.
M.B.M. B.A.B.
That's all it says.
And that's it.
...
The small ways I used to travel through the world,
now I have to go back again.
Oh, uh, what's up?
N-Nope...
Um, could you help me buy a 1000 yen ticket?
Would you like to pay for it?
I'm sorry, but this is an exit, so I don't want to pay for it.
I see.
Good.
Wait a minute!
Give me all the coins you have!
I pay with cards.
I don't carry coins.
How much is it?
It's 238 yen, but it's not enough at all.
I don't know.
I'll pay a little.
Naga, please change at the convenience store in front of you.
I see.
Do you have to do that?
I do!
Please wait a little while to stay here for a while.
Hey, customer!
If you do that, you'll fill up too much laundry!
That's not the duty of the exit office, Ryo!
What?
Are you trying to serve the public?
Did you think about it?
I may want to stay here.
Do you want to wait here?
No, I think that's dangerous.
Let's go.
Let's go before the end.
Let's go before the end?
No, please.
Let's go.
Please.
It's a temporary escape room!
Here!
No one can get in here!
You can get a temporary escape room that won't get in the way of anyone!
It's just a street.
What if it rains?
You can't work in a place like this, Ryo.
Leave it to me!
It's like an eel's sleeping room escape room.
Even if you put a chair in this small room, you can't use the desk.
This will be the desk.
I'll write the documents like this.
I see.
If it's not a temporary escape room, you can't get in and out of here.
That's solved too.
This way, there's no danger of an emergency exit.
Only Ryo-chan can do that.
It's not a temporary escape room.
The three floors of the building next door are soba restaurants.
There are also a beef bowl and a bento shop here, so it's easy to come and go.
Oh, I won't let you guys have a hard time!
Somehow, I feel like this is the best place I've ever been.
That's right. If you live here, it's a capital.
Above all, it's nice to be able to relax without anyone's care.
Let's decide!
Then, this is my temporary escape room in front of Kameari Park!
The temporary escape room in front of the park!
What?
Stop it!
Get out of the way!
What?
Damn it! What's going on?
I see. This alley is the shortcut to the station, Ryo-san.
Oh, the morning commute rush!
Our escape room is...
Hey...
Yes?
Huh? The escape room is ready?
Is it ready?
Y-Yes! The escape room!
It's the escape room, Reiko-san!
Yeah, it's not an illusion, is it?
We're finally back!
It's our escape room!
Then, I'll give you the sign.
You did a good job.
Well, I'll leave it to you to take care of your family.
What?
Huh?
Oh!
We've been waiting for you, Chief!
Did you use magic?
I'm glad you made it in time.
I'm Yamashita, the Chief of Staff.
Then, I'll start the investigation of the escape room.
Please, please!
Come on!
Oh!
Oh my gosh!
Where's the exit here?
Where is it?
It's right here!
I see and I know!
Here it is!
The escape room!
LUYOSAN!
What is this?
What is it?
It must be a hidden entrance ...
A secret entrance.
Move quickly!
Hey, what's wrong?
Where did you get the restaurant?
Hey, where did you get the restaurant?
It's broken!
No!
What's this?
As you ordered, it's a paper craft that Marufuska made and completed.
Huh?
For now, if it looks like it,
it can be a paper craft or a writing board, anything is fine!
I'm counting on you!
Paper craft...
What do you mean by this?
Can you explain?
It's impossible to re-create a real writing board in two days!
Wait!
Hey!
It's so...
Kyoichi!
You bastard!
B-BAKENMON!
Huh?
Ah, right!
Can I do a California roll?
Oh!
I don't want a California roll!
This isn't America!
I'm sorry!
Um...
Excuse me!
Yes, sir!
Well,
Kushi-age, Kaki-age, Katsu-age, whatever, Age-age, what was it again?
What do you recommend?
Just be careful with Katsu-age!
Huh?
That's...
What does "Oyaji gag" mean?
Well, I'm so sorry!
I don't get it!
Huh?
Who...?
Who?
Seriously?
Welcome!
Please come in!
I was forced to meet President Ohara
I thought that a good partner would come
This is amazing
She is beautiful, kind and can do anything
Moreover, she seems to like me
Next time, Ryo's love declaration
Thank you