Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset in the middle of the river ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was joking with the head of the taiko ♪
♪ But he laughed at my words ♪
♪ No matter how much I try to cheer up ♪
♪ I can only get angry ♪
♪ The cityscape is kinder than the devil ♪
♪ The crows are crying, the rain is falling ♪
♪ The yakitori is running wild ♪
♪ It's raining ♪
♪ From the shaggy and pale corner of my hat ♪
♪ I got a cold and feel help from the sun setting down ♪
♪ I'll wake up tomorrow ♪
♪ So it's the end ♪
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I found myself being a fool ♪
"Separation"
Senpai, this is...
It came out of the drawer.
It's a picture of Yves' wedding.
It's like a father who makes his daughter his wife.
It was a big deal that Honda made a fuss.
They're good siblings.
I was worried because they were getting married.
But Yves and Kawasaki are about to graduate, aren't they?
Where will they get a job?
I wonder.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Kawasaki, Yves.
Long time no see.
I really appreciate your help at the wedding.
We were just talking about you two.
Where will you get a job?
Actually, regarding the job...
I have some advice for you all.
What?
Is that so?
You two are great.
I haven't told my family yet.
Especially,
I'm worried about how to tell my brother.
That's a big problem, isn't it?
Don't worry.
I'll tell Honda.
What?
Senpai will do it?
I know how to handle Honda.
I know the least shocking way.
You failed at the wedding, too.
Yes, yes.
You'll be fine this time.
Leave everything to me.
Y-Yes, sir.
Thank you.
See you later, Honda family!
Mr. Ryozuma!
What's the matter?
Why are you suddenly talking?
Huh?
Ryo-chan is the one who's talking.
Is that so?
Hey, you're here, Honda.
What's the matter?
Well...
Yves gave birth.
Yves gave birth!
What?
What are you talking about, senpai?
Yves hasn't had a baby yet!
It's about a game.
A game?
Yes.
It's a pretty interesting simulation game.
It's like watching a person's life.
A simulation game?
Yes.
So, the character I'm raising now is Yves.
Yves's brother was a boy.
But...
I want to name him the same as my sister.
What should I name him?
If you name him the name of a friend,
you'll get a sense of closeness.
But it doesn't make sense.
It's okay. It's a game.
Ryo-chan, I wonder if it's really okay to leave it to one person.
I'm worried.
So, what's the story?
Well, it's...
What's going on?
Yves is going to go far away with her husband's transfer.
Finally, Yves is going to leave her hometown.
What?
Oh, my God!
Senpai!
Are you all right?
Yves is going to go far away with her husband's transfer.
Don't cry.
Yves!
What's wrong?
It's just a game.
I just heard the name Yves.
It's a Honda.
So, you haven't told me about the story yet?
I just talked about the game.
I can't talk about it.
Why do you talk about important things while playing games?
I'm telling you.
While we're talking about the game,
Yves goes overseas.
I thought it would be less shocking if I talked about going overseas.
Yves is going to go far away.
Thank you for your help.
Goodbye.
To overseas.
Yves is going to go...
Hey, Honda!
Mr. Honda!
Yves is going to go overseas.
Are you all right, Honda?
Please be strong.
Yves is going...
What?
Oh, my goodness!
Really?
Yves is going overseas?
They're thinking of moving to Africa.
Africa!
Ahhhh...
Is that okay?
Be calm and listen closely.
Yves is going to Africa.
Now desert is spreading all over the world.
And it also causes poverty and famine.
To do so, many people are following the land where they live.
And to stop her from eating, you need to eat.
Kawasaki used to volunteer to go to the African Karahari Desert.
He thought it was a good job to spend his life.
So after graduation, he decided to go to Africa.
As expected of the partner chosen by Eve.
He has a very solid idea.
So you don't have to take Eve with you, do you?
You are a married couple.
So you have to stay where I can see you.
Please, please, senpai.
Please make sure Eve doesn't go to Africa.
Hello.
Welcome.
It's the first time you've come to my house.
It's a small place, but please come up.
Yes.
Hey, Mr. Ryotsu.
What about the story of the example?
Tell me.
I was a little surprised, but I was convinced.
Is that so?
So I have a little discussion about it today.
What?
I'm at Eve's house?
Yes.
I'm wondering if you would like to work with me until I go to Africa.
Why suddenly?
Actually, I talked to the family of Honda about going to Africa.
Are you opposed?
No.
If it's a good idea, everyone will agree.
Is that so?
But.
Mr. Honda's father.
He is sad that Eve is not going to be able to see him from now on.
Then how about living with the shop until I leave for Africa?
I see.
I guess the two of them were working at the convenience store to earn money for Africa.
Yes.
But the rent and living expenses of the apartment are not very good.
Then, it's even more convenient.
And, originally, Kawasaki likes motorcycles and has a license as a mechanics.
Yes.
Yes, that's what we're talking about.
We're here to help you.
Right?
Yes.
I see!
That's the deal!
I'm glad!
And I want to ask you something.
While you're at home,
people in Hondake are hoping that you'll forget about Africa and have a fun day.
Kawasaki, I don't want you to tell anyone about going to Africa.
What do you think?
Yes, I understand.
Hello!
Hey, Ryo.
Long time no see.
What's up?
Actually, I have something to tell you.
What? Kawasaki is at home?
Yes.
He wants to work here.
But why are you here all of a sudden?
Actually, I was talking to Kawasaki the other day,
and he told me about this shop.
He said he wanted to ride on the white horse for the rest of his life,
so he wanted to be a police officer.
So I told him.
My brother's brother hates bikes.
He said he wouldn't ride on a bike for the rest of his life.
So?
Then Kawasaki said he wanted to ride on a bike.
Really?
Yes.
He said he's been interested in riding on a bike for a long time.
Hmm.
That bastard.
He's a bad guy.
I see!
Then it's a deal!
I'm glad!
But, sir, I have a request for you.
What?
Kawasaki doesn't want to be spoiled by you.
He wants you to be a good boy.
So I want you to be strict with Kawasaki,
just like a part-time job.
Don't tell him to let you work here.
Don't make him feel at ease.
I got it.
Leave it to me.
You're a good boy!
I'm a very good boy!
You're a very good boy!
But, sir, will this really work?
Yeah!
Anyway, if I can make you two work together, it'll be fine.
Huh?
You got it?
Think about it!
What'll happen if you do that?
What will happen?
Kawasaki looks at his father, who works hard every day.
He watches his father
But the Honda Ringo is closed down by his father
Kawasaki-kun who likes to ride a motorcycle
It must be hard to watch it
He tries to convince Kawasaki-kun to follow him
Kawasaki-kun can eat a lifetime with his favorite bike
He doesn't have to go to Africa
Your father is satisfied with the after-sale
You are satisfied with the car
Kawasaki-kun is satisfied with the motorcycle
Everyone is satisfied
How is it?
I'm not used to it
Please change the motorbike oil
Kawasaki-kun, how long do you need to change the oil?
Sorry
I've finished changing the oil
The brake is getting weaker
I was looking at it
I see
You noticed
I was thinking of doing it later
I'll do it
As expected
I'll show you
No, no, no
Show me
You want me to show you
Honda Hayate's favorite
Chichikurimanbo
I like it
My father likes it
Chichikurimanbo
I like it
My brother is really interesting
Really?
I'm funny
No, no, I was praised
I said I couldn't go to a restaurant
I see
Kawasaki-kun
Eve is making dinner tonight
Did the food get better?
Yes
Please look forward to it
Eve can cook any ingredients well
For example, Africa
No, no, no
Afu?
I like Afro Namie
Kawasaki-kun
Yes, yes
Afro Namie
That's it
So you can't say you're going to Africa
Oh
Smile, smile
Let's eat
This is also delicious
That's sweet
It's pretty good
I'm happy
Well, it's delicious
Eve has improved a lot
Really?
It's good to have dinner with everyone like this
After all
It has to be like this
Hmm
By the way, Ryoji's part-time job
What!
Part-time job?
No, no, no, not that
Ba Ba Ba Barito
Barito is nice
I'm stupid on the southern island
I'm not interested
Yeah, that's right
No, more than that
But I'm very happy, Kawasaki.
So he's coming after me.
- enslaved? - No!
- Ass Octupik! Octupik! Movvvvvvv! - Oh?
- All
- Stububububububububububububububububu! - Stububububububub!
- Is this OK? - Stubububububububububububububububububububububububububububububububu!
- series? - This is quite...
Oh! Sorry a bit, Sturubing!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's go!
It looks good.
I'm sure this is OK.
Eh? Kawasaki is working for Honda Rinyo?
Yeah, it's a matter of time before he gets a job.
What about going to Africa?
I don't think he'll quit.
No way!
It's OK, Kei-chan.
Ryo-chan's plans won't work out.
Right?
I don't know what to say.
This is bad!
They found out everything!
What!?
I knew it.
What are you going to do, Senpai?
What happened, Honda?
Well, that's...
I have to go.
Guess I'll get you a car.
Like this?
I'll just go.
I'll just take my car.
No.
Jason!
It's been a while.
Since you last saw us.
Not so much!
You drove me all the way to Kakocho.
You scared the fuck out of me.
There's more?
What?
They saw our movie and didn't know when.
What? You want to ban those guys from going out?
Yes.
What's the deal?
If the shop is popularized as a place where the gangsters come and go,
this shop will also be seen with the naked eye.
It will be hard for the general public to enter.
That's a problem I can't solve.
Father!
I choose my customers.
This is how the Honda Ringo works.
If you want to run a shop, remember this.
Run a shop?
What are you talking about?
If I and Eve get paid,
we plan to go to Africa.
I don't intend to run this shop.
What?
Brother, are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Did you fool me?
I was the one who fooled you.
What are you talking about?
I didn't ask you to run a shop.
I didn't ask you to go to Africa either.
What?
Stop it, you two.
Father!
Zephyr!
Why did you do this?
Excuse me.
Zephyr.
Kawasaki-kun didn't come back.
Eve has to bring him back.
He's going to be in trouble with me.
Senpai!
Please do something!
What are you going to do, senpai?
Zephyr, Senpai!
Please do something, senpai!
Zephyr!
Zephyr, Senpai!
No, Zephyr!
Zephyr!
I can't forgive the
only the
only the only the only one
Can't you believe that old man?
I can understand if I talk to people
I don't believe in cheap humanism
But that old man is real
Those who are dating with that old man
I don't think he's such a bad guy
How about you and that old man
I'm sorry about yesterday
Please let me work again
This is the one?
Yes.
Can you fix it?
Kawasaki A1 Samurai.
No parts left.
The fork is bent.
Is this bike your own?
Yes, it's my husband's.
He liked to use a motorcycle since he was young.
But 20 years ago, he couldn't turn the curve at night.
He was in a hurry because he had a baby.
He left without seeing the baby.
He was taking care of the bike, so he couldn't throw it away.
I see.
I don't like the bike that took my father's life.
I asked my mother to throw this bike away many times.
Really?
But recently, I suddenly thought.
Is the motorcycle so good?
What did my father like so much about the motorcycle?
Then, I wanted to ride a motorcycle.
I took a motorcycle license.
I wanted to ride the motorcycle that my father liked.
Through the motorcycle, I may have wanted to touch my father.
If I could, I could ride this motorcycle that my father was riding.
Really?
What do you think?
Would you like to hear your daughter's selfishness?
Please.
It's okay.
I'll manage it.
You.
Please.
I understand.
Thank you.
I left this to you.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
It'll be okay.
Are you okay.
Yes.
Sorry.
I was too lazy to repair it.
That's right.
But.
I want to put her on this bike no matter what.
That's what I thought.
Aoi.
Work is more severe.
There are things that just don't work out.
Yes.
But.
I think it's necessary to cherish such feelings.
I think.
If you hadn't said it then, I would have been dragged into this.
Father?
Those two are pretty good.
I'm glad.
How are you feeling?
Yes, I'm almost fine.
But this carburetor won't be of any use.
I knew it.
I've asked around the manufacturers and the used shops.
But nowhere.
I see.
If only this could be fixed.
Boss! I found it!
A1's carburetor!
I see. You found it well.
It was pretty hard.
We all went looking for it.
But I couldn't help but listen to my father's request.
If I didn't, I wouldn't have any choice.
Idiot!
Here.
Yes.
Thank you all so much.
Thank you.
Don't throw all those jokes around.
But you didn't do anything bad, right?
That's horrible.
To Heyama
OK, go!
Yes.
We did it!
G существует
It's the feeling, it's the feeling
My feeling
Dad, this is the scenery you were looking at.
If I can carry my luggage
Let's go touring as it is!
Yes!
Go Honda!
Let's go!
If I can support you
How wonderful would that be?
Dad, you're great at using the microphone.
What? You finally understand.
Please, let me take you to that shop.
It's the feeling, it's the feeling
You...
No!
You're going to Africa, aren't you?
Don't turn back what you've decided once!
I'm going to bike rather than Africa.
I've decided.
No, no!
Everyone in the exhaust,
Thank you for your assistance.
Right now, me and Eve are working as volunteers in Africa
and running a bike shop.
As if to start the name of the Honda Ringo Africa branch,
I work hard every day.
Eve....
I'm sad because of my brother
but Eve is well,
so please don't worry.
But sometimes,
elephant comes to the shop.
I'm a little troubled.
Elephant?
This is...
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Don't run like a black sheep!
Yeah!
Jugem Jugem
Five slicks
Goldsmith
♪ ♪
♪ That's right! ♪
♪ I'll do it the way I want to do it! ♪
♪ The thunder of the butch-minister ♪
♪ Shedding smoke from his head ♪
♪ Running and running, a camera! ♪
♪ Of course it's an honor ♪
♪ To make a pretty performance ♪
♪ Ryosan typhoon mayto! ♪
♪ Let's get back to work! ♪
♪ We work hard and we make a good name! ♪
ращ ben Kurataka
♪ Like a boat pushed by a boat ♪
♪ Waiting for the water ♪
♪ Waiting for the wind ♪
♪ Waiting for the water to blow ♪
♪ Who is convenient and who is lots to fill up ♪
♪ Quelisk ♪
Koji, Bura, Koji, Paiko, Paiko, Paiko, Shurinkan
Shurinkan's Kurindai, Kurindai's Onpoko
Hiro, Onpoko, Naano, the super famous Chosuke!
"The End"
What's wrong with you?
Lemon stopped eating.
What? You don't want to eat anymore because you're fat?
What are you saying as a kindergarten student?
Lemon, what's going on with the super-fantasy city that relies on your good looks?
Next time, "Lemon's Strike"
I'm counting on you!
There's a turtle there.
There's definitely a turtle there.
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!