Important
Thing
To
"When
you
TV,
make
the room
bright and
look
away!"
Come
here
you
money!
I
don't
have
money
but
I'm
worried
about
you!
Look
at
the
blue
sky
and
the
white
clouds!
You
will
get
something
don't
worry
about
me!
Look
at
the
red
clouds
that
know
you
can
do
I know, I know!
If you know, then be quiet and follow me!
The Legend of the Red-Headed Girl, Teacher Kankichi!
What are you going to do with that doll?
Today we're going to have a class on traffic safety in elementary school, right?
We're going to have this doll play the role of the car's bump.
Even if it's a truck with a lot of bumps, you can't get hurt.
I see. All right, let me borrow it.
No, not yet! I haven't finished yet!
All right, all right.
Like this.
Just like that.
Like this, like that, like this!
Imagine what it would be like to be bumped into!
Give that back, Ryo!
I haven't finished yet!
All right, give it back!
Ah, the chief's head!
Chief!
Is something wrong with my head?
No, not really!
Idiot!
Ryo!
You're going to be the one to replace the broken doll!
I, I...
Listen, everyone!
Today, the principal of all elementary schools will also be here to see you.
I want you to be able to teach them something that will not be embarrassing.
Yes, sir!
Ah...
I see.
Wait, what?
I see!
I see.
Ah, my head.
Unfortunately, I can't get it to work.
I can't stop myself.
Ah, I see.
I see, I see.
Ah, are you nicely dressed, Mr. Temohikawa?
This is like...
I can only turn it into a sisters gown.
Oh?
Oh, a cute29th year is in progress.
Oh, no, it's a story from here.
Even if the traffic light turns blue on Odan Road,
look right and left carefully before crossing.
Yes, sir!
If you play on the road because there are not many cars passing by,
you may not be able to see the car coming from behind.
Be careful not to get hurt.
Yes, sir!
I can't believe you were blown off so many times.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
My coffee can!
What? What happened?
It's a chimpanzee.
No, Mio!
I know!
Come on!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, but it's really...
My handbag!
Hey, Mio!
Catch that chimpanzee!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Give me back that handbag!
You're such a fool!
Don't let it go, Mio!
Mio, hold on!
I can do it, Mio!
All right!
That's right!
I caught it!
Oh, it fell!
Ouch!
Let's go, chief!
All right!
If you give it back quietly, I'll exchange it for a banana!
That's right, you get it?
I see, I hope you get it.
I got my handbag back!
That's amazing!
You're persuading a chimpanzee!
It's Ryo-chan's specialty.
She's closer to a chimpanzee than a human.
Be careful!
I can't believe a chimpanzee that's being transported to a zoo is running away.
I don't know what's going on in the world.
That's great!
He's the one I've been looking for!
What?
You're asking me to be a teacher?
Yes, I've already received the chief's approval.
Really?
No, seriously.
If you ask a man like this to be a teacher, the students will think you're stupid.
Chief, what are you talking about?
Ryo-chan, do you have a degree in teaching?
Of course not!
Even if you say you're a teacher, it doesn't mean you can teach.
You have the strength of a wild animal.
You can talk to chimps like you've been friends for a hundred years.
I want you to learn how to express yourself.
I don't mean to teach you.
I want you to show the students what you're made of.
But I'm not a teacher.
I'm not a teacher.
I need someone like you in my school.
But...
Of course, I'll thank you.
What?
Thank you?
You're too arrogant to say you're a teacher.
I'm born to be a person who leads people.
You're in a good mood.
This is what happens when money gets involved.
Let's accept it.
For the future of Japan.
So, where are we?
We're in Tokyo, but...
Here.
Shodoshima?
Yes.
That 24-year-old girl.
No, that's a different place.
Shodoshima is in the Seto Inland Sea.
Our island is called Azuki Island.
Azuki Island?
Yes.
A small island.
To Azuki Island.
That's Azuki Island.
Yeah, it's a little island, like a bean.
Yes.
But it's full of nature.
It's a very beautiful island.
The set is this way.
I see.
There is a dormitory to sleep in. Please use that.
Yeah.
This is the classroom of Ryōtsu-sensei.
There are two classes in three years.
There are many students for the small island.
No. There is only one class for one year to six years.
Huh? Then what is this?
I like it. Mr. Golden Hair.
What?
As a special teacher for one week from today,
Mr. Ryōtsu-sensei will take care of you.
Everyone, listen to what Mr. Ryōtsu-sensei says and study hard.
Hi, fu, mi, yo. All 12 people.
Mr. Ryōtsu-sensei.
Huh?
Then I'll leave it to you, Mr. Ryōtsu-sensei.
But it's late now. What should I do?
For the time being, please play with everyone.
Play?
Yeah.
I'm looking forward to it.
Why do I have to play with them?
But, well, I have to thank them.
Well, let me introduce myself first.
Sala, sala, sala.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Mr. Ryōtsu-Sensei Kankichi.
You can't be underestimated here.
Everything starts with the beginning.
I'm a student of the TV Academy.
So, when something like this happens,
Hmm...
Listen up.
The word "human" means to support each other...
Sensei.
Huh?
That's not human. It's "Hailu."
No, I can't do it.
I don't care about it.
Hey, Koichi.
What are you doing now?
What are you talking about? I'm in class.
Hahaha.
What's wrong with them?
They're talking on their phones in the same classroom.
So, once you install it,
download the version data from the site...
That face looks like a gorilla.
Look.
Hahahaha.
Hahaha.
It's an island full of nature,
so I thought it would be more like summer vegetables,
but it's a sunflower bean.
Hahaha.
Shut up, you idiot!
Stop talking on your phone!
I knew you needed 12 megabytes.
And?
Listen to what he's saying!
If the person next to you makes your phone ring,
be careful!
You'll get in the way of your studies!
What's with this gloomy atmosphere?
Unlike the old people,
we don't interfere with each other.
What?
That's why you should leave us alone.
If we're all the same,
there won't be any conflicts.
It's not cool to sweat and work so hard.
Yeah.
The times are different.
The times.
You're making a fool of yourself.
You're completely different from the TV school guys.
No, no.
You can't get angry here.
Oh, right.
This is the standard sports of the school guys.
Get on it!
All right!
Let's play soccer together!
I can't play soccer.
How dare you!
Let's go!
All right!
That's it!
No, no, no.
I kicked too hard.
I don't care.
If you don't hurry up,
you'll fall into the sea.
There are almost no flat places.
Because it's a small island.
What?
We were injured.
We have to go straight ahead.
I can't fall.
Okay, okay.
I'm going to complain to everyone
when they get here.
It's a little scary.
I am a bad guy,
but with my power,
I can set a good course.
Then,
let me show you
I'm ready.
You mean sharks?
Trouble for such a hot-blooded student.
Help me!
I respect your teacher a bit, you childish child.
Hmm...
Ah!
Oh, this is bad.
What's wrong? You were so quiet.
What's wrong?
Oh, no, I...
You're Ryou Tsukankichi, right?
I've heard from the principal.
He said that the old-fashioned kid leader has become an adult.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm late.
I'm Hideko Takahishi. Nice to meet you.
Oh, no, nice to meet you, too.
Nice to meet you, too.
You must be tired of your first class.
Oh, no, I'm not.
The kids these days are not cute at all.
They're not bad kids.
There's nothing wrong with what the principal said.
But I believe in you, Ryou Tsukankichi.
Oh, I think Kan'kichi is better.
The principal will definitely lead the students of this school in the right direction.
I'm in the eyes of the principal.
I'm sure the principal will be in the right direction.
Takaishi-sensei.
Good luck, Kan'kichi-sensei.
Yes, yes.
Ryou Tsukankichi will accomplish his mission.
He's a naughty brat but he can't befriend me, can he?
Oh, I have a call.
Yes, Ryou-tsu.
Oh, what is it? Nakagawa?
Reiko is here, too.
Shall I call her?
Yeah.
How are you, Ryou-chan?
Are you doing well?
Oh, I guess so.
The principal is very worried.
He says all the kids Ryou-chan has taught will become like Ryou-chan.
I thought I'd be like you.
What's wrong with being like me?
Don't hit me.
The chief said so.
When I was a child,
Wait.
I see.
Let's go with that hand.
Return to Nakagawa.
I have a favor to ask.
Nakagawa's guy.
Did you deliver it to me immediately?
Ta-da!
How is it?
The latest mobile phone store.
What's wrong?
Do you want it?
I want it!
But I won't do it.
I'll make this a tribute.
Tribute?
What do you mean?
I'm going to do a survival hide-and-seek with you.
You can hide anywhere on this island.
Of course,
you can contact me by phone.
When the sun sets and you can't find everyone,
I'll go back to Tokyo quietly.
If you can't find anyone,
I'll do this mobile phone.
How's that?
What if we lose?
No problem.
It's the same as before.
How is it?
It's not bad, right?
What?
It's easy.
All right.
Let's do it together.
Yeah!
It's the same as when I was a kid.
First, take it with you.
Great success!
All right.
After 10 minutes,
let's go find it.
There are more places to hide in the mountains.
Koichi is over there.
Norika is over there.
Yeah.
Ryouchi,
you're finally starting something.
Yeah.
All right,
10 minutes have passed.
First,
from the mountains.
Let's go.
Okay,
let the
This is Hiro.
Here is the file you found.
I'm Hiro làm
Hello.
I've found Hiro.
what are you two doing?
I found Hiro.
This is Hiro.
Let's party.
What?
I found it!
What is it?
Well, that's common sense.
Now, what's next?
If you're coming from the one on the hill, you can just run to the water tank.
Let's go!
Daisuke, Tomoko, Mikke!
Why are we here?
Life is all about not going to the manual on time!
Now, give me your phone.
It's no use hiding in the water tank.
We're going to see through everything!
Oh, no!
Norika, Mikke!
Masahiko, Toshio, Mikke!
Yayoi, Mikke!
Suri!
Yoshiko, Naomi, Mikke!
Koichi, Mikke!
Shigichiro, Mikke!
Oh, no. Koichi's been caught, too.
I wonder if this is a matter of time.
Oh, no.
Ah!
S-S-S-S-S-Ss-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-s-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-
Hirooni, Daisuke, Tomoko, Norika, Yoshiko, Naomi, Koichi, Yayoi, Masahiko, Shinichiro, Toshio.
First of all, is Kenta still missing?
I don't think Kenta can be found.
He's a smart guy.
He's hiding in the sea while cutting off the mountains.
Yeah.
Shio can't leave or leave any message or contact, so he's Strange
Shio is getting crowded – what should I do??
I dropped my cell phone so I can't get in touch with anyone and I can't go outside!
If Shio comes up to the ceiling as it is…
Please, someone please help me!
Somebody! SOMEone!
I can't hear anyone screaming in a place like this.
That's strange. You can't find anyone looking for you.
Is there anyone who got a call from Kenta?
What happened?
Help! Someone!
Did you hear something?
No, nothing.
Nothing?
Listen closely.
I can only hear waves.
Yes, I heard it. It's from below here.
There's no place to hide.
It's dangerous. If you fall, you'll get a lot of sharks.
Be quiet.
It's from below here.
I found it. It's that cave.
I can't get out of here because it's a dead end.
But how can we help?
That's right. The entrance is already in the sea.
Bring the rope.
I can't get out of here.
You can't help if you don't get out of here.
Move your body more than you think.
Kenta, I'll help you now.
Someone, help me.
Listen, this rope is a life rope.
Hold on tight and let go.
Kankichi, be careful.
Yes.
Everyone, hold on tight.
Kankichi, do your best.
I'll save Kenta.
Everyone, do your best.
I was saved.
Okay. Stretch the rope.
Kenta, let's go now.
Teacher.
Kenta, look.
Now we've found everyone.
Okay.
Your legs are fine now.
Listen.
Don't be afraid.
Be brave.
You can do it.
Okay?
Okay.
Be brave.
Let's go.
Okay. Pull me up.
Kankichi.
I dropped my phone.
I thought no one would hear me anymore.
I thought no one would come to help me.
Teacher Kankichi.
Look.
There's such a big nature.
You have to make friends with nature
not just with your cell phones and computers.
If you don't acquire the strength of the wild,
you won't survive in the future.
Got it?
Yeah.
Yes.
Shizugawa and esto democracy become the Origenri Senator.
Shizugawa andisto democracy become the Origenri Senator.
Shiita Kankichi becomes the Origenri Senator.
This place was not a place to ignore or take a mosquito class.
Every teacher at school used to go to a school with many kids.
The reason for this is the fighting of kids like me.
Everyone seems to be fine.
I'm not stupid! I'm not going to waste my time again!
Ah, Chief!
This is the information society...
Hey, you!
Ah, teacher Kankichi is angry!
Hello, we came to see if you were doing well.
Hello!
Everyone!
Ah, teacher Kankichi's cell phone!
And it's the latest model!
Huh?
No, you can use the adult one.
We have the same one, too.
What?
I bought the computer in Akihabara.
I can't be late in the era.
Eh?
Senior...
You are talking about something different.
Well, even if the nature is full, the children now are different from when I was a child.
I knew it!
Alright!
Teacher Kankichi will make a lot of holes in the hole place of Tokyo!
Yay!
Let's go!
Dad!
Nemon-chan is a kindergarten child, but he likes historical dramas. Why?
The little beard of the mayor is slightly small. Why?
When he rides a Honda-san bike, his personality changes. Why?
The four years of his life are only once in a year. Why?
He doesn't lend money to the mass production company, but he can easily lend money to the tankers and fighter jets. Why?
Reiko-san is amazing.
Why?
What? I'm the head of the transportation department?
I'm the head of the transportation department?
The police is finally evaluated.
Zupan етрiferu
What a great reputation.
Next time, "Ka-Chou Ryou-Sukan-Kichi"!
Thank you.