"How to Get a Person to Love You"
When watching tv on television, please bright up your room and try to leave.
For those who don't have money, come to me!
Even I don't have one, but that worries me.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
If you don't have a job, come to my place
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red-hot cloud
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, be quiet and follow me
Come and get me!
COMPLETED
OOFARA is addicted to games!
Ah, here it is!
Damn it!
Crap!
Ah, here it is!
Good!
Run!
Alright!
I won! I won!
Hooray!
Yahoo!
Oh, it seems like you're having a lot of fun, Ryotsu.
Of course.
This week, I've been stealing the leader's attention,
and I've been doing it over and over again,
and finally it's clear.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Well, how much trouble did I have to make
to get you here?
Huh?
You idiot!
Ah, leader!
I don't like this, leader.
When did you get here?
If you're here, please tell me you're here.
Ryotsu!
You were the one who said,
"If I look away for a little bit, I'll skip work right away,"
and you've been playing games for the past week.
Well, I was just playing during my work.
I was just playing during my work.
I've been playing games for a long time without knowing,
and playing games is still a scary thing, leader.
And I'm sick of it once I get hooked on it.
and I'm sick of it once I get hooked on it.
I can't get it out of my head.
How about you give it a try, leader?
What a fool!
I don't play games, do I!
What do you think your job is, after all?
A way to survive during work?
You know nothing about work!
You'll pay for this.
No way! Give it back!
Shut up! No need to ask!
Do not bring games to the post office anymore!
Understood?
Yes sir!
This one too.
I'll take care of the games.
I will not play games during work, so please return the club.
That is my life.
Who would believe such a thing?
You don't play games all the time, do you?
I'm in trouble because adults play it and it's fun.
Idiot!
Don't do that!
It's like a mother's fight with a primary school student.
Indeed.
Please, sir!
Each and every game is a treasure chest of my memories.
Let go!
Here you are, kids.
This is a present for you.
Bring your favorite game.
Yes, yes.
Don't push it.
There are many games in order.
There are many.
Up to three per person.
This is ...
What?
Wow!
It's a game!
Well, it's mine.
This is no good either.
Huh?
Ryo-tsu!
You and that guy are giving up!
This is a great punishment!
No!
I will not play games!
Ryo-tsu!
You're not allowed to play games in the future!
You're not allowed to play games!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Grandpa!
Oh ...
Oh, Daisuke, you're here!
Yes!
I'm with my mother and Sakura.
Oh, that's right.
It's good to see you, Daisuke.
Grandpa, this is ...
Huh?
What is this?
This is a present for Grandpa.
Oh ...
I see.
This is a present for your grandpa ...
Thank you.
Thank you, Daisuke.
Well then ...
I wonder what Daisuke's present is.
Is this a game of chess?
Yes.
Grandpa always plays chess by himself at home, so this is no problem for him.
I went to the department store the other day and Daisuke said he would buy it for Grandpa no matter what.
That's good for you.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, try it, try it!
That's right.
But before I tell Ryotsu about it, I can't get this.
Hey, Grandpa.
Hurry up and try it!
I'll tell you where you don't know.
I see.
Wow, it's amazing!
It's so small, but it's a real chessboard.
Use this cross key to move the cursor.
I see.
Cursor?
This arrow.
If you choose the piece to move with it, press the B button.
B button?
It's moving!
Oh, the other piece, too!
This is amazing!
Honey, are you playing the game of chess?
Hey, shut up!
This is an important moment.
What are you talking about?
All right, the master has waited.
How do you like it?
Did you manage to come?
As expected of our master.
I'm going to the game.
I didn't notice the game.
I'm worried about the game again.
But I can't run away anymore.
I see.
Then I'll leave.
I'm in a tight spot.
I can't move.
Chief.
I've organized the Japanese.
I see.
I was surprised.
I was surprised that you started talking to me.
I wanted to put you behind me.
I could understand Ryotsu's feelings.
I wanted to be as good as him.
How did you get this?
Oh, well.
I'm not very good at books.
Okay.
Good luck.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
No, no.
Now I'm just like Ryochi.
I'll forget about the game.
Now I have to work.
At Kameari Park...
Oh, right. The corner.
3, 4, corner.
And where the opponent runs away...
5, 4, gold.
If I attack, there is no place to run.
This is it.
No, no.
I can't get away from the game.
I'll forget about it.
I'll work.
Shoking the book
One more! One more! I'll finish it off with this!
Well, this is like this...
So this is like this.
I see, I see.
I did it! I finally defeated the great man!
What's wrong, chief?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
This is dangerous.
I thought I was done, but I'm so absorbed in it.
It would be terrible if Ryo-tsu finds this place.
What's wrong, chief?
Ryo-tsu!
You must be surprised to see someone suddenly talk to you!
What should I do when I have a job?
Even if I have a job, I'll just be quiet.
What should I do?
Can't you tell the chief anything?
Shut up!
Don't just stand there and talk!
You go over there!
I'm not going to be quiet this time.
If you can go, go!
Yes, sir.
What's wrong with the chief today?
The chief is a little weird, isn't he?
He's been so calm lately.
Why hasn't the chief seen a word of Akira for a while?
W-what?
Ryo-tsu, you've been very peaceful lately.
Why is it
Ryo-tsu, you're angry.
Ryo-tsu, you're a young man!
I can't play games anymore...
I'll go patrol.
Just one song... Just one song...
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
I thought I'd patrol along with you, Chief.
What? You don't have to follow me.
You can go back to the station and work.
You don't have to say such hard things.
Let's go.
The weather is nice, Chief.
The town is peaceful, so there's nothing to say.
That's right.
Hey, Ryotsu, how far are you going to follow me?
I'll follow you anywhere.
You're my superior, so I should respect you.
Damn it.
Ryotsu, you're always like this.
Chitan, hurry up and make me shoot the next shot.
I knew it.
Chief.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
That girl is cute.
What class is she in?
I think she's in the 5th grade.
5-3-5-3-4.
I see.
Chief, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Silver.
Gold.
Blue.
Red.
Yellow.
Blue.
Red.
Looks like you're glittering.
Let go of me!
I see.
I already told you I can't play games anymore.
Will you be all right?
2. Inhabitants
4. No room.
Um, what is this place?
This is the problem.
Um, there are two missing pieces.
*Groan*
Nakagawa, isn't it time for you to go to the library?
Oh, that's right.
Reiko, you go patrol the library.
Yes, sir.
*Groan*
Chief, what's wrong?
Oh, uh, nothing.
*Groan*
I can't work at a time like this.
Chief, I'm going to patrol the library.
*Groan*
Oh, I see.
*M Dialogues*
*Groan*
Oh, oh.
The second stage will begin soon.
Are you today's opponent?
He spoke!
You don't know how much you can challenge me.
I'll make you pay for this!
I see.
So this is what the second stage is all about.
Alright, I won't lose.
I'll see you later.
What's wrong?
Isn't it Meijin's turn?
If you're impatient, you lose.
This is a piece of cake.
A psychological battle.
As expected of Meijin.
It's a nice day today.
Don't you think so?
I do.
I want to forget about work on a day like this.
I know.
I'll hurry up and get my motivation up.
I can't afford to lose.
What?
Meijin, leave this to me.
You call me a jerk?
I'll admit it if you beat me.
That's funny.
I'll be your opponent.
How's that?
You're so cowardly.
What's wrong?
How dare you call me a coward?
I'll defeat you,
and I'll get my motivation back!
How dare you call me a coward?
I'll get my motivation back!
♪
Oh...
I'm going on patrol!
Well, well...
The gold is going to be like this...
10 seconds left.
8, 7, 6...
How's this?
I'm here.
With 147 points,
Mr. Greer wins.
I lost to you.
Then I'll take the punishment.
I'll take it off.
Stop! Stop!
I'm not going to let you do that!
Don't look at me like that! It's embarrassing!
What the hell?
I didn't expect this to happen.
See you later.
Then I'll be your opponent.
Finally, it's the Meijin battle.
I've been waiting for this.
What the?
What?
If you get hurt, it's game over.
If you want to compete with the Meijin, you have to catch up.
Then, ready, go!
Why... why is the car game changing?
I've never played a game like this before.
It's the Meijin's car.
Give me back the Meijin!
Oh, no!
Damn it!
Okay, this is the last game.
Oh, the Meijin!
You've done well.
I'll praise you.
It's finally over.
It can't be helped.
If you want to get back the Meijin,
you have to compete with me in a marathon!
Marathon.
Then, run as I say.
By the way, this game machine has a speed meter built in.
If you're going to be late by any chance,
I won't let you get back the Meijin!
What?
Then, ready!
Hey!
Now, hurry up and run!
Meijin, I'll help you now!
Yes, go straight!
Why do I have to run?
Go right there!
This is the Zig-Gag Park!
Go!
Meijin...
I'm sorry.
It's going to be the final soon!
Catch it there, Geist!
You got it, Geist!
I did it!
O-Harakuro...
Hmm...
S-Shyo-Shyo!
"I'm not playing games anymore."
Ohara-kun!
What's going on? What are you doing while you're working?
You're so mature, but you're still obsessed with games.
What do you think your job is?
You're always being careful about your parents.
What are you supposed to do?
"I'm not playing games anymore."
Oh, I see.
If you think the game is weird, it's all Ryo's doing.
Damn it!
Hey, Ryo!
You were having fun, right?
Why?
Ryo is playing for games all the time.
Why are you always playing games?
Why?
It doesn't matter, but
The title of this anime is so long
This is Katsushika-ku, Kameari Park, my first appearance
Why?
Everyone together!
What?
You said there's something you don't like about lemons?
If you say that, even if you go to elementary school, you'll have trouble with your school lunch
Leave it to me, I'll fix your likes and dislikes
So, what's wrong?
Next time, "I hate lemons without eating them"
Please watch
There's a Kameari over there
Ah, there's definitely a Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
which is a
"The