"A Christmas Day"
Ryo-san, it's almost Christmas.
What Christmas?
Everyone's so excited.
Christmas is usually on your birthday,
not for a couple!
Ryo-san, you're always alone.
Sorry!
Damn it!
Give me a present too!
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and look away!
Come to me,
you poor thing!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky,
and the white clouds.
It'll be alright soon.
Come to me,
you jobless!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the fire,
and the red clouds.
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the fire,
You know it, right?
If you know it,
then come to me,
and keep quiet!
Come to me,
I
and keep quiet!
We're not good at that.
You're not good though.
That's why
you kept quiet!
You were making fun of me!
A pig!
Are they making a new one?
It's suddenly quiet.
Let's go and see.
Okay.
Senpai, what's that?
What is this?
Huh? Can't you see?
It's a helicopter for one person.
A helicopter?
That's right.
It's a shoulder-type helicopter with an even more compact auto gyro.
It's like a motor on a bamboo stick.
So it's called a "Takekobuta."
I've heard of that somewhere.
Really?
Then let's make it a shoulder-type helicopter.
It's pretty easy.
But, are you really going to fly?
If I don't fly, it's just a big fan.
But, that's not it.
In this shape, it'll rotate even a human.
It's okay.
There are many gears in the shaft and body,
and it's synchronized with the propeller's rotation in the opposite direction.
No matter how many turns it makes, the front is always the same.
That's very creative.
It would be great if you could just listen to the story.
This is the first prototype.
If this works, it will be sold in large numbers.
Huh?
You're going to sell it?
Of course.
I wouldn't make something like this just for my hobby.
Modern business is a one-minute, one-second fight.
When you get caught in a traffic jam on a highway,
and the car doesn't move at all.
Even if you have a cell phone or an email,
you still have to meet and talk to it directly.
Right?
I don't have time.
Only then,
this shoulder-copter will be active.
It's a very rare project.
Hello, everyone.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You see,
No.1 took over 1 million yen for hand-made,
but if you have a sponsor and mass-produce it,
you can sell it for half the price.
If you buy it now,
you can fly around the city like a red-haired sheep.
This looks strange.
transport mansion and so on.
If you say so, the demand may be quite wide.
Is that so?
That's right!
Okay, let's try it!
Oh!
It's dangerous!
It's impossible in the room after all!
Ah!
Okay, let's go to the park!
Hmm, you should do it here from the beginning.
Hmm, a little.
It looks quite heavy.
It's 30 kilometers, so it can't be helped because it's an engine.
Are you okay?
Please don't get lost!
Yeah, if anything happens, I'll contact you on my cell phone.
I understand.
Then you guys are in danger, so stay away.
Let the engine start!
Yes!
Engine start!
I'm going to land!
Oh, it went up!
It's a success, Senior!
See you!
I'll come around Tokyo with a test flight!
If the chief comes, I'll trick him!
He went.
It really looks like Takedonbon.
Ehehehe.
Alright, let's go, let's go!
That's it!
This is a really good view.
I'm a genius after all.
I wonder how the outside world is like.
Oh, I found a temple.
Alright, I'll make a little fun of it.
It looks fun. Let's ride this next time.
Yeah, let's do it.
It's expensive.
I'm not good at this kind of thing.
It's fine, dad.
Let's go.
It's fine if you close your eyes.
It's not like you're really flying in the sky.
The monk is just giggling.
Alright, let's have a full-scale walk in the air.
The monk is going to be surprised.
Here we go!
Mom!
It looks like something is flying in the sky.
It's rising rapidly!
It's flying at 8 o'clock!
It's going up!
I made it in time.
It's going down!
I need to think fast.
It's flying at 8 o'clock.
It's still going!
She's over there!
What's important is to find it.
Let's see, what's going on?
Let me explain the others.
One, two, three, go!
Ouch!
Gah!
Ah!
Oh?
Ouch!
Gah!
Oh, wow!
Ouch!
Gah!
Ah?
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
No call. No call.
Excuse me again!
Good-bye!
I don't know why.
Ah, it was terrible.
Oh, gas.
It's about time to supply fuel.
Oh, good.
Gah!
Ouch!
Oh, gas station!
Get me gas!
Why from the sky?
It's full of waste.
Yes, welcome!
Yes, it's OK.
Now, let's continue.
Get out of the way.
One, two...
Open the door!
What was that?
You, young sports car! Stop!
Stop!
Gah!
Huh?
The speed limit is over 30 km/h.
Hooray!
Huh?
What's wrong with you, Mr. Ryoji?
Let me rest!
Ouch!
Hey, you're in the middle of work!
It's OK. It's OK. Don't say anything harsh.
Get off!
Gah!
I'm so nervous.
Gah! Gah! Gah!
Hey, hey!
Don't be so reckless!
I'm afraid!
I'm scared!
It's because you suddenly lifted the power valve.
You're so mean.
Please let me down.
Don't be so reckless.
It's too difficult to control with one hand.
Gah! Gah! Gah!
Gah! Gah! Gah! Gah!
Engine trouble!
Ouch!
Gah!
What's wrong?
The engine is...
It's dead!
The engine is back!
Get out of the way!
Ouch!
It's the nose, my ass!
Let me go!
I still can smell the beer.
You're a big b*tch!
Let me go!
Your nose's gone!
It's the fun part!
Kentou no Oda
Let's see...
Like this...
The gasoline chiller and the maintenance took longer than I thought!
I'll have to blame the repair shop for this one.
Here we have the next news!
As a special gift, the king of the Ahorstan, Chappie, who is known as the pet of the king of the Ahorstan, has gone missing.
Chappie is a bird with an IQ of 380, and can speak human language.
Even in the New Book, the name of the bird is displayed, and the king of the Ahorstan is in great shock.
There are rumors of a kidnapping by anti-king.
The king has said that he will give a reward of 100 million Ahorstan dollars to the person who protected Chappie.
This is it!
If you use the shoulder copter to capture this bird, you will receive a reward and become a great advertisement.
You will also get a sponsor!
Hey, Chappie!
Come out!
Where are you?
I'm asking you a question. Do you know this bird?
I don't know!
What bird is this?
Have you ever seen this bird?
I'm sorry, but have you ever heard of this bird?
It's a bird that can be easily found.
Well, we can't find it that easily.
Mr. Chappie, take care.
Thanks.
But it's not as convenient as a cartoon.
No way.
Wait a minute. This is the top of the chimney.
Teko-chan!
Ita! You're Chappy, aren't you?
I'm Sadie.
Eh? What?
No, no, no! I can't catch that! I can't catch it!
What the hell are you doing?
It's a trap!
It's a trap! It's a trap!
Teko-chan! Teko-chan!
Damn it. You're going to let me run away, aren't you?
Wait!
Where did that bastard run off to?
It's there!
Teko-chan!
Damn it.
This guy!
The world is pink.
What is this?
Thief! struggles!
Thief...
Thief...!
Wait! Wait! I'm...
Thief!
Thief...!
Where is the Thief?!
Where are the Thief...
The Thief...
Thief...
Thief...!
Tmap!
T limo!
Ba...
Trap!
Thief...!
I'm going to that place!
Alright, let's go!
Your majesty!
What the hell is this?
Toho! Toho!
What are you doing?
Ryotsu! What are you doing in such a place?
No, that bird is the best and the prize is...
What are you talking about?
Come down here, you fool!
Chief! You fool! You fool!
What?
What are you talking about?
You're so mean!
Hey, stop it!
Ryotsu, you're so mean!
Chief, that bird is not me!
You're lying!
Birds don't talk!
It's true!
Say something!
Don't be stupid!
You're stupid!
Come down here, Ryotsu!
Hey, wait!
Ryotsu, you idiot!
Don't you dare to live like this!
It's the death sentence!
It's not me!
Damn it!
You said you wanted to die and you ran away!
I won't forgive you!
It's here.
And here!
What's this?
A rock!
You're abusing the Quetta!
Hey, wait!
You touched the rock, and now you're in trouble!
You slapped your hand over here, back to the quetta!
It's too much!
And what do you have there?
A fare!
I'll take care of it!
"The quetta is here!"
And who were you talking to?
The quetta is here!
Please, I'm going to save the quetta!
Where did he go?
He shouldn't be looking for me.
Ryo-san! Ryo-san!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You're not going to tell me?
I'm not!
Shut up!
You're making me angry!
Ryo-san! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Damn it! Wait for me!
How dare you insult me!
This way, Ryo-san!
Hurry up, you idiot!
Shut up!
You're going to be killed, Ryo-san!
If you let me say that, the engine will start!
I'll catch you this time!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
This way! This way!
How did you like that?
You can eat me or whatever you want!
I'll do whatever I want!
This is bad! This is bad!
What's bad?
Your life is going to be in danger now, right?
But I won't forgive you!
Ryo! Ryo!
You're a tyrant! You're a tyrant!
You're a tyrant!
I'm not a tyrant!
What the hell are you talking about?
You're lying!
I'm not lying! I'm not!
Even if you lie to me, I won't let you get away with it!
Damn it! Wait for me!
Stop!
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
You're going to get me!
Be quiet!
Oh boy!
I'm in trouble!
Ryo! You're wrong! You're wrong!
Huh? That's...
That's the A perseveranceu king!
Are you serious about this?
Ryo! Look after him, princess!
OK, I got it!
For the money to come back to me, I'll have to help you in return!
Will you?
Alright! Let's go!
The submarine is waiting for us at sea.
The plan is a success!
Hahaha, Ido!
The strange helicopter is circling around.
What?
That's Chapin!
Chapin, this way, this way, this way!
What the hell!
Chippy!
I got it! Leave it to me!
Ah!
Take this!
What? What? What?
Ah!
I'll get you!
Get down!
Alright!
Now I can pull the machine gun!
You, get into the helicopter and break the king's rope!
What about the submarine?
We'll manage!
That's it!
That's it! That's it! That's it!
This way! This way!
Come on!
Damn it!
This bastard!
Now, Chapin!
Come on!
The helicopter!
Oh, Chapin!
Hey, what are you doing?
This way, this way!
G-G-Get up!
G-Get up!
Chapin!
Take this!
The ferry!
Can't way!
Take it!
Take it back!
Awesome!
You did it!
Chic!
You did a great job, Chapin!
Gyo General!
You're great!
Well, well.
I bet you know what to do.
The next morning, the next day, the next day...
The next day, the next day, the next day...
Mr. Ryozu, you finally found Chappy.
I'll give you a reward.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Heh, heh, heh... That went well.
I'll take 100 million Aho Standard Law.
My future will be pink!
Alright, Mr. Ryozu.
100 million Aho Standard Law.
Nuhaha!
Is this 100 million Aho Standard Law?
Heh, heh, heh...
By the way, how much is 100 million Aho Standard Law in Japanese yen?
It's about 5,700 yen today.
Hmm, 50 million is not bad.
It's 5,780 yen.
Huh?
That's ridiculous!
You worked so hard!
Even if you say that...
Today is the first day...
The first day is about 17,301 Aho Standard Law.
100 million Aho Standard Law is about 5,780 yen in Japanese yen.
Hey, say that quickly!
Ahaha, Ryozu.
Too bad! Too bad!
Ahaha, hahahaha...
Hey, you bastard!
Don't laugh!
Ahaha, hahahaha...
It's funny, it's funny.
Hey, don't laugh!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you, Ryozu!
Do it nicely!
You idiot, Ryozu!
I'll kill you!
Shut up!
Ryozu, don't laugh!
Stop it!
Roger that!
What are you doing?
You're not doing anything.
What are you all doing?
Save me!
Move over!
Get out!
No use!
Oh oh, what are you doing?
Why did you scare me?
What happened?
It's notù
I arrived at the home with Chappy.
Iq 380 was not just a bird.
Indeed, I want to give someone a drink with a red nail.
What's wrong with Senpai?
I don't see you for a while.
News from overseas.
At the top of the Alaskan Mountains,
A snowman-like creature was found on the top of Mount McKinley.
This creature has a strange voice that says, "I am Ryo-tsu."
Ryo-chan?
Senpai, it was blown to Alaska by a jet plane.
It looks like Tanpopo's seed.
Perfect. Leave it alone.
It's better to end your life as a snowman in Alaska.
It's better for the world and for people.
I am Ryo-tsu!
Dax!
Someone, help me!
After the rain, someone called me.
I walked back and forth.
I asked my mom.
When an elixir was drawn,
I thought I had a new feeling.
I felt an unusual feeling at that time.
So I took this charge of "Agedo3"
And I walked only in black.
Everyone was a child once.
But everyone forgot.
I forget
The politician with a great face
The blue aunt in the eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
New invention, Jumbo Manju!
If you eat it, it will be as big as you think it is!
It feels good to look down the river!
Hey, how big will it get?
This is too big!
Do something, Tondemo Professor!
Next time, Ryo-san will get bigger!
Please look forward to it!
Well, if you look outside
there is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!