Akari Takahashi
♪ When you watch TV ♪
♪ Light up your room and take a peek ♪
♪ It's after the rain ♪
♪ It's as if somebody's calling you ♪
After the rain
I looked back and walked
I was drawn to my mother
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I gave it to her
I tried to walk on the black tile
Everyone was a child once
But everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can see everyone
There is a wall there
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
To be continued
S.F.!
Aliens have been attacked!
Ryo!
What is this?
This is...
No!
It's Ryo!
He is definitely a senior!
I...
I have been so embarrassed!
I have never had such a difficult feeling!
I don't like it!
This is not me!
Look!
In the world, there are three people who are similar to me!
This is definitely my similar!
You idiot!
Look at this!
Ryo, who is happy to earn money in the field,
I'm riding it with a polite name!
No!
There must be a same-sex alliance among those three!
There is no such thing!
There must be no such thing!
There is only one idiot in the world!
You are the only one!
There must be no one else!
You are the shame of the Japanese police!
The source of the evil!
The enemy of humanity!
The devil!
Look!
Accept that the person in the photo is yourself!
Come on!
Admit it honestly!
Get rid of everything and relax!
That is me!
You are so stubborn!
It's not me!
I couldn't confess my guilt, but it is clear that you have committed a crime.
So as a punishment,
I will give you a day off tomorrow for your duty.
What?
Boss!
Don't be so rude!
Tomorrow is the day of the Kamen Rider, which I have been waiting for!
Besides, tomorrow I have a lot of plans...
Shut up!
I won't let your useless plans get in the way of my plans!
Boss!
Go away!
This is the fuel that can be obtained through the Earth.
Go to Sennai to procure this!
Understood!
However, it is not good to keep it as it is!
Have to change its appearance!
Copy the earth-man!
Hey, Reiko,
tomorrow we'll manage without me.
And now you are somewhat tympered.
I was supposed to take a break.
I don't mind, but it's not good to go against the director's orders right now.
If you make the director angry any more, you might not be able to go to work on holidays.
That's right, senpai.
There's an event at the shopping street tomorrow, so I haven't overstepped my limits.
Ugh!
You took a picture like this!
You're free to do whatever you want in front of the working hours!
I think it's based on the position of a police officer.
You need to have a common sense as an adult before you become a police officer.
Who do you think you are?
You say whatever you want!
This is a sign of my love of horses, the expression of my forgetfulness.
Who should I be ashamed of?
I'm proud of myself for that day!
Hallelujah!
Huh?
Ryo-tsu!
Stop it! Stop the car, now!
Okay!
Huh?
Ah...
What's up, manager?
You changed your mind or something, and are you trying to finish what we talked about earlier?
Ryo-tsu. Are you at the Alberto police station right now?
No limit, you don't know what you're talking about right now.
So you've been there this whole time?
Yes, I've been working by being very serious all this time.
So, since you're here...
Chief, you're off tomorrow.
I might be a bit tired.
I'll be back early today.
The chief suddenly said something I didn't understand.
Huh? Mr. You?
Hey, everyone.
What are you talking about?
Did you change your clothes?
That thing earlier was the stuff for tomorrow's night.
It was pretty good.
Anyway, please take care of the thing tomorrow.
I'm sure Ryo will do well.
What's wrong with him?
Mr. Onomawari!
It's terrible!
The girls' school has a new recruiter!
A new recruiter?
I'm sorry.
Where is the new recruiter?
Oh, it's me!
Oh, no!
Who was it?
Oh no! I'm a police officer!
Wait! How did you become so similar to me?
And how come you could be so fast?
You bastard!
How did you become so similar to me?
Explain yourself!
Chok chok!
Shut up!
I picked it up from the trash can.
And then I copied it.
Copied?
What the hell are you?!
I'm an alien!
I came to Earth because of the UFO's fuel shortage!
I'm looking for this! Help me!
This is the fuel of the UFO?
Yes! Otherwise we can't go back to the stars! Help us!
You can change your appearance freely?
Yes!
Anytime!
Anywhere!
Anyone!
Transform!
Isn't that amazing?!
Of course! We're all aliens from the past!
Don't use half Japanese! I don't get it!
We're all aliens from the past!
You should practice your words!
You should practice!
Listen, it's hard to get this fuel on Earth. It's a rare item!
Oh, lucky!
So you should be disappointed!
But if I cooperate, we might get it.
Really?
Instead, you should cooperate with me.
Reiko-san, did you read the newspaper this morning?
Huh? What?
Look at this!
Ah, the article about the UFO's shortage.
I read the newspaper yesterday.
Apparently, there were a lot of reports from the observers.
But in the end, they couldn't find the real thing.
Kei-chan, do you believe in UFOs?
Reiko-san, don't you believe it?
Well, if there are aliens, I want to meet them at least once.
I think Ryo-chan is familiar with this kind of story.
Ah, you believe in it, right?
Huh?
What's wrong?
I wonder what happened.
Ryo-chan seems to be serious today, like a stranger.
I think the one who was scolded by the chief yesterday answered so much.
But it's a little creepy.
I hope nothing bad happens.
It's convenient to have your own copy.
I'll keep him on Earth as long as possible and use it all my strength.
Stop it!
Hey, Pramoya!
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you.
Ouch!
If you don't hurry, Noriko Sueyoshi will come.
What are you talking about?
I promised you yesterday.
Promise?
Anyway, Ryo-san,
You have to help me with the stage for the Kameari Shopping Street Festival event.
Yes, sir.
That's not me!
I've checked that you're not on the stage.
Come on, hurry up!
No, that's not me!
Stay there.
Thank God!
I'm in such a hurry, not you!
Sir!
Pick me up, please!
My time's up!
My time?
That looks awesome.
Merch, you have to be on the stage, too.
Ah.
That sounds like a good opportunity!
I'm looking forward to it.
Can I ask you a favor?
Yeah?
What do you need?
Well then, let's go and see what we can do.
Okay, this is great.
We were sick of it, but thanks to this we got to experience that fantastic performance of the Kamairi Shotengai!
No success!
That doesn't make any sense!
I'm really sorry.
Ryo-chan, did you get any rest?
You have a very light at the end of the day.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
What?
Huh?
It's the other side.
Is it the inside?
Right.
Ugh.
Hot pot, ramen, dumplings!
And change the money, too.
Ryo, you're back.
I'm not going to change my mind.
Sueyoshi can't come.
What do you mean?
What? Sueyoshi Noriko can't come?
Yes.
The drama in the morning has been delayed.
Is that true?
Yes.
The drama was delayed because of the delay in the book,
so it became a mess.
That's terrible.
The event in the shopping street was very popular.
There were many customers looking for her.
If she doesn't come, it'll be a riot.
I'm sorry.
It's terrible.
What should we do?
This is a good chance to make money.
It was a good chance to make money.
It's over.
What should we do?
We have a problem.
We have to make money.
What's the matter, Ryo?
Actually, Sueyoshi Noriko has a problem.
Is that true, Ryo?
I wonder if you could give me 30% of the original price.
30%?
Of course.
No matter how much money you spend, you can't ask for it.
It costs a lot.
So, the amount is the number.
30%?
How much do you need?
The other day, I got a big problem.
What are you going to do?
I don't mind, but...
100%?
That's too much.
That's too much!
Then, I'll take it.
OK.
Listen, this time, you will be this guy.
Look closely.
Look closely!
You will see it!
You hear me?
This is all to get the fuel for the UFO.
Do you understand?
Why...
No!
Why is your filler standing still like a statue?
-You're right. -That was great!
Thank you, Ryo!
-This is what I promised. -I see.
Well, I won't hold back.
If you have any trouble, I'll be here for you.
-Well done! -Did you find the fuel?
-I did. -You did!
I did.
Well, I did find it.
But the fuel you're looking for is very expensive on Earth.
You can't buy it without a lot of money.
-Do you understand? -A lot of money?
I'm an idol of Takahai.
I'd like to have a bottle of Takuya Hoshikawa's Sokkuri in 30 minutes.
Here you go.
What on earth did he start?
It's not that easy.
Takuya Hoshikawa and Takuya Hoshikawa.
Takuya Hoshikawa.
What should I do?
Riko, please calm down.
Don't be panic. He's Takuya Hoshikawa's Sokkuri.
What?
I don't think he's Sokkuri.
He's just like him.
From the front, from the side, from the back.
If you ask him...
He's just like him.
The client is a high school girl.
She wants you to walk with her to the center of Shibuya.
Come back in an hour.
Come back.
Hello?
I'd like to invite Ken Shimura to the kid's birthday party.
He's a young man.
If you're a young man, you'll have to pay extra money.
But you'll also get a strange old man for the service.
It's very good.
You'll get 25,000 yen.
Ken Shimura!
Not someone you'll meet.
I see.
So you are the Sokkuri.
Got it.
As you wish, please come back otherwise the price will be fair.
Matsutaka!
Trapi!
Gita!
Amida Baba!
Komayomachi!
Takechampan!
Butcher!
Money in the bank?
Golden Harf by EVA!
Good! Good! Good!
The reservation is only for 3 months.
I see. Then, on that day...
Yes, Nerima's Edanaga-san.
Yes, I understand.
Hey!
The company's secret is in the room.
Don't peek.
I understand.
But Ryo-chan,
is it okay to be such a big guy?
If Chief Ohara finds out, it'll be bad.
That's right.
This time, I'll really be fired.
Fired?
Shut up!
This is not just a money-making.
It's a help...
No, it's a help.
What is it?
Nothing.
Go ahead.
Yes, I want to date with Max's Nina.
Yes, yes.
I want to date with Ikemure-san.
Yes.
I want to fight with Chixon Gracie.
I want to date with Natsukawa-san.
Yes.
I want to have a skit with Masayuki Watanabe-san.
I want to date with Komia-san.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
Yes...
Yes.
Hey, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Even aliens get tired, don't they?
Let's call it a day for today.
Take a bath and enjoy yourself.
But we have to hurry.
We can only stay on Earth for 60 hours.
60 hours?
If we go over that, our spaceship will return to the planet.
So we have only two hours left.
Two hours?
Why do you say such important things so quickly?
I don't think it's that hard to get that fuel.
Hey, hey, get a grip.
Hey!
Fuel...
Don't worry. I'll go get the fuel.
But the money...
It's okay. I'll do something about the money.
But this is still...
I'll cancel the rest, so don't worry.
Fuel...
Fuel!
What are you doing?
It's proof of our friendship.
Friendship, huh?
It's okay. If you call a friend in the UFO, the rest of the work will be done immediately.
What? You have a friend?
Call a friend!
UFO!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, no!
Farmers, the
Hey! Where are you? Hey!
What the...
Do you have any fuel?
Oh, it's you. I bought some fuel and brought it here.
Thank you, Ryo-tsu.
This isn't it!
Huh? There are 18 carbon batteries in here!
No, this isn't it!
You know, this card says there are 4 carbon batteries.
Carbon and carbon won't change batteries.
You just need to connect them.
This isn't it! I can't change it!
I don't care what you say. There are no carbon batteries.
Why not? I can't change it! I can't change it!
I told you to use carbon!
I'll do it!
Ryo-tsu, you liar! I can't change it!
I can't change it!
Why don't you just give up?
Carbon batteries are cheap, so 4 of them will be about 200, 300 yen.
I bought 18 of them.
And I can get them easily.
But I had to go out of business or I ran out of money today.
So I ran around here and there.
I have to thank you.
Who's the one complaining about you?
It's cheap. Two or three hundred yen.
I can get it easily.
Liar of the 4!
Help me!
I won't forgive you!
I'm so happy to be able to date you.
Good luck!
What's that?
I won't forgive you!
You're not going to play anymore, are you?
Help me!
What's that?
That voice is Senpai, isn't it?
It seems like someone is chasing us.
Now I'm scared.
Everyone, it's Ryo-chan!
Please help me, Mr. Ibu!
Let's go!
Don't just goodbye!
What's going on here?
What are they doing?
They're aliens!
Why are they all scared?
It's a long story...
Let's go!
I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
I-I'm dead...
Hey, Ryoutsu!
Help me, Butch!
But if you don't know who the real senpai is, help me, Okaka!
I-I'm the real one!
I'm the real one! I'm the real one!
I'm the real one!
I don't know who the real one is, after all!
Stop it! Stop it already!
So the story that the UFO crashed was true, after all.
That's right.
Ryoutsu is so popular by himself, but...
I'm getting dizzy.
Let me know when the real one is decided.
If you do, let me know.
No way!
Please wait, Butch!
The town began to move again as if nothing had happened.
No one cared how many people I was going to be.
They didn't care, and they didn't care how many people I was going to be.
Stop it!
Hey, are you serious, Pramoya?
You're retiring for the last time this year?
Pramoya, that's why I,
that's why you don't want me to give you flowers!
Next time on Bonus Gathering War!
I'm counting on you!