"The End"
♪ When you watch TV ♪
♪ Make the room bright and look away ♪
♪ After the rain, as if someone is calling ♪
♪ I walked as I looked back ♪
♪ I reached out to my mom ♪
♪ I felt a strange feeling at that time ♪
♪ So I walked on the red and black tiles ♪
♪ On the red and black tiles ♪
♪ I walked on the red and black tiles ♪
♪ I looked back at everybody's faces ♪
♪ Everyone was a kid once, but now they have forgotten ♪
♪ Even a politico with a tough face with an angry face ♪
♪ Even an aunty with blue eyes, turn and look at those corners ♪
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Dad, what is that place shining?
It's Tokyo Stadium.
It's a new baseball field.
The light of Tokyo Stadium is clearly visible from the train.
It was built in Minami-senshu, Arakawa, as the home of the 大マイオリオンズ in June 1937.
It costs 3 billion yen and has a capacity of 35,000.
The light of the American league is very bright in the small town.
It was a field of light.
This is the light of the Tokyo Stadium.
But why did you bring it?
The Tokyo Stadium had a pleasant memory.
It was when the history was destroyed in the last ten years.
Stand clear, everyone!
Hey, Kikichi!
It's dangerous!
Stop it!
Hey, Ikkura! Get off!
I'll break it anyway, so just one is fine, right?
Kikichi!
You didn't turn it off?
I'm sorry!
After all, it's the source of the light of the light.
It must be selling high.
Certainly, there are many enthusiasts at the auction of today's baseball goods, so it will be very expensive.
It's a memory, right?
Are you really going to sell it?
It's tomorrow's meal rather than old memories.
It seems that time has not advanced since a while ago.
Oh, that clock stopped when I came.
It's 10:05 now.
What? The auction starts at 10 o'clock!
Oh!
Hey, idiot!
Put the clock together!
Senpai!
Kikichi!
Are you okay?
The light bulb is safe.
I didn't expect that Senpai would be fractured by hitting the car.
It's a memory, so I'll sell it.
It's a memory.
That's right.
Kikichi, why are you so hard on me?
Don't add to it!
This is not your fault.
Senpai!
I'm just sorry!
It hurts, but I'm really sorry.
Do you know it?
It hurts a little, but keep my love.
Don't do it.
That's right?
I said do it.
Have you met him before?
No, this is the first time.
I see.
Ryo-san, are you really injured?
As you can see.
What are we going to do about today's match?
I see. It starts at 3 o'clock.
What's going on today?
It's a match against PTA.
I was supposed to be there in their parents' place.
But I can't.
But you can't.
Ryo-san, you promised to hit me with a homerun.
Don't worry. I'll keep my promise.
Here I go.
Sorry.
Senpai!
Are you okay?
You can't do that.
I know. They'll understand.
A man promised once. I'll keep my promise.
Both of your legs are fractured.
What's that?
I'm a man who hit a homerun with a fractured whole body to keep my promise with this cheeky kid.
What's that warrior's name?
Hyuga Kenji.
Hyuga Kenji?
I don't know.
An old player?
Yes, a long time ago when you were born.
There was a stadium called Tokyo Stadium in this place.
Hyuga was a professional player.
What?
So the Tokyo Stadium we talked about earlier was here.
Yes.
It was the stadium that gave us lots of dreams.
It was a rescue that gave me a dream
Dad, faster!
It's okay, the night is until 9 o'clock
Wow, it's bright
Will everyone get together?
Hey Gin-san, you're early today
I was approached by him
Two tires
Hurry up
Hey, which one do you want?
Wait a minute
Taima is the champion
Yay
Mr. Asakusa, I've made a seat
You're here at the right time
Hozu, I'm counting on you
Go, Kankichi
That's right
Flare, flare
Daimai
The missile boom
Good, good. Enomoto
Good, good.Enomoto
Escaping from the beginning
The first-class team has come out.
What should I say?
Mr. Shimura, let's say that it is a hit that has been supported.
Now, the hero of the Orions is entering the game.
4th, third, Hyuga, number 0.
At that time, Hyuga Kenji was still young.
He was a slugger who was entrusted with the missile shooting 4th.
Fly away, Hyuga!
Defeat Hankyu!
That's right!
Fly away, Hyuga!
Adachi on the mound.
From the set position, number 9, Nagelos!
Hyuga Kenji has entered!
3 runs, homeruns!
I did it!
Thanks to the boss, I got an extra point.
It's a reward yakisoba.
Oh, thank you.
There's also cider.
How about a bento?
I did it!
Thank you for your always support.
Oh, I was called by Hyuga.
Hey, Kankichi, eat a lot.
That's your dinner.
It's your dinner.
Yeah.
Damn it, a change.
I'm going out for a while.
Actually, there was another purpose for me to come to Tokyo Stadium.
No, rather, this book was the real purpose.
Hey, are you lost?
Oh, nice.
It's just a book.
I see.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're here.
Me, too.
Let's go to the stadium together.
Yeah.
Let's go.
This is so fun.
Thanks, Kankichi.
Thanks.
Thank you for the baseball card the other day.
I found a lost child again by chance.
Thank you for your hard work.
No, I'm happy if you can help my sister.
I will call a lost child.
Mr. Yamada from Mikawa Island.
The child, Taro, is lost.
Please come to the office below the stand immediately.
It's a good voice to hear.
It seems that your heart can be washed.
Here you are.
Candy.
No, thank you.
Wait quietly until your father comes.
Yes.
Here you are.
For Kankichi.
This candy is also the best.
Her name is Yayoi Kurihara.
She used to play the game in Tokyo Stadium.
Her voice is not only beautiful, but also beautiful and kind.
I went to the stadium to see her.
Well.
She is like your daughter.
I couldn't find her for once.
So I took her to Kansai to see her brother.
Her father found out and hit her.
Oh.
Of course.
Hey, what's the story of the home run?
I don't care about the story of the woman.
Don't be in a hurry.
She has a big relationship with that legendary home run.
The new home run
Here, Kankichi.
Wow, Huga's autographed ball.
Huga said thank you for always supporting me.
I can brag about the cross 12.
I thought I'd give it to you now.
That's right. It's almost time.
What?
Yayoi, I'm going to quit this season.
I'm going to quit this season.
Why?
I'm going to get married.
With who?
With that person.
Huh?
Huga?
Number 4, third, Huga, number 0.
I'm sorry, Kankichi.
I was going to say it sooner.
What's wrong with you, Huga?
He did it!
It's a comeback.
Good job, Huga.
You're playing well.
On that day.
I decided to Years out of this position.
What!?
Episode 5
Number 4, Third, Hyuga.
Number 0.
Let's do this, Hyuga!
It's a reverse!
If that kid doesn't show up, it'll be a big deal.
She hasn't shown up lately, has she?
Yeah.
It seems she liked you.
She was shocked to learn that you were getting married.
You're so stupid, Daimai.
It's a 8-loss draw.
Hyuga's not a hit again.
How about we go to the Tokyo Stadium this evening to get some katsu?
If you want to go, you can go on your own.
I'm not going.
But I've decided not to go again.
You were so loud the other day that you said you'd take me every night.
Daimai, you're so...
Hyuga, you're so...
You're going to cheer me on even if I die, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
Here.
It's Hyuga!
I told you I don't like Hyuga.
That Hyuga is coming to the store!
What?
He's serious.
You're Kankichi, aren't you?
W-Why do you know about him?
Because he always supports me on the bench.
And I've heard about you.
Do you have time?
How about a football game?
Why don't you try it?
You're throwing a good ball.
I can see that.
I don't want to be a professional baseball player.
I don't like professional baseball players.
Look at the ball.
Kankichi, how are you?
I haven't seen you lately, and I'm very lonely.
Show me your happy face again.
Yayoi wants you to bless our marriage.
Can you accept our marriage?
I'll make you happy.
Can you believe me?
Even though you didn't score 20, you're a professional baseball player.
How can I make you happy?
All right, I'll do it.
The last match will be held in Tokyo Stadium in two weeks.
It's the last match for you, Yayoi.
I'll make you hit the home run in that match.
What?
That's impossible.
Yes, it's impossible.
It's absolutely impossible.
It's absolutely, absolutely, absolutely.
It's a promise between a man and a man.
Yes, it's a promise between a man and a man.
Kankichi?
I saw the trash.
I won't admit it if you don't hit me.
Yes.
What?
Ahh!
Hyuga Kenji was injured for 2 months.
What are you going to do, Kankichi?
This is the last match of the year.
Are you going or not?
I'm going.
You go first.
I have to go somewhere.
No, just 5 minutes.
Hyuga is still in a bad shape.
Yeah.
Oh, Hyuga!
No way...
Now, the 9th round is coming to an end.
It's a big deal.
It's a two-out, but it's a full-time game.
The score is 3 points.
If it goes out, it's a comeback.
Daimai can finish this season with a white star.
But...
The order of the game is terrible.
The next batter is the pitcher, Sakai.
If Hyuga was here at a time like this...
Damn it!
I've been chasing him all this way.
Coach!
Please use me.
Hyuga!
But...
But you're in good shape.
I'm fine with a big hit.
Please, coach!
I got it.
Is it a big hit here?
But...
I'm sorry.
The weak point on the bench...
I should have played well, but...
It's a stand-off.
Yes!
Daimai Orions' batter, Sakai...
Pinch hitter, Hyuga...
Cebang Go, zero.
As I expected.
This is a surprise.
In this situation,
A supposed to be hospitalized...
Hyuga is coming!
What a surprise.
A miraculous recovery, let's say.
But...
The opponent pitcher has suddenly turned in from the 9th hole.
The ace of the South Pole, Stanker.
Will he be able to defeat the dark-haired Hyuga?
Play!
Stanker.
From the set position, the 9th hole.
He threw it!
Strike!
The 5th ball is in the middle!
Hyuga can't make it!
The 1st ball is a game.
I knew it.
It's the end.
Everyone!
Kankichi.
Hyuga is standing in the corner with his body in pain.
Don't cheer him up here!
When are you going to cheer him up?
Let's go!
Play!
Hyuga!
How many times do I have to say it?
Play!
Hyuga!
How many times do I have to say it?
Play!
Kankichi.
I won!
Hyuga!
The stand is a tremendous support.
Can Hyuga respond to this voice?
Stanker!
He has become the 2nd ball!
For Yagai.
For Kankichi.
That's what I'll do.
I'll get him.
Never forget that.
I'll be sure to do it for Kankichi.
See? You too!
Amazing! Amazing!
I've never seen such an amazing home run!
It's a promise made by men.
Sis!
Yayoi!
Mr. Detective!
Thank you! Thank you!
You're the best, Mr. Hyuga!
Yay!
The home run of Mr. Detective Hyuga
was a legend at a distance of 200 meters.
He was an amazing guy.
Your father was Mr. Hyuga Kenichi.
Why did you say my name?
It came to my mind when we first met.
You looked just like Mr. Hyuga when you were young.
You were a slugger who was in the 9th grade of college.
Then will you be a professional?
Like your father?
Certainly, I've been invited by several clubs.
But I don't have the confidence to be a legendary batter like my father.
You idiot!
Your father was amazing not because he made a legend.
He risked his life to keep his promise.
To keep his promise with this cheeky kid.
A legend is a result of doing your best to do something.
Hey, Mr. Ryo!
Everyone is here!
Okay, the game begins!
Ryo!
Mr. Ryo, please let me play this game.
I'll do my best to do a home run!
Okay, it's a promise!
Not only me, but Junpei, Kappei and Nakagawa and Reiko.
Yes, sir.
Go for a home run!
It's a promise!
Good!
Amazing!
As expected of a college-class swagger!
I do it!
We did it!
It's his turn.
He is the right one for the owner.
Besides, the treasure is important.
We should hold it carefully.
♪ ♪
♪ Even the annoyance that continues today ♪
♪ I'll get rid of it with annoyance and cleanliness ♪
♪ Every day is No Problem ♪
♪ If you cross the hot shower ♪
♪ Recover your energy with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ Every day is No Problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ On Monday ♪
♪ 1, 2, 1, 2, Go Go Go ♪
Huh? Are you going to the police station under Ueno?
Leave it to me. That area is my hometown.
What is this police station?
Why are dogs and cats...
...near the police station?
What are they doing there?
Next time on The Post Office Diary
Thanks for watching!
♪ Over there is the Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, I'm sure it's the Kameari ♪
♪ Everybody come to our town ♪
Thank you!