When you watch TV
Make sure your room is bright
And try to stay away
From the other
"The Greatest Dinosaur"
A day comes
And the sun
Shines over the river
And the stone
Flies into the shoes
I'm going to
Go to the gym
I wonder if I'm going to
I was laughed at
Even if I try
To cheer up
I can't win
There may be
Unuko
In that
Gap
Sleeping Gap
Sun
If you
I realized I lost my happiness
Because I'm such an idiot
Maria, let's go on a date!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, senpai!
Be happy, Maria-chan!
I'm so jealous!
Ryo, spring has finally come for you!
Listen, you can't talk about Maria no matter what happens!
I know, chief!
Ryo, I'm too happy to be scared.
I agree.
Ryo...
Maria...
Maria, what's wrong with you?
Oh, my!
Men are the best when they are wearing six-legged.
Man?
Oh, no!
Maria is a man!
Ryo!
I'll never leave you!
Stop it! Let me go!
Help!
What?
What's this? A dream?
What are you going to do this time?
Go to hell!
Good morning, Ryo-sama.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
*Gasp*
*Groans*
Well, it's ready!
Ryo-sama, please have breakfast!
*Cough*
*Groans*
Oh!
Here you go!
Thank you!
*Groans*
Here you go, Ryo-sama.
Wasn't the miso soup too thick?
No, it was just right.
How was the pickles? Did they suit your taste?
I made them myself.
Yeah, they were delicious!
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad! I'm so happy that you're happy!
*Groan*
No, you're not!
Why are you in my room?
I can't go.
I can't live with you.
Of course you can't!
Why?
Why can't you go, Ryo-sama?
Because...
Because you're a man, Maria!
*Groan*
You're so cruel, Ryo-sama.
Why is it so cruel that you don't let me live with you?
*Groan*
Actually, I've talked to Komachi-san and Naoko-san.
I've been with Ryo-sama for over a year now,
but he's still not getting along at all.
But how can he understand my feelings?
Hmm, so you really like that primitive man.
Of course, I do.
When I think about Ryo-sama,
my heart almost breaks,
and it's so painful and painful.
It's bad for Maria,
but we don't know it at all.
Hey, what's so good about that man?
Everything!
He's so manly and has a lot of life!
His legs are so short and his face is so big!
He's short and thick,
Can you please be serious?
Please be serious!
I'm seriously worried!
How do I make him decide?
I guess we have to be more orthodox.
Orthodox?
Like cooking for him.
Or sewing his sweater.
Or we could force him to do something.
Yeah, like "pushing-and-pushing-girlfriend."
"Pushing-and-pushing-girlfriend"?
Maybe he'll forget that Maria is a man and start to roll around.
Roll around?
Yeah, like "pushing, pushing, pushing."
Yes, I'll try it!
That's what it's all about.
They're just blowing in nonsense!
Lord Ryo, I'm a bit of a coward, but I'm counting on you!
Here, your lunch.
Have a good day!
Grandma's
Then, why don't you make up your mind?
What do you mean, "make up my mind"?
Of course, I'm ready to get married, Ryo-tsu.
Even the director doesn't know that!
You know that, don't you? Maria is a man.
Oh, Maria is more like a woman than a real girl.
That's right, Senpai.
It's so strange to see Maria's way of living with her seniors.
I wonder if anyone who's willing to come to Ryo-chan's place to get married will show up next year.
I'm not saying it's a guess.
No, this is your only chance.
Ryo-tsu, don't worry about the details.
I'm thinking it's time for us to get married.
I'm not kidding.
I don't have a bad feeling about that.
Oh, Ryo-san.
Hey, Plum.
We're finally married.
What?
Who said that?
I-I think it was a girl from Minipot.
That's Naoko Komachi.
They're a bunch of useless people.
Thank you.
Ryo-chan, I heard you got married.
That's why I said no!
Ryo-sama!
Maria, you're so mean!
We're bound to meet Ryo-sama here.
We're bound to meet the god of love.
What? You're exaggerating.
You're exaggerating.
What?
You're married, aren't you, Ryo-san?
You're making me blush.
You're not Maria, are you?
You're such a waste.
You're such a waste. You're such a waste.
You didn't do it, you're wrong, Plum.
Yeah. I didn't do it, I know, but .
That's so dramatic!
Maria, come here and see what I'm saying.
Yes, everyone.
How are you?
Hello, I'm Ryo-san.
inhabit me happily.
Maria, do you have the right to hug him?
I'm so sorry, ryo-sama.
I was so happy about that.
By the way, you don't mind sukiyaki?
Sukiya- inspect?
What?
Ryo-sama think me so, I'm really satisfied with that.
So I go there and order sukiyaki.
I bought some good stuff.
Please come home early today.
Sukiyaki?
You haven't eaten for a while.
Get me a beer.
Okay.
I'm waiting for you to come home, Ryo-sama.
Don't hug me.
Okay.
I feel like I'm getting into Maria's pace.
Hey, you're always together in the morning.
Miss,
Where do you like this guy?
Leave him alone and come with us.
I'll take you to a fun place.
You're so naughty.
You're a waste of a man like this.
You little brat!
Shut up!
Ryo-sama! Don't look!
Get him!
You!
You little brat!
Give him to me!
Don't get so angry!
Ryo!
I'll beat you up.
Get him!
Ryo!
She's my wife.
Shut up.
I'm just saying that I like her.
Yeah, that's right.
I mean, you're a towe.
Wanna know what I mean?
I said we're not a couple!
I've been in the office for 3 hours.
I don't like it at all.
It's all Maria's fault.
I have to tell her.
I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like it.
I don't like it.
Ryo-sama, welcome back.
Would you like to take a bath? Or do you want to eat first?
I've prepared sukiyaki.
Sukiyaki! Meji! Meji first!
Yes!
Sukiyaki, sukiyaki, I'm so happy!
Ryo-sama, before that, I'd like you to take a look at something.
What is it?
I've been thinking about wearing it with you.
Stop it. You can't wear something like that.
Why not?
It's strange for men to wear something like that.
Men, men, Ryo-sama, that's all.
Don't say such a small thing.
It's not small!
That's right, Maria. You are a man.
You have a lot of power.
Thanks to you, I've caused you a lot of trouble.
Trouble?
That's right.
It's a big trouble.
I understand.
If you say so, I will never use this stupid power again.
All right.
Then, if you use that stupid power again,
I'll have you leave this place immediately.
All right?
I understand, Ryo-sama.
Stupid power is never...
Stop!
I told you not to use stupid power!
I'm sorry, Ryo-sama.
But the cockroach...
I won't listen to excuses.
Get out of here right now!
Ryo-sama...
I don't know if it's because of your stupid power that everyone is bothering you.
If you say get out of here, get out of here!
I understand.
Then I'll leave.
Ryo...
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you too.
type,
I wonder if the ambush strategy worked.
Maria, are you there?
Yes, I'm outside.
I finally found you.
Maria.
Reiko.
Can you help me?
Maria is here.
I'm glad.
What is it?
The locker is old, so I want to move it.
Maria, it's easy, right?
Yes.
I told you not to use your stupid strength!
I can't do it.
Maria.
How is it? It looks like a figure, right?
It really looks like you.
You have a good eye.
What is it?
Do I look like that guy?
Shut up!
This is Detective Otsuka, the drug investigator of the main office.
Drug investigator?
Yes.
You look like a drug dealer who is on a mission.
Please help the investigation.
I want to block the trading site and make the smuggling organization a big hit.
Listen, Ryo.
You're the only one who can do this job.
I'll give you a small new machine.
I'll leave it here for 24 hours.
If you can find the trading site, please contact me immediately.
It's already closed.
What?
The information we have is under the protection of JR.
The password is GONZALEZ.
GONZALEZ?
GONZALEZ.
It seems that the contact with the members of the organization was successful.
The next day
Chief, this is Mr. Yamashita, the new member of the group.
Nice to meet you.
Well then, let's go.
Hey, that guy.
Hey, turn the car.
The other day...
I'm sorry, Mr. Iguchi. I have something to talk to you.
Actually, the other day...
Hello.
Hey, Saeki.
By the way, Mr. Yamashita.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I knew you were around at that time.
It was a pity.
I just got in touch with the real Mr. Yamashita.
Damn it!
Yes, something like this.
He found out about it.
He is in danger, let's step in.
No, I can't do that.
They are just above the order to contain the transaction.
No, I can't do that. They are just above the order to contain the transaction.
No, I can't do that.
Don't worry about it.
- - I
see. You're a good looker. You
're a fool. Huh?
These are
the places we can think of as the trading places. If we
do this, we'll have to kill them all. But if
we go to the main gate, we'll find them. We'll
do it ourselves. - Okay?
- Yes!
- - Maria!
- - I
think it's all right because it's Ryo-chan. - - That
's true.
All we have to
do is finish this guy off. Let's do it
after we've fried him a bit more. - - It's
pretty quiet.
- - Maria,
we can't do this. We can
't. - - R
yo-
sama hates us for being so hard on him. That's right.
I wonder if this
is the right place. - - Huh?
is this
thread?
- - This... - - It
's the
made for
Ryo-sama. - - Ryo-sama,
you're
wearing it. - - Are you sure?
yo-
chan, I've taken off the sweater under the jumper to let us know. - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
*Dun Dun*
Mr. Yamashita, are you tired?
Not yet.
Big brother!
Kumi-chan!
What's up?
A woman with great power has entered!
Woman?
I can't beat her! Let's run away!
Alright, let's take care of her.
*Dun Dun*
*Kumi-chan!*
Mr. Ryo!
Where are you?
*Dun Dun*
Get with him!
If you get any closer, I'll kick him out of here!
Now, right now!
Maria, stop the helicopter!
Shut up!
Maria...
Ryo-sama! I'm sorry! I used the power of a fool that you hate!
Maria, I forgive you! Use your power to knock that helicopter down!
Yes, Ryo-sama!
Fire!
You did it, Maria!
If you keep doing that, you'll end up as a perfect couple!
R-Rego, you idiot! What are you talking about?
Because you were really worried about Ryo-chan!
I won't ever leave Ryo-sama again!
Maria, you did a great job for Ryo-chan.
After all, the power of love is so strong.
That's right! My power is not the power of a fool, but the power of love, Ryo-sama!
What are you talking about?
I mean, don't hug me! Get away from me!
I'm a man! I don't have that kind of power!
In front of the power of love, that's a trivial matter!
It's not a trivial matter!
I'm not an alien!
You're a pervert!
What, is that so?
It's just that I'm an alien.
From now on, I won't let you do such a thing!
Maria!
Ryo-sama's house!
♪ Power is the most powerful thing ♩
♪ Gather up everyone ♩
♪ Come here ♩
♪ It's like a dream, the final energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday, draw the universe ♩
♪ If you stand on the ground, the stars with a mask will come ♩
♪ Draw a circle ♩
♪ Draw a circle by yourself ♩
Yaaahhh!! What the hell! I've turned into a panda!
Is this your line of work again, bat-ass old man?!
I don't know if the heaven police or something, but without that spear,
you're nothing!
Next time on .