Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the river ♪
♪ I kicked a stone ♪
♪ And flew to the end ♪
♪ To the head of the gym ♪
♪ That was jogging ♪
♪ And laughed at me ♪
♪ As if I was still alive ♪
♪ I'm fine somewhere ♪
♪ I'm fine wherever I am ♪
♪ The city is kinder than the night ♪
♪ The crows are singing ♪
♪ The moose is singing ♪
♪ The yakitori is singing ♪
♪ From the
Next Episode
It's so good!
Thank you for the meal, Reiko-san.
You're welcome.
You guys shouldn't skip patrol and drink tea like that.
But it's cold outside.
It's a little bit nice, right?
You're riding a mini-pat.
It's true that it's getting really cold lately.
It's winter already.
Speaking of winter...
Right, speaking of winter...
Ishi-yaki-imo!
Here it comes!
Chachachachachach!
Delicious, delicious potatoes!
Here you go. Thank you.
Mister, can I have one?
Me too!
Yes, yes. Just a moment, please.
What? Ishi-yaki-imo?
I'll go buy some, too.
Why do women like yaki-imo?
It's a typical winter sweet.
It's rich in fiber and it's cheap.
Huh?
Our bio-development factory is in trouble because we've taken too many sweet potatoes.
Should we donate them to the office?
What?
Wait a minute! I'll get rid of those sweet potatoes!
A fierce battle! The Night Market War in front of the station!
Hey, Gimpo-ji!
What is it, Mister?
What is this?
What is it? It's an octopus.
Don't ask me that!
I'm asking you what this cut is.
A cut?
We sell the biggest octopus in Japan.
That's too small.
I'm sorry!
Do it again.
You'll lose customers' trust.
Yes, sir!
I remember that the company where my brother worked was destroyed by customers' complaints.
Yes.
It was said that it was a fraud.
I realized that at that time.
Business is best done on a daily basis.
Excuse me.
Two takoyaki, please.
Yes, I'm home.
Hey, wait a minute!
Thank you for coming every time.
I'll come again.
That's why I'm selling you a pack of takoyaki for 400 yen today.
That's right.
Ferrari!
What?
You know that?
I was a dealer before I got a job as a restoration worker.
One day, we will...
I'd like to be able to ride a Ferrari.
Ferrari can't do a yatei.
Yakiimo!
What was that?
Ferrari's Yakiimo Yatei?
No way...
But it's true, the back of the Ferrari was a Yakiimo Yatei.
It was a Ferrari.
Yakiimo!
It's a Ferrari!
The car just now was going around.
It's delicious, it's delicious.
Nakagawa, you're going too fast. Lower the speed.
It's impossible to keep going in the low.
I'll tell you if you don't come soon.
Here it is.
It was a Ferrari!
It was a Yakiimo Yatei.
It's impossible to keep going.
Bro!
Are you okay?
What kind of car is this?
Running while dropping the firewood?
I feel like I'm back.
I'll give you some advice.
Bro, the opponent is a Ferrari.
I don't know what kind of rich people are on it.
I don't know!
Are you afraid of the rich and doing takoyaki?
Fire...
Hey, hey!
Running while burning a car on fire...
What kind of rich people are on it?
What's wrong with that?
Sir.
I'm sure there's no law prohibiting the road traffic law to run while burning a car on fire.
I agree.
But it's impossible to burn a Yakiimo in my car.
It's too fast.
I see. It can't be helped.
I'll stop the car around here and start a business.
That's right.
What?
You can't start a business?
No, not at all.
Please do your best.
What's wrong with the police?
And it's Ferrari.
I don't know.
But I can't do anything about it.
Well, well.
The world's first Ferrari Yakiimo shop is open today.
Welcome, welcome.
It's a delicious Yakiimo.
Give me one.
Here, two.
Yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
Cool.
Hey, don't swear at people who don't buy.
How about another one for the ladies?
Yes.
The customers are amazing.
Well.
All my customers have brought it.
Even when they're in the middle of writing.
This happens when you're doing business.
I can't stand it at times like this.
I can't stand it.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I'll take three.
Yes, three please.
Please take two.
Thank you so much.
The next day.
I don't have sweet potatoes anymore?
Well, yeah.
I mean, I still have a lot yesterday, right?
That's because the person in charge of the company is trying to donate a lot to the children of the country who are suffering from disaster.
And the children are now on the plane.
What a story this is.
No, it's not.
It was just about to happen.
You should give up on the idea of doing business on the street.
Nakagawa, you have several laboratories in your company, right?
Don't you have any other places that have left over potatoes?
I heard that there are still octopus left in the marine research team of the marine research institute.
Octopus?
It's not baked potatoes, it's takoyaki.
It's not baked, but it's takoyaki.
What?
No, it's takoyaki.
You're not here today, are you?
Ferrari's baked potato shop.
I'm not here.
I'm here.
I have...
The largest octopus in Japan.
As long as I have this, I won't lose anywhere.
Brother!
Yes?
What's wrong?
Look at that.
Huh?
A takoyaki with a whole octopus!
Don't... Don't joke around!
If you have a whole octopus...
It'll become this huge!
How do you sell that?
How do you eat it?
I can't do that.
It's an unvaccinated word.
I'll complain about it.
No!
No, no, no!
No, no!
No!
No, no, no!
I know how much you're a liar, but...
If there's one octopus in a whole octopus,
I think it's a bit exaggerated.
Do you want to say it's a bad display?
No, it's not that bad.
There's one octopus in a whole octopus.
Look at this one.
It's small in size, but it's got one whole octopus in it.
That's a good octopus.
Yes, yes, there really is one octopus in it.
I know.
That's what a police officer does.
It's almost a fraud.
You're going to perform?
You can't discriminate against me to win in front of the station.
If you ask me, it'll lead to revitalization.
Are you really going to do this?
It's okay. I'll definitely take it.
Hey, waiter! Thank you for coming!
You're welcome.
I'm coming today.
You know, those police officers...
Don't worry about it.
I'm here to make takoyaki all day long.
Gimpachiri, it's on fire!
You're going to burn yourself!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Takoyaki is more important than anything else.
Huh?
Fire!
That police officer...
Hurray! Hurray!
Yeah! Come on, baby!
It's a fire dance!
Oh! Takoyaki!
Yeah! Takoyaki!
Yeah!
Mmm! Takoyaki is delicious!
Hey! Fire dance!
Yeah! Rainbow!
Yeah! Yeah! Everyone, buy it!
What's that?
It's just an insect. Don't worry about it.
This way, this way!
Oh! They're really doing it!
- Turn the camera! - Yes!
Um, what's this?
To the station.
There was a special call that said there was a takoyaki shop that makes takoyaki while dancing fire dance.
Yeah, this will work. Let's go!
Yes!
As expected of the TV station. The information is fast.
It's okay to be a little wild, so cut your chin.
Yes.
Buy takoyaki!
Buy more!
Three more!
Five!
Buy more!
No! Thank you!
Thank you every time!
Thank you!
Ah, the TV station! Finally!
Okay! Nakagawa! Increase the fire power!
Senpai! It's dangerous to increase the fire power any further!
I called the TV station! I have to do it more flashy!
But!
Hey! Fire!
I'll do it myself!
I'll show you a special show from now on! Fire!
Fire!
Senpai!
It's amazing!
You do as expected. It has power!
Uh, isn't it round?
It's iku takoyaki!
Engage!
Brother, that police officer...
He told me not to worry about it!
But he's coming this way!
What?
Damn!
I'm sick and tired of Takoyaki!
Okay, it's done!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Now, let's try it!
It's delicious, Ryo-chan!
You're as good as a professional!
Right?
But, usually, the Taiyaki has anko in the tail, right?
This doesn't have it.
No, no. The tail is the same as the corn in ice cream.
You eat it after the sweet one and then you eat it again.
Yes, it's refreshing and delicious!
You're right!
It's a Taiyaki set that was sold in the shopping street, but it also has flour and anko as the ingredients, so it's pretty authentic.
I made it!
Speaking of anko, it's a problem that we can't get azuki beans in our bioplant.
What?
If that's the case, leave it to me!
Hey, Silver-Hair!
What is it, Aniki?
What is this?
What is it? It's an all-purpose green onion.
Don't ask me that! I'm asking you what this cutting method is!
Cutting method?
You didn't cut it.
Oh, sorry!
When you cut an all-purpose green onion,
you should use your left hand as a tool to cut it.
I'm Izumikaru Aniki.
If you can't do this, you won't be a good carpenter.
As expected of you, Aniki!
I've been doing this for 25 years.
Aniki!
What's wrong?
There's a strange car.
What?
A Taiyaki!
I thought a disturbing policeman had disappeared, but it's a Taiyaki shop this time!
What are you going to do, Aniki?
All right!
I'll teach you how to do it!
You're so cool, Aniki!
Give me an old man's Takoyaki!
Welcome!
Hey, wait!
Don't take it off because it's heavy!
Yes!
Bye-bye!
Thank you very much!
Wait, Aniki!
This business is the first customer, so...
All right, let's go!
Don't underestimate me!
Two Takoyaki, please!
Yes, yes, I'm home.
This Takoyaki is delicious.
Right?
Takoyaki is different.
Thank you very much!
Aniki, when are you going?
Wait a minute.
If I don't cook it now, I'll have to wait for the customer.
That's true, but...
I'll make it a little thicker.
It's pretty detailed.
All right, let's go!
Yes!
Two Takoyaki, please!
Here too!
Yes, yes, I'm waiting.
What's this?
There are too many people, so I can't go forward.
It's okay.
Go back to the store and bring me the soy sauce can.
Soy sauce can?
Yes, Aniki!
Is that okay?
All right, take a good look.
Yes!
Get out of the way!
Who did you refuse to work for?
The police officer...
What?
It's you again!
Do you need anything?
No, please do your best.
What were those two doing?
I don't know.
What's going on?
When he comes again...
Are you ignoring him this time?
If I ignore him, he will definitely have an influence on us.
Like the last time...
He's like that.
Then...
He's been like that for a long time.
When I left the company, you were fired.
The work that we started...
We're finally on track.
You can't be crushed here.
Aniki...
It's war.
I'll use all my know-hows and crush you!
Aniki!
-The next day-
Alright, I'll make some money today too!
Senpai?
What's up?
The takoyaki place across the street is a Taiyaki place!
What?
The tasty, tasty custard cream is the best!
Taiyaki Hitosugi 25 years, it's the best taste!
One Taiyaki please!
Me too!
Eh, wait!
Thank you very much!
Boss, you did a great job!
I'll beat that police officer to death with this!
Custard cream?
How about that!
But it's on sale!
Alright, I'll take that!
I'll take this too!
Nakagawa, get the custard cream!
Yes!
Hey, wait!
Thank you very much!
Huh?
From now on, we will also sell custard cream-like Taiyaki!
And it's sweet, and it's half calories!
Even the size is smaller!
It's half calories!
It's smaller, and it's easier to eat!
Oh, thank you!
Hello, customer!
Welcome, welcome!
Thank you very much!
We got a customer!
Don't copy us!
I'm the police officer of the city!
What are you going to do, boss?
We're here to increase the variation!
Huh?
This looks fun!
I want to try it too!
What?
At this shop, we have various types of Taiyaki, such as chocolate, melon cream, strawberry jam, and so on!
Please try it once!
Chocolate!
That's funny!
Come on, let's go!
Let's go!
Did you come with that kind of hand?
I can increase the variation as much as I want!
I'm going to lose!
From now on, we will sell 100 types of various types of gourmet Taiyaki, including the world's first caviar, drift, foie gras, etc.
It is a limited sale today, so please do not miss it!
Caviar!
It's a limited edition!
Wow!
This is definitely...
It's caviar?
At this time, how do you spend money is different.
I hope there is no problem, brother ...
I don't have any money, so I have no wisdom!
The
開τ
*Round 2: Rice
*Round 1: Rice
It's sparkling!
*Round 2: Rice
The world's first rice fried dish!
There's a lot of ingredients in it!
*Round 2: Rice
You made it with a great skill!
It's just a rice ball, right?
It's shaped like a Taiyaki!
Senpai, what should we do?
Senpai!
Yes, don't rush!
Don't rush!
Take a break!
Senpai!
This is the real battle!
The world's first Okonomiyaki Taiyaki!
Pour the sauce and eat it!
It's just Okonomiyaki!
Then this is...
*Round 2: Rice
The world's first Taiyaki!
We're back to the original takoyaki shop!
No! This is the real thing!
It's a Taiyaki Tempura!
*Round 2: Rice
Is it good?
I don't know!
The audience is the test subject!
*Round 2: Rice
Bring them to a deserted spot!
Yes, sir!
*Round 2: Rice
This was dangerous!
That was close.
That car is heading that way.
It's coming.
*Round 2: Rice
This is it!
He jumped now!
F-","F-F-Front! " AAA
AHH! At
least his death didn't kill him. Are
you alright, Boss? Thanks
for giving us a bit of trouble. You
're soаты, bet way. But
I never knew what would happen to us.
That's right.
What should we do, Senpai?
Let's jump into the river and put out the fire.
No, it's a pool. Jump into that.
I got it.
That color is not a pool.
Yes! Now we can put out the fire.
Senpai, but this deck...
It's oil!
Damn it!
The food stall is already empty!
After all, the most important thing is to be stubborn.
Yes, that's right.
Damn! The people of the shopping street!
To take away my bonus,
it's a cowardly thing to hire a professional debt-taking army!
Every year, you and I
have fought the fair and square bonus debt-taking war!
Next time, "Bonus Debt-Taking War 8"
Thank you for watching!