의
Is that you, Chief Special Investigation Officer Chonmage Deka?
I have no grudge against you, but could you look at me for a while?
W-What!
Subtitle by Subdivers - Genki Bakuhou or Tempest
So much in there, huh?
We can't do nothing about it, scent-mailer Tiger Dekasan.
Who are you?
Whaaa!
What're you doing?!
Hope!
Advanced Mustang
prepare yourself!
Roquette Kingdom!
This time they're all out of the way!
Stand up, you special detective.
I will avenge you.
Daihard 2: The Lowest Battle on the Land
You are so talented.
You should grow up soon.
Chief.
Good morning.
Oh, it's a cactus.
Did you start growing cactus?
I got it from Hiromi on my birthday.
Is it a gift from your daughter?
I guess so.
What is this smell?
As expected of you, Chief.
It smells good.
Oh, this is a pine mushroom.
This is a crab.
What?
Oh, it's amazing.
It's a crab and pine mushroom.
What happened to so many?
Dad sent me.
But I can't eat them all by myself.
So I give them to you.
These are my gifts.
I thought it would be better to eat them together.
You guys are really good people.
I'm so happy to have good friends.
Don't cry.
I haven't eaten anything here before the holiday.
When you finish your work, let's eat together.
Then let's have a hot pot.
Hot pot?
It's luxurious to have a hot pot with a pine mushroom and a crab.
Let's invite Honda and Maria and have a hot pot party.
Sounds good.
If it's decided, I'll go and tell them.
Hey, Ryo.
I'm so excited for this kind of time.
I wonder if pine mushrooms and crabs are okay like this.
Yeah.
That's a lot.
I'll eat and eat and eat tonight.
I bought Chinese cabbage and green onion.
I bought tofu and shirataki.
I bought konbu and chicken.
I borrowed a pot, a chicken dish and ponzu from Ryo.
You borrowed it?
You're like a thief.
I'm sorry. It's a day off.
It can't be helped.
Then boil the hot pot and take the soup with the konbu.
Okay.
By the way, Ryo.
What did you prepare?
I didn't prepare anything.
Idiot!
Why are you saying that to Honda?
I'm a human being in this depot.
I won't let anyone who doesn't give anything to the pot.
Don't be so mean.
I was looking forward to lunch.
If you want to eat, bring the ingredients.
Okay.
I'll bring them.
It's very good.
Please take에
I don't have money.
No?
Don't you want to eat?
You don't eat.
This is all.
You don't have money.
I don't have money.
You don't drink up.
No money.
He's a genius!
A cactus.
I don't have any blue ones, so I'll take them.
A frog!
I'll take this one, too.
You're late, Ryotsu.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Ryotsu, did you bring the ingredients?
Of course.
Here you are.
What is that?
I got it from the pachinko store.
No, it's not that.
I can see something in it.
It's a frog.
You're in trouble because of this.
Frogs are on the menu at the Izakaya.
What are you doing?
It's a dark pot.
A dark pot?
I put it in, so I'll take it.
A frog?
You put it in?
You told me that you don't need to put anything in it.
Well, I did, but...
Then there is no problem.
You didn't put anything else in it, did you?
Don't worry.
You can eat it because it's a pachinko-based product.
But...
Well, you ate it, you ate it.
It's the beginning of the dark pot party.
It can't be helped.
Then, let's eat in order.
Starting with Maria.
Okay.
What's wrong?
The rule of the dark pot is that you must eat the food that you put the chopsticks on at least once.
I understand.
It's sweet and delicious!
I didn't put anything sweet in it.
Then that's the pineapple can I put in it.
I'm glad.
Okay, next. Nakagawa.
Y- yes.
Here you go.
Oh, this is a pine mushroom. It's delicious.
Reiko-san, this is the best!
I'm glad, Kei-chan.
He's a lucky guy.
Okay, next is my turn.
What? It's a frog!
Why do I have to eat it?
It's because you're not doing it right every day.
Eat it properly. It's the rule.
I understand.
Okay, next is my turn.
Ouch!
Oh, that's a hairy crab.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm different from Ryotsu and I'm good at doing things on a daily basis.
The hairy crab is kind of...
What is this?
It's no good, Chief. You have to eat it properly.
It looks like a vegetable.
The key is not a vegetable.
Then, how about this?
Hey, Terai! Turn off the lights!
Ah, yes.
Tch.
Tch. Tch.
Tch. Tch. Tch.
Tch. Tch. Tch. Tch.
This is a cactus, isn't it?
I put it in there.
Does the paying for pachinko bring that?
No, I picked it up from there.
What? Ryo, I thought it was in front of thecombination.
Ah, I see.
It's not good, Chief.
It's not good?
Cactus is a proper food in Mexico.
It's not good.
-Not that... -Nakagawa, enough!
Ryotsu! You put my important Saboten in the pot!
Eh? No way! This Saboten is...
The Saboten that the chief gave to Hiromi!
I-I'm sorry, chief! I didn't know at all!
C-Chief...
"The Adolf Dinosaur"
It was an idiot!
The public only included Chiyoko one of the today's specials!
You are fired!
You fell in love with Saboten just by putting it in the pot?
Rather than somebody who worked together for years,
raelions are more important than subordinates!
That's right!
Hey...
Ah! I get it now!
I'm sorry to work under a boss like you!
Stop it as of today!
-What? -What?
No way...
Ryo!
-Senpai! -Ryo!
Senpai!
Ryo, the boss is also reflecting on what you said.
He said that if you lower your head, you can shave off your neck.
But he said that's fine.
So...
You're too late.
Senpai, please don't be so stubborn...
Shut up!
You're a boss who's cuter than your subordinates.
You should lower your head!
Stop it!
Ryo!
If you take the police officer from Ryo, what will remain?
What?
Ryo, if you become the boss, I'll quit the police too!
Maria, I appreciate your feelings, but this is my problem.
Anyway, I'm going to bid bye to Hashizoto as of today.
Have a good time, everyone.
-Ryo, Senpai... -Senpai...
Senpai, Ryo.
...
drugs
What's the last thing that will remain when
I take the police officer from Ryo?
What's this?
"Love the sea and protect justice."
Who read this? Poseidon.
I'll put it in my pants.
I'm the captain of the police force on the water.
I'm the sea's Dozaemon.
A mischievous Yashiki Kappo is the trademark of Dolphin.
It's you, as I thought.
It's been a while, Ryotsu.
You're always so long.
By the way, what are you doing here?
I heard you became the head of the park before the launch.
You're pretty quick-witted.
There's no place to go or stop.
Well, well.
Then come to the special police station.
Bang!
To the special police station!
You guys live in a place like this?
It's like a hotel.
The 5th floor is now a dormitory.
Dormitory?
How many people are in the special police station?
Six people so far.
Six people?
Only six people live here?
This is the Yua-buro.
What?
This is the sauna.
There's even a sauna?
There's also a game center and a karaoke room.
Oh, right.
Not only this floor, but there's also a movie theater.
It's a big difference from Niko Niko Ryo.
We special police officers are the elite among the elite.
You don't look like an elite.
This is the training room.
There should be a
Special police officer,
and one black eyed girl.
The Sovereign.
I'm coming, Sanjiro.
Ryoji,
it's been a long time.
Why are you grabbing the door?
What's the matter?
T- this music is --
Moonlight Power
It's them again.
The power of this powerhouse.
Envision the power of this powerhouse.
I'll show you the power of the Moonlight Deca.
Big Dinosaur, you're too fast!
Sorry, it was the short version.
Let me explain.
The Moonlight Deca can show 7 special abilities by changing its costume.
Then I...
Hey...
The Moonlight is my energy!
The master of the Moonlight, Moonlight Deca!
I'm also Venus Deca!
I'm back, Kenzan!
Why can't you guys appear normally?
I'm going home, after all!
Wait!
I really need your help.
Let go of me! I can't be of any use to you!
The Special Police Department is being targeted.
The Tiger Deca, the Mustang Deca, and the Chief's Chonmage Deca are all in the hospital,
with serious injuries.
Then I can't stay here.
I see.
Can you help me?
What?
I knew it, Ryotsu.
I knew you'd say that.
I didn't say that!
Are you listening to me?
I'm going home!
Then,
will you bow your head to Chief Ohara and go back to the station?
I can't do that!
Then, go to the Special Police Department.
We'll welcome you.
I got it.
I'll be in trouble for the rest of my life.
I see.
We'll have to organize the moving luggage today.
We'll greet the Chief tomorrow.
What?
Chief's Chonmage Deca is in the hospital, isn't he?
He's a new chief.
What?
Did he get a new job from the head office?
No.
He got a job from my department.
The criminal's research rate is 100%.
Me too.
Maybe it's a dolphin.
Maybe it's a moon.
He's the one who set up the gold-stone tower that couldn't be accomplished.
Who is he?
You know him well.
I know him well, too.
I see.
Good morning, everyone.
Chief.
Good morning.
What?
Is Ryotsu late again?
That idiot.
Well...
Oh.
I remembered he's casually resignation.
Chief, please forgive him.
And make him work here again.
I'll do.
What?
You can be quiet because he isn't here.
This is how the old department should be.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah...
The End
Good morning.
Chief, I've brought the Chief of Police.
The Chief says, "Good job!"
Ah! It's Damon!
He says, "Don't abandon me!"
What did you say? Hey, what on earth is going on?
You're the one who's in trouble.
When I was working as a special detective as a pigeon-puppet department,
at that time, I used pigeons to watch over Chief Ohara,
and I made him collect the money he was losing.
Well, well.
At that time, Chief Damon used the techniques you used to collect information,
and used the rich capital of a nobat, of hundreds of thousands or even millions of dollars,
to become a subordinate and to collect information
that was more powerful than the police.
So, I've created a network of subordinates.
Thanks to that...
Ah! It's a bird! Someone, catch it!
The End
What did you say?
Now, he even has a beautiful wife and has a self-sufficient life.
Isn't that amazing, Dengemon?
It's like he's made a name for himself because of me.
He said, "Don't make it easy for you to come."
What? With the dove's body?
Stop it, Ryotsu.
It hurts! Stop it, you idiot! Stop it! Stop it!
He said, "I won't forgive your grudge."
I understand. I understand, but stop it! Stop it!
You guys! You're making such a big face for that dove!
Don't you understand?
Even if it's a dove, the chief is still the chief.
Even if it's a special detective, we're going to Miyazuka, too.
What? What? You're really good at understanding things.
Mr. Ryotsu!
Huh?
W-What?
The chief said this.
This?
"We're going to hire you as the teacher of the Hato Poppo, so keep it in your mind."
What? Are you kidding me?
You're not going to watch under that dove!
Ryotsu!
Let go, you big dolphin!
If you ruin the mood of the chief of Dengemon here, you won't be able to stay in the dorms.
You have to be patient here.
That's good.
Gah...
Dengemon...
It's the man who made me mad!
I'm going to show him how good I am!
Mr. Ryotsu!
I'm so proud of you!
I'm so proud of you, too!
Now, listen to this.
You can do whatever you want.
That's right.
I'm happy for you, too!
This is the best choice!
We're in a coffin!!
Damn!
*Gunshot*
* foarte fine Gunshot*
I am Champion!
Rocket Fueler!
I want to make a new dojo,
He's much better than Kaipan, Dolphin, and Gekkou Deka.
Boss!
Hmph.
I won't forget the grudge of losing to Kaipan's pervert move and being put in jail for five years.
I'm the same.
I used the shark to revenge Dolphin and the dolphins.
I used this transformation move to defeat Gekkou Deka.
They're a reliable bunch.
Now I'm thinking of a way to take down those three detectives at once.
Until then, keep burning the flame of revenge.
Emergency! Emergency!
Special agents, please gather in the strategy room.
I'm Hato Poppotekami Nanai, Ryozu Kankichi.
I've arrived!
The pistol gang is standing in the way of the financial company.
There was just a request for a special agent to come with us.
Where did the criminal stand in the way?
Wow! It's all set up!
It's so high-tech!
This is the culprit.
He's standing in the way of this building's fifth floor.
There's a river. I'll go.
No, if it's the fifth floor, we can enter through the sky.
Leave it to us.
This is a land case. It's my turn.
The chief said if we have Gekkou Deka and Hato Poppotekami Nanai,
the case will be solved easily.
All right. Hato Poppotekami Nanai.
Let's go.
Team Hato Poppotekami Nanai
The
That was a word in a long sentence!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Give the money to me!
Stand up. Go!
What is this?
You fool!
You idiot! Are you going to make me a scarecrow?!
He's going to jump in!
Let him go!
Roger!
You idiot!
I did it!
The Yamauchi Family
The Special Investigation Department is very active...
I wonder if he's worried about Ryo-chan.
Don't be stupid!
Who cares about him?!
But, Chief...
If we keep this up, Senpai will keep getting involved with the Special Investigation Department.
That's right.
We're getting along pretty well.
Y-You think so?
I just remembered something.
I'm going out.
Damn it!
He's using me to make him a scarecrow!
He's giving me a lesson!
What's going on?!
The snake's legs are loose, and he's hanging wider!
Don't be overreacting!
Junji!
That really was ailsome!
Just now you were overreacting, so I have to apologize!
Then do me a favor and apologize.
I was not exactly overreacting at all.
But I'm not sure I'm not gonna make a change yet.
It may be that if I apologize, I might not be able to get out of here.
What are you doing here?
Well, I...
If you want to go back to the office, I can talk to you.
Who said that?
The chief of the special police department is kind to his subordinates, unlike the chief of another office.
What?
I'm relieved that the troublemaker is gone.
Oh, really? That's good.
I can't go back to the office, so I have to make myself comfortable.
Hey, chief of the special police department. We've arrived.
Why are you in a hurry?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I won't do anything to the chief.
What's with that wing-waving pigeon?
It's the chief's wife.
What? Are you married?
Did you get married?
Why were they fighting?
The chief had lipstick on his body
with another female's.
Oh, the one in the car?
The chief was still
under the command of his wife.
That's a good thing.
The boss is a troublemaker.
The kids are all over the place.
In this world where
I don't know what to believe,
I believed that the chief and Ryo
were the best pair.
The fool and me?
Yes, they often fight.
But to be so serious
about it,
even the parents don't care.
I'm sure Ryo wants to go back.
He can't help it.
Really?
Yes, he's just being stubborn.
Why don't you tell him
that the chief is here?
Oh.
He's a good-for-nothing.
I'll tell him.
That's all right.
Do you want to kill me?
I want to kill you, too.
I'll kill you.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I beg you.
Oh, if you don't want to, it's fine.
I'll just show this picture to your wife.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I beg you to spare me that.
I beg you for a lifetime.
Then, you'll admit me as a special detective?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yes, I understand.
Good.
From now on, you can be my subordinate.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's a little...
Oh?
Then, from now on, your wife's...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I understand.
I'll do as you say, so please forgive me.
Good.
From now on, I'll be the special detective behind you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
This is the Katsushika-show.
I'll lure the people here and do it at once.
Yeah!
You're quite bold to be on the police show, boss.
Revenge is better in a flashy way.
Now, let's go.
Yasashii and Yumiya!
You're right.
I thought we'd forget about you two.
You can't do anything to me.
I've always been like this.
Come on, yuki!
You have to do it!
I'll help.
Oh!
Yes, yes, yes.
No!
Don't kick him!
What's wrong, Yuki?
I'm in a bad mood, or I'm not laughing.
You said you got a head start.
Oh, yeah.
I don't mind, but the people at the police station are not feeling well.
Or something like that.
You're the most boring person out there.
No, that's...
That's true.
I got it.
I'll contact the special police and go back to Ryosu.
What?
No way!
Why are the police so good?
We're in trouble.
The sun's water and sand came out from the roof of the first floor.
What?
Ohara.
Yes.
Raise your hand.
What?
What are you doing?
Oh, if you don't do as I say, the wind will blow through the
We just got on the Katsushika show.
Who are you?
What are you doing in the Katsushika show?
Me?
Did you forget?
You...
You're...
You're that weenie.
That's you!
It's you.
You're Tewi...
I want your name...
Oh, wait.
Oh!
How dare you。
Oh, wait.
You're being passing the king's order.
I'm going to see what you're talking about.
What is it?
I'm going to ask the king.
What are you talking about!
Hey, wait a minute.
What's this thing?
This is the Katsushika show?
Do you know what the Katsushika show is?
What?
Jack?
This is the culprit of the C-Jack I arrested.
Aniko!
This woman was arrested for our brilliant transformation.
The fake spirit.
Kaipan.
Dolphin.
Eko.
Long time no see.
It was our fault to kill the Chiefs of the Chonmage.
What?
Look at that!
Chief!
The Chief is the Chief!
If you want the life of the hostages,
the gold of the
That's all.
I'm done for.
The Chief is the hostages.
I'm done with you!
You're all dead.
Chief, let's all step in.
Yes, sir.
No, the culprit is asking you to come in alone.
You should go alone.
What?
The Chief and I have other jobs.
I understand.
We are enough.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Damn.
The hall was filled with water.
No way we can get through.
Kaipan,
I colored
Minoshiro's 300 million Jewish coins.
Thank you.
How dare you say that of Nakagawa Group?
But why isn't Ryo here?
He has other jobs.
He has others?
They say the Chief is in danger.
I'll go join Ryo.
I'm going.
I don't have time.
-Let's go, everyone. -Okay.
Here they are. They're coming from the moon.
Open the breakthrough port.
Let's go, Venus.
-Let's start the operation. -Roger.
I am champion!
Missile launch!
What?
Moon Decker. Venus Decker.
It's okay. We're safe somehow.
Leave this to me.
We're going to enter from the underground tunnel.
What?
We've successfully entered.
We're here, Dolphin!
I did it.
Eat this fish!
I won't let you!
Fish!
I can see through your attack.
I saw the cute dolphin under your hand being the prey of the shark.
I saw it.
There's nothing I can do but watch.
Stop it!
Bring back more fish.
Since Dengenbo gave 1 million,
Just by collecting 100,000 miles, I can get 100,000 yen in a blink of an eye.
Ryo, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Senpai, why aren't you coming?
The chief is a hostage.
It doesn't matter if you're a boss or not.
It has nothing to do with me.
What are you talking about?
The chief was involved in the case by telling the chief to lower his head so that he could return to the escape room.
What?
Ryo, please help me.
Ryo.
Please come with us.
I'm relieved that the troublemaker is gone.
You know? I'm in a hurry. Go home.
Ryo.
I didn't know you were such a person.
I've let Senpai down.
Let's go home.
Let's rescue the chief by our hands.
Ryo, you idiot.
What's with this kind of attitude?
You don't get anything, do you?
Hiromi!
Chief.
Hey!
Stop collecting coins!
Tenemon, gather the friends from the inn right away!
He says he's already prepared.
What?
What's that?
Wow! That's amazing, Dengemon!
Alright! Let's go, Dengemon!
Pat-Pot-Potega's...
...Return!
Return!
Dolphin's a jerk.
It's only a matter of time before he becomes a shark.
All we have to do is defeat the big guy and get 300 million yen.
You criminals, get out of here!
Are you scared, you villains?
Ryo Tsukankichi...
No, Pat-Pot-Potega is back!
I don't care! Get rid of him, too!
Get back!
Oh, Pinka!
Pat-Pot-Potega is back!
That's a message from the big guy!
You won't be scared if you get rid of the shark, either!
What?
I see.
Alright, I got it!
What's that?
What?
Stop it!
But...
This is too dangerous!
I'll cover you!
What?
I'll rip you up!
And this is...
What?
Because this is my gift to you!
Where are you going?
You want to shoot me down?
I don't care.
No, no.
I'm going to...
I knew you would come.
Well, I can't help but cry for you.
Oh, Lord Ryo.
Kaipan Dekka, Gekkou Dekka, Venus Dekka.
We will enter this place by leaving it to Dolphin Dekka and Nakagawa!
Yeah!
Damn you, Lord Ryo.
It's finally my turn.
You're out, pervert!
This is my opponent.
Kaipan Dekka, I will make you pay for waiting for this day.
A man versus a man.
A bare-faced match!
How dare you.
Hey, Kaipan!
Don't touch me.
This is a man versus a man.
A bare-faced match.
What?
It's time to recharge your energy.
I told you to stop with the bananas!
It's a splendid attack.
But if you're a banana,
I'll give you a mask melon.
What are you thinking?
I got one.
I can't let you get away with this.
I'm going to get you, Kaipan.
You're getting away with this?
I said you're going to get away with this.
You have to stop.
All right.
Stop.
Please subscribe if you like this video!
What the hell does that mean?
How's this?
I'm defeated!
You should follow me!
Here we go, old fool!
-Chief! -R- Ryoichi!
What did you do with the chief and the criminal?
The culprit... The culprit ran to the roof with Oharu-kun.
The roof...
You're still alive.
You're not the Moon King, you're the Venus.
This woman is dangerous.
You've defeated the Moon King.
This time, I'll stop your breath.
Moonlight Power!
Reika!
Ah, it started again.
Don't look!
Tekumakumayakin, tekumakumayakin!
Become a horizontal rope!
You're just changing your clothes.
Don't look!
Fighting! Moonlight Power!
Let me explain.
By transforming the Moonlight Power into a female pro-wrestler,
you can show incredible strength and technique.
Yippee!
I'll explain myself.
I'll transform into a female pro-wrestler,
and use Rocket Harute to get rid of Sekinen's grudge.
Yippee!
Rocket Harute!
Ah, Moonlight King!
Moonlight King!
He's a guy who can't even speak.
Damn it!
Now, I'll be your opponent, Hato Popo!
Gen'emon!
It's the "Hato Popo" strategy!
What?
Then, it's not Hato Popo,
but Hata Popo!
That's what I was talking about!
All right!
It's too early to be happy!
Huh?
Chief!
Ryousu!
Ryousu Kankichi,
I'm going to pay for this grudge!
The grudge before?
Who are you?
Hey, who are you?
Huh? Who is it?
Who?
A fat Katamura from the summer special!
Yeah, I saw you.
I forgot it, since you're not that impressive.
Thanks to the special detective team,
I met with you in Hidomi.
My brother is still missing!
I'll check this case next time.
It was all because of him!
So that's what it was.
You lost, Ryotsu.
I wonder about that.
Don't do that!
If you get close, he'll die!
Ryotsu!
Can't you hear me? I'll really shoot!
Go ahead, as you wish.
What?
You're a boss who cares about his subordinates more than I do.
You don't know what's gonna happen.
Ryotsu!
Alright, go ahead and shoot.
I don't care at all.
Why don't you ask your subordinates to help you, too?
Right, Ryotsu?
What?
Ryotsu!
Hey!
I won't forgive you!
Ryotsu, calm down!
Shut up! You don't know what's going on!
It's a plan! A plan!
A plan?
You want me to get angry and make him go crazy on purpose?
That's the plan!
I thought he would die.
When did you expect this?
So you were the one who did this.
I did this?
I knew what you're like.
So I knew you would do this.
Ryotsu...
What's wrong, boss?
No matter what, you've come to help me.
Thank you.
Chief, I'm sorry for being a important sabotage.
It's okay.
Then, please return to the station.
Yes.
I see.
Thank you.
Everyone.
By the way, Denemon.
This photo is...
He said, "Please stop. Please forgive me."
Don't misunderstand.
I'll do this.
Look.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Yes?
What was that?
Nothing.
But why don't you go out today?
Oh, that's good.
We're going to say goodbye today.
Okay.
I'll treat you to a hot pot party.
Sounds good.
Then why don't we have a hot pot party?
Idiot!
This is a joke!
Chief!
Urgh!
Mr. Murase
♪ Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dab
Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia! Dabia!
♪ I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm
But if you have the first feeling, the fairy-tale star will come and draw a circle.
This is good, right?
There is no reason to say that!