Light of
TV,
make
room
brighter
and
look
away.
I
look at
the
river
of
and
look
the
sunset
that
at
the
moon
that
floats
on
river
and
look
at
the
moon
that
floats
on
the
I
also
look
at
moon
look
at
the
I
look
at
the
sunset
that
And it all ends with a kiss
I'm happy again
I'm in a daze
And I realize
I'm stupid
Counterattack!
T Accused!
Tenbatsu Techimen Tenbatsu Techimen Tenbatsu Techimen!
Monopolis Chief!
How's the underworld?
Yeah, it's still the same.
I see.
I was the one who was self-respecting the officers.
It seems I've completely disappointed my subordinates.
Huh?
I'm not going to patrol around in the middle of the day.
Good night.
Damn it! It's all his fault!
My honor was trampled on by this man!
Damn it!
Tenpaku!
Ouch!
You're in my way.
Hey, Hanayama!
It's you again. I know you.
You're always giving me the wrong punishment.
Why don't you do something bigger, you idiot?
What?
Hanayama!
S- sir!
If you don't behave, I'll have to show you something.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you idiot!
I'll slap you in the ass!
It's all because of that man.
I'll have to kill that Ryotsu and get back the trust and respect of the police officers!
Is there a Ryotsu officer?
Ryotsu is patrolling right now.
Patrolling?
Is there no Ryotsu?
Is he a friend of yours?
Well, not really.
Even if you say he's patrolling, he's talking about you.
If you don't mind, please wait in the back room.
Thank you.
What's wrong, sir?
You've been kind to me for a long time.
It's delicious tea.
Oh, it's a cheap tea of 100g and 200 yen.
Your kindness is making me feel the fragrance of tea.
Well, good job.
I wish I could have a view like you.
View?
You're really...
You're so annoying.
Are you patrolling again, Ryo?
Sir, lend me the lunch. I'll double it.
I don't want to, Ryo.
I've never said that and given it back, have I?
Oh, by the way, it's a guest.
Guest?
Ha ha ha ha ha.
That's right.
I've been patrolling the outside world for a long time.
Then, last time, it was a man of Hanayama who said that
"Ryo-chan has become so small".
Yes.
I intended to punish him with a heavy punishment at that time,
but it seems that that man still lacks it.
Ryo-chan, you can change any painful coincidence into a positive one.
Hmm.
As expected of that man, I'm also a little bit anxious.
This time, I stood in the middle of patrolling
to add even more pressure.
He he he.
If you don't have this cane, you can't get your hands and feet out.
Huh?
He he he.
Let's try it with a hand.
Ten-batsu!
Huh?
Ryoh-san, you need something?
Ah, no, it's nothing.
Hmm, as expected, I can't use this cane unless I'm an old man from Hanayama.
Huh?
Hey, mister!
It's a nice day for driving beauty.
Let's buy the one-way road!
Ten-batsu!
Huh?
Ah, a new muffler!
Look, Mr. Honda.
I got a hit because I tried to skip it.
That's why I got hit by a bat.
I see.
So the whole village is a temple,
and there's no punishment for it.
Did you say something?
It's just a small thing. Don't worry about it.
But if you just hit people,
it's not productive.
For example, if you do this,
you'll get paid.
One million yen!
Here you go!
Wow!
This is the Kozuchi we got from the house!
What a shame, Terai!
If you hadn't been so stingy and lent me money,
I would have paid you ten times or a hundred times more!
No, Ryo-san.
That's not fair.
It's got a little bit of money, too.
It's a real 10,000 yen note.
How long are you going to pay me back my cane?
Who would pay me back something so useful?
I got this cane.
No, Ryo-chan.
Give it back to the old man.
Here's the cane.
It's mine now.
I can't do anything with it.
It's just a piece of junk.
No, Ryo-san!
What are you doing?
Thank you!
I'm sure you'll go to heaven!
Here, I'll give you a ten-thousand yen note!
What the hell?
Are you okay?
Oh, where's Ryo-chan?
Over there!
You're a big man,
but you're not good at anything.
This is just a simple task that anyone can do.
Huh?
What's going to happen if we return it?
Oh, that's it!
The Ten-Bastard is back!
The Ten-Bastard has just beenらい~
I'm sorry!
Senpai!
Ryozu!
Chief, you've been a real pain in the neck when you were little.
What are you doing, Ryozu?!
Please stop!
It's okay. I won't crush you.
It's a bell!
Take it!
Damn it!
I got it!
Huh? The string...
It's easy to catch Ryo-chan.
Who do you think you are?!
You're a crazy man!
I'll punish you with my sword!
What's this? It's a panda!
You should be ashamed of your own ugliness!
I'll leave to patrol from now on.
Hey, Hanayama, get back to your place!
Ryo-chan, you're so cute!
Chief!
Don't get on my nerves!
How am I supposed to live in this outfit?
How am I supposed to live in this school?
Mama, Kanda-san is here!
Oh, really?
Hey, each of you gets 100 yen for your sword!
I'm scared, Mama!
Hey, pay up!
Ryozu!
Ouch!
The Ueno people have the right to pay for swords, Chief!
This is terrible!
What's the matter, sir?
Grandpa!
Grandpa, you'd better get me back to my place!
Well...
Huh?
You lost the magic wand?
Y-Yes, I did.
I was busy with my studies.
Huh?
That's...
What?
Then what's going to happen to me?
If you don't have the wand, you can't go back to your original form...
Don't talk nonsense!
You want me to spend the rest of my life as a panda?
I can't stand to see if I can go buy a magic wand in this form!
Senior!
Hanayama-san didn't lose it on purpose, either.
Oh, of course!
I'm in trouble, too.
If I don't have that wand...
Where did you lose it?
At the end of the third signal...
Kyaryuu!
Ryo-san!
Senior!
Don't worry, Nakagawa Terai!
Call the insurance office!
A violent norapanda is wandering around the city.
But...
That's just not going to make you around!
Yes, sir.
What should I do?
If I lose the magic wand of the police,
I won't be able to go back to heaven on my first-day job.
Ryo-chan, when it comes to you,
If you do, you'll be dead.
So I'm sure you'll find him.
It's okay.
No!
If I give him the staff,
he won't know what to do next!
Even if I die,
I must get the staff back before that man!
Uncle!
Oh, damn.
Who took it?
What's that?
What's this?
It looks like a snack.
I'm sorry.
It's a snack house!
Bandera, stop!
It's really a cookie.
It's definitely the work of the man who took the staff.
But who did this?
What's that?
It's like he turned the toy box over.
Okay, I got it.
The staff took it.
It's a kindergarten kid's book.
They can't tell the difference between manga and reality.
Hurry up and take it!
It's getting smaller.
Now it's easier to use.
Lend it to me.
I'm going to get Mika's doll.
Next time, I'll...
Oh, it's a panda!
I knew it.
Hey, let's go fishing before we play.
Where's the fishing rod?
We're going too.
What should we do?
Oh, right!
Let's put it in here.
Let's use it later.
I'm not here to play!
Let go of me!
It's a nice weather for golfing, isn't it?
It's a close course, so I'll be back in the evening.
Oh, you asked for a panda doll.
I didn't ask for it.
I'll play with it later.
Wait a minute!
Where's the fishing rod?
Fishing rod?
I put it in the golf bag of the principal.
Oh, principal!
What?
Wait for that car!
The panda is waving at us.
He's a passionate part-time student.
I'm telling you to wait!
Damn it!
My body is too heavy to run.
I'll get a taxi.
Hey, taxi!
Crap, don't discriminate animals!
Good timing!
That's Ming's sedan.
I'll get it with you.
I'll get it back by myself!
Ming, please, get it back.
You old-timer!
Did you remember it?
Just follow Ming's taxi.
Yes.
Yeah!
We have a good view of the course.
Shall we aim for the rear?
You are not allowed to enter except by the user!
I came here to collect the staff, so let go.
I finally made it.
Okay.
The bear has appeared!
RUYA isn't gonna be happy about it...
Oh, now!
I'll do the rest of his hell!
You're...
going to die!
That's...
not gonna do!
I'll finish you off!
I won't let you finish me off!
Kangaroo can swim!
Don't mess with me...
There he is!
It's Panda the Tsunodori!
Let him sleep in the water!
But Kangaroo has jump power!
Panda has become a kangaroo!
I'll punish you with my power!
Come on, Kasumi!
Wait!
I'll go first.
Damn it!
I failed.
I should have bought that old man a slimy turtle.
Wait for me!
Damn it!
I'll lose sight of the crow and the old man.
I have to catch them and go to the zoo.
I have to do something.
Come on, let's go to the zoo today!
That's it.
I'll go first.
What's the matter, Mr. Tsunodori?
Excuse me, but I'm late for the opening.
It's a little bit...
I didn't know that you were a Tsunodori.
Well, I'm a Tsunodori.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
I can't believe it.
You're a Tsunodori, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm a Tsunodori.
Yeah, I am.
I'm a Tsunodori, aren't I?
Hey, I'm a Tsunodori, aren't I?
Hey, where's the XL size dress?
Welcome.
Naoko is here.
I feel like I'm getting too much attention.
I can't stand the legs of a panda.
Oh, no!
I'm tired of being a kangaroo.
It seems to be over there.
If I can find the screw, it's mine.
Wait, excuse me.
Go to the roof!
It's a weight over!
Shut up!
Go straight to the roof!
Young man, use the stairs.
Yes, sir.
Where's the crow?
There it is!
It's the crow's nest!
I did it!
You bastard!
It's so noisy!
Shut up!
Stop!
If you go back to your original position, it's mine.
I won't let you do that.
You're so persistent!
That's your fault!
Let me go, old man!
Oh my!
And here I am.
Why?
I'd be disappointed if you left behind me.
Don't talk nonsense!
You deserve the credit of my years of hard work.
Don't interfere!
You bastard!
W-what is that?
I-I don't know.
It's a panda and a kangaroo.
I know that!
That's why I told you to give me two billion yen!
Listen, I'll pay for the next time.
Two billion yen!
I'll pay for the next time.
Hey, Retsu!
Can you move a little?
My turn!
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move!
What?
Want to play?
You'll get kicked out if you keep going like this!
Alright!
One more...
One more breath...
I'm going to drown.
I can't swim with a kangaroo.
What?
Don't bother!
Give me the rod!
I don't want to run!
Stop!
I'm going to drown!
So...
I'll pay for the next time!
I'm saved.
Hey, old man!
I'm still an animal!
If you're an animal, don't you dare turn me into a floating fish!
He's gone, Senpai.
It seems Chief Ohara was called by the chief in this matter.
Was the old man of Hanayama alright?
Shut up!
Don't talk about him!
I guess the panda was better than the floating fish.
The floating fish only come out in summer.
But it seems that we can make a thousand people with it without being suspicious.
A floating fish?
That's great!
Ryo, if you do that...
You're talking nonsense!
Sorry!
Everyone is here.
Old man of Hanayama...
What's up with your outfit?
Actually, the TV program "Tengoku Keisatsu 24" was broadcasted.
It was very popular.
I was scouted by the talent agency of Tengoku.
Reiko, I brought the lyrics of the famous song of Tengoku.
Can you bring me some tea?
Yes.
I see. That's good.
From now on, let's do it with talent and the second-class of the troupe.
No! Before that, bring me back to my home!
Hey, Tenbatsuji!
Bring me back!
Please!
It was the video from the second-class TV Tengoku Keisatsu 24.
I was surprised to see what kind of machine it could be.
Shut up!
Well, why don't you cut this video and get rid of me?
This one is...
I'd like to take a break.
Where are we going?
Ryo-chan and Ran!
My skirt is short, so shut up!
Ryo-chan, why don't you dress up properly?
And when she said that, she found a thief!
Kiiin!
This won't make me run!
Next time, "Run! Reiko's Great Trace"!
Look forward to it!