Translated by Shion
I look up at the setting sun floating in the river
When I kick the love stone, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym I used to work out
I was laughed at for being a
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yoke is strangely gentle
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
The sun goes down to the Kaishakuten
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again because of the Katsushika Shiba
I'm a fool
Since morning
Absolute security 4 visits
An announcement for traveling to Hawaii?
Going to Hawaii at the karaoke party.
It 's so strict.
We're in trouble even in the afternoon
You're still here after all
Hey, Grandma
I bought all that stuff
Then we'll run out of money.
Is there anyone here, Grandma?
I'll take you to the hospital!
Hey, Grandma!
Don't let him get away!
If you're here, I'll give you a reply!
What's wrong with you?
You look so serious.
Don't tell me you're in love with someone.
No, I'm not, Mr. Ryo.
Actually, I...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
I'm the old man who took the money from the Hawaii trip to the
Inchiki Travel Company.
I mean, you don't have to laugh.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone was looking forward to it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a shame.
Huh?
What happened to that money?
I was trying to do something about it.
We all helped each other out, but...
Uh-oh.
There are over 20 people in the
Yeah.
Okay, leave it to me.
What?
I'll take everyone to Hawaii with that money.
Can you do that?
Leave it to me.
There's no letter that's impossible in my dictionary.
Forty-nine, forty-six, twenty-eight, forty-nine, forty-nine, fifty-nine...
Oh, yeah.
I have 500,000 yen.
That's a lot.
It's for two or three people.
What are you going to do?
What about your husband?
Of course.
Ask Nakagawa or Reiko.
They're kind people.
The 20 or 30 of my grandparents will take me to Hawaii for free.
My grandparents are happy.
I have a profit of 500,000 yen.
I thought that was it.
What?
There's no Nakagawa or Reiko.
Oh, I see.
I heard that they were both on vacation.
They went abroad yesterday.
Don't joke around at this important time.
Yeah.
Yes, I'm Nakagawa.
Nakagawa! Where are you?
Senpai?
I'm on vacation.
Come back immediately.
Well, that's...
What?
I heard that there was trouble at the Amazon resource survey site.
I'm heading to the site.
We're in the middle of the jungle that can't be used by a helicopter.
So I can't move right away.
Senpai?
Yes, Reiko.
Ah, Ryo-chan.
What's wrong?
What?
You're not going back to Japan?
That's impossible.
The South Pole is in danger.
Come here from Ryo-chan.
Damn it.
They're useless when I say so.
It's impossible for us to go to Hawaii without you two.
I should return the money.
Wait.
There must be something else.
I'm sorry.
There shouldn't be.
Ryo-chan, are you there?
What?
Maybe you're Hidami's grandmother?
No.
You're because of me.
I'm really worried right now.
Tell me what you're thinking later.
I'm worried later.
No, thanks to Ryo, I can go to Hawaii.
He said so.
Hmm.
And he's helping me out.
The sweet potato pork roll.
Oh...
Has this information been transmitted now?
This may be creepy.
Senpai...
And here's the yam構.
But what's wrong?
Ah...
How about some lunch?
Fresh vegetables from my relatives.
Thank you very much, Ryo-san.
It's our first time to travel abroad.
That's right.
That's why we're looking forward to our next trip.
Please, Ryo-san.
Is that so? It's your first time?
Don't worry.
We, Ryo-tsu Kankou, will take you safely to Hawaii.
We?
Us too?
For the citizens.
Of course we'll help you.
Of course.
That's why.
Don't worry, everyone.
Please leave it to us, Ryo-tsu Kankou.
I'm so happy.
Now we can make a souvenir for our maid.
Thank you.
Leave it to us.
This is so unreasonable!
How can we make a souvenir of 500,000 yen and bring 20 people to Hawaii?
Don't tell me you'll let us pay for this.
That's impossible.
Our house loan is 19 years old.
I don't know how much you can pay me.
You just have to lend me your hand.
Now, I'll explain the Trip Plan.
There is a map of Hawaii.
Ryo-sama, this is a map of the Kanto region.
Look!
There is Hawaii here!
That's Kanagawa, isn't it?
According to the source,
there is a place called Hawaii in the far west of the Pacific.
But the road leading there is difficult.
It takes 40 days to reach Kanlinmaru.
Everyone!
It's impossible for an old man to carry the weight of a man.
So he decided to go to Hawaii.
I had a bad feeling about it.
I'm not kidding.
How can you fool the old people like that?
Everyone is looking forward to the trip to Hawaii.
Are you going to have a dream with the old people who have no reason to go?
It would be terrible to take them to Hawaii.
I can't help you.
What is this?
This is the gift of Saori that I received the other day.
Someone took it.
I was going to give it to my sister.
Who was it?
If the trip is canceled,
there may be old people who will be shocked.
Let's enjoy the feeling of traveling to Hawaii.
I see.
Do you understand?
If it's for you,
I'll go in the fire or in the water.
Let's have a fun trip to Hawaii together!
Yes!
I was so excited I couldn't sleep last night.
I dream about Hawaii.
It's all thanks to you.
Oh!
Someone is here!
Hello everyone at the ruin operation.
Thank you.
Hello.
Well, we've been waiting.
Let's have a fun trip to Hawaii together!
See you later!
"Narita Airport"
Thank you for waiting.
We will arrive at Narita Airport soon.
Look at this!
This is the Super Jumbo that will take you to Hawaii.
It's a good souvenir for your grandchildren.
Thank you, thank you.
It's completely different from the picture.
What?
What are you talking about?
There is a body, a wing, and a tail.
It's exactly the same.
But there is no propeller in this picture.
It rotates at high speed, so it is not reflected in the picture.
You may not know it because you do not have the opportunity to fly.
The propeller is installed to stabilize the current near the main wing of the latest type of jet lander.
That's common sense.
I see.
As expected of Mr. Ryo.
It's a good sign.
Please be careful of your feet.
Welcome.
Welcome to Tokyo.
The Stardust is beautiful.
Oh, my.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My feet are cramping.
You have to be careful.
But you have a good butt.
I don't like it.
My hands are slippery.
I'm dizzy.
I can't move.
My feet are cramping.
If you know Maria is a man, you may be shocked.
We will soon depart for Narita Airport and head to Hawaii Honolulu Airport.
Please fasten your seat belts.
Oh.
Is this all we bought?
This is like a volunteer.
I'm grateful just to get money.
Mr. Ryo.
What?
I want you to say hello to the captain.
By the way, the captain will say something before we depart.
Wait. I'll go now.
What's wrong with the captain?
He must be busy.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Yatarou, the captain's opposite.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Captain.
Hello, what can I do for you?
Please call Mr. Ryo.
I see.
You old man.
Hello.
How can I help you?
Mr. Ryo.
Can you ask the captain how long it takes to get to Hawaii?
Mr. Captain, we want to know the flight time.
Yes, sir.
The flight time is 6 hours.
I can hear you clearly.
I'm sorry, but can you come out?
The flight time is about 6 hours.
Mr. Ryo, where can I get your passport?
I have it in my hall.
You don't have to show it to me.
By the way, Mr. Captain.
Yes?
Mr. Ryo.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Captain.
Yes.
Mr. Ryo.
What do you want?
I don't know.
You can't do this forever.
Let's go, Maria.
Okay, Mr. Ryo.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm ready, too.
It's the captain's reverse-flying car.
I'll take off now.
It's moving.
I was told to lend me the plane that was being dismantled.
I thought I'd use it.
I'm not going to be fooled.
Here, Maria, from the top.
Hello, S logical to the maximum.
Hello, there.
Is there a reason why?
It doesn't feel like it's going to be a big step, but I can tell you're going to be really fast.
Really?
Why not?
Theторов and Ryo, stop moving.
Please.
You're going down?
I was told you should be careful when taking off.
Oh, I see.
You have to be careful.
Yeah.
I can't even read the guide book.
Don't look outside when you're going up.
There's a neon right there.
No, it's a symptom of neon disease.
Neon disease?
The guide book doesn't say that.
It's in reality.
When you look outside from the plane,
there are things on the ground that look big,
and at the end, you'll see a pink elephant or a white crocodile,
or anything that doesn't exist.
It's a terrible disease.
I-Is there such a disease?
It's okay for now.
It'll be better if you close your eyes for a while.
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
You've been staying still for a while.
I was caught by a sphere.
The plane is stuck.
What?
Don't say such stupid things, Grandpa.
The signal...
No, it's just a headwind,
and I feel like I've stopped.
This is the common sense of Super Jambo.
Anyway, you're not allowed to enter here except for the people involved.
Please return to your seat.
I'm sorry about that.
Give me a meal.
I'll let the food focus my nerves.
And I'll give you plenty of alcohol to make you sleep.
Okay, I understand, Master Ryo.
Thank you for waiting.
It's time for dinner.
Here you are.
Oh, this is the meal inside the plane.
I've never seen this before.
It's going to last a long time.
I'm sorry.
Please give it to me as soon as possible.
Okay.
It's made by Maria.
It's better than the real meal inside the plane.
Oh, this is good.
It's going to last a long time.
Thank you.
Well, how about some alcohol?
I've been waiting for a long time.
Anyway, there's plenty of time in Hawaii.
Please drink more and more.
Doug, you're such a great old lady.
I'll take a breath too.
Huh?
What the hell?
What are you doing?
I got caught by that stupid crane.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Fr. Genie?
What?
Is It raining?
Well, it's me.
You're going to get your ass kicked!
What are you looking at?
You kiss my ass!
Your ass is Momo's.
Hey!
H-hurry, they are in our way!
No way!
U-ouw!
They are too strong!
Right! Right!
A-young man?
This is the Kuranohi.
T-they're breaking through Lankin Ryu right now.
Keep the seatbelts tight!
Nankiryu! It's Nankiryu!
Gear Pocket!
How many do you want?
What's that?
We're going to the Miura beach!
I'm counting on you!
Here we are!
How's the preparation?
Perfect.
From anywhere you look, this is Hawaii.
You know, it's a beach house.
Great job!
Everyone, we've arrived in Hawaii!
Now, get up and get ready to get off!
We've really arrived in Hawaii?
I'm sure it's not like that.
Now, it's the Hawaii we've been longing for!
Why are we here?
It's a long trip.
You can see the beach right after you get off.
That's America, isn't it?
Yes, it is!
Welcome to Hawaii!
I feel like I've been here for a long time.
Welcome to Hawaii.
Oh, as expected of an outsider.
Your body is big.
Give it to me.
What?
What's wrong?
Saori, please forgive me.
This is all for you.
What?
Oh no, let me go, I'm going to drink.
What a cold day!
What's up to you?
I'm just a guy.
No, it's just a stranger.
I know, I know.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Who is this?
Now, is "monoca" a thing?
No!
Ahhh!
Aloha, pineapple, yes!
What are you saying?
Just go back to the station.
I'm not going to Fuji!
That was a close call.
When you come to a tourist destination overseas,
you can get close to them like you're a friend,
and they'll steal your luggage.
Everyone, please be careful.
They're very similar.
Now, let's take you to a tourist destination in Hawaii.
First, this is the famous Waikiki Beach.
It's really wide.
You can't see it in Japan.
It's a long way.
But it seems like there are a lot of Japanese people.
Recently, there are a lot of Japanese people in every tourist destination.
That's the Diamond Head, which is also sung in the song.
It's a diamond-like shape.
I can sing that song.
Diamond?
It's not a diamond, it's more like an island.
There are a lot of people like that.
And this is the King Kamehameha.
The king of Hawaii was also a little bent.
It's a lot different from the picture.
This is old.
It was repaired like that after the war.
That's the Kirauhe Ya-kazan.
This is Shinji Bay.
Recently, Hawaii is a wedding.
And this is the Royal Hawaiian Hotel.
Please enjoy the taste of Hawaii tonight.
Itadakimasu.
Oh, sashimi and tempura.
Is there such a thing in Hawaii?
It's a hot fish sashimi and a shrimp tempura.
It's a specialty of Hawaii.
Excuse me.
I told you to make it look like Hawaii.
Even if you say so.
What's that?
Yes, it's a pot.
OMG.
Sir, what would you like?
It's a delicious tropical hot pot.
It's the most famous ingredient of this country.
It seems good.
There is hot pot in Hawaii.
Let's try.
The fish soup of this can be used for this dish.
And it will create a good harmony.
It's good to eat.
You believe in design.
Yes, it is.
Let's do better.
I don't care what you say.
The passion of the young fire will be revived.
Me too.
Lord Hirao?
Idiots!
Ryotsu, you are...
I didn't get injured, so I'm fine.
That's the problem.
Why are you like the people of the Kero club in Hawaii and the Miura club?
There's a deep reason for that.
What is it?
I wonder if Ryo is there.
Everyone.
Everyone, I'm really sorry for what this idiot did this time.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm here to say thank you today.
It was a really fun trip.
It's been a long time since I've been so noisy.
You are really young.
But what about Hawaii?
We went to Hawaii for sure.
It was Hawaii we even dreamed of.
Let's go on a trip together, Ryo.
This time, we'll go to Hawaii beyond the sea.
What?
Why?
Ryo…
I know something is going on.
Please explain this to us.
What?
That's a pretty fancy book.
Those are here for you.
De de!
And it's decided
Bako!
And it flutters
Kuya!
And it's decided
Debe debe!
Baki baki!
And it's decided
Look at tomorrow
And believe in yesterday
Draw the universe
And stand on a plane
And the Mosquito will draw a circle
And draw a circle
Is this all right?!
No excuses!
"The