♪ NECROPOLIS
♪ I watch the sunset on the river within
♪ I kick a stone
♪ and I fly into the slippers
I wonder if he went to the gym where he was saving money
He laughed at me saying I was still a kid
Even if I try to cheer up, I can't win
There is no change in my yawn
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the fountain of a pointed hat
To the taishakuten, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again
I realized
I'm an idiot
So
Kareinithenshin Gekkou deka
I pulled back to the special patrol
From the east, no abnormalities
You did a great job
Senpai, it's our turn next time.
Shut up. This is important.
Ryo, what if the Nekonome Settou-dan shows up while you're just playing around?
What's wrong with Nego's gold ball?
Nekonome Settou-dan!
Recently, the Settou-dan has been stealing high-end items such as jewelry and jewelry in the Katsushika Prefecture.
Six of them have already been damaged.
They're strengthening the night patrol to catch them.
Now that you mention it, that's what the chief was talking about.
Damn, he's making me work overtime.
It's a rumor that there are three women.
Maybe there's a beautiful woman like Ryo-chan.
I'm not interested in stupid women who are all about high-end items.
Nakagawa, I'll leave it to you.
Go patrol by yourself.
I'd love to, but...
I'm sorry.
You idiot!
Do you have any sense of self-awareness as a police officer?
You don't, do you?
Of course you don't.
You don't!
You don't, right?
What are you talking about?
If someone like you is here, the head of the prefecture will worry and send reinforcements.
Reinforcements?
Is someone coming from the prefecture?
That's right!
In order to solve the incident involving the Nekonome Settou-dan this time,
we have sent a 100% elite detective.
We will all join his command.
What kind of person is he?
We haven't heard his real name, but he's called "Gekkou Deka" in the prefecture.
Gekkou Deka?
By the way, there used to be a program called "Gekkou Kamen."
There was also a "Ninja Unit Gekkou."
I wonder if he's wearing that costume.
What are you two talking about?
The enemy is an elite detective.
There's no way he's wearing that kind of costume.
Then what kind of person is he?
I wonder.
He's a musician.
Once the incident is solved, he will definitely play Beethoven's "Gekkou."
By the way, Gekkou Deka belongs to the Special Police Department.
Special Police Department?
The Special Police Department is where the "Kaipan Deka" and the "Dolphin Deka" are.
I can't expect him to be a musician.
I'm going to go home because I'm going to be in pain.
Oh, I see.
You're going home, Ryo-tsu.
We're going to get a special bonus when the incident is solved.
A special bonus?
Then we'll arrest the culprit and get the bonus.
Ryo-tsu, I'm going to join the command of the Gekkou Deka.
Hmm...
Bonus, bonus.
Is the moon out?
It's out.
That is...
That back and the car weight attached to the door.
That is the Gekkou Deka, the night-time fighter that was active in the end of the Pacific War.
They call it Gekkou.
Then is that the ones who drive it?
The Gekkou Deka?
Grrr...
Everyone prepare to be shocked!
An awesome pervert father will come!
There are three private detectives in Japan.
The sea, the dolphin, and me in the sky!
The Moon Dekka.
He's a good guy.
No way!
He's a special detective of the Moon Dekka.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
And the other one.
My partner, the Venus Dekka.
I'm Venus. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
There's a normal person in the Special Investigation Department, too.
I got a bad feeling about it.
That's not mine.
It's mine.
The Pekomei Thief Squad has appeared.
Get ready to go!
Right away!
Aren't we going to the scene?
Before that, there's something we have to do.
Moonlight Power!
Dゃàn!
Like a
There's something wrong with that guy.
Let's hurry!
Look out!
Let's go!
I've got a bad feeling about this car.
I can't believe you're in the car.
I'm changing into something special.
Let me explain.
By changing your costume,
you can display 7 special abilities.
Now, I'll...
I-Is that so?
As expected of a special detective.
You're a real one.
But...
What kind of costume is he wearing?
The moonlight is my energy.
The messenger from the moon.
Moonlight Deca!
And Venus Deca!
I'm back.
The criminal who disturbs the world is...
I'll turn into the moon and...
I'll crush you!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?
It's a ceremony.
Why are you wearing a sailor suit?
This is easier to move when the criminal is chasing after him.
And by showing the punch line,
I've killed many criminals so far.
You're getting sick and tired.
All right.
Now, let's all go.
You guys should change into this.
Me too?
Of course.
And then, me too.
You and Daijirou are like...
super love-love.
Well, it can't be helped if it becomes a mission.
What are you doing, Chief Ohara?
No, I'm changing into something else.
You're a contact officer.
You can stay here.
I-Is that so?
Sorry, everyone.
I don't want to!
I can arrest the criminal like this.
I can't stand wearing a sailor suit.
Then, Yamuen.
It's a forced transition.
The subordinate who defends the superior's orders...
I'll turn into the moon and...
I'll crush you!
Make up!
What?
Ouch!
I'll change into this.
I'll change into this!
I'll change into this, so let me go!
I see.
Are you okay, Senpai?
It was just a small accident.
What's wrong?
I heard a scream.
Hurry up and put on your pants!
I'm not going to show you anything.
I don't want to scare you!
Then, hurry up and transform!
If you keep on moving, the criminal will run away!
Oh, that's right.
Make up!
How is it?
It's not bad.
M-Make up!
How is it?
It's not bad.
It's like a rural school girl from the war.
Make up!
Look at those wicked duties!
"So cute!"
"Will you add tequila here?"
"You're making me angry!"
How can you say such things right now?!
It's not ok!
Ouch!
And what's that trunks for?
Any underwear of yours is my own!
You won't be able to bring that to the trunks!
Wait a minute!
You're wearing a new outfit.
What?
The next day
What do you think?
Wow! It looks good on you!
You look like a real high school girl!
Thank you.
But Reiko, you can't wear trunks on a sailor suit.
What are you thinking?
I don't wear trunks, do I?
Who's who?
What are you doing?
I don't want to!
Then everyone get on the moon.
There are two people on the moon!
If you get on, you can get on three more people.
Three people? There's one more person!
Don't worry. I have a special seat for you.
Huh? I feel like I'm being locked up in a nursing home.
Why are you doing this?
Go!
I'm scared!
Stop! Stop right now!
There it is.
Get off!
Get off me!
I just got a call from the moon that the culprit has just been taken away.
What?
No way!
I'm going back!
I did it! I'm on the moon!
What are you doing, Chief?
What?
This is too far away.
I'm gonna take you on a trip.
I'll be on the moon.
Watch it!
I'll catch you!
A lot of people are enjoying the view of the
It is amazing.
The view is amazing.
The Ekonome Setotan is the most famous sapphire
shop in the world.
So, this is the notice board.
This is the notice board.
When the culprit was caught last night,
they didn't come to this place.
The chief's elite heard and they were amazed.
You should have changed your clothes
on your last night.
If you had changed your clothes,
you wouldn't have missed your culprit.
If you were told to wear sailor clothes,
there is no one who would change their clothes.
I'm curious.
I'll show you my ability today.
I don't know where the culprit is.
Let's disguise ourselves and guard the place.
Yes, sir!
Prince Venus, transform!
Moonlight Power!
Makeup!
Again?
Is he going to get a sale this time?
Let me explain.
I'm going to search for the clothes I bought last night.
At the moment, I'm transforming into a very ordinary person.
Then, I'll...
You look like a normal person right now,
so I don't think you need to transform.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes!
I've finished my makeup!
Wedding Moonlight Power!
Same as Wedding Venus!
I won't lose again!
What kind of ordinary person is that?!
During the wedding, the bride who was taken away by her ex-boyfriend
stopped by the department store as she was running away.
It's a common thing, right?
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, if you wear these clothes,
you can see the woman's eyes.
If you're sensitive to the woman's eyes,
and if you try to steal the jewelry,
you can see it in one shot.
I'm going to give you a candle service tonight!
Look, look, Venus.
This jewel looks really good on you!
Oh, my sister looks better on you.
Oh, my!
Venus is a good girl.
You look good on her.
My sister looks better on...
her.
Oh, Sam Genghis.
I don't think this is the world.
It's creepy.
Well, we can't say anything about people like that.
After all, we're in this outfit.
I never wanted to wear it.
What?!
What's wrong?
Hurry up and turn on the light!
The tears of the princess!
It's gone!
What's this?
It's over there!
Over there!
You silly people!
I got the tears of the princess.
Then, adieu.
It's the building next door!
Hey! Hey!
This is strange.
There should be no suspicious woman.
Anyway, let's go!
Yeah!
What are you doing?
The game is over.
I'll show you the true power of Moon Dagger!
Even if you chase a dark cloud, you can only escape like this.
First, transform!
Moonlight Power!
Make up!
Venus, please give me a helmet!
Yes, sir!
Lovely Nurse Moon Dagger!
Also, Pretty Nurse Venus Dagger!
Transform!
Why are you a nurse?
Because I'm a man of honor!
Quiet!
There is a car that is running at a high speed toward South China.
It's the culprit's car.
Then, let's rush after it!
Okay!
Before that, transform!
Me again?
Moonlight Power!
Make up!
Oh, my goodness!
It's connected to the fans!
No way!
I feel sorry for Venus!
The queen is the moon, my lord!
The queen is Venus, my lord!
-I'm... -Pen-san!
What's with that outfit?
This is better for the night.
-I'm going to sleep. -What?
Is this it again?
It's stronger than last time.
Don't worry about it falling.
Attack!
Hey!
Don't we have enough distance to land?
It's okay.
We'll manage.
What?
Why are you driving?
That's it!
Let's go!
He's so playful!
I can't run away anymore!
Give me some food!
You cat!
I won't let you go!
You're a bad guy, Ojogeya.
Hey!
It's climbing!
Climb!
Don't worry.
I'm surely very good at driving.
It's not safe at all!
It's bad!
I'll take it with one blow!
Hey! Don't just leave me!
If you don't leave me, I'll die!
I'll take it!
You idiot! You'll die here!
What's that?
They're trying to escape from the sky!
Look at that, it's huge!
You bastard!
Fly over that airplane, Ryotsu!
What?
You're going to die before they get on board the ship!
What? They're three women. You can do it!
Don't joke!
You'll die if you fail to fly!
I'll give you two special bonuses!
Two special bonuses!
Got it?
I'll do anything for the world and for the people!
I'll arrest the culprit!
Alright, let's go!
Yeah!
I'll be the moon's savior!
I'm sorry!
No, don't do it!
Look!
You were looking for me!
No, no!
You're scum!
I'll take you for the world's emperor!
Yeah, okay!
I'll take you!
What do you want?
게?
He won't be able to fly...
I won't even be able to see him!
This is the end!
"I'm the most perfect monster for my age!"
Ouch!
What a mess!
They're all men!
They're all dressed up like women!
I don't want to be told!
Mission complete.
That was a good job, Ryo-tsu.
Well, if I were to be serious, it would be that easy.
The Kitten Eye Thief was disguised as a woman to attract the police.
The police thought she was a woman, so they couldn't catch her.
That's a double bonus!
Here's a special letter from the Special Police Department.
Here it is!
A cardboard box?
It's so big!
There's a letter in it!
As a special bonus for solving the case,
I'll send you a special police figure.
You can't get any other specials.
The Kite-Pan-Dekka, the Dolphin-Dekka,
the Moon-Dekka and the Venus-Dekka.
And to honor your performance,
I also got a special figure for you, Ryo-tsu.
Please cherish it.
Don't let me display it in my room.
I'm sorry.
This case is like Ryo-chan solving it all by herself.
I'll give it to Ryo-chan.
I'll do it.
Me too!
Here, Senpai.
Here you go.
I worked hard,
and worked hard,
and this is the result!
This is a double bonus!
I can't believe I'm getting this much money!
Why, didn't he buy the Iron Thread-Gun?
This guy was with the ordinary Secret Weapon Otaku.
We'll get back this Iron Thread-Gun to the key of the exit.
Next time: I'll deliver the Iron Thread-Gun.
Thank you for watching!
rätt
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe.
I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I
ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight, I'm ready to fight...
See the tomorrow, believe in the yesterday.
Draw the universe and stand up on the ground.
The roundhouse planet drawn a circle.
This should do it, right?
This content is by circumstances separate for entertainment purposes.
The film is not intended to represent the views of kamikaze viewers, but we take all'...
This video has been edited without the permission of the member of pronouns.