The End
I can't do this. I've got the wrong handwriting.
Do you have an eraser?
I can't erase with a ball pen.
I can't help it. I'll erase with a stick.
It's dirty!
It's even dirtier.
I have no choice but to paint it black.
You idiot!
If you want to erase an important document with a stick,
you don't have any intelligence!
You idiot!
It's always so hard, boss.
Read this.
Who wrote this dirty handwriting?
It's yours.
Mine? That's strange.
Was I this desperate?
Read it.
September 1st.
This handwriting...
Do you know what this handwriting is?
Don't write your own handwriting!
People with good handwriting
are good at everything.
Money is also good at everything.
And so is your way of life.
That's you.
You're being prejudiced!
You can read it!
You can read it better than Nakagawa and the others.
Look.
I've stopped at the end.
The "Kichomen" is in the handwriting.
Yours is a dirty handwriting that you don't want to stop.
The next handwriting has a good balance of parallel lines.
Yours has no parallel lines at all.
It's the other way around.
This handwriting has a good balance.
Yours is a good balance of parallel lines.
And what are you going to do with this?
What are you going to do with this?
You know what?
I'm going to rewrite the report until tomorrow.
Got it?
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and
look away.
If you're not rich,
come see me.
I'm not rich,
but I'm worried about you.
Look at the blue sky,
look at the white clouds,
look at the blue sky,
and you'll see
what I'm talking about.
You understand, right?
I understand! I understand!
If you do, just shut up and follow me!
You idiot!
Huh?
I told you to submit your work by today!
I'm always sending you a life without any responsibility, so this is what you're doing!
Senpai, did you do something again?
I forgot the report that I was told to rewrite by Chief Ohara, so I was just doing it.
You can finish it all tonight!
Do it, Ryotsu! No matter how many hours it takes!
Yes, I understand! I should do it, right?
Hey, the character there is wrong!
What?
That Mimizu is dancing to Flanance!
The character there is dancing to Flanance!
Don't write a manga and cheat!
Finally finished.
I can't believe you're so weak just by writing a report.
Huh?
Chief, what is this?
You can see it by looking at it. It's a death certificate.
I was doing pachinko while I was on duty.
Senpai, I'll excuse myself first.
Do your best, Ryo-chan!
Huh?
You guys...
Don't go around talking nonsense! Hurry up and write a death certificate!
Oh, by the way, Chief, where did you decide to go on your next trip to the escape room?
Huh? A trip to the escape room?
No, Kei-chan. You said you were looking forward to seeing where you're going.
Wh-what?
Ah, that's right. Well, I'm looking forward to it.
Then, I'll excuse myself first.
Oh...
Chief, I don't think you're saying you forgot.
You said you don't have any sense of responsibility for people.
Huh, Chief?
I forgot! What should I do, Ryo-chan?
Then, I didn't have this death certificate.
What?
That's right. The Chief had forgotten an important matter, so he's your partner.
That's a different story!
Is that so?
Everyone was looking forward to your next trip.
So, what should I do?
What should you do? You can't make any reservation for a hotel from now on.
Can't you do anything about it?
I was impressed by the words you always say.
You said you'd take care of what you did yourself.
You're right. But it depends on the occasion.
If you leave it to me, I can do something about it.
This death certificate is...
Don't worry, Chief.
You can leave it to me at any time.
I see.
So, how much did you pay for your travel expenses?
I forgot to pay the rent for the travel expenses.
What?
What do you mean?
The budget is zero.
Huh? What?
I just remembered something.
Please, Ryo-chan! You're the only one who can endure it.
You're the only one!
I understand. I'll do something about it.
Please! It's a promise between men!
Ryo's North Town Trip
Now, we're going on a trip to the Kamayari Park Exhibition Center.
Today's trip is specially designed to review this megacity, Tokyo, from the ground up.
T-Tokyo?
Does that mean we can't leave within the range of the Yamanote Line?
That's right.
Tokyo is too short and I don't know much about it.
As a police officer who protects the capital, I need to know more about Tokyo.
Otherwise, I can't protect the safety of the city.
I see.
Good idea.
Thank you for your understanding.
And if you're in Tokyo, leave it to me.
I'll buy a coke from the Shinchu army in Tokyo,
and I'll be called the first boy to drink coke in Japan.
I'll be called the first boy to drink coke in Japan.
Oh, you're right, Ryo-san.
You're not born yet, are you?
Well, that's all I have to say.
The detailed course is written on this hand-written pamphlet I just sent you.
Well, first of all, it says "visit the traditional Tokyo".
I wonder if you're going to watch Kabuki or Noh.
Next, we're going to go on a water cruise.
After that, we'll go on a walk around the best outlet in Japan.
The end is a
Let's go!
Yes!
Wait a minute!
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy a ticket.
You're going to take the train, right?
You're so naive!
You don't know the purpose of this trip.
I'm not buying a ticket.
The station is on the road!
You're going on a water cruise?
It seems so.
Water cruise?
Let's walk!
It's okay.
Walking is good for health.
Such a trip is fitting for a policeman.
Come on!
Let's walk without complaining.
Eh...
Where did you get the fish?
I took this in Ueno...
In the Edo period, the sea won't wet the area here.
It was a fairy tale.
Really?
You're just like the senior.
Right?
Maybe it's Ryo-chan's ancestors.
Yes, you can see the history, but what about the tradition?
Speaking of tradition, it's a tradition that has been going on for a long time.
In other words,
This is the Japanese tradition, the pigeon bean magic!
I don't know such a tradition.
Besides, the pigeon.
You're running away, senior.
I see. This is the tradition.
If you're Japanese, you don't have to do pigeon bean magic at all.
As expected of the chief.
Yes.
Give me your hand.
I'll collect the bean stand later.
The water cruise written on the pamphlet.
It looks like this.
I feel like I'm walking, coming, and getting tired.
I'll go.
Go on.
What?!
Senior, don't just look at the sky, and love yourself too.
Looking at the sky like this, I remember the Ryo-tuke-chan's years when I was a child.
Ryo-tuke-chan's years?!
Senior, what's that?
In the past, a lot of people in the department store of Oka-chi-machi told me about the story of the principalmente from the Tsu-kunaniya store in the Ik permis.
Oh, I see.
He borrowed money from the bank and took in the watch that my father always bragged about.
However, he used the money for the bar and the sake and spent it all in one night.
My father was chased by his mother and finally jumped into the Sumida River from Azumabashi.
It was exactly the crisis of the Ryotsuke.
In the end, the watch that he cherished became a junk.
If he were my father, he would have looked at the money he didn't have and come up with it.
It's like Ryo-chan.
So what were you doing?
I was resting on the boat here all the time.
You're so strong. I can't do that.
If I had been the manager at that time, I might have been the manager by now.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
The upper one was broken by half an hour.
I want to take a break.
Not yet. Let's go next.
I'm just looking forward to it.
Well, that's okay.
Next is...
The best outlet in Japan is a budget.
After all...
Now, let's act freely.
Gather here in an hour.
Act freely?
Even if you say that, you will be pushed and washed away by the crowd.
Ryo-chan, what should I do?
Oh, there he is.
Ryo-chan.
What?
This is too much.
I paid for the entrance fee and the boat fee of the museum myself.
I'm just a fool.
Even if you say that, the budget is zero.
It can't be helped that you pay for it yourself.
But...
As long as I leave it to me, the manager should not speak.
Ryo-chan.
Ouch.
Idiot. Where are you looking at?
That's it.
No, dad.
Idiot.
Is the store okay?
I'm selling oil here.
Hey, you.
You went to skip the class again, didn't you?
It's the liquor.
You also wasted the money in the store and drank in the daytime, right?
Shut up!
I have to be polite to parents, right?
Awful.
You made it.
Don't you do that!
He did it.
Come on, catch it!
We will catch you, idiot.
Pretend not to be.
comparing.
Come on!
Let's go home!
What are you doing?
It's a movie!
Who's that?
I'm going home!
What's going on?
You're gonna get in trouble with your parents!
Don't kick a kid!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Everyone, it's the police!
The trouble has subsided!
What? The police?
That's right! Even if you resist, you'll be a sinner!
Ryo-tsu!
This is Senpai's father!
He's the one who causes trouble wherever he goes, this idiot!
Don't worry about it!
I won't do it today!
I'll go on a trip to Japan!
Let's look forward to the police's visit to Tokyo!
You get it, right, Chief?
You forgot about this, too.
You'll look forward to seeing Tokyo from my feet?
Being so bold, isn't that my turn?
What is it, Dad?
I'm already tired of you!
Don't be stupid!
We'll go to Ueno first!
We'll visit the art museum and visit Saigo's statue,
a dove and an egg!
Yay!
What?
Then, let's go to Shinobazu Ike
I rode a boat.
Damn it.
Then, in the rain...
Oh, I see.
You did it too.
My father has no way out.
Come on, I'm back.
What a son to disturb his parents.
I won't let you cross my line again.
You came the other day.
By the way, it's already evening.
Where is the inn tonight?
Oh, it's in Asakusa.
Asakusa?
Are you staying at a city hotel?
Well, that's the place.
Let's go.
Are we going to walk again?
Let's go by train.
No, no.
This trip is meaningful to walk.
Isn't that right, Chief?
Oh, yes, everyone.
It's only two or three kilometers.
Let's walk.
Chief Ohara today.
Don't you feel like you're holding your senior's shoulder?
That's right.
I wonder if you're holding something weak.
The talent to attach to the weakness of seniors is the best in the world.
Now, this is the inn.
Isn't it your senior's house?
That's right.
All you need is a roof and a futon, right?
But there is a Viking in the trip, which means that you can eat dinner anywhere.
Of course.
I'm not lying.
I'm telling you that this is a Viking who will eat dinner.
Which one among the three is the Viking who can eat at the end?
Viking?
I've heard in the village.
Hey, you're not going to inserted.
Not already inserted?
Today, there will be six residents.
If that's the case, you should say so.
But what will we do?
Our house is too small.
We don't have a bed.
I don't have a place to sleep.
It's okay, it's okay. Leave it to me.
Well then, everyone.
As I announced,
each of you brought a piece of food.
What? I brought something.
Please put it in the pot.
But mine is a cookie.
I brought a Chinese bun.
I put it in. It's a melon.
I brought a banana from Ameyoko.
I brought a caviar.
I don't care.
I'll put it in the pot.
It's the same as a dark pot.
You must eat what you grab with a chopsticks.
What?
I'm sorry, everyone.
I was wrong.
Chief?
What?
Actually...
What? I knew it.
I thought it was weird.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm a fool for leaving it to someone like you.
Chief, I'm such a fool.
But this was fun.
Yes, really.
We bought some good souvenirs.
That's right.
Hahahahahaha.
Ah, I'm sorry.
There is a lot of food, but Shime-kukuri is a fun meal.
Do you really eat this?
Of course. I am the only one who is on this trip.
As planned, I will eat this meal and go on a long trip to the Kamayari Park.
Look, the melon is also edible.
Let's eat.
Melon is quite good.
You can eat well, Ryo-san.
He has been eating anything since he was a kid.
Hey, chief. If he doesn't listen to you, please beat him up.
You don't have to say unnecessary things.
What are you doing?
You bastard.
Are you going to do it? You are a thief.
What did you do to your parents? I won't forgive you anymore.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm here.
You will start again.
Come on, everyone. Come here.
Are you all going to eat that strange thing?
I won't.
Let's eat rice with tsukudani.
It smells so good.
It smells good.
I feel bad for Ryo-chan.
What?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
This is a good one.
He is still doing it.
What?
Don't worry. Don't worry.
It seems that it has ended.
It seems that the pain is over.
Good night.
If you get angry, I won't forgive you.
You shouldn't say that. Stop snorting and being a coward.
What is that?
What?
Look! Over there!
Where?
What?
Can't you see because it's moving forward?
I'm not joking. I can see.
Hey, father.
Did you see the shooting star here long ago?
Oh, it was so.
What?
Father, there's a fire!
Where are you? Where are you? Where's the fire?
The store's cooking place is...
Someone call 119!
Father, let's go!
Yeah!
You're too stupid!
Next!
What's that?
Leave the rest to the main job.
The fireman's like his parents.
He's spitting water.
That's the job of a fireman.
Good work!
But he's gonna catch a cold if he's wet.
I heard the siren.
Right.
Oh, it's fine. I'll do it alone.
Just go to sleep.
Siren
I don't have money.
Don't worry.
I took it out of my mother's wallet.
As expected of your father.
You're the same as you used to be.
You idiot.
It's a secret from my mother.
If you're chased by me like when I was in a fight with Ryo,
I'll kill you.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Anyway,
Cheers!
Phew, it's so sweet.
But still.
You were so useless.
I'm grateful that you didn't become the police's troublemaker.
Well, in another way, you're a troublemaker.
Oh, I forgot.
I have something to give to my father.
Take it.
Kankichi, this is...
I bought it at Ameyoko.
It's your birthday tomorrow, right?
Huh.
It's cheap to buy it with your salary.
It looks old,
but it's similar to the old one, right?
Well...
Ryotsu.
Chief.
Can I have it, too?
Here you are.
Come on, Kankichi.
Put it over there.
I heard there was a fire right there.
The two who were active in the fire left without saying their names.
I'm sure they were good parents and children.
It seemed to be a good thing.
Yeah!
Let's drink tonight. I feel good.
Nice.
Boss, please give me more sake.
Yes.
You're a good drinker, boss.
Boss, the konnyaku here is delicious.
Really? Then I'll have that too.
And half a pen too.
This year's summer has come.
It's here! Here it is!
Let's drink a lot and have a great time.
Ah, I feel good.
This year's summer has come.
It's here! Here it is!
Get out! Get out!
Ah, this year is also a summer song
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Oh, I'm dying
Big, small waves, small waves, small waves, small waves, big waves, big waves
The wind of the south is blowing
Big, small ass, small ass, small ass, big ass
I'm getting excited
Ah, Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri Puri
The wind of the south is blowing
Nagisane-Puru-Puru
Nagisane-Puru-Puri
Terrible! What a terrible script!
Why do we have to do a swimming competition full of women in an old-fashioned play?
It was a mistake to leave the script to Ryotsu.
Next time, the masterpiece "Momotereira".
Thank you.
Thank you!