Closed Captions are on. Please do not redistribute. - ♪
I looked at the proportions from a long-legged horizontal grid ♪ ♪
Then topstruck by love, I even jumped into my shoes ♪
I wonder if I should go to the gym where I used to work out.
I was laughed at for being a crybaby.
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere,
I can't help but make a fuss.
The cityscape that never changes even when I yawn is strangely kind.
From the tapestry of a cap,
the sun sets to Taishakuten.
Tomorrow, it's already over.
If I win, I'll be happy again.
I'm not sure if I'll lose.
Because I'm such a fool.
Luslax Syndrome
Enomoto...
No more discussion is necessary.
I'll go by myself, okay?
Hijikata!
The flowers we sowed in the end of the explosion...
...will have to fall in the new era.
Sorry.
Hijikata, wait!
What will you do if you die?
Next time on the Flower of the End of the Explosion...
Please look forward to the final episode.
I can't watch it again.
I'm going to cry.
Even if I go against the flow of time...
...I will live without losing faith in myself.
I will not be led astray by the flow of time...
...and I will have to learn from the recent young people...
...who are always hanging out at night.
This...
No.
If it was this way...
This is it.
No!
Ouch!
That's it!
Hey!
Calm down!
This is it!
It's here!
What's up?
It can climb.
How long will it take?
How old are you?
How did you go into our town?
Are you afraid?
I've made friends a lot.
There's nothing else to do...
Oh crap...
Don't worry.
We don't know how to use these anymore!
We wet our pants.
Harry, you need to do something!
Why don't you take out the cordless electricity?
Hey, look!
-Wait! -Teacher, can I be a pilot?
Please do your best!
That show's ratings went over 30%!
Over 30%?
It's Bakumatsu no Hana, isn't it?
Komachi and the others said they were watching it.
My god is into it too,
and he watches all the TV shows.
The chief always makes sure to record it,
and he watches it at least three times.
Huh?
The chief is a huge fan of the historical dramas.
What are you two talking about?
It's about the historical dramas on TV.
I've never seen Bakumatsu no Hana, Ryo.
Bakumatsu no Hana? What's that?
No, Ryo.
You really don't know?
It's rare for a senior to be so loud.
I don't know!
I only watch TV, documentaries, and variety shows.
All I do is watch videos or play games.
Action!
Good morning.
That's why your head is always like a elementary school student.
Chief...
You're getting old, and you're making a railway model while working.
You're an idiot.
I'm not!
You're lying!
You're watching a video?
I bet you're a professional.
You're a completely newbie.
It's fine.
I don't care what people think.
Chief,
tonight is the last day of Bakumatsu no Hana.
I see.
I'm sorry about that, but I have a favor to ask.
Me?
Today's night shift is for the temple and the ryo,
but I can't make it.
I can't help you.
What?
Chief!
What do you want me to do?
I'm sorry to bother you,
but can you make a video of the last day of Bakumatsu no Hana?
My video is broken, so I'm fixing it.
That's easy.
I'm sorry, but I can't watch it tonight.
I'll leave it to you, Chief.
I'm tired.
I'll take a break.
The one with the dragon.
Starts at 10:00 on December 7th,
and ends at 10:56.
I'm sure of it.
But I'm worried about whether it will fit.
I'll watch it here.
The low pressure is approaching the Kanto region,
which has developed like a typhoon.
What are you doing?
I'm recording the Bakumatsu no Hana asked by the chief.
If it's a recording, you can set it with a timer.
Don't touch it.
I set the timer,
but if it doesn't work, it won't be recorded.
I have a responsibility asked by the chief.
I have to make sure.
You're so worried.
Then, look at the screen and record it until you feel good.
I will.
Don't worry about me.
It starts in 10 minutes.
What's the timer for?
Let's continue.
It's strange.
The power is out.
I don't know which one is which.
It's all right.
I did it.
Ryo, it's terrible.
The power is out.
I used too much electricity.
That's not true.
It's going to start in 5 minutes.
The breaker has fallen and the fuse has flown.
Don't worry.
One minute is enough.
It's not good.
The power is completely burnt.
I broke it. It's impossible to repair.
Why would it be like that?
By the way, when the fuse was cut off, it was not good to use the wire.
What are you going to do? The program will start!
If this happens, I will give up.
It's not like that. The chief asked me to do it.
I'm not asked.
You're so white. I'll tell you that it's because of Ryo's railway model.
That's not good!
I'll tell you even if it's not good. If this happens, Ryo and Shinju will be in trouble.
Wait, wait, I understand.
If there is no electricity, we can go to a place with electricity.
Eh? Where?
I don't have time anymore!
There it is. Let's get it from there.
What should we do?
What's wrong with the vending machine?
We have to turn off the power.
Eh? Are you okay, Ryo?
That's good.
How many minutes left?
Only 3 minutes left, Ryo.
Okay, 3 minutes is enough.
Ryo, you can't see anything.
That's strange.
I forgot the antenna.
Eh? What should we do?
I don't have an antenna.
Only 2 minutes left.
Okay, find something that will replace it.
Even if it's replaced...
Okay, that's it.
No, Ryo, only 1 minute.
Don't give up.
Connect the cable.
Okay.
Ryo, what are you doing? Hurry up!
Damn it. I didn't mean to do it.
How's that?
No, Ryo. Don't shoot it.
How's this?
No, no.
How about this?
Just a little more.
How about this time?
It's going to fall.
That's great, Ryo. It's going to fall.
What's the big deal?
It's not impossible for me.
Are you okay, Ryo?
No, I almost died.
Ryo?
No, I'm okay.
Good job.
Thank you.
How was it, Ryo?
There is no antenna.
No way.
How should I tell the director?
It's not good, Ryo.
You've improved it.
It can't be helped.
I'll have to turn it off.
It's an accident.
There's no choice.
It's not an accident.
The director came to enjoy it.
Calm down.
I'm not!
Ouch!
You should just say you got the video.
I'll know right away.
No one will know if you play it.
What?
In other words, you should get angry before the chief sees it.
The End
I'm home.
Chief, please leave.
Thank you.
What should I do? The chief is finally back.
Don't be so nervous.
Leave this to me.
Chief, thank you for your hard work.
It must have been tough in this cold weather.
Well, yes.
By the way, where's the temple?
The temple?
Oh, about the video from last night.
The video was...
Here, it's right here.
The video from last night?
Yes.
You took a good picture of it.
I don't want to, chief.
Of course I do.
I can't forget the earthquake, the storm, or anything else.
Hey, Terai!
Terai!
Yes?
I see.
I'm sorry.
No, thank you.
Then I'll give it to the chief.
Here you go.
Please give me a lesson, chief!
What?
Please, chief!
He...
Chief!
What are you doing?
The tape...
Please don't do that.
The tape!
The fireworks...
What are you doing?
You took a video from last night.
I see.
The chief hated me and got mean.
I'm sure he did.
N-No, that's not true! That was just a flash of a moment...
You're a devil, you devil!
That's why I said no, Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-chan, did you really record the last episode of "The Flower of the Eternity"?
Of course!
That wonderful last scene...
Even now, when I think about it, I feel so moved that my heart is pounding.
Don't stop me, Mother.
Meiji, call me!
I have to go!
That last line was wonderful!
Ryo-chan, Ryo-chan!
The "The Flower of the Eternity" that aired last night was canceled due to a special broadcast.
The final episode will air next week.
What?
Oh, is that so?
You idiot!
I won't forgive you for trying to hide your mistakes by making excuses!
Your life is always full of lies!
You'll regret it!
Oh, my EF-58!
You don't know that!
Chief, I'm really sorry.
Yeah, it's fine.
Ryo-tsu is to blame for everything.
The hero isn't to blame.
Damn it.
How can I leave him with such a grudge?
Look at this.
Look at the horror of making me the revenge demon!
I risked my life to climb up the elevator in the wind for the chief.
This is what happens when the chief is a mecha-ghost.
He must not know how to use the deck.
Well, for me, that's more convenient.
All right.
This is done.
Father, call Chief Ohara!
Hehehe.
The curtain of revenge has been cut off here.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm coming out now.
Yes, this is Ohara.
Yes, is that so?
I understand.
What's wrong?
It's from the electrician.
He said the video he put out will be tomorrow.
What did he say?
The last episode of the EF-58 is tonight.
I can't help it.
Oh...
I see!
What's wrong?!
What's going on?
Where have you been?
Chief, I have video !
Huh?!
What did you say?!
Video?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the other day I didn't come out pretty.
Well, well!
It's actually a good timing.
The video and the TV I put out for the repair have to come back by tomorrow.
Have you been there yet?
It's a video with audio reservation.
Even the chief of the Mecha-Onchi can easily operate this.
Anyway, all you have to do is talk to this TV.
You've made something useful.
Well, thank you.
How about you, Ryotsu?
Why don't we eat dinner together and watch the fireworks?
No, I have to go back to the station and get on the night shift.
So, today I'll do this.
Wait a minute!
It's strange that you refuse to invite me for a meal.
Is there something wrong with this?
No, I don't think so.
I'm going home to complete my duty as a police officer.
Like exploding when you turn on the video switch?
No way.
That's not going to happen.
Listen, like this.
Open your mouth.
Today's guest is Mr. Suzuki Emil.
Mr. Emil.
All you have to do is tell him to come here.
Today, you can watch the new movie that will be released next week.
When you're done, you can do this.
Open your mouth and clap your hands.
I see.
It's easy.
Right?
Then I'll do this.
Are you sure?
Ryotsu, I have to go.
It's time for the bus to come.
No, it's really okay.
Really?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm looking forward to this one.
Look at this, chief.
Okay, done.
I'll test it.
I'll try it.
I was surprised.
My heart isn't in good shape, chief.
What is he doing?
What?
Are you ready to see it now?
I don't know what's going to happen.
Like this.
Which one?
I'll try one.
Well...
I'll put it here.
And then I'll put the ojigi.
You're doing it, you're doing it.
Good.
Stop!
The ojigi doesn't feel right.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
No, don't say that.
Then show me your righteousness.
Awesome.
You're here.
Do you want to book a program?
Would you like to make a reservation for the club?
Yes, please.
A cherry blossom...
Then take off your clothes.
No, clothes?
And dance.
If you don't do that, you can't make a reservation.
No...
Huh?
Yes. I took it off and danced.
Don't lie!
Why?
You'll know right away by the sound of dancing.
If you're not motivated, you can't record.
I got it. I'll do it.
Ah, ice, ice.
I'm dying. I'm dying.
The rhythm is bad, but it's okay.
Now let's put on our pants.
What did you say?
Take off your pants and drink water in the garden.
If you don't, you can't record.
This is for the cherry blossom.
What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold.
Don't stop me.
I have to do this.
Oh, it's cold.
Okay, now it's the real show.
Oh...
Hey.
If you're so worried, father,
why don't you just turn on the TV?
I had a reservation.
I don't want to play dumb and break again.
Oh, forever.
Because you're still a child.
The news at nine o'clock.
I'll finish it.
Oh, it's working properly.
No matter what, it's the latest type.
This music is so good.
I'm looking forward to the last scene.
Izukata, wait!
What will happen to you if you die?
Why has Ryosu...
Good evening, captain!
In the next episode, I will be the lead actor
for the final episode of
"Bakumatsu no Hana."
What are you talking about?
Please move.
I can't see you.
That's not the point.
Hey, Ryosu.
Get back!
If I think about it,
you're going to turn on the switch with a big hit, right?
What should I do to turn off the video?
Oh, right.
I got it.
It's a lie!
Damn! You're a fool!
Oh, I see. It's a power outlet.
This time you tried to unplug the power outlet.
It's useless. If you unplug it, it will switch to the internal power.
It's called a backup function.
What the hell is that?
Well, here's a video of the chief's favorite performance.
It's called "The Sound of the Eclipse".
Oh, that's good!
Enjoy the music at high volume for eight hours until the morning.
That's good!
The Chief's Favorite Performance
Where's the big idiot of Ryo-tsu?
Ryo-tsu, come out!
He went to see a white bear in the south pole.
He went out earlier, but...
What?
Ryo-tsu!
I know some people say that I'm one of those women who can't even fall in love,
but I can't resist the desire to try a few things.
I want to ride through the desert on a motorcycle
I want to be free more than anyone else
The ready dream changes at the speed of a telescope
Love heart, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Dive into the future of the panorama
You know, right? I'm sorry, wait for me