Murakami Museum
When TV is on, warm the room and stand away!
Come to me, you people, who have no money.
I do, too, but I worry.
I'm worried about you
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen
When the sun goes down
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Come to me if you don't have a job
I don't have one, but I'm worried
Look, it's burning
Red
Red clouds
I wonder what will happen
I know, I know, I know
If you know, just follow me
Get out of there!
Thief!
Stop it!
Episode 2
Another of those scumbags.
This is the eighth case this week, right?
And they're still in the office.
I think we're incompetent.
They already think so.
What's the criminal going to do with the photos of the victims?
I think it's a bad habit.
Speaking of habits, Ryo, did you go get the thing the chief asked you to?
Huh? Oh, I forgot.
Please be careful, and be nice to Ohara-san.
I feel like the chief is paying 300,000 for something like this.
Thank you very much.
I'm hungry.
Then I won't eat beef.
I'll have to wait until tomorrow, Friday.
It's seven.
If I put this in seven...
No, I can't! This is the chief's precious...
But I can't change the flowers.
No, that's not good.
Because this is the chief's...
The chief won't die until tomorrow, will he?
I see.
Hmm.
So, how much are you going to lend me?
10,000 yen.
That's about 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
This is the white thing that has been worth 300,000 yen in that store until now.
You're doing a good job.
I can only lend you 10,000 yen.
If you don't like that, let's quit.
You're so stubborn.
But if I have 10,000 yen, I can eat grilled meat.
I'll borrow 10,000 yen to eat grilled meat.
I'll get paid tomorrow.
When that happens, I'll give you the money and take this.
The day after tomorrow, when the chief returns from his trip,
I'll give you a
Wait! Thief!
This is bad! I'm in the picture right now!
Wait!
It's the next round!
The受賞者緊張役会
There won't be another left turn.
I won't let you get away.
the受賞者緊張役会
I'm counting on you.
Three, two, one, go!
The car was wiped out in a flash.
I can't let this happen.
Wait.
The car was wiped out in a flash.
You can take me with you.
We have the head of the investigation department.
It's just a matter of time before we catch the culprit.
We need to get that picture back before the chief sees it.
The scene of the attack was in front of you.
Ryo, what were you doing?
I was patrolling, no matter what you think.
Ryo, you went to get the kakejiku that the chief asked you to, didn't you?
What about the kakejiku?
The kakejiku?
What?
You didn't put the chief's kakejiku in the sieve, did you?
It was on holiday.
The store was closed and I couldn't go get it.
And it was late at night on the way home, so I thought it might be something to dig up.
I just took a peek.
I see, I see.
I'm relieved.
That's right.
It's a robbery to put someone's things in the sieve.
I wouldn't do that.
I'm going to look for the kakejiku.
So bad!
What?
It was open until just now.
Give me the kakejiku back.
Please.
Hey!
I'll take the kakejiku back tomorrow.
It's a picture.
I have to get that picture back.
If you don't give me your own kakejiku, I'm going to eat you properly.
It was just on holiday.
I'm coming back.
To be safe, you have to thank me.
That something happened to that store's kakejiku,
It was a fraud.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to take that into consideration.
I was wondering where the kakejiku was.
That's right.
He's here! Don't let him escape!
Leave it to me.
There were two of them.
Yes.
They disappeared.
Damn it! Again!
I'll take care of the rest. Let's go, Honda!
Roger that.
What should we do, boss?
Honda! Follow that trailer!
Roger that.
Wait until I call you.
Mr. Furioso!
All right, I won't let you escape!
I finally arrived at the base.
Well, the boss is a rough man.
Mr. Furioso!
I don't think they will let me go.
I hope they don't let me go.
Boss, new employees?
I'm counting on you.
Me?
You're not like me.
Bingo!
Alright.
...
Where are those two?
Sorry!
Ah, you're a new employee, right?
This is the conference room.
No, that's...
...
This is the sales performance of the past 6 months.
Oh well.
Hm?
In this way, Hittakurika's
...
The results of the half year are in the process of processing.
Is it a trick?
Along with the promotion, it is becoming the luggage of my thief company.
Thief company?
That's all. At this rate, the March financial settlement and the June financial resolution will be canceled.
Thief...
You even put out a sign.
You put them out as hard as you can...
It's gonna be late soon so you should try to work harder.
Yes!
It's them!
Sir, where is the report of today'sезation?
Yes, sir.
Hm? I haven't seen it.
It's a group from today. Thank you for your kind cooperation.
Ah, right. Have you visited often.
I want to borrow your cat's hand too. I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, let's do our best together.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
You have to stop wearing uniform until the first button.
And our job is to run away.
Go to the general assembly later and get the shoes for the beauty.
No, I have this sandal as a trademark.
No, no.
I want you to do something that will disturb the atmosphere of the company.
You're disturbing the atmosphere of society.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
I have a question.
You all take pictures of the work site, right?
Why?
This is a proof photo that I did it.
This document is used as reference.
I will make a calculation of the salary.
Salary?
You're a thief, but you're paid?
This is a company.
You, take this as a proof.
Yes.
That's not all.
Two bonuses a year.
Employee trip.
I'm proud of my company's hardworking student.
It's like an ordinary company.
Thief company.
If you make this company a big deal, it's not a dream to raise the bonus.
I'll do my best.
By the way, Chief, what do you specialize in?
I'm a fraudster inbrewed in flowers.
I knew it.
Let's do our best.
Yeah.
You can't tell me your godfathers made you rend it to aって .
I'm sorry.
Oh, right.
This is...
Don't call me like that.
I'm glad you're okay, senpai.
I was worried.
Where are you now?
I stepped into a terrible place.
I'm sorry.
What? I can't hear you well.
Drone Co. Co. Trade?
It's close, but it's not.
Anyway, wait.
I'll contact you if you use the specific movements of the people.
While checking the enemy position, I have to take that picture back.
Kirikawa...
Hey, did you hear?
The president of Akisuka is moving out.
No way!
The police of the marriage fraud is also retiring within a year.
Shou!
I was aiming for it.
Is Izuko also the same landscape?
Oh, here!
Yeah, there he is!
The practice for the new person is going to start, so hurry up.
Practice?
100 yen, 200 yen...
If you count the three, four, and the small, you can ask the owner of the soba restaurant for a time.
What time is it now?
Then the owner of the shop...
It's five o'clock.
Six, seven...
Hey!
Nice to meet you!
The secret trick to earning 100 yen in a bid.
Oh!
Great!
What's the secret?
It's Rakugo's Tokisoba.
Even kids these days don't get caught with such a thing.
What did you say?
I was surprised.
I didn't notice at all.
Hide.
I can't see your stomach.
Pull it in.
OK.
Next is this.
Butt.
If you can't hide anywhere,
our company's employees won't work.
Stomach.
Next is this.
Butt.
I can do it!
OK.
It's done.
What's with this old-fashioned look?
It's the uniform of our company's night shift workers.
I'm glad to see you're back.
Let's go.
Hello, Senpai.
Hello?
Where are you going?
Let's start with the new employee.
Just follow me.
Don't worry.
We'll find the way out soon.
If we don't get good results,
If we don't raise the price, we'll be in trouble.
The company's management is also very strict.
I have a question.
Oh!
What?
If you're a thief...
Huh?
I can hear you. Speak loudly.
If you're a thief, you should work alone to earn money.
What?
Why do you work in a company?
The more middle-class thieves like us live,
the more this industry is not sweet.
The world is a mess lately.
We have to live together like us.
You can't eat alone, so you joined our company, right?
No, it's just a rust from the body.
Shinjin, if you stay here and there's a suspicious person,
let us know.
Okay.
I'm the suspicious one.
Let the siren ring and let's go.
Come to the third warehouse.
You don't have to let the main army know?
It's still early.
When you catch it, you'll be in trouble.
How is it?
A little more...
Hurry up.
No, it's like the latest Jomae.
Emergency call! Emergency call!
What?
A suspicious person is wandering around the truck.
What should I do?
I got it. I'm going right away.
If you see him, take him out.
What's this?
Five or six people with sunglasses and a black man in black clothes suddenly...
What?
I'm sure they're from the Gouto Co., Ltd.
Is there such a thing?
I can't do this.
I'll get back to normal soon.
What's wrong with this?
Sorry?
I thought we were a small company.
We have few employees.
Sometimes we're hired to help.
Don't say useless things.
Carry it on.
Shinji, you go with me.
What?
Honda.
Not yet?
Get out of my way.
It's a patrol car.
It's a white horse.
I can't help it.
I'm going back to the car.
Shinji, carry the rice.
He runs fast.
He's a good guy.
Today's result is zero.
Idiot!
He left the car on the scene.
It's not a waste.
The police wouldn't have done it anyway.
Try to keep the current law.
Come on, change the law.
If I move this, I can't eat anymore.
That's a shame.
I can't give my month's pay today.
It's a bomus topic.
The company trips are all dreams.
I'm sure this is it.
If we can't hit a big mountain with this.
We're all gonna end up in the sun.
I have something to tell you.
A big project that I've been working on is in progress.
Senior!
What? That's so reckless.
That's so reckless.
There's a thief, a thief, a thief, a thief, a thief.
I'll catch him in the second half.
This is a chance.
Hey!
Hey, you!
If you know what's going on, I'll follow you and contact you.
Hello, Ryo.
I'm in trouble.
It's too cool to go into the enemy alone.
It's better to call the headquarters.
The underground tunnel to the Kameari Bank is complete.
Yes, I'm ready.
But...
What's wrong?
The security is getting more and more strict.
It's better to postpone the next period and wait for the fire to cool.
If you say such a reckless thing, my company will be disbanded.
Should I do it or not?
Let's do it!
Hey!
We should definitely do it.
Let's make this project a success so that all the employees of the company can get through the March deadline.
What are you talking about?
This is not the place for newcomers.
That's right.
I want to pay for today's failure.
I'm ready to go to the party.
That's also fine.
But...
At the end, we have to be passionate about our work.
We have to have passion.
We have to have a feeling of going forward.
And the hopes of all the employees.
The company we love is life.
A difficult job is the path we should take.
Well, that's great.
Hey, Tokisoba.
Let's make this a success.
President.
Okay.
That's great.
I'll contact you later.
Before that...
I brought you the deadline.
But there's no one here.
I'm sorry.
Um...
The report...
If I can get this, I'll take this one.
What are you doing?
I brought you the deadline.
You're a newbie.
You brought me the deadline.
Anyway, it's work.
You should get ready.
Night shift?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
A maintenance team
One staff member
We have a cash
for rent.
All the employees are here, President.
Yes.
It's a job we've been doing since we started being peak employees.
I hope you won't get injured.
Please, be good.
Good luck.
We must do it well.
It's not like a endureance.
I didn't even know you're going to do something to me.
Eh, what?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
I can't contact you without a cell phone.
If I can't contact you, I'll be a thief's enemy.
But why am I the first to run away?
Good luck, newcomer.
All right, this is what real work is!
Go straight, go straight, go down the path you believe in.
Okay, my head is spinning.
Ouch!
Why is there a wall here?
All right, here we are.
What?
It's a bank that faces diagonally.
Then you don't have to dig this out.
You can just walk.
I finally fell down to where I was going to fall.
Oh, my God!
It's a bank!
Who is it?
Huh?
I did it, Mr. President!
Yeah, yeah.
It's the Bank!
In this case, I'll take care of them all by myself.
All right!
What?
Be a fool!
Y ocho!
Are you okay, Ryotsu?
Hey, sir! Welcome back!
I'm not worried about this life. I can't use it for hot springs.
But I understand this place.
The headquarters also grasped the existence of the people, but they were trying to measure the timing of the arrest.
Thanks to Ryotsu, I was able to solve the early problem unexpectedly. I was happy.
That's good. Senpai, I respect you. You're amazing, Senpai.
I don't like to act alone, but this time it's a good thing.
I'm proud of you, Ryotsu.
I feel uncomfortable when I'm praised by the chief.
Senpai, something fell.
What?
It's a photo.
This is the kakenjiku I bought. Why is it in the mirror? Why is Ryotsu receiving the money?
Explain, Ryotsu!
You idiot!
= A
"I'm home, Mom!"
♪ I think I'll be able to meet all of you ♩
Let's go!
♪ There's a wall over there ♩
♪ There's definitely a wall over there ♩
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♩
Thank you!
Eh!? It's Christmas, but I have to do a cake shop part-time job in the morning!
I'm helping Reiko volunteer, and making presents for the chief's grandson.
I can't let the temple be used as an amusement park for the best date of the Honda!
Next time, "Let's Jump, Christmas!"
I hope you'll join us!
♪ There's a wall over there ♩
♪ There's definitely a wall over there ♩
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♩
Thank you!