One
TV,
please
your
and
watch
a different
angle!"
Come
to
if you
money!
I don't
have
money,
but
I'm
worried
you.
Look
at
the
blue
sky,
the
white
clouds,
and
you'll
be
able
to
do
in
the
next
life!
I
'm
afraid
that
people
who
don't
work
Wait for me! Follow me!
Lemon's Unwilling to Eat!
What? Are you still sleeping?
Wake up quickly!
You're still early.
What are you talking about?
Stop talking and wake up!
Geez, you're short-tempered.
Kankichi!
Oh, Lemon. Good morning.
Kankichi, look!
Oh, it's a land cell.
I'm a first-year student from next year.
Grandma bought it for me.
Oh, I see.
It suits you well.
You're a quick-witted old woman.
Miss, have a nice trip.
Be careful.
Wait for me.
You're too early for anything.
I like the fresh air in the morning.
I was a little late because elementary school was close,
but I always go out of the house at this time from junior high school.
So,
I always go to school.
My family was early in the morning at Tsukudaniya.
I was always late.
You're late to your home.
Get up and do it.
Hmm.
Usually, women are late to do makeup, aren't they?
Why are you so early to do makeup?
Because,
I just wash my face, brush my teeth, and eat breakfast, right?
I'll be done in five minutes.
That's too early.
Maria said it would take one hour to do morning shampoo.
Too early.
Shampoo is at night, right?
Hey, you.
Ah.
She went to school early,
so,
you gotta wash your hair, too, right?
Mari,
It's an up Lower.
Ah,
I see..
It's so easy to get off the train in the morning.
But I'm not good at that long escalator.
It's always seen by everyone.
No one sees such a thing.
Kameari! Kameari!
The girl over there was energetic in the morning as well.
Maybe she's going to be an elementary schooler next year.
Are you telling me she's a inside little one?
Oh, the bus is here.
Well then, I'm going to the depction site.
Oh! Oh, right, you!
I have to go to the depction site over there.
Huh?
I made some lunch.
I made some kankichi, too.
Come to my place for lunch.
Okay, see you.
Chief Ohara, what's wrong?
R-Ryotsu is coming to Chikokubo Line.
I don't have to be surprised.
It might snow today.
He said he came to work from Matoi's house this morning.
Here's your tea.
Here, Chief.
Thanks.
Ryo-tsu, did you come to work at Matoi's house again?
It's a day before his payday.
Well, it's not a part-time job.
I went to get him some food.
So you came to work with Matoi.
So you didn't have to be late.
It's just a long day for him to come out early.
Matoi is really a nuisance.
You idiot!
You're always late and don't do your job properly.
What are you talking about?
Don't get so angry.
What?
Nothing.
Matoi, is that sushi?
Yes, it's sushi.
I made it this morning.
It looks delicious.
Can I have one?
Here you are.
It's delicious.
Komachi, one, please.
Sorry, I don't like fish with a lot of vinegar.
It's delicious.
But Komachi really hates fish with a lot of vinegar.
I don't like hijiki either.
Would you like to eat it?
I'll take it.
Here you are.
Oh, Ryo and Sankichi.
Who told you that I'd give you?
I already ate it.
You're such a Toad.
You're the one who hates to eat.
It's noisy.
You also have one or two things you don't like.
In my case, I only have two things I like and love.
You're a Toad.
I was a fool to think you were.
You know I'm a Toad.
Speaking of likes and dislikes, there's a little problem with the lemon.
With the lemon?
The lemon is a little bitter.
Ita-cho.
Yes?
You're a bit lost.
A famous flower.
A young stone.
It's true that this is a popular shop.
It might be impossible to say "don't be conscious."
But I don't need it.
The chokanda has the taste of chokanda.
It looks simple, but it's a good taste that you can enjoy with two or three people.
Be confident.
Yes, Lady Lemon.
Next, Sanpei.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you grill this fish?
There are too many fins.
Yes, ma'am.
And the seasoning.
What's the problem?
You're always so generous.
No.
I've been thinking that I've never had a liking or a dislike for food.
You don't, right?
As I thought, the soy sauce with miso is 6:4 white miso.
You always eat anything without leaving it.
You always nag.
It's.
It's a pamphlet from elementary school.
I brought it.
I made it for you, Lemon.
You're so quick-witted, Grandma.
I'm not bad at being quick.
Lemon, when you enter elementary school,
you'll have lunch instead of lunch.
What's lunch?
It's a meal you get at school.
You get it at school?
Look, it has a menu on it.
Wow! It looks delicious!
What's wrong, Lemon?
N-No, nothing.
The pamphlet I was looking at at that time was that.
Apparently, there's something you don't like in that menu.
It's a luxurious meal that doesn't compare to our time.
Times are too different.
It was a time of dashi stock, wasn't it, when Kankichi was young?
Well, yeah.
But...
I don't think there's anything you don't like in this menu.
I've eaten all the lemons except for the bread in the menu.
What? Bread?
You've never eaten bread, Lemon?
Yeah.
Hmm...
If you ask me,
I've never eaten bread in my family.
It's an unknown food.
Can you ask him?
Okay.
Hey, Lemon!
What is it, Kankichi?
Hmm...
I'm not sure, but...
Do you hate bread?
Of course I do!
I...
I don't think so.
Hey, don't lie to me.
Your eyes are running away.
They're not!
I...
I... I... I...
Hey!
Lemon!
Where are you?!
I'm sorry!
I'm not saying that you don't like bread.
There's a rule in elementary school lunch.
You have to eat without leaving anything.
What? I can't leave anything? Even if I don't like it?
That's right.
Really? Is it true, Matoi?
The rule is...
What if I left something?
Then what happens?
In that case, you'll be left in the classroom.
Left...
You'll be turned upside down!
Don't lie to me!
That's right, Kakichi!
I don't like turning upside down!
See? You scared Lemon, didn't you?
Yes.
Lemon doesn't want to go to elementary school anymore!
That's right, you idiot!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Don't worry, Lemon.
What?
You can't turn upside down.
That's good. But what about the leftover bread?
If you leave it for lunch, you can eat it after school.
You have to eat it alone in a classroom where there's no one.
If you do that, you'll be left behind.
Huh?
If you keep turning upside down...
Ahhhh!
You idiot!
You're persistent!
Lemon's scared again, isn't he?
Don't say that!
Does Lemon really hate bread?
We don't have one to try.
I'll go to the bakery and get it.
Lemon, I'm going to the bakery.
Lemon!
Hi!
I can already see it in your face.
It's easy to spot.
You're right.
Can't you eat it at all?
If I eat it...
Well, like this...
Maybe it's like eating biscuits until death...
I'm so thirsty that my throat is dry.
I don't know if you're hungry or not.
Anyway, just try it.
So, what should Lemon eat?
It's bread.
Then let's eat it.
Let's eat it.
I'm hungry.
It's not good.
I'm done.
It really doesn't taste good.
You've had my Katsu-sand before, haven't you?
Katsu-sand is moist, so you can just pour it in with milk.
But...
The problem is that it's a single-use product.
It's not dry, or soft, or fluffy like it used to be.
That's not good.
But I have to fix it before going to school.
I feel like going to school is getting depressed.
You've gotten worried about how it is, haven't you?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
I just hate it when it's not eaten.
I'll make sure it's edible.
Hey, wait for me, Chutorou!
I'll add the milk colored with saffron.
All right.
All right, all right, I'll shape it, roll it up, and put it in the oven.
Next, I'll...
What are you making?
Making food using bread.
It looks like he's trying to make me eat it somehow.
I think it's a difficult trick to trick your tongue with lemon.
Let's eat!
It smells like bread.
What are you talking about? There's no bread anywhere.
That's right, it smells like bread.
It smells like bread.
What's this?
It's a grilled egg.
You can see it's a grilled egg from anywhere.
See, it's bread.
It's a four-color French toast.
I knew it.
What's this?
It's a mo-men tofu. It's delicious.
It's a bread.
I'm surprised.
I didn't know there was bread here.
It still smells like bread.
It smells like bread.
What's this miso soup?
It's fried tofu.
It's bread, too.
That's right, it's fried tofu-like bread miso soup.
What about sushi?
It's all bread.
That's right, it's a new menu, Western-style sushi.
I told you I don't like bread.
I see. I'm sorry.
Hurry up and eat.
Oh, my God.
I don't like the bread that you made with your teeth curled up.
No, no, no, no.
You shouldn't do that.
I lost.
Lemon is quite tough.
It's impossible to deceive.
Damn it. I'm not giving up.
All right.
Let's go, Lemon.
Oh, nice catch.
Kankichi, I'm tired. Let's take a break.
What? Are you tired already?
You can't go to elementary school like that.
What?
Elementary school is hard, unlike kindergarten.
Is that so?
If that's the case, tell your teacher to start over from kindergarten.
I don't want to.
Kankichi, let's continue.
You're a child after all.
You should exercise until you get tired and get hungry.
There.
Hey.
How is it? Are you tired, Lemon?
No, it's not a big deal.
As expected, you're a child.
I'm getting hungry.
It's not a part of your nature to be an adult.
What?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
If you get hungry, you're an adult.
I'm hungry.
Grandma, is dinner ready?
Kikyo and Matoi will get it ready.
I'm ready.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Itadakimasu!
Here we go.
I'm sorry, Lemon. The rice is gone.
You can put up with this tonight.
Did you cut the rice even though we're a sushi restaurant?
It doesn't matter.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I'm sure it's delicious.
Itadakimasu!
The ham tastes so good.
The bread doesn't get in the way.
It's a beautiful harmony.
This vegetable sandwich and egg sandwich are delicious.
It's a luxury.
I can eat as much as I want.
I'm sure everyone wants to eat.
It's really good.
I'm hungry, so I'll eat as much as I want.
It's delicious.
How much?
Idiot!
his food!
Kankichi!
Oh, my goodness.
I think I've cooled off.
L- Lemon!
I'm sorry!
As I was expected.
What is it, Kankichi?
You fed us all the bread that Lemon didn't like, didn't you?
I'll ask Sanpei to make something for us, so it's fine.
T-too hard!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
It's not like that.
Kankichi is just stupid.
That's right.
Damn it!
If this happens, there will be no other way!
Mikan, eat.
No!
Mikan, don't worry.
Mikan, don't you want to eat?
I'm not good at eating spinach.
I eat other things often.
But I'll make you some cocoa now.
Okay.
Mikan, you can't grow if you don't eat well.
You can't do whatever you want.
Mikan, I don't hate lemon.
And I don't hate oranges either.
Oh, you're great, Mikan!
Mikan, don't worry.
I'll give you a burger.
The next day
What's going on?
I don't know...
Who convinced Lemon?
I don't know, but it must be a very skilled negotiator.
But it's the first time in 102 years that bread has been alive since morning.
Lemon, you're the best!
I don't have any likes or dislikes.
Let's eat!
Yes!
Lemon, you're the best!
Well done!
It's delicious!
You're not a bad boy!
You don't eat bread!
Who are you?
I'll eat you if you don't eat!
You're eating well, so you're not fat.
What's going on?
Kankichi!
Lemon, you can eat bread now!
Yes, it's delicious, Kankichi!
Really?
Kankichi!
What?
You're surprising people!
No, I'm not!
Wait!
Because of you, my life has shrunk by one year.
Even though 102 years have been alive, it's only one or two years!
Even if it shrunk, it doesn't mean anything!
Shut up!
I'm going to eat it!
Come on!
Help me!
Wait, I'm going to eat it!
I'll understand if you let me go!
You'll understand, Kankichi!
Stop it!
I want to eat it!
I'm looking forward to going to elementary school.
Stop it!
I want to eat it!
Why!
Why?
Good job, guys!
Even though Lemon is a kindergarten student,
he likes historical dramas.
Why?
His little beard is a little bit small.
Mr. Kida, when you ride a motorcycle, your personality changes. Why?
Why?
The "Neruo" who lives in the sun only happens once every four years. Why?
Mr. Nakagawa does not lend money to the mass production company,
but he can easily lend a tank or fighter.
Why?
Mr. Reiko is very rich,
but he works in a gas station. Why?
Why?
What? You want to be my teacher?
Okay, let me do that.
I wanted to be a teacher like a TV drama.
Why?
Everyone, listen to me.
Next time, "3-year class B teacher, Kankichi",
Thank you.
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!