When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and look away
The end of the rain, as if someone is calling
I walked while looking back
I reached out to my mom
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black side of the Ake-do-gai
I walked on the black side of the Ake-do-gai
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a grand face
A blue-eyed old lady
Turn around and see that corner
You can see everyone
There are a lot of walls over there
Ah, the Kamehameha
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
Change it with calcium!
The story is going up!
How about we start the lesson now?
Hey, your eyebrows are connected.
Don't mess with me!
Are you going to teach me or not?
Okay, I'll do it.
Really?
If you pay me a million yen for the lesson, I'll pay you.
You bastard!
You're not going to pay me!
Are you going to take off your clothes?
I'm against violence!
Call the lawyer!
Call him and teach me!
Stop it, Ryo!
Take that!
Not yet!
I don't want to see you anymore!
Hurry up and teach me!
Come on!
Hurry up!
I'm not going to leave you!
Hey, you're so stubborn!
You should have beaten this villain!
He's not a real villain!
That's right.
This is a research competition.
Hey, stop it!
No, no!
It's my turn!
Do you always do this kind of research?
No, not at all.
This is where my true power comes from!
If you beat him a little more,
you will be punished for sure!
Okay, you got it!
Come on, Ryo!
Take this and teach me!
That's right!
Ryo, it's a game you want to play!
Do you hate to watch the police doing this?
You're right, Geogre.
I can't lose to them.
If you're going to thank them,
you should have pretty good luck.
You heard, give it away to Kikuni.
Hey, stop!
Oh, no, the Roman numerals.
It's a "buzz." That means you're disqualified.
What about my bonus then?
You can't get it! There's no bonus!
No! No way!
Damn it! I thought I'd get an extra bonus, but I can't get it!
Ryo-chan's way of doing things is too rough.
Why? I'm doing worse things in the historical drama!
I'm doing even worse things in the historical drama!
Unlike in the old days, we need to be more considerate of human rights now.
You need courage and patience for investigation, like Chief Ohara.
What about the Chief? I have courage and patience!
I made 100 plastic models and played games for 48 hours in a row!
Excuse me, the ball...
You... You just hit me with the ball!
I-I'm sorry.
You're never going to play here again!
Where was your patience and patience for such a moment?
That was a light joke, wasn't it?
I wanted to bring a story to bring your bonus back to life.
The bonus is back?
It's no use getting worked up.
Then please say it soon, Chief.
That's a bad boy.
Anyway, follow me.
Yes, I will follow you.
Debate school?
Let's go.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm the head of the school,
Katta Toron.
I'm Ohara from the Katsushika school.
And this is the problem,
Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
Ouch!
Please stop, chief.
What school is this?
That's why I'm talking about debate.
Was "debate" a pun?
If you're going to say that, it's "rebate"!
Debate is a discussion session.
For example,
you decide on the themes of socialism and democracy,
discuss which is better,
and tell the other person.
The winner or loser is decided by the gallery.
Well, you can say it's a sport based on words.
Hmm, I see.
In short, it's a quarrel.
It's not just a quarrel.
You have to convince the surroundings with words.
Courage, patience,
and even more,
you need to have a very advanced debate technique.
I see.
Your biggest problem is that you can't say anything.
From now on, you have to go to this school for two weeks
and you have to do something about your personality.
Two weeks?
Do I have to spend two weeks with this old man?
Not "old man",
it's "Katta Toron".
Otherwise, you won't get a bonus.
I understand.
By the way,
I've been wondering,
why are the letters of "tsu" so small?
Hehehe.
What's wrong, Sensei?
You're already losing.
What did you say?
You still don't get it?
You've fallen into the trap of the debate I set up.
A trap?
What do you mean?
Anyone will soon realize that the letters of "tsu" are small.
Next question.
I'd like to ask you a question.
But,
I'm sure the person who asked the question
has already guessed it.
I'm sure the answer is ready.
Therefore,
I'm going to ask you a question,
but you'll have to use your theory of the theory.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
You'll be beaten to death.
This is "Katta-ryu Debate Jutsu".
"Katta-ryu Debate Jutsu"
See the description below for 20 minutes.
Here it is.
"Katta-ryu Debate Jutsu"
"Kight risen from the Maleno"
No matter what the other party says, you must not use violence.
Yes sir!
What is it, Ryotsu-kun?
Why are your "tsu" letters so small?
I told you earlier that it's a trap!
I'm worried about it, so it can't be helped!
I'm waiting for the real theory!
I want to hear that theory!
Well then, one more important point is...
Hey, don't fool me!
I'll tell you strongly.
Hey, you don't really think about theory or anything, do you?
Actually, you just want to get attention, that's all.
You're so stupid.
Damn it!
What are you doing? You suddenly...
Stop asking me stupid questions and concentrate on my attack!
I thought violence wasn't allowed!
You're so noisy.
I'm the one who rules here!
This is the "Katta-ryu" debate technique.
I'm the one who rules here, Ken.
That's not a debate!
If you're going to do that, then you're fighting the Ryotsu-ryu!
What are you doing towards the front?
There are teachers and students here!
What are you doing?
You two are each on my side.
Alright, then, I won't be fighting at the front.
Let's do it thinking about the front.
Let's do it thinking about the back.
I'm not going to fight against the front.
I'll make Ryotsu-ryu in my area, then, me in your area, and...
Oh, that's far out!
Of course, I'm the one who rules this school.
I am, of course.
If you're going to be angry, you have to supply calcium.
But it won't work even if you supply it during the debate.
You should have said that!
I'm in charge here.
You didn't use any calcium at all.
I was just trying to be angry.
You were serious.
I don't care. I'm in charge of whether you graduate from this school.
You know that, right?
That's right. My bonus is in charge.
I have a nice present for you.
A bottle of high-quality calcium from the right.
A little high-quality calcium from the left.
Which one do you want?
Are you taking money?
I'll fix your angry life!
You think you can buy it?
No! You fix it first.
Besides, I don't have money to buy such a thing.
Then, I'll buy all your meals from today.
What?
Fish with a lot of calcium.
This is the only way to get rid of it.
Fish are full of calcium, so you should eat them as usual.
You're joking, right?
Why do you have to eat all that?
Don't you want a bonus?
Oh, I see.
I see. I should eat them.
Then, I'll go patrol.
Damn it! I was so frustrated that I didn't want to eat fish for three days.
I'll listen to the radio and calm down.
It's time for the race.
The hero this time is a raccoon.
Take this raccoon to the front of the court and sing like this.
Tan-tan-tanuki's
And finally, the butt.
That's it.
It's easy, isn't it?
But won't you get angry?
It's okay.
If you see this sign, you'll forgive me.
Because it's famous on TV.
It was popular before that a raccoon carried a bag and went to a bag shop.
If you like this time, I'll think about it.
Really?
Yes, I'll do my best!
All right, good. That's it.
There, there.
There, there, there.
Why can't I reach it?
Um.
What?
No, no. I cut it.
What can I do for you?
Well, um.
Tan-tan-tanuki's
I'm Andriyanov.
No, no.
But, but, my butt hurts.
You!
You! Are you kidding me?
No, no.
I'm not kidding.
I'm just a job.
Do you have such a job?
Yes, I do.
Hello, hello.
It's a surprise camera.
What?
Um. That surprise camera.
What's wrong with that?
Normally, if you say surprise camera,
I'll forgive you.
No, no.
No matter how much I try, I'll be angry now.
The patience is not good at all.
You!
I'm waiting.
I have to get into the kitchen.
I should have prepared this question.
Oh, that rice.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's talking about you.
Don't hold it up.
Hey, what's up with him?
He's my teacher.
I've a chance to teach him.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
That's not true.
I'm what?
What?
I don't see the meaning.
But I can say all Digimon's names.
What's the use of knowing that?
I'm familiar with military weapons and I know how to shoot the Patriot Missiles correctly.
Even if you know that, you can't talk to the common people.
You're naive.
The one I'm debating against is mainly a criminal.
A criminal is a person who has violated common sense.
There's no way a common sense would work against such a person.
That's true.
To tell criminals, the more useful is to have maniacal knowledge.
I see.
Oh no! I was told off!
Cut!
I knew you were good at teaching me.
You've mastered the debate technique so far.
So, are you graduating?
Yes. But...
But?
Well, if you don't get angry today, you'll get a little bit of a promotion.
Oh, I don't have any bonuses.
I'm sorry. I didn't think you'd put it here.
I-I'm sure this is a super rare plastic model that you got from overseas.
What?
This?
A-A model that has a shape will break one day.
Don't worry about it, Reiko.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
Excuse me, ball.
Uh...
I-Is that a ball?
You're not going to play here from now on, are you?
Yes! Thank you!
I-I'm sorry.
Ryo, you were always so loud.
I'm not stupid enough to get angry and get a bonus for this.
I'm going to call Ryo the Buddha from now on.
Oh no!
That's where the drunkenness is raging!
What?
What did you say?
Uh...
What should I do?
Here.
Is Ryo really going to investigate?
Hey, leave it to this Buddha Ryo-san.
Damn it.
Don't you have any alcohol?
Well, will you tell me your name?
You're an idiot.
Wait, I'm just kidding.
Senior.
Senior, it's important to listen to your partner.
I know.
Don't worry, Kagawa.
Hey, alcohol.
You like alcohol too? I like alcohol too.
Yeah. You're a good match, Omari-san.
Yeah, yeah. Alcohol is delicious, isn't it?
I want to drink it with you two.
Yeah.
That's right. Will you tell me your name?
Oh, my name.
Okay, I'll write it down.
Senior.
You did it, Ryo-chan.
Yeah.
If you come this far, you'll be in trouble.
Okay, I wrote it down.
Which one?
That's a rare name, isn't it?
I'll take a deep breath.
You're lying, you idiot!
Senior.
Ryo-chan.
She's laughing.
Are you okay?
I'm not.
But you always take your hands out long ago.
I was born to be like that.
I can't do anything like that to my father if I take my hands out during a discussion.
Is it the effect of calcium?
I wonder how long it lasts.
Well, after your play is over, will you tell me your name and address?
Yeah.
I'll tell you if you show me your address.
Nakagawa.
Yes.
Bring me some small fish.
Okay.
Here you go.
I'll give you some calcium.
What?
You're eating small fish.
You're a big fish, aren't you?
Actually, I was a whale in my natural life.
That laugh is scary.
Really?
If you show me your address, I'll tell you.
Of course.
Here you go.
Wow, it's real.
Well, will you tell me?
You're a really nice person.
Yes, I'll tell you anything.
I finally understand.
You did it, Senpai.
I'm glad, Ryo.
Well, it's all thanks to you, Ryo.
What?
I won't be fooled.
I've been caught.
I did it.
Senpai.
Didn't I tell you?
I won't get angry anymore.
This much is enough to play.
Now, will you give it back?
I'll write! I'll write! I'll write anything!
So please forgive me!
Eh?
I-I've endured it...
But, Ryo-chan's now is 100 times scarier than usual!
Ah, it's big!
After this festival's celebration, today's work is done.
Yeah, with this, my training is over.
I can get a bonus too-
Ah!
You!
It's not you!
It's Katta Toron!
Hey, Ryozu!
You're rude to your teacher!
Katta-san came all the way here to give you a bonus for graduation!
That's right!
Ah!
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
If you give him a bonus for graduation,
I'm sure he'll be able to...
Kanda, I'm really sorry!
If you're going to give him a bonus,
I'd like to ask you to hurry!
Ouch!
If it's not past 12:00,
I'm not giving you this.
Tch.
I was told that I'd be fine.
Nakagawa-kun,
is Ryozu really okay?
Yes.
No matter what happens,
he won't get angry.
Well then, I'll get going!
Ouch!
Oh!
I-I'm sorry...
It's fine.
There are a lot of people out today.
If you run, you'll get hurt.
Yes, sir!
Be careful.
Oh, I see.
His personality has changed.
He's fine in this state, though.
Everyone,
thank you for your hard work.
Please.
No, we're still working.
Please, have a drink.
No, I'll have a drink.
Isn't that a little too much?
It's a festival.
Well, here you go.
Don't hesitate.
Is that so?
Then, just one drink.
This is a wonderful drink.
As expected.
Today seems to be a day of good health.
What?
What happened?
The police are scared,
so I can't drink.
Senpai, that guy...
You're trying to try me again, aren't you?
Leave it to me.
What's wrong, sir?
I saw him somewhere.
He's lost his mind again.
Now, he's in the way of other people.
Let's go over there.
Don't touch me!
Are you all right, sir?
Don't be so rude!
This is...
I can't stand it!
What?
He's just going crazy over a drink?
Yeah.
I didn't think he was that bad at drinking.
Then, are you trying to test him?
I'm sure he's thinking a lot.
I see.
I-Is that so?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
For the bonus, I...
I-I can't stand it!
Hey, you're gonna have to pay for it.
I can't stand it!
I don't care about the bonus.
I'll destroy you!
I'm still not done!
I'm finally scared of you.
I don't care.
Let me go!
I like alcohol.
But I hate drinking!
Ryo, you're gonna hit my heart!
Wait!
If we talk, I'm sure we'll understand each other!
Shut up!
You bastard!
How dare you!
Help me!
Stop it!
I had a bad feeling about this...
I know. Ryo-chan's personality doesn't change suddenly.
So, where is Senpai now?
So that we don't bother other people, we're doing special training alone.
You! It's dirty! It's the fish we caught!
The bones of the fish contain a lot of calcium.
The bones will be yours later!
What are you talking about? Let me eat it too!
You bastard!
Stop it!
Let me eat it!
I'm the genius magician Pierre Nishikaguchi.
I'm sure you're cheating by calling me a mansion.
I'll show you how to escape with my magic.
Next time, I'll be a body magician.
See you!