Please turn on captions for the sake of the video.
Please turn on subtitles for the sake of the video.
When you're watching TV, make the room bright and look away.
Come to me if you don't have money.
I don't have any money, but I worry.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I wonder what will happen in the meantime.
Come to me if you don't have any work.
Come to me.
I don't have any money, but I worry.
Look at the red cloud burning.
I wonder what will happen in the meantime.
Come to me if you don't have any work.
See you at dawn.
I know you don't have any work, but I worry.
I don't have any work, but I worry.
The sky is blue and the sun is shining.
I know nothing happened on this day.
I don't know what you have done on this day.
There's nothing to be ashamed.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
"Hara-heeey!"
"Drink some water and let that Harana-mushi stay quiet, you idiot!"
"Ah, sir!"
"Good morning!"
"Good morning."
"Sir..."
"I don't know anything!"
"Huh?"
"You're telling me to use my salary as a marketer and to borrow money from you, right?"
"Amazing! I'm seeing through everything!"
"As expected of you, sir."
"Huh! Everything is written on your face, you idiot!"
"Idiot..."
"Ah, that's right! Listen, Ryotsu!"
"With the salary you're receiving as a police officer, you should be able to eat enough!"
"Don't just do your job and spend money on stupid things, and save it!"
"You're asking me what I'm going to use my money for, right? That's too much!"
"That's no use!"
"I'm hungry, I'm hungry..."
"Aah! It's the blessing of God!"
"Wait, wait, sir."
"Huh?"
"I dropped it, you know."
"What?!"
"I can't help it..."
"Ugh..."
"Oh, you're hungry?"
"Uh, yeah..."
"Then come over here!"
"Huh?"
"Huh?!"
"Huh?! I finally feel comfortable!"
"Aah..."
"Even so, it's a big garden..."
"Even so, we're the most popular neighborhood around here."
"Huh..."
"If it's this big, cleaning alone alone is a lot of work."
"What are you going to do with that?"
"A trash bin in the backyard..."
"I'll just throw it away."
"Okay, thanks for warning me."
"What's your name, sir?"
"Are you Shogun?"
"Your name is Shogun. Are you a Shogun, too?"
"You're a Shogun, too, aren't you?"
"No. What's your name?"
"I'm a Shogun. I don't know why I am..."
"Oh, I'm Shogun, too."
"Ah..."
"I have one too!"
*Dogs barking*
Hm?
What is this?
Ah!
It's a...
It's a bat!
I mean, it's a toy anyway.
It's not that sweet in the world.
*Gasp*
Huh?
*Growls*
*Groans*
*Bite*
Is this...
Is this real?
*Groans*
Hey, Tomari!
Good work!
Your tea's ready.
Come over here and take a break.
N-No!
Never mind!
I hate tea!
I hate taking a break!
Huh?
Never mind!
We're still in the middle of work.
Right?
Is that so?
*Sigh*
500 yen is a little
different from what you'd expect.
I'll be back.
Ryozu?
Ne... captain!
What are you doing over there?
Not that.
How suspicious.
You are hiding something, arent you?
No, I am not hiding anything.
What is this?
Isn't this a hospital bed?
Looks like so...
Not a mother!
Grandma!
Grandma! Grandma!
Yes?
The old man came out of the garden.
What? The old man?
Damn it! I found him!
The old man belongs to the old woman!
There's no other way, Ryo.
There was definitely a writing saying that the ancestor of the road builder was buried.
It's bad for the factory. You should give up quietly.
That's right. It's happy to just taste the old man's food.
Is Ryo-tsu here?
Who?
Ryo-tsu is here, but I need to help dig a hole.
Chief, I'm good at digging holes.
Oh.
Oh, oh.
Ryo-tsu's performance so far has been very good, dear.
Even the way he speaks has changed.
He's becoming a Miyabi.
Therefore, I have granted a reward to Ryo-tsu from the road builder family, dear.
Please accept it without hesitation.
Well, goodbye, dear.
I was surprised to see that change.
Oh, what?
He said it was a reward, but there's only one piece.
He's so stubborn.
Don't complain about getting things from people.
Oh, what?
It's just a piece of paper.
This is called a piece of paper.
1, 10, 100, 1000, 10,000, 100,000, 1,000,000, 1,000,000...
My heart is getting faster and faster.
10,000,000.
100,000,000.
100,000,000?
100,000,000 for Ryo-chan?
Ryo-tsu, be strong.
This is the last chance God has given you.
Spend all your money right now.
That's right.
This time, you should listen to what the chief says, Ryo-tsu.
If you think about using it for your senior's sake,
it will be gone in no time.
Spend?
That's my book.
I don't have such a book.
You idiot.
Listen carefully, Ryo-tsu.
There's a fairy tale called "Ari and Kirigiri".
I don't know such a thing.
I know about the battle between Ari and Inoki.
Once upon a time, there was a place where Ari and Kirigiri lived.
One day, God gave them 100,000,000 yen for free.
Wow, that's a lot of money.
Let's play hard with this.
Kirigiri-san thought it was better to play when he was young.
Let's buy a car.
I want a bike.
And then, let's go abroad.
He spent all his money on leisure activities and enjoyed his life.
On the other hand, Ari-san spent 100,000,000 yen on regular activities and worked hard to increase his income.
Eventually, he bought a small land.
It's my land.
Let's build a house here.
Twenty years later, he built a house.
All the money was transferred to the house and he started to buy more and more.
Later, when Ari-san was up on the bench, he used 100,000,000 yen to sell the house on the motorway.
The 기리기리.
I guess you messed it up.
Did you understand the importance of saving?
There is something we shouldn't have told you.
Ah, I see.
Actually, that's true.
But money can be used.
What did you say?
Don't say it in the stereo! I got it!
Then, this time, I'll listen to what the chief says and save it all.
That's right. 20 years later,
"Oh, I'm glad I listened to what the chief said."
The day will come.
But is this really worth 100 million?
You don't seem to understand unless you show me the cash.
This is all my money!
Now, I understand, Ryotsu.
Senpai!
Ryotsu!
Are you alright, Renko?
Wait, Ryotsu!
Senpai, as soon as I saw the cash,
it was completely wild.
It's like showing a cat a dried bonito.
I don't care anymore!
I want to be a stray like Key Gillis!
It's all my money!
It's all mine!
What should I do first?
Try to make a full account of the money you have.
They said it's a special sushi.
I'm going to buy some sandals.
Oh, I see.
I'll buy sandals for 10 years!
What?
What are you going to do next?
I have a lot of money.
What?
That's right. Let's buy sandals.
Is that so?
The third race
The fourth race
The fifth race
The sixth race
This is the Kirigiri style.
The fifth race
Did you spend all 100 million yen?
I knew it.
It was only a day.
I said that much, but I was completely stunned.
I thought you would help me.
I spent 500 yen.
Please help me.
I don't know.
I don't think I've lost 100 yen.
Is it your day-to-day bath?
Are you sick?
What's wrong?
Do you hurt somewhere?
No, I'm a little dizzy.
It can't be helped.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I'm hungry.
I'll pick up a strange old man.
Thank you.
I feel much better.
I'm going to eat bread.
We will eat together.
Are you drawing a picture?
Yes, it's a picture of an old man.
Which one?
I'll take a look.
What's this?
It's not easy to understand.
I'm often told that.
Anyway, the picture is terrible.
I'm 100 times better.
I can't draw what I like.
I'm a serial manga artist.
But I became an anime director in the series.
Do you know?
That's a bit of a lie.
I'll teach you how to draw.
You should start over from the basics.
You're very modest.
So you drew my face.
What do you think is similar?
It's worse than manga.
I remember seeing this picture somewhere.
I did, too.
Look at this.
This sign...
It's Okamoto Bakudan-sensei!
What?!
He's a world-famous abstract artist!
If it's Bakudan-sensei's painting, it'll be worth thousands of dollars!
A poor artist like him?
I-If you say that, it feels like an artistic work.
Ryotsu!
What the hell did you do?!
W-What are you talking about?!
The human-revealed Okamoto Bakudan's painting is for you!
I even visited his office!
I visited his office!
Did you paint or light a fire in the studio?
Be quiet and say your lines!
You're wrong!
Senpai saved the place where Okamoto Gahaku was dead!
What did you say?
This is... this is... Ryotsu-sama...
You're from that old man's place, right?
In fact, my husband passed away the other day...
I'm sorry...
Huh?! That old man?!
Sorry...
She was alive...
I was afraid that I couldn't hear...
I should have martyred him, no matter what, but...
You're right.
I was very curious about this, and I've decided to ask you to give your property to me from now on.
Ryotsu-sama...
I heard that Okamoto Gahaku's estate used to be his property, Ryotsu-sama.
You can see that there's a lot left in his house.
I think I can even make a transfer to him now.
I can!
Why?
I, Ryotsu, will do anything this time!
W-w-wait a minute!
There are so many numbers, I can't find them!
There are 200 cases worth 100 million yen.
All of them are 10,000 yen bills?
Of course!
That's amazing!
I'm getting dizzy.
I have a little blood pressure.
Are you okay?
Master is envious of Ryotsu's free and honest way of life.
He said he had a lot of fun meeting you.
So, please use up all of this property as you please.
Use up everything?
Ryo, that's not good! Stop it!
However, there is a deadline.
A deadline?
That's right.
Master's request is to use up all of it in one week.
If you can't use up half of the 100 million yen in one week,
you'll be fined for the whole amount.
100 million yen in one week?
I can't take it anymore.
Me neither!
All right! I got it!
You said you got it, Ryo!
I'll use up all of it with my grandpa's will!
Are you serious, Master?
That's my grandpa's will, so I have no choice but to do it!
Even if you use up 100 million yen,
you'll still have the remaining 100 million yen.
Is there such a good story?
I'm glad you said that.
That's why you're the man I saw in my husband.
I'll take this will to my husband and deliver it to him.
Leave it to me!
All right, let's go!
Otaro, you're a big man,
and you're a big man, too!
Let's eat!
Yum!
In a gold box!
Well!
How much is this?
It'll be 180,000 yen!
What?
Just that much?
That's 99,99882,000 yen.
What?
Okay, I'll buy three more souvenirs!
We're still starting.
I'm going to Tokyo.
I bought all the toys in the market.
It's a bit cramped.
The master who died can't be found.
What the rich guy is doing is...
It's a big cruiser!
Move, move!
You will die if you crash!
You drink champagne while looking at the sunset.
This is what the rich guy does.
You still have a long way to go.
I know.
Speaking of what the rich guy does...
The other day, a policeman who owned a huge property in Okamoto Bakudan started doing something terrible.
He said,
"Where do you live?"
He started to build a house to run a private railway from Shinshin-ryo to Kimusaki-no-Koban.
Ryo-san, are you sure you want to run a train here?
I'll get back to Ryo with my Nico Nico-ryo!
It's called Gorgeous Nico Nico-ryo!
This is the Cinderella police officer, Ryo Tsuchi.
Today, he plans to buy all the seats at Tokyo Dome and play baseball.
Gorgeous Nico-ryo!
What's that?
It's a
This is not a regular show.
This is the
Gorgeous Nico-ryo police, Ryo Tsuchi.
This is not a normal show.
This is the
If that's the case, Master will be in pain because of the grasshopper.
I got it, I got it.
All right, I'll go to Ginza after this and get rid of the grasshopper.
That won't happen.
You can't throw it away, bury it, or burn it.
This is Master's order.
You have three days left, and you have to use it all up.
Hmm.
It's surprisingly hard to use money.
Huh?
What's under the chair?
What's this?
It's a jewel.
There it is!
Oh, Baghdad! Sindbad! Oganbad!
Huh? What is it?
This person lost that jewel.
It's worth tens of billions, so he's giving me a share.
W-What?!
I told you I didn't need it!
I have one more truck.
Master Ryo...
I know.
All right, next is Tokyo.
He won't be able to find it.
All right, now we're having a workaholic cały.
Here we go.
Oh, good idea.
Hey, what's the Can I do esto?
I know the
Shimmyland!
I know you!
How's that?
Oh, wonderful! This is the character I've been looking for!
What's your name?
My name is Walton Mazmy!
Please let me use this painting!
I'll spend 1 billion yen for the character's usage!
I told you I don't need it!
You've got another one!
Oh, my lord! My late master has been thrown into the well!
It's not my fault!
Now, I've got a horse! I'll spend 3 billion yen on it!
Hey, sis!
Yes!
I'll spend 3 billion yen on the Thunder Roller!
200 meters to go!
The 2nd popular Riding Bull is coming up!
The most popular Thunder Roller is coming!
The popular Sidebinder is coming!
A fierce battle is about to start!
Oh, my!
The sidebinder is falling!
It's attacking the Aegean Hyacinth!
The 2nd horse is on the move!
The Riding Bull is also coming up!
The horses in the middle are coming up, too!
The real match is about to start!
The 1st place is the most popular Thunder Roller!
Why?
Huh?
The 2nd horse is coming up!
The 4th horse is coming up!
The 6th horse is coming up!
Oh, my God!
Not if you're a player!
All right!
What if I pull this!
It's okay.
You're both a piece of shit!
I've brought out all the money.
I'm finally free from you, old man!
Oh, right, I'm saving!
If I save this much, I can live a luxurious life with only my money!
What bell is that?
I'm sorry, but I'm running out of time.
Wh-wh-what?
Goodbye, old man Ryo.
Tickle.
What kind of thing is that?
So what about Ryo?
It's not known where he dropped it.
He was running out of money, so he got the punishment.
He's self-sacrificing.
I'm hungry.
I don't need money, so let me eat something.
To be continued
To Be Continued
To Be Continued To Be Continued
The politicians who have been defeated
The blue aunt who is above us
Please come up and see
That corner
Everyone, everyone can meet
Let's go!
There is a wall
Ah, there must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
There is a wall
Ah, there must be a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!