The
Willing To
When you watch the TV,
make your room bright and beiutiful
Sleepy
When you have no money,
come with me
I'm also not,
so worry about me
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
It will be fine in a while
You know, right? You know, you know
If you know, then keep quiet and follow me
Translated by Vortex
I can't sleep at all. Who is it?
What is this?
Who wrote this?
It's not written by anyone. It's my own luggage.
Camera?
Huh?
What is it?
This camera is a cursed camera.
If you don't take 100 photos of the police officer's swimsuit within a week, you will be unfortunate.
Moreover, if you take other photos, you will be unfortunate, so please be careful.
What is this?
It's stupid. What is a cursed camera?
Such an idiotic story. Who will believe it?
Why is the washing machine...
It can't be...
It's such an idiotic story.
Where does it come from?
It's a cursed camera.
It can't be...
Is this really a cursed camera?
Why is this kind of thing in my place?
I don't need this kind of thing.
It's just a piece of cake.
It's really cursed. This camera is cursed.
Uh, uh...
Eh? This is the cursed camera.
Within a week, a picture of the lady police officer in a swimsuit...
Now that you mention it, I'm going to the beach on my trip to Katsushika.
What? Isn't it easy?
100 or 200 pictures of swimsuits.
Wait for me, cursed camera.
I'll take as many pictures as you want!
Get the pictures of the swimsuits!
What? You're saying that this year's trip is to the mountains?
Senior, didn't you know?
No, I didn't!
I thought that the trip was always to the beach.
The police decided it on their own.
We're not even men.
You're kidding!
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
Why did you change your trip to the mountains?
What are you talking about, you primitive?
Do you have any complaints?
The sea is the best in summer.
We've built a shelter for the mountains since this year.
That's why we're going to the mountains this year.
Right?
The sea and the sea water are full of UV rays.
That's right. It's a mountain that's perfect for preventing sunburn.
Right?
What?
The mountains in summer are quiet and cool.
It also has the effect of healing.
Right?
No, it's not right!
I will never accept it!
The sea is not the sea!
What are you saying, you primitive!
I've already decided.
I can't change it yet.
Come on, if you're done.
Go home now!
Come on!
Come on, Jenny!
Oh my God.
I thought that I could take a picture with no protection on the beach.
But I was wrong.
It's very natural and easy.
I didn't get suspicious at all.
But I didn't expect to be forced to wear a swimsuit in the mountains.
Anyway, if you call the people in the mountains to take pictures,
I'm sure they'll be suspicious.
I have to do something.
What?
You said you'd cooperate to take a picture of the mountains with no protection on the beach?
That's right.
I need your help right now.
No, I don't want to do that.
I'll ask for your help somehow, Nakagawa.
No, you can't.
Are you sure you can't?
I'm sure you can't.
Can't I ask for this much?
You can't ask for anything.
I'm angry!
What do you need to take a picture of the mountains with no protection on the beach?
Well, that's...
You're planning to make some money again, right?
Senpai, you shouldn't be doing that.
That's not a part-time job.
No, it's not.
Then what is it?
That's...
You can't tell me.
I can tell you.
But I don't know if you can believe me.
Anyway, please tell me.
Actually...
What?
This is the cursed camera, right?
That's right.
If you take pictures of anything other than the swimsuit of the
poor, misfortune will come.
What's with that face?
Senpai, if it's a lie, let's make it better.
No, it's not a lie.
I'm really in misfortune.
No one believes in such a story.
Look at my eyes.
This is the lie.
It's really true.
If you doubt it so much, you should try it.
Me?
That's right.
Take pictures of anything around there.
Then, this flower...
No, this bear.
Or this lantern...
Take pictures of anything, hurry up!
But what's wrong with wasting the film?
Hmm...
Maybe the angle is different.
Maybe it's better from here?
No, I think it's better from here.
Hmm...
Maybe it's better from the front?
No, no, no.
I don't care where you take it from.
Hurry up and take it.
Hurry up.
I don't like the subject.
Come on, come on.
What?
Since we're here, I'll take a picture of you.
Me?
Is that okay, Senpai?
Here, cheese.
Shut up.
Just take it.
But since we're here, I'll take a picture of you.
Senpai.
Here, cheese.
Cheese.
Senpai!
Why are you here?
How is it? Did you get it, Sakagawa?
Yes, somehow.
Then you'll help me, right?
Yes, I'll help you.
But it's strange.
Don't turn around, idiot.
Don't take it anymore.
I know it.
Huh?
It's kind of good.
This is the right answer, after all.
Right?
Oh, I'm starting to see it.
I found it!
Where is it?
It's not a deck!
This is the ocean, isn't it?
Why is there an ocean here?
Huh?
Nakagawa Leisure Development?
Nakagawa-san, what is this?
That's...
Welcome, everyone!
Ryo-chan!
You're here!
The ocean is the best!
The ocean, my ocean!
The ocean is...
Big and wide!
Speaking of summer, the ocean!
This is the best!
Come on, everyone!
This beautiful ocean is your private beach!
Let's swim as much as you want!
What is this?
You don't have to swim all of a sudden.
I don't have a swimsuit!
Hmm...
Don't worry.
I've got a rental swimsuit for you.
The latest release this year.
It's all of the latest products.
Come on!
You can have whatever you want.
By the way, what's the rental fee?
Of course!
Just!
Wow! Lucky!
Which one should I get?
Oh, this is cool!
This and this, which is better?
Wait a minute!
Isn't it weird?
I don't want it!
It's not weird at all.
No, no, no, no.
It's too suspicious that Ryotsu would lend money for free.
That's true. The money witch is so strange.
There must be some trap.
It's strange that there is an ocean here.
No!
It's the last one.
Please.
I can't get in that hand.
It's a trap.
Damn it. They are very sharp.
Okay, it's the next one.
It's hot even though it's a mountain.
It's good to experience nature,
but...
I wanted to follow them around.
It's over 40 degrees.
What?
Senpai, you don't have to do this much.
Shut up.
You can choose your way at this moment.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong about the ocean.
Hooray!
What?
It's hot!
The ocean is great.
When it's hot, I'll go to the ocean.
I can only think about the ocean.
I don't believe you.
I can't be bothered anymore.
Over.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
I'm really wrong...
Ah!
I'm sorry.
Hooray!
Still, I can't get in that sea!
Oh, my goodness.
If only they didn't come here.
What?
If I get in that sea,
I don't know what he's thinking.
Oh, I'm at my limit.
I'm going to swim.
I'm going to swim, too.
No, I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
Welcome.
Please choose your favorite swimsuit.
I don't care if it's hot.
No, no, no.
Don't come.
No way.
Why, senpai?
Shut up.
This is a women's only.
You can't enter.
What a way to get angry.
It's not normal.
That's why I said so.
You can probably wear a transparent swimsuit.
No.
It's dangerous to get close.
This is the same as the ant hell.
Hey, everyone.
Come on.
Damn.
It's just a normal day, so I don't trust you at all.
Ryo-sama.
I'm going to wear this.
Um?
I was thinking about the harmony with the ungrateful people.
But I won't betray you.
I'll make you happy and let you go into the sea.
I see.
Maria was still with me.
Maria is a man, but she's ungrateful.
And she's a woman.
Ryo-sama.
Do you think it will suit me?
It's perfect.
You look like a model.
I hate it.
You're embarrassing me.
That's right.
Let's take a picture, Maria.
Please pose.
All right.
Is this enough?
Is that okay, Ryo-sama?
Okay, okay!
I'll take it then.
Here's your cheese!
Ryo-sama!
Th-they're all for the sake of the year.
We're at our limit!
Let's make it the sea.
We're going to the sea now!
Yay!
Huh?
What?
Are we going somewhere?
It seems that the amount of the sea has changed.
What?!
Hey, you guys!
The sea is right in front of us!
I'm sorry for swimming in such a suspicious sea.
Oh, Ryo-sama.
See you later.
You're completely an insect, damn it!
But, as a result, we're going to the sea,
so it's all good.
Let's go!
What?!
What did you say?!
What's wrong, Naoko?
Ryo-san! Ryo-san!
I just got a call from the second car.
Wait for me.
I'll take a picture of you in a suspicious swimsuit soon.
What?!
Ryo-chan did that?!
That's what I was after.
I'm sure they're going to sell it to someone.
What are you going to do, Reiko-san?
Yeah.
I have a bad feeling.
But we can't wait to get on the sea!
You sure can't help it.
Let's go to another beach.
Let's leave first!
Let's go!
Let's go to that beach!
I don't want to swim under the sea faster than that,
but I'm serious.
I'm out of here.
Why???
There is a person of men who wants to sell a photo of his swim trotter.
So I will give it to my girlfriend.
Why are you looking at me at once?
I didn't intend to do that.
You suspect me, don't you?
Damn it, it's like a criminal case.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't do anything like that!
I'm sorry, Ryo-san!
He said he'd be a senior soon.
I have a message from the entire community.
Don't take pictures of Ryo, Tsukan, and Kichi!
That's all.
Damn, he even covered his eyes.
Yes!
That's it!
Ah, it feels so good!
The ocean is really nice after all.
It's the best!
But, as expected of Reiko-san.
She even made a fence.
Her opponent is Ryo-chan.
I have to do this much.
This looks fun.
It's like a bathhouse.
Hey, everyone!
I'm not even going to take a picture of you.
How did you know?
Aren't you stupid?
It's obvious.
What a pervert!
Yes!
That's it!
I got it!
I'll take it!
Huh?
It's obvious!
I'll take it!
But I'll take it!
Oh, no!
It's me!
Yeah, it's me, isn't it?
What the.
It's not easy for me.
sachiko!
You are not qualify to take on me.
Huh...
My man!
Ugh!
It's too much to think that it's a wave-generating device.
No, it doesn't matter. My life is at stake.
-Sara? -What's this?
-The salt is dripping. -It's weird.
To be able to go down the road so fast.
-What? -What?
This time, I'll get it right.
No, it's not there. What?
-I'm sorry. -Stop giving up.
-I'll get it. -Gee.
That's no good. This is no good either.
I'm going to be unhappy for the rest of my life.
Senpai, don't lose your temper.
I'll introduce you to a good onmyoji who will pay for your curse.
No! It's not a joke to be unhappy for the rest of my life.
It's not as dangerous as saying it's not.
-I don't want it! -You're too good, Ryo-chan.
I'm thinking stupidly about selling our swimsuit pictures.
That's why it's like this.
That's right. I'll never forgive you this time.
I'll talk to the president of Tonda and get you fired.
Everyone, wait a minute.
Actually, there's a reason for this.
I don't know if you can believe it,
but Senpai's camera is a cursed camera.
So, if you don't take a picture of Fukie's swimsuit, you'll be unhappy.
Nakagawa-san!
No matter how much you lie,
-you're covering up for Ryo-chan and Kancho. -That's right.
It's strange to say, "believe."
Senpai!
I can't believe it!
Did you believe me!
There is no seed or trap.
It really seems like a curse is on you.
Well, I'm asking you...
Can you take a picture of everyone's swimsuits?
Why are you doing this to me?
"I'm not sure about this."
"It's okay. I'll make sure you get it this time."
"That's great, senpai!"
"Here's the cheese."
"Now we have 100 pieces."
"It disappeared!"
"I did it! Now I'm free!"
"I'm so happy!"
"That's great, senpai!"
"If you'd told me honestly from the start, I wouldn't have to go through all that trouble."
"But it's normal to be normal."
"Even if I told you honestly, I wouldn't have believed you."
"You're right."
"But you were able to get 100 pieces of Fukie's swimsuit."
"That's a strange curse."
"What on earth was that camera?"
"I did it! I did it!"
"You're pretty good at taking pictures of Ryotsu, aren't you?"
"No, no, no."
"This is a punishment from the Chief of the Underworld Security Department who is trying to make Ryotsu Kan-Kichi angry."
"Ryotsu will also become a human being trusted by the public with this."
"I'll have to work a little harder."
"Chh."
"Heh, but to my surprise, it's not a bad punishment."
"Ah, summer is here again this year."
"It's here! It's here! It's here!"
Big, small, small, small, small, small, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big
big, big, small, small, small, small, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big-big, big, big
big, big, small,
big,
tight,
It's a long time!
"Hashijyo Onsen"
Yay! It's a hot spring!
I was digging a well behind the hot spring and a hot spring appeared!
This is a great deal!
The name is "Hashijyo Onsen"!
Wait, I'd rather build a large hot spring, Leijer Land!
Next time, "Hashijyo Onsen" is a good idea!
Please watch!
"Hashijyo Onsen"
Thank you!