"Multi-future Kuni-kun"
♪When you're watching TV,
bright the room and look away♪
♪In a place where everyone comes and goes,
♪ The place where the sun rises ♪
♪ I walked while looking back ♪
♪ I held my mother's hand ♪
♪ At that time I felt ♪
♪ A strange feeling ♪
♪ So I tried to walk ♪
♪ Of the Ake-dogai tile ♪
♪ I tried to walk ♪
♪ In the black place ♪
♪ Everyone was a child once ♪
♪ But everyone forgets ♪
♪ A politician with a big face ♪
♪ And a blue aunt above his eyes ♪
♪ Turn that corner ♪
♪ To everyone ♪
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ There's a wall for sure ♪
♪ Everyone come to our town ♪
Thank you!
Henshin! Shominha! Nakagawa-kun!
Will Kei-chan change her life?
Yes.
I'm going to try to live as a civilian as possible.
Why did you suddenly think that?
Actually, I attended a company meeting the other day.
Our Nakagawa Group is moving forward with other companies,
and is making a big and innovative progress
by reducing the cost of cutting the bones of companies
and reducing the cost of cutting the bones of companies.
We will continue to work hard to improve the business of railways, hotels, banks, real estate, cars, and other departments.
we will continue to work hard to improve the business of railways, hotels, banks, real estate, cars, and other departments.
This is nothing but the fruit of your hard work.
I prepared a present for you today with gratitude.
This is what I bought with my pocket money.
Please enjoy it.
Oh, it's the supply of nutritional drinks.
O.K..
I will have more with the money I get from this lot.
I order more with the money I get from these lots.
I can see the importance of all of these.
I can see all of these.
Thank you, Takumi.
He changed his special drink into a cheap egg and did his duty.
That's crazy.
I'd like to drink with you, but I have to go to the next destination for the 21st century project meeting.
That's all.
Cheers to President Ryuichiro Nakagawa!
Cheers!
I learned what it's like to stand on top of my father's flexible posture.
I thought about what I could do, and I thought about how I could be a model for other employees.
I thought about how I could be a model for other employees.
You're great, Kei.
No, I'm still working on it.
You're a great manager.
Senpai!
What's wrong?
What's that?
I don't know.
Senpai, what are you doing in the kitchen?
Ryo, you're the worst!
You shouldn't wash your body with water.
Ryo, you should get dressed quickly.
If the manager comes, it will be a big problem.
I understand. I understand. I'll be right out.
So, you're living a commoner's life?
What are your thoughts?
I bought my favorite Ferrari from Porsche.
I bought gasoline from High Oak Standard.
It's not funny at all.
It's not a joke!
I'm seriously aiming for a commoner's life.
Are you kidding me?
Porsche is not a commoner's life.
Stop driving and get on the train.
The train?
When I was a kid, I was a teacher and a home teacher.
I was a teacher and a home teacher.
A teacher?
Then, maybe most of the stations in Tokyo are automatic trains.
Really?
Even Tokyo, which was said to be impossible?
There's a limit to being a teacher.
I don't know.
Oh, right.
I'm riding on Porsche, so I'm on your side.
You're two people on the train.
It's funny in Harunosoko.
No, I've never been on the train.
Kei-chan says someone who knows how others feel is a kind person.
I know.
It's more humble and appearance than Ryo-san.
What?
What did you say?
Don't fight over me, you three.
Well, I'll tell you this.
What will happen if a guy like you becomes president?
A few days will pass, and the whole group will be in trouble.
Ryo, you're being mean.
I'm giving you a warning for Nakagawa.
You're threatening your junior, but you're enjoying it.
You have to cheer him up.
Cheer?
The support of the Nakagawa Group.
The smell of money floating in the air.
Don't worry, Nakagawa.
I said something harsh, because I'm going to teach you the basics of a commoner's life.
You?
The authority of the Shisso prefecture, the commoner's life advisor, Ryo Tsukankichi.
I'm on your side, so don't worry.
Don't ride it.
What?
Stop it.
Let's start with this dirty look.
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
See?
Senpai, this bamboo is too short.
A character like you who left his home can balance out just fine.
No way.
By the way, Nakagawa, you paid for all the meals, right?
Yes.
Basically, I paid with 100% card.
By the way, do you know how much the dinner I ate yesterday was?
It was 40,000 yen, no, 50,000 yen last night.
I'm sorry.
I haven't checked the price in detail.
That's what I call being divided between the commoner and the commoner!
Nakagawa, give me all the cards you have.
All of them?
Yes, all of them.
I got it.
You have a lot.
All of them are gold and platinum cards.
As of today, cut the cards and the circles.
What are you doing?
Pay with cash every time.
That's the first step to a private life with a bond.
I got it.
If you have a deposit of 1 yen like me,
you can concentrate your whole nervous system on the same menu, such as ramen and dumplings.
I see.
Especially, when I can take dumplings and ramen together,
I feel like I've taken over the world.
Is that so?
When I have no money but I'm very hungry, I eat fried rice.
Fried rice?
Then, I mix a large amount of rice with fried rice and eat it in double.
But you don't have to mix it.
Why don't you take two fried rice?
Are you Marie Antoinette?
You have a different price.
Take two fried rice for 1,000 yen.
One fried rice and a large amount of rice will be 350 yen.
I see.
I didn't have to calculate the amount of money in the card payment.
I just...
You may not have enough money to take a business of hundreds of millions of yen every day,
but it's a smart private life that doesn't need to calculate 10 or 20 yen.
Yes, I got it.
What?
Money?
I haven't paid it yet.
Yes, I've been paying it all in cards so far, so I don't have any cash at all...
Oh, I remember!
Senpai, I lent you 3,000 yen the other day.
If you return that, I'll pay it.
What?
Damn it!
You have to pay it here before you get rid of the card.
Look, it's ramen.
It's 2,550 yen.
Oh, sorry.
What? Senpai?
I have some money.
This is not Ito Hirogumi.
Is this really a 1,000 yen bill?
Don't underestimate me!
Your design has changed over 10 years!
Oh, really?
It's been a long time since I saw a picture of you.
You're a good detective.
Oh, maybe this is...
What's this time?
I don't think you don't know the 500 yen bill.
Is this really the 500 yen bill?
What?
When did you become human?
Live with that money this month.
What?
Only 2,000 yen?
2,550 yen.
But there's still half a month to go.
Only half a month?
Don't worry.
I've secured a place to stay.
What?
Really?
Here.
This is a lot of money.
That's right.
And you'll be staying in this room from today.
This is Senpai's room, isn't it?
That's right.
If you pay 100 yen per night, it's much cheaper than the transportation fee to your house.
Really?
It's much cheaper than the transportation fee to your house.
What?
Are you taking money?
Of course.
This room looks dirty at first glance, but there are many ideas of life-saving wisdom based on contracts and product ideas.
For example...
This is it.
Isn't it bean sprouts?
That's right.
Put the bought bean sprouts in a sponge soaked in water, and then eat them.
This is called dry breakfast.
The green onion and parsley can be once season if you plant them in soil like this.
For example, the tissue det Gold media asked to deliver to the town will sell their without mistake.
Get the deal in the end of the year, at the shopping street, service information such as sales of hangover drinks, and verify advertisements.
Don't forget to write the paper to the bean.
I've never had a chance to spend money on a product that's not legal.
In the case of the company, it's a luxurious life of virtual poverty that is a part of social studies.
I'm serious. For a while, I will contact my family and my company.
Okay, I got it. It's a tough road, so get a good job.
350 yen. There are still 4 or 5 days until the end of the month.
Here, Kei-chan. Tea.
Oh, sorry.
Kei-chan, are you making a tie at the convenience store again?
Yes. It's fast, cheap and easy.
I started to eat at the convenience store, and I found a lot of things.
Even if you make a knot, the price, taste and way of rolling the seaweed are slightly different depending on the store.
For example, pulling from both sides or pulling out the inside of the paper.
But today I found something even more amazing.
Ta-da!
The classic three-storied type with seaweed is cheap from the beginning.
I like the seaweed that is wet, so I bought this.
This is an ideal dish that can be wished or granted.
Kei-chan is surprisingly talented.
I have something to deliver to the director, so please take care of it.
Yes, I understand.
Excuse me.
Yes, what happened?
I heard that I dropped my wallet somewhere.
Okay, I was able to deliver the paper.
So, if possible, I want to borrow a train ticket.
That's a problem.
Well, how much is it?
Can you return it if it's available?
Just about 350 yen.
I'm glad.
350 yen is just right.
Okay.
Well, take care of this and please return it.
Thank you.
You absurd!
What's the point of lending the money to the Red Valley?
It's the security of the post office.
It's natural.
I'll do it.
No, you can't.
I'm underestimate the people of the city.
What?
Even if you become a dead body,
I'm sure someone will help me.
I'm not. I just wanted to save someone in trouble.
You're the one in trouble now.
You gave him 350 yen worth of cash as a life-saving gift.
Do you know how reckless that is?
It's a million years too early to save a person.
I'll cool my head a little.
You gave him 350 yen worth of cash as a life-saving gift.
Do you know how reckless that is?
I don't think the owner will show up, but I'll keep it for now.
You're so quiet that I can't tell. You're a crazy person.
I thought about what you said last night.
But I think what I did was right.
You're so stubborn.
You'll be gone in 4 or 5 days.
You can't live without food.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Turn that corner and look to the right.
I feel sorry for him.
You're so unfair.
You don't know when I'm hungry.
You're being too nice because I didn't eat enough.
You can see, you can see.
You're the same person. You're the same man.
In Ryo's case, it's different.
Nakagawa will...
Shut up!
Ah, fuck.
Special service, Nakagawa.
Let me introduce you a part-time job.
Alright, please.
I don't care, just eat your fill.
What's your name?
My name is Keiichi Kawanaka.
Kawanaka?
I'm late to work because the previous rain is making it hard.
Alright, I'll do my best.
Alright, I'll take care of you.
I'm counting on you.
Kanaka, wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
What's your name?
Well...
What? Everyone's at your place.
Yes, it was the scene of my company.
If you were the owner of Nakagawa Group, everyone would be upset.
I know. I can't say it out loud.
Hey, Kanaka.
Yes, sir.
Kanaka, you're going to help me today.
Take, take care of him.
Oh, that's tough.
Are you okay, brother?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
The fried rice and rice at that time...
What?
Are you Nakagawa's boss?
This is what I mean.
The fried rice and rice industry?
Hachinosu Real Estate?
Dotanba?
You came to see Kei-chan?
I think I want to make a promotion for the next president of Nakagawa Group.
I see.
Unfortunately, Nakagawa is not present.
But I, who is his boss and a relative of his, will take over.
You are a relative of yours?
Yes.
My brother, Kinjiro's wife, is the eldest daughter of the wife of Nakagawa's grandmother's sister's son's divorced wife.
Ryouchi-san, how about drinking?
I'm more or less liquid.
How well can you go around the golf course?
I will go around.
What food do you like the most?
Judo...
Oh, I mean steak.
It's in Matsunaka.
hyo, what are you going to do?
Oh, dear.
Oh, brother, where are you rolling in the concrete?
This way.
I'm sorry.
How is it? Isn't this job easy?
Yes.
You're a police officer, right?
Did you get into card law?
What?
No, I heard you were talking about that at that ramen shop.
Well, there are various reasons for this.
Well, you seem to be serious, so I'll tell you a lot.
Thank you.
Hey, Yama, please organize the traffic on the front.
Yes.
Are you going to organize the traffic?
Yes. I'm saving the security personnel expenses at this station.
To such a place.
Kanaka, please help Yama.
Yes.
Don't look down on me like my real brother.
Listen to me.
Yes, sir.
Come on, come on.
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'll guide you.
Hey, hurry up.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
Can I go to the national road?
Yes, sir.
I'll guide you now.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll cut it again today.
Yama, I'll go ahead of you.
Oh, I got it.
Wait a minute.
OK.
Thank you for waiting for a long time.
Please go ahead.
I'll go.
Thank you.
It's a must-do.
I've been working on my own business for a long time.
What?
That's right.
Don't you have anything to say?
Yes.
That's great.
I'm sure you'll be able to sell it.
Yes.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I'm glad I got the money.
I'll go upstairs.
What's up, Nii-chan?
Are you going to meet the field director?
No, I'm...
Nii-chan, do you want a drink?
Yes.
Well, the cup is...
I don't need anything like that.
Just close the lid like this with your finger.
Delicious!
One more!
Come on!
As expected of Maruno.
He's different.
Foie gras, caviar, and steak.
I'm sorry for having you eat this in the middle of the day.
Nii-chan, what are you going to do in the future?
Huh? The future?
I'm going to be a great architect of the future.
Right, Yama?
Stop it.
I'm going to be a night shift at the industrial college.
Huh.
Next year,
I'm going to take over the design office of Nakagawa Construction,
but it's a high competitive position there.
Yama has different eyes from other people.
The other day,
you said you wanted to combine the zoo with the hotel, right?
It's just a thought.
It's interesting.
If I'm the president, I'll take over immediately.
I want to hire someone like that, too.
Oh, no.
You're like a president, Nii-chan.
It's fun.
Then let's get going.
Are we going to Ginza this time?
Or Akasaka?
Before that, let's go to Nakagawa Junior.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Okay, that's it for today.
Oh, it's over.
It was a tough day.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Here, here.
Onzoshi from Nakagawa Group is here.
Hey, Nakagawa.
Senpai.
That person is...
Nakagawa Junior...
Nakagawa!
I brought you a business story as a relative.
Nakagawa?
You've got the wrong name.
Please tell your father about it.
I can't do that.
I'm...
I see.
Of course, I'm the son of the president of Nakagawa Group.
I can't say it without saying it.
Senpai is trying to see if I'll protect him.
Nakagawa?
Who is that?
I'm Kawanaka.
Kawanaka!
Kawanaka?
Yes, it's Kawanaka.
Why?
Don't make a fuss.
You're not the same person.
Ryo, what's going on?
Did you trick us?
Please, tell us the truth.
Senpai is trying to test my courage.
I can't do that.
That's not true.
Don't joke, Senpai.
I'm Kawanaka.
Kawanaka!
It's true.
It's not a lie.
Believe me.
Anyway, let's talk over there.
He's the founder of Nakagawa Group.
I'm sure you can't afford to take money from the two of you.
Is he really from Nakagawa Group?
Hey, Kawanaka.
Take your pay today.
Okay.
Thank you for everything today.
You helped me.
Someday...
Nakagawa!
Don't say it again.
Help me!
Hey!
Ryo, I'll take your lunch.
Steak on Matsuzakagyu.
There's no such thing in Tsurukame Prefecture, Ryo.
Can I eat ramen now?
How about paying for it?
Damn it.
They just stole it.
And they gave me a bank note.
What are you going to do, Kei?
I'm going to make something and eat it.
I don't need it.
Kei, you're getting better.
Really?
What a jerk!
You can eat expensive food like a rich man.
That steak was delicious.
Hey, this is for Mr. Nakagawa.
Nakagawa?
Yes.
Sign here, please.
I got it!
I won the prize!
I kept my senior's advice and put out a postcard.
I'm so glad!
The last time.
The other day, Somo helped me a lot.
I want to thank him.
So, I'll invite him to my house.
What?
Well, of course.
Huh?
At that time?
This cat is eating real cat food!
What?
I gave 100 million yen to Mr. Nakagawa,
the honest man who gave me 100 million yen.
What?
100 million yen!
After all,
No matter how Nakagawa turns around,
he will be rich.
So, compare this.
The
Day of the
Day of the Day"
"The
"We
♪ When I look around, every day is no problem ♪
♪ I get well with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating, Monday ♪
♪ Monday, Monday, no problem ♪
Translated by 方 Hou.
Oh, this is the simulation game that I developed with Nakagawa-sensei?
Okay! Let's try it together!
Huh? If I'm not here, how will everyone's life be?
Is there such an absurd story?
Next time, "Repeat Life"!
I look forward to working with you!