When you watch TV, you should light up your own room and see the light behind it!
Nى chéo
nia chéo
Come to my place!
If you don't have money!
I don't have money but I'm still worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Let's have a good time
Come to me if you're jobless
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, come to me quietly
Just wait a longer
I need to go to the toilet
Just stop
The red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I think I need to go to the toilet
I need to go to the toilet
I want to run away
and the store is full of gaps,
so I think they're trying to make us look cool.
Well, it's a local convenience store
that the CEO just opened,
so I don't think it's impossible.
Ryo-san, this is the CEO.
The CEO of a inexperienced convenience store.
Well, there are gaps,
but it's not all bad.
We need to be careful.
I checked the tape for the last few days
of the Kameari 24 store,
and I found that there were strange people
showing up for a long time.
The thief said he would check in advance.
You!
This is you, Ryo-san.
What? You look like...
I don't look like...
This is you!
I think it's me, maybe.
Look at the tape carefully.
Send it to me quickly.
Yes, sir.
It's been 30 minutes since then,
and you're still reading it.
This is a patrol, sir.
I told you to leave it to me.
You're reading a manga, aren't you?
A manga!
Well, at first glance,
it looks like I'm reading a manga.
But actually,
it's a post-production, sir.
Post-production?
I had a feeling that the thief would come today,
so I pretended to be reading a manga...
Hey, send it to me three hours later.
Hey, I waited, but he didn't come much,
so I thought I'd go back to the station,
but as expected, the post-production continued.
Do you think I'm being deceived by such nonsense?
What's wrong with skipping the night shift and reading a manga?
It's not a stand-up.
It's a sitting reading.
Idiot!
Don't you think you're embarrassed to be old?
Because I want to read the latest manga before anyone else!
Yeah?
I don't need any serious,
stupid,
lazy,
and useless police officers like you,
Katsushika-cho!
I'll just make you my boss!
It's so hard!
Well, Mr. Ohara,
that's enough...
The chief executive, Fuyuki Toboki,
is my responsibility as a boss.
No,
as a store,
it's more secure to have a storekeeper.
Did you hear that, manager?
Mr. Katsushika-cho,
please tell us more about it.
Well,
of the 24-5 shops in the town,
only the 5th store,
where Mr. Ryotsu often stands,
has not been affected by the robberies.
Hey,
did you hear that, manager?
I was doing my job while reading the manga.
What?
That was...
a flash.
This is the convenience store.
Wait for it.
That's just a flash.
I'll tell you what.
Come on.
I should!
There you go.
There's a lot of great things
You also have to come and see it.
Huh?
Hey,
I know the hotиз.
That's true.
The hotiz?
You really want to come and see it?
You can simply use it and I'll give you
the information you need.
Hey!
Let's have some fun.
Convenience stores are exposed to the heavy traffic and the heavy traffic,
and they require a lot of security to get out of their way.
So, we, the Katsushika office,
will take the lead in the country and test the delivery police.
In other words, we will do the police officer's convenient store delivery.
What?
Convenience stores that are closer to the far station.
If you send the police officer to the convenience store one by one,
you can immediately work.
If there is a station in a nearby convenience store,
the city will be protected.
This is Columbus's great idea of one-by-two.
Oh.
First, my members of the park delivery office,
will work at the convenience store and prove the effectiveness.
Eventually, the delivery police will come.
The natural age will come.
The delivery police will revive the Japanese safety myth.
And then, the washing machine will come.
And when both of them come,
Chinese people will take their places in the car,
and that's all they have to do.
It's hard to get rid of the old man now.
That's the kind of culture that's good.
And the people who run my department,
Utsu.
Of course.
Andышi.
This is us.
Okay.
Well, it's time you left JESSICA.
Soon, they'll be working here.
We'll keep up the work.
They are friendly.
I know.
"Akari 21st Century"
I'm too conspicuous here.
I'll move the bookshelf over there and...
"Akari 21st Century"
Ryo-chan!
Don't be selfish!
Do your best for the sake of the bright 21st century, Butchon!
"Akari 21st Century"
The image of the neighborhood is also the home of work,
so like the reception hall of the department store...
"Akari 21st Century"
Smile, smile!
Can you do that?
If you can't handle the changes of the times like these,
I'll give you a reward box!
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
President.
Oh, you're good at it.
Right? Right?
You're all fit.
Now, I'll give you a seat, I'll give you a seat.
"Akari 21st Century"
Come on, come on, I'll give you a smile.
I go to 5 stores every day.
I'm a regular customer.
If anything bad happens, please tell me without hesitation.
"Akari 21st Century"
No, this is my job.
Of course.
Then, Yasuoka-kun, please.
"Akari 21st Century"
Then, please.
Yes, sir.
Then, I'm in your way.
Are you going too?
Do your best.
"Akari 21st Century"
I went.
# "Akari 21st Century"
"Akari 21st Century"
"Akari 21st Cherry"
I'm working at the 5th store.
Just sitting here will make the crime more difficult.
Please don't make any unnecessary comments about the convenience store business.
Working at the 5th store?
What? Did I just say that?
Oh, well...
Now, you can read the manga's latest volume right away.
It's all-you-can-read!
And if you're hungry, you can have hot oden,
meat buns, red bean buns, pizza buns,
coffee, tea, oolong tea,
and this is the official business.
It's the best!
Thank you, Kanbei.
Ouch.
Kanbei, I'm sorry, but can you pat my shoulder?
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Daito Rishi.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
He left what he dropped behind.
Here.
He's quite the talker.
Hey...
What is it?
Your...
Listen, Chief!
The cash is for the convenience store business.
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll take a patrol now.
It's past 11 o'clock now.
Oh, it's them.
Are you sure, chief?
I can't believe you're talking about the convenience store business!
This is the police officer's mission.
The fruit juice looks good.
Yeah.
You're high school students, right?
Ah!
I was just looking at you!
Yeah.
Zaya, let's go home and study!
Put your shirts in your pants properly.
You're high school students, right?
You shouldn't read such books!
It's past 11 o'clock in the night!
Your parents won't scold you?
My parents...
Yeah, they're fine.
Anyway, go home and sleep.
You have school tomorrow, right?
Yes!
What a trouble.
No, no!
If you put the bread on the bottom, it'll collapse, right?
Put the heavy stuff on the bottom and put the soft stuff on top.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for waiting.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
And you dropped the food you dropped earlier.
You put it in a bag and handed it to the customer.
At that time, you should replace it with new food.
Shut up.
What?
It has nothing to do with it.
When you talk, look at the other person.
Shut up, old man.
You're the kind of person who doesn't care about others.
You're the kind of person who doesn't have the power to have a soul.
I don't have the strength.
People...
What are you doing?
You're on a job.
I don't understand.
What are you doing?
I have to find a way to do this for three hours.
I don't understand this.
I can't see, I'm losing control.
I'm running!
I can't see too much.
I'm losing control!
I can't see anything.
I can't feel my body.
No, not at all.
What?
All right, tell me this.
Huh? What? President!
Only Mr. Ohara's store is selling very low.
It's a big problem.
What? That's impossible!
The First Store
It's true. The first store is selling very low.
What's the matter?
Mr. Ohara, he removed all the ugly books from the store.
He also banned young boys who are under 16 from entering the store after 10 p.m.
He also quit his part-time job late at night.
That's a business obstacle!
What's your authority?
I guess the idea of making a second-store in a convenience store itself was too much.
Should we stop it?
Hey, wait a minute!
Look here!
Reiko's second store and Nakagawa's third store are selling at a high price
with more customers for two people.
Reiko's second store and Nakagawa's third store are selling at a high price with more customers for two people.
The price was low because of the number of customers.
The cost to make a second store in a convenience store is count was written in the code.
There was a big sales issue.
I don't care about the boss.
I don't want to be confused anymore.
He said that the price for each batch was only 2.5p.
All you have to do is get more vegetables.
all you have to do is get more vegetables.
We eat as much sweet food as possible.
All you have to do is get more vegetables.
Make it a nutritious milk or fish.
Eww!
Wait a minute!
You'll lose your calcium!
What's with that old man?
Gross!
I'll take this.
Yes.
Manager!
Oh, Ryotsu.
Didn't you just preach to the girls who went out?
No, not that much.
You should just sit here quietly.
If you preach, the customers will run away.
But, Ryotsu, there's something you can't see.
Most customers go to convenience stores to relax.
What's the point of living like that?
You quit your part-time job, didn't you?
But...
130 yen.
Oh!
You should read the newspaper like this, not patrol.
You're not good at it.
Oh, Yasuoka.
Huh?
Hello.
What's up?
I'm worried.
I was close to the game, so I was going to quit it.
Game?
Huh?
But maybe...
Isn't this him?
What?
When Yasuoka was the champion, he was drunk and was about to give up.
After all, the case was about the defense of the world, but he was beaten by the general public.
So his title was taken and he was missing.
I wonder if he has any questions about his ability to return to the ring after a year and seven months.
Oh, so that's what it is.
Well...
I'll pay you later!
Yes!
Yasuoka, you're good!
Mr. Koukaku!
I didn't know you had that kind of situation.
In other words, I thought you were the Freeter of this time.
Freeter?
You know me?
As long as you keep doing that, you can't get out of there!
I heard that.
Oh, that's right. Don't overdo your nutrition drink.
I can't win without overdoing it.
Thank you. I'm on a diet right now, so I'll drink it when I'm done with my weight.
Yeah, then.
Do your best. Do your best!
Young people are at the convenience store of the father-in-law who sells the best wine,
and the one who sells the best wine, and the one who sells the best wine,
and the one who sells the best wine, and he's good at everything,
but who sells the best wine.
Yesterday, I came to consult with work,
though.
Oh, you? Well, you quit your company, didn't you?
After that, I took an office exam.
That was good. But the hard work is still to come.
Don't without this firmness.
Tha ...
Then...
... do your best.
Hello~
You are ...
Ehehehe
Ah!
Oh, it's you guys. I've mistaken you for something else.
We graduated from Cogel!
Haru is a college student.
You haven't changed much except for your clothes.
Isn't it a waste to go to college in that condition?
That's terrible!
Ahaha, sorry, sorry.
You should study properly.
Yes!
Oh, Mr. Ohara.
Thank you for the place where you were lost the other day.
This is this.
Taro, say hello.
Hello!
Oh, hello.
This is a book.
Ah, no. Grandma, I can't accept this.
Well, don't say that.
If the manager's shop gives it back, it's safe for now.
However!
Eh!
President!
A new problem.
Currently, Mr. Ohara's No. 1 store is in the surrounding area, and Mr. Ryochi's No. 5 store is...
Really!?
Is my shop also lost to a monk!?
This is a problem.
I'll just restore Mr. Ryochi's No. 5 store.
Eh, wait a minute!
I'll get it back soon, so don't hurry!
The delivery police is my idea in the first place.
Why does my shop have to be restored?
What?
If I make a little effort to make a convenience store,
I can sell it in a blink of an eye.
Ah, that's no good.
Eh?
That's a new product.
Hmm.
You can't put it down there.
Huh?
The charm of convenience stores is new products.
The repeaters look forward to that, so they come.
I will also make my own pop like this, and I will appeal to new products more and more.
Yes.
I made a paid standing reading corner like this.
Let's see.
I collect 300 yen per hour for a oberez book.
A manga book is 100 yen.
Huh?
Hmm.
I make a game corner, lure children, and place children's favorite lyrics at eye level.
Huh?
Don't you have any ideas that are useful or do boxing?
What?
If you make this much effort, sales will increase immediately.
It's not growing.
It's actually going down.
Ryōchi's 5 store seems to be dependent on children.
Even if children are many, the cost of using is low.
Hmm.
What about other stores?
Oh, Ryōchi.
Eh?
Me?
I see.
Brand products are popular for girls.
Brand?
Oh, wait a minute.
I want to choose this one.
That's right.
Try to guess.
Hmm.
Oh, this one?
Oh, this one is good.
This one is good.
What is he doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was giving advice on customer clothes.
What?
You're doing that?
Yes.
I gave advice on online sales to students.
I heard that the reputation was good, and I wanted to buy products from the manufacturer.
Oh, I'm calling again.
Bye.
I didn't know.
Reiko has excellent sense of fashion.
What about Nakagawa?
I have 90% of female students as customers.
I can sell character products and stuffed animals.
I think it's a pretty good deal in total.
Stop it!
The rule was to not interfere with the convenience store business and not talk about it.
It is natural that I, who have been strictly following the rules, will be late.
Everyone, I have a regular contract, and I have been cooperating with the store.
Oh, yeah.
How about the shop of the emperor?
Hmm?
Oh, hello, Ryo-san?
What?
My shop hasn't changed much.
Hey!
I'm losing to someone who hasn't done anything.
Hmm.
Are you going to stop, Ryo-san?
No, I'm begging you.
Give me one more chance.
I understand.
The problem is not the number of items.
I've been pampering customers.
The key point of selling is preaching.
The modern people who gather at the convenience store are preaching to their fathers.
I want your preaching.
I'll go to the line of the head of the department and aim for the top sales at once.
I'm here.
Cheers.
Yes.
And?
Hey!
What time do you think it is?
4:30 p.m.
I don't remember raising you to be such a child.
I haven't been raised.
Don't talk back.
No way.
Hey!
What's this?
I won't forgive you for wasting it.
I'm sorry.
I haven't finished talking yet.
You're all grown-ups, so you have to eat more nutritious food.
Is this dog food?
You can't say you don't like it.
There's nothing dogs can't eat that humans can't eat.
Yes.
I'll take 13,260 yen.
Hey, stop reading.
That's not my child.
Get out.
Hey, you guys!
Who are you feeding?
You're not?
What?
I've got a little something to feed you.
I'm hungry.
Listen to me, kid.
I want to eat.
Eat.
I heard that the 5th store is closed.
Huh?
Ah!
Hello.
Oh, there you are. I've been waiting for you.
Well, have a drink.
Yes.
You bought it, didn't you?
Well...
I'll take this.
Oh, sure.
Be patient with the beer until you recover.
Yes.
Here's your drink.
Oh, thank you.
Here. This is for you.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations, Yasuoka.
Congratulations, champion.
I'm not a champion yet.
Anyway, I'm glad.
Cheers!
It's good.
Mr. Ohara, thank you for your lecture.
You're a bad person.
Thanks to this convenience store,
I was able to meet Mr. Ohara and be reborn.
I'm glad to meet a young man like you.
Oh, you two are a perfect couple.
Huh?
It's my idea.
Peace.
I'll have a drink with Mr. Ohara.
Sure, Mr. Ohara.
Thank you.
You're here, aren't you?
Oh, I'm not yours.
No, I'm not.
Then give me a drink.
Are you serious?
Take this, and...
Oh, that's...
My geldia, honey.
I brought it.
This is exactly what it is.
I don't care
Even if I lie or cheat
I'm helping someone, sometimes
Baby, do you know me?
I'm heading to tomorrow
Nice breathing
Don't get sick
I'll do what I have to do
Cute breathing
It's hard to understand
I want to show you my talent
It's better than looking down on me
Na na na na
Who are you?
What?
You're the owner of this tsukudani shop?
What are you saying?
This is my place
This is my father's shop
You look strange
Are you shooting a TV drama?
Next time, live broadcast
I'm counting on you
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Come on everyone
To our town
Thank you