Translated by Releska
When you watch TV,
Make sure you look out of the room and look away!
I look at the sunset that floats in the river
I kick the love stone and the shoes fly
I wonder if I'm going to go to the gym
I laughed that I was still a baby
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I feel like I'm going to win
The town's waves are so gentle
From the fountain of a pointed hat
To Taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow it'll end like this
I'm going to Katsushika and Shiba
There's no happiness
I've lost my way
And I realized
I'm such an idiot
Kame no Ongaeshi
Kids, look at this.
What is that, granddad?
You can't bully a turtle!
No! No! Stop!
What's so bad about it?
I think it was a pretty good performance.
It's hot when you two are together.
Ryo-tsu was the one who split the roles.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry for the role of a child who bullies turtles.
I agreed to it because it's a play to be shown in the children's world.
Ryo-san, if you don't do it seriously, you'll get no bonus.
That's why I'm doing it seriously.
Nagagawa, you're the worst.
Me?
What kind of person do you think Urashima Taro is?
He's a fisherman, isn't he?
That's right.
He went out to the sea on every day to catch fish.
Okay?
When you go out to the sea, it's not just sunny days.
There were also rainy days.
There were also snowy days.
On a stormy day, you might have been thrown out into the sea.
And he's a kind person who helps the bullied turtle.
He doesn't have to live a rich life.
He must have worn a suit until it was worn out.
The torn part is the needle and the turtle's butterfly made of fish bones.
The thread that dried the turtle is the thread that hits the next.
Do you think that kind of man has such a refreshing white skin?
Do you think he has such a tightly fixed hair?
Do you think he's wearing such a clean-up suit?
You can't feel the severity of living in the sea at all.
The reality is definitely reduced.
If you say so.
But Takada's play in the children's world is so much more realistic than that.
Idiot!
Children these days are much more eye-catching than adults.
If you feel that you're missing out on anything...
I'll buy you a new house!
Then what about my bonus?
You still have 30 years of home loan left.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Ryo-chan.
What?
Is it still your turn?
You're like a real princess.
Reiko, you look great in it.
Really?
Not at all.
What?
What's wrong with this outfit?
It's all wrong.
Reiko, how many years do you think you've been at the Ryugu Castle?
That's...
When you returned to your village,
I heard that no one knew you.
We were so young that we hadn't heard of you,
and I could barely Edwards,
until the day you came to us.
you just became a stubborn old man.
Considering your age and present,
50 years of service might think like that.
At least 50 years you'd stay there.
I see.
Can you keep firing after me?
You think you can do that?
Then it's three days at most.
Then what kind of clothes do you want?
Yeah, that's...
What are you doing?
That's not enough.
If it's not that colorful,
I can't put a man in it.
It's a matter of reality.
Then what about Ryo, the turtle actor?
You're going to wear a real turtle, right?
Leave it to me.
That's right.
I'm just taking a little bit of your shoulder.
Just stay still.
Taking a shoulder from a real turtle?
That's Ryo-tsu for you.
Oh, this is the turtle's costume!
It really looks like it's real!
Ryo-san is really into it this time.
And he's getting a bonus.
I wish he'd work this hard at his usual job too.
That's a good idea.
Nakagawa-san's Ferrari!
Nakagawa-san!
Good morning!
You're Nakagawa?
Yes.
I wanted to use your story as a reference
and seek out some reality.
This is the ultimate Urashima Taro, right?
It's real, but...
Nakagawa-san's image is...
Ryo-tsu and Kakichi are all so bad!
Ryo-san!
How is it?
Ryo-san is very loud, so I came up with a very bold and realistic Urashima.
I-it might be realistic.
But it doesn't have to be that...
Ryo-san, the characters are different.
Oh, as expected!
This is Ryo-san's costume!
I can't believe you let me dress like that!
I'm not going to forgive that primitive man!
By the way, what about the important ryo-tsu?
Today is the real show for the children's section.
It's already here.
Komachi!
Who do you think won't be forgiven?
I'm here, Chief.
What?
You can store your limbs inside?
It's real.
It's only...
Thanks to the reality tests,
the legs are over 50 kilograms.
It's really hard to stand upright.
This is bad.
I was wrong!
Stop it!
Yowls can fall easily!
Darn it!
I can't reach it!
If this happens, I'll use my left hand!
One, two, one, two, one, two, three!
That was close!
You were almost there, Senpai!
Now, let's try again!
Alright!
Someone's gotta lend a hand!
I'll practice my turtle movements.
I've got to get used to this guy's weight before the show starts.
You know when the show starts, right?
If you're late, you're out!
I know!
I think I can practice as much as I want here.
Oh, no. I'm getting tired.
I'll try here.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. I'm getting tired.
I'll try here.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I can't get up!
Oh, no!
My right chest!
I can't help it.
I'm going to the toilet.
Ah!
I'm going to the toilet!
Ow!
Ah!
I lost my will!
Ow!
A big one just came out of the water!
Really?
- This way! - Damn, it came this way!
- It's a turtle! - It's huge!
I'm gonna run away! Wait!
This is fun!
Hey, you guys try riding it!
You guys, stop it!
- A turtle spoke! - It's a man-faced turtle!
A turtle is not scary when it turns around.
- I see! - Yeah!
There!
Hey, stop it!
It thinks it's a kid!
Stop it! Stop it!
Damn, if it's a fairy tale, it'll come to help Urashima Taro!
Isn't there a turtle?
Isn't there a troubled turtle?
Isn't there a troubled turtle who was bullied by a kid?
To Be Continued
Kids, you can't bully turtles!
I was saved!
It's out!
Don't hesitate! Just stay still!
I'm Urashima Taro!
I'm Urashima Taro's ghost!
I'm Shindoran!
Then, open the box and do like this!
It's not opened yet.
I saved the turtle.
Then, I'll ask him to bring me to the Dragon Castle.
Ouch! The shoulder is really hurt!
Are you hurt?
You're not helping him.
Don't be a little bit passive to help him!
It's not your place to come to my house.
But, you have to bring me to the Dragon Castle.
You can't do that!
What is this old guy doing?
To Be Continued
Huh?
I'm starting to get confused.
This old man...
What's this?
Did he live in such a luxurious house?
He's got a lot of money.
Welcome home, Masai!
Wow, it's like a dragon castle.
It's a fake.
An important thing is coming.
An important thing?
In order to get it,
we have to go to the dragon castle.
Flaming Six, is Flaming Six here?
Yes.
Come to my room right away.
Yes, sir.
I'm really flamed.
There's my room in the back.
Why is there such a shabby hut in the building?
Because I'm Uroshima Taro.
No!
I don't want to go there anymore.
Thank you, sir.
You did a great job.
I'm saved, old man.
I see.
I'll take you to the dragon castle right away.
Wait a minute.
Are you serious, old man?
I've been studying Uroshima Taro for 78 years,
and I have the evidence that the dragon castle exists.
Really?
You're so annoying.
The dragon castle was in Tokyo Bay, wasn't it?
If you know the place, you can go there by yourself.
Don't get me involved.
At first, I believed that I could go to the dragon castle
if I had this map, but...
At first, I believed that I could go to the dragon castle if I had this map, but...
Okay, let's go to the dragon castle shortly.
It's not true, is it?
I found out.
Well, let's get back to the point.
This time...
I'll visit the mountain here.
Ah!
I'm sorry.
Now we're talking.
Now?!
That's enough!
Are you a donkey, or a dolphin, or a camel?!
I couldn't reach the Dragon Palace no matter how many times I went there.
I was troubled, but one day I finally understood.
Long ago, long ago, in order to save Urashima...
I see, so that's what it was.
The key to the Dragon Palace was in this song.
It was in the song.
It means...
Death!
If I don't get carried away by the god who saved me...
I won't be able to reach the Dragon Palace!
Stop fooling around with people's backs!
I'm sorry.
I immediately returned to my mission as Urashima Taro.
And...
From that day on, I went all over the country to save the turtle.
And the turtle I saved...
9,999 times!
But no turtle has ever taken me to the Dragon Palace.
Of course!
Ow!
You're the first one to have 10,000 turtles.
Now, take me to the Dragon Palace, turtle.
I'm not joking!
I have to go on stage for the children's play!
First of all, I'm not a turtle!
Wait.
He has this much money.
It's no loss to get along with him.
Besides, that map...
Isn't it a map that shows something?
For example, a ship sinking with treasure.
This might be a big story.
Ah!
Urashima Taro!
I'm going to take you to the Dragon Palace!
Oh!
You're so curious, turtle!
Now, I can finally fulfill my wish!
You're late, Ryotsu.
I've been calling my phone a few times, but I can't reach it.
What would he be?
On the other hand, it ain't his fault.
It's got to be this big, right?
Oh.
Oh...
This can't be it.
Come on.
On your way to the Dragon Palace.
I'm even glad I rode my turtle!
Me, too!
My friends,
Hey, you're older than the turtle at times like this.
Don't say such stupid things.
Hey, we need oxygen bombs in the future.
Let's go get some.
That's a good idea.
We're going to get some.
Let's go.
What about me?
You don't need a turtle.
Oh, that's right.
If you stay on the ground for too long, you forget to breathe.
I can't help it.
I'll just pop it.
Chizuta, it should be about time.
What?
The tide is getting stronger around here.
The turtle is getting stronger.
Damn it!
I can't give up like this.
What should I do?
I said, what should I do?
Oh, Ryugu Castle.
Oh, it's a turtle.
What's this?
Isn't it a sinking battleship?
Why is it here again?
I see.
There's a treasure hidden in this ship.
Treasure, treasure.
Treasure?
Huh?
Oh, my God!
It hurts!
Oh, it's a big box.
Is this the treasure box?
Let's open it and see what happens.
All right.
I'll open this in three, two, one.
I'll give you three!
One, two, three!
Let's give this to her as a souvenir.
You can open it when you're in trouble.
Yes, thank you very much, Princess Oto.
She's become a real old man!
How realistic!
I'm a bug.
I'm a dragon queen.
Are you okay?
You're Princess Oto?
No, I'm not.
We finally met.
Now I have no regrets in my life.
Thank you.
I'll give you Princess Oto!
No!
Give it back!
Princess Oto!
No!
Thank you!
According to the research,
there have been a lot of accident in that area.
Recently, a demolition ship has sunk during the exercise.
Yes.
Then, why is there a dragon's tomb on the map of that old man?
It seems that a person who caused a disaster in that place
was called like that because he was scared and became white-headed overnight.
What a thing!
Ah!
Huh?
Hey, stop it!
One more time!
I'll wear this clothes and become Princess Oto!
No!
It was my dream!
Please, one more time!
I said no!
Princess Oto
"Oriya!"
ze no youma saimo no eneruki
ashita o mutsume kino wo shinji
uchuu wo egaki chijyou ni tateba
kame ani no hoshi ga kururi to wa o kaita
kore de ii darou
ii wake nee darou
Episode 2
Oh no! The new car the manager bought has been damaged!
If I don't do something about it, I'll be a big help to the manager again!
Well, well, well, I guess I don't know anything about this at all!
Next time, "The New Car of Manager Henshin"
See you then!