A
When you watch TV,
make your room bright
and look away.
A
B
I wonder if it's true
Ahahaha
If you don't have a job, come to my place
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen
Do you understand?
I understand, I understand
If you understand, keep quiet and follow me
Ryo's Double Facial Expression
What's wrong, Senpai?
What is that "K"?
This magazine's article
I don't know if it's handsome or not
But what is the relationship between sports and a good face?
Ah, that's it
I'm sure you'll get a lot of fans.
There are people who are almost like TV talents.
Shut up!
What's good about sports and what's good about your face are completely different things.
What happens if you become a hot spot for your fans and you can't get into sports?
Well...
That's true, but...
You're a sports player, so it's more important than whether you have a good face or not.
Sports and what's good about your face have nothing to do with each other.
Humans are not faces.
It's important to know what they did and how good they are.
I think you're right.
Ryo-chan is a little...
B-B-We are the boy scouts.
What?
Hello there.
It's been a while.
Professor Ezeki.
You're wearing some stuff, aren't you?
How old are you and what are you wearing?
I'm not a gorilla.
I'm a...
A double-faced monster!
Hehehe...
♪That boy scouts and what's good about your face are completely different things♪
♪ Ayuki-rinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrinrin ♪
Huh?
You're singing the wrong thing in the middle, aren't you?
That's the finger five!
What's the point of the "Kaijin Nijumensou" singing "The Boys Detective Squad's" song?
I don't care about the details.
I'll give this to you.
Huh?
This is the "BD Badge."
That's why I said the "BD Badge" is the "Kaijin Nijumensou's" song, not the "Kaijin Nijumensou's" song!
I can't keep up with the maniacal topics.
Me too.
By the way, what are you doing here today?
You're just pretending to be asleep, so I guess it has something to do with the two-faced monster.
That's a different story, Gorilla-kun!
Our super-brain has also made a huge invention by chance!
A huge invention?
A HENTAI MASK!
A HENTAI MASK!?
If you put this mask on your face, what will happen is...
What's this?
It's stuck perfectly, and I can't take it off!
What are you going to do!? It hurts!
No problem!
Like this...
What are you doing?
It's strange.
What!?
He looks just like the manager!
Like this...
You're still surprised?
This time, I'm going to do this!
This time, you're the manager!
I see.
If you put this HENTAI MASK on, any face will be free!
Gorilla-kun will have 20 faces, 20...
No, 200 faces!
He's a super-brain man!
How about that, Gorilla-kun?
Isn't it interesting?
Umm..
Like this...
I hope this way...
Well...
You're Reiko-san, eh?
Uh...! Stop it! It's so disgusting!
You look like you're FM-ing at the camera.
Well, how do I take this mask off?
Phew...
That's for the next time.
The next time? What do you mean?
It's a fun time until we meet again.
Hey, hey!
Goodbye, Kyendai-chikun!
If you say that, I'll beat you to death!
Damn it! What's going on with this face?!
Coming soon!
He's still unresponsive!
I'm sure he still doesn't know how to take off his mask.
I'm sure so.
Mr. Nakagawa!
Do you need anything from me, ladies?
Mr. Nakagawa, is your schedule free this Sunday?
Would you like to drive with me?
That's right.
I'll take my special Ferrari and have a good time at 1:00 midnight.
Let's have a coffee at dawn.
That's so cool!
That's what I'm talking about.
We don't have time for you.
You, Ryōtsu!
You're impossible to fool with your eyes.
Of course not.
I just pretended to be on your side.
What kind of trick is this?
How could you do that to me?
You're not good enough for me.
This is a new toy for you, Ryō.
Please, don't do that to me.
Well, I thought you were a fool.
I thought it was just a joke.
You're the worst!
I have some good money.
Actually, I have a special mission for you.
Special mission?
Yes. From today onwards, you will be assigned to the Special Police Department.
S-Special Police Department?
Yes. You will be assigned to the department where there are no other people.
So there are no other people.
But I don't have any special skills.
No, you do!
You may not have noticed it yourself, but you are a very special person.
That is because you are very stubborn.
So from today onwards, you will be called "Fundoshi Deka".
F-F-Fundoshi Deka?
What does that have to do with being stubborn?
If you want to be stubborn, you have to be a stubborn father.
And a stubborn father...
There is no such thing as a stubborn father who always reaches out for money!
We have done a thorough survey of the charges filed by public officials nationwide.
And, among all the police officers in Japan,
you're one of the people who are the most suitable for being a stubborn father!
Yes...
I don't think they would say you have a problem.
But that is...
Then hurry up and change into those uniforms!
Yes sir!
Ah...
I-is this all right?
Hmm, well, it's fine.
But what if someone who is a special detective is embarrassed?
Be more honest and honest.
Yes!
But just the look alone doesn't make you feel like a special detective.
Here's a scene with a factory you promised to appear in.
Let's make it a scene.
Ah...
Yes!
"A man comes to town in a red hood."
"A man comes and goes, and a man comes and goes."
"The special detective of the police station, Daijiro Ohara."
"He calls for someone."
"A big hood!"
Hmm, I'm starting to get the hang of it.
But I'm still not sure how to move it properly.
When you turn, you have to go like this.
You can't go around like this.
Ah, yes.
And the important pose is like this.
Raise your right elbow properly, and stretch your legs as much as you can.
Ah, yes.
Well, you can practice here for a while.
Oh.
You can do it properly now, so come to the chief's office.
Yes, sir!
If you can't do this properly,
you'll have to live in a very tough way in the era of the restaurant.
Okay.
Well then, I'll be looking forward to it.
I'll be waiting for you.
Hehehe...
I'm sorry.
I'm Ohara.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Mr. Ohara!
Please, have a look, chief.
This time I'm going to make a perfect decision.
He came to the town with a big
How is it, chief?
Will this connect my neck?
Ohara-san gave all this to Ryo-san?
He's a rare person.
Please give me the money.
Yes, sir.
Please give me ten special sushi.
Five ramen, eight fried rice, and eight dumplings.
Please give me all of them.
Thanks to Mask, this is heaven.
I'm just like the chief.
Well, who will I meet tomorrow?
I'll think about that tomorrow.
I can't. I'm late again.
I have to think of something.
Where is the uniform?
Ah, there it is.
Oh, good morning, Yohoma-chan.
What are you surprised about?
When did that person get in?
What?
I think I'm getting a lot of attention.
Good morning.
Good morning, Ryo-chan.
What are you surprised about?
It's Ryo-chan.
Of course.
What's wrong with your face?
I fell down.
What?
Is this my face?
Damn it.
So that's why everyone was surprised to see my face.
What?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Your face is deformed.
What?
It's kind of stiff like a mochi.
It must be a defective product.
It's Professor Ezaki's invention.
Hello, everybody.
Ezaki, you!
What's going on?
I don't know.
What?
Pa?
That's not it.
Pa.
I will tell you why my face got so stiff!
No, it's still a couple of hours.
Two or three hours?
Two or three hours.
After two or three hours, it will be fully hardened
so I can peel off my selvata.
So you can peel it off, right, Gorilla-kun?
Until then.
You have to wait for a while with that face!
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Farewell, Horm!
What the hell are you doing here?
But, can you really get away from me in a few hours?
I'm not sure...
Well, senpai, please take care of the night shift.
Huh?
It's better not to appear in front of people.
It's not good for the heart to see you for the first time.
Please don't make any strange noise.
I know.
Damn, was it the night shift today?
Even so, I can't take off my mask at all!
Um, where is the house of the newly married Amano-san?
What did you say?
Help!
Damn, he judged people by their faces.
That's what he said, but it's pretty amazing.
It's night, but I can't take off my mask at all.
I'll put it here until my face is back to normal.
Ugh, I'm hungry.
Come to think of it, I haven't eaten anything since last night.
Hmm?
Hmm, I don't have anything.
I guess I'll go buy some ginger.
If I get robbed and stolen, it'll be terrible.
I only have a gun.
I'll eat this.
I really don't want to go to jail.
I'm hungry.
OK.
I'll eat it anyway.
It's all you.
That's right, but when I was the only guest,
That's all I had.
Hmm?
I think it's this one.
I could see, "What's going on?"
Welcome!
Um, bento, bento...
Which should I choose?
Oh, it's wasabi-taro-mayonnaise!
I-I'm sorry! Please!
Will you give it to me?
Y-yes, please!
Thank you very much!
What are you doing? Please line up properly!
What?
Hey, you!
Do you have a problem?
You!
You're trying to ask me to do something!
No, I-I-I can't do that...
Don't bother me!
What?
I'll cut you to pieces!
Y-yes, sir!
You saved me!
I see.
Well, then.
This is awesome.
You're really something, big bro.
You really show off.
H-how is that face? It looks familiar.
What is this?
This is it!
This is the time when the Kyo-Waku Hand is in danger.
Please be careful.
Kyo-Waku Hand?
That sounds like a bad idea.
Well, I'm full now.
I'll go take a bath.
Welcome.
Here's 400 yen.
What are you looking at?
Suddenly, there are no customers.
I'm lucky.
Have fun.
The culprit has a gun.
Please be careful.
I'm going to the culprit.
This place is completely surrounded.
I can't run away anymore.
Drop your weapon and come out immediately.
Throw the grenade in 30 seconds.
Repeat.
It's kind of noisy outside.
I'm here.
Thank you for your hard work.
And the culprit is this man.
What? What's wrong?
This photo looks like Ryo-chan.
If that's the case, who is inside?
Ryo-chan?
What does that mean?
That's...
Time is running out.
Ryo-chan, you're out of time.
What?
I'm going to the culprit.
Drop your weapon and come out immediately.
What's going on?
This is...
I see.
He got it wrong.
Oh, no.
If I get caught with this face,
the chief will find out everything about yesterday's accident.
That's very bad.
He's out.
He's running up the roof.
He even went to the learner's room.
Currently, the culprit is fleeing to the welfare building.
He is escaping to the welfare building.
It's bad!
Why does it show up here?
Rock with it!
You even used the police force!
Damn, I can't move!
I'm just like you!
Who are you?!
You too!
You're the criminal of Shibete High!
Oh, crap!
Hey!
You bastard!
I thought it was weird.
I see.
So it was all Ryo's doing.
I knew it.
He used that mask.
He did that?
Hey!
I'm doing this because of you!
This is...
Damn it!
Let go!
I'm not letting go!
Ryo!
Which one?
I got it.
The mask...
What?
Get him!
Stop him!
What!?
I'm not getting rid of him!
Stop him!
All right!
I'm not the one!
I'm not!
Don't copy Ryo!
Don't copy me!!
I said I'm not!
You're so bald!
I forgot the mask, but I can't take it off.
It's a invention of Professor Ezaki after all.
It's personal gain.
It's better to be in the prison for the sake of me and the people.
I'm wrong!
I failed the first test.
I failed the second test.
I failed the last test.
I failed the fourth one.
What's wrong with that?
All thechnolian.
I failed the third one.
I failed the fourth one.
I failed the fifth one.
I failed the sixth one.
I failed the seventh one.
I failed it again!
Why, I wonder?
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Why, I wonder, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
I got it!
I got it! The lottery that I bought with the 2,000 yen I borrowed from the manager is worth 1.4 billion yen!
I thought about it, but I dropped it in the bank vault I entered by the check.
Moreover, the deadline is tomorrow.
If this happens, I have no choice but to do it!
Next time, "Return the lottery!"
Thank you for watching!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, surely Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!