Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new era lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city with the hero ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing trendy clothes ♪
♪ I'll be more handsome ♪
♪ Let it rain! ♪
♪ Everybody come on ♪
♪ Start running ♪
♪ Dreams can't always be stopped ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♪
♪ Love you one ♪
♪ Everybody can do ♪
♪ It's a little dark ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt to spit it out ♪
♪ I'm in a hurry ♪
♪ Hold my curiosity ♪
♪ Strong and high, strong and down ♪
♪ I don't care what people think ♪
♪ What's going on? ♪
♪ I don't like people talking about themselves ♪
♪ I'm in a hurry ♪
♪ Being hurt is in vain ♪
You're so ungrateful!
Nakagawa, you go in front!
Yes!
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is the gun?
It's mine!
It's the underwear robot!
It hurts!
I'm the police!
Hey!
It's me!
I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi, the first officer of the police!
Oh, it's true!
It's Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
It's me, but it's Ryo-tsu!
If it's Ryo-tsu Kankichi, then it's not a big deal if it's the underwear robot!
Ryo-tsu!
We're going to arrest you!
The current suspect of the underwear robot!
Don't mess with me!
I'm not an underwear robot!
Then what are you holding in your hands?
Huh?
That's the proof you can't move!
N-No!
I just grabbed it when it fell!
I heard a scream, so I got in here!
Do you think that kind of excuse will work?
It's true!
There's another one here!
That's not true!
Ah!
Phew...
Mr. Nakagawa!
Really?
It's a misunderstanding.
We heard a scream, so we got in here.
It's useless.
I said it.
What?
Is that so?
No!
We were confused.
I'm sorry.
Come to think of it, we were doing a special training for the Chikan troupe.
We were screaming "Chikan!"
Hey, you!
You're saying the same thing, but you don't believe me at all!
Don't you doubt Nakagawa's words?
Oh, that's natural, right?
Of course.
You guys, what kind of basis do you have to judge people?
Of course, it's their face!
In general, it's the face of a man with thick and painful eyebrows.
I can't trust a man like him.
You're right about that.
Besides, he was short.
Nonchalantly sluggish.
And with a short body.
How long can you hang on to it?
And his hair stinks under his feet.
Listen to my words!
Please, please.
Don't!
You're getting into my way!
Stop it!
Don't!
You idiot!
Stop it!
Ryo...
No, I misunderstood!
Mr. Nakagawa.
Didn't you try to steal the underwear?
No!
Yes, I did!
I'm not!
I'm an imposter!
That was a disaster, Ryotsu.
But you're not doing the right thing.
You should be grateful for that.
Grateful? I'm not joking.
Women these days think men are nothing.
I don't understand what you're saying.
I understand women these days.
And...
You're so mean!
Right?
And you look so pitiful.
You should date me.
No way!
You're so rich!
Hey, man!
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Shut up.
You're such a pain.
I'm sorry.
I'm an alien.
I've decided!
What are you doing, Senpai?
I'm a man.
I can't date a woman.
I can't date a woman within two meters of me.
No way.
Then you can't get a job.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Which way is the station?
No way!
Don't come in from that line.
What?
You're a security guard, aren't you?
Oh, the station.
The station is...
The first corner is on the left.
This...
You idiot!
No matter what anyone says, I won't date a woman.
I'm sorry.
I can arrest Ryo-tsu in a little while.
Ryo-tsu?
Prepare for an emergency.
Ryo-tsu is the best.
Ryo-tsu is good at roam me.
Ready?
Can you feel anything?
Wait a minute!
What are you doing?
Get out of my way!
Senpai, I must go right now.
Please take it.
Okay.
Oh, please.
Look, that's the one!
Oh, that's the one from the magazine!
I applied with a light heart, but I didn't know I'd really get it.
But Ryo's garden is easy to use, so it's good.
Right.
Look at Ryo's bed.
It's so nice!
Well, the materials have been imported, so this is the video of the log house being assembled.
Well, please do your best to assemble it.
What!? We're going to assemble it?
What should we do? We can't assemble this.
Doesn't anyone know who's good at this?
There it is!
But...
They won't do it for us.
Right! There's a good way!
Wait, wait!
Let's gather everyone tomorrow.
Hey, hey! This is bad, Ryo-san!
Look at the survey article for the book club this month.
Yeah, I know that!
Man, every month they do a boring project.
That's clearly a Seco-Hara!
They're making fun of men!
What? What?
You're the number one who hates Ryo-tsu again?
Then we've finally achieved V7.
What's wrong?
This is...
The number one who hates me who asked the survey...
It doesn't have my name on it!
What!?
But the number one who's good at exchanging...
This is...
The number one who's good at exchanging, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The number one who wants to be my lover, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The number one who wants to marry, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
He always keeps the top in the middle and gets third place.
Isn't this a misprint?
That's not true.
If it's a misprint or a misprint, then it's just a misprint.
That means...
You!
You've done a cowardly impression again!
Why would I do such a thing?
Chief, I don't think you would do something like that on purpose.
Hmm?
That's true.
But to suddenly be number one from the top...
That's weird.
It's not weird!
The women of today have finally realized the true manliness of men.
They're more likely to choose the truth over the good of the story.
They're more likely to choose the truth over the bad of the story.
Heh heh.
Ryo-tsu senpai.
The number one for exchanging...
Congratulations!
Congratulations for the first place.
Congratulations.
Ah.
We've been deceiving Ryo-tsu-san all this time.
That's right.
We've finally realized the charm of Ryo-tsu-senpai.
I'm... I'm popular.
I can't believe it.
You're too much.
You're not going to go against the woman, are you?
Huh?
What a useless guy.
Hn...
Don't cross that line!
What?
I've decided not to go against women.
Don't say such things.
Shut up!
Get out of here!
Ugh...
Senpai!
You!
Go away!
What's with that attitude?!
Well, well.
calm down.
First step completed.
I'll see if that idiot gets his food.
There's no way it's not coming.
How do you like it?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Here it comes.
Hello, this is Rai Rai-ken.
I wonder who's playing with that.
Shhh!
This is Rai Rai-ken. I brought you some ramen.
Here you go.
I knew it. Ryo-tsu's charm is his manliness.
Yeah.
He's not like the guys in the store.
His eyebrows are so sharp.
Seriously, a good man is more important than looks.
But it's sad that we can't accept his passion.
Thank you.
We're always against men we like.
That's his personality.
Hey, Ryo-sama!
But he's not that popular.
He's always against men he likes.
Well, women are complicated.
Hey, you two.
Oh, Ryo-tsu-senpai.
Senpai, you didn't accept our bouquet earlier.
It's not mine.
I'm sorry, Naoko.
Well, I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's a cup of coffee.
Good, because we're in the cold.
Here, have a sip.
What?
You bought it yourself?
Naoko.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thank you.
It's good!
Here, drink it.
What?
Don't hold back. Drink it.
But, but...
I'm happy, Ryotsu-senpai!
Huh? Why am I in this situation?
You put up with it, Naoko!
I won't waste your precious sacrifice!
I'll finish you off!
Hey, Mr. Ryotsu!
Good evening, are you free?
How is it?
Do you want to go out for a drink?
I thought it was someone else, but it's you, Honda-kun.
You look fine.
What are you wearing?
I have an appointment tonight.
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to be with you.
Appointment?
Ryo-san, you'll be invited to the female dormitory tonight.
The female dormitory?
You're jealous, aren't you?
I can't take you there.
Anyway, I'm the first one to be invited.
Well, women these days
know what it's like to be a man.
It's different from what they usually say.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Good evening!
Lady!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Hey, Shibana!
Did you know?
It's actually a male dormitory here.
Only Ryo-san is special.
Oh, my.
You're so impressed.
Naoko.
Ryo-san.
The moon is so beautiful.
Hey, it's clear. Let's go see it.
Huh? It was cloudy last time.
Whatever. Whatever.
OK. Now!
Roger.
Hey!
This must be the legendary Pigeon Man!
Boo!
Huh? What's that?
What is this?
Oh, that. It's a log house kit.
We have all the logs, so we just need to put them together as it says on the map.
Gas and water are also one-touch.
If we put it in Ryo's garden, it'll be a place for everyone to live.
But we don't have the right log builder.
We can't build anything like that.
Is there a strong and strong man somewhere?
There's none.
All the men around here are weak.
It's great to see a man working with sweat on his forehead.
Yeah, the trend these days is a man with a smell of sweat.
I don't know if it's a trend or not, but you guys forget someone.
Oh, what?
A strong, strong, reliable man.
Who?
Is that Ryochi-senpai?
No, I don't want to tell Ryochi-senpai about that.
Why not?
Because Ryochi-senpai is wearing a suit like that.
Right?
This is my temporary form.
This is my true form.
Yeah!
Seiji!
And this is my army.
It's a disaster, but it's a force.
Shut up! Don't say that!
First, the foundation construction.
I know, you guys!
Come on!
Hey, don't be so angry!
Honda, what's that little thing?
Hmph, men are simple.
Hey, bring it on!
What?
Why don't you two do it too?
I'm sorry!
Everyone, it's lunchtime!
It's our homemade lunch!
We'll make a cookie ourselves.
Amazing!
It looks delicious!
Terai-san and Honda-san, thank you!
You can do it!
I can count on you!
That's great!
You're much better than you look.
Really?
Wow, Terai-san, you have a good arm.
No, you're mostly Z.
You guys, let's go home!
Let's go home!
Oh, no!
But they've come all the way here.
It would be better if you all cooperated.
I can do this alone.
Go home!
We don't have enough lunch boxes!
That was a little bit of a mistake.
It was a mistake.
I guess it's impossible to do it alone.
I can't ask them for help.
You're slow.
If you do this, you'll be praised,
you'll be praised, you'll be praised,
and you'll be put on the stage to work.
Okay?
Ryo, hang in there!
Hang in there!
You look great working here!
You look great working here! You're cool!
Well, you're right.
Wow, I'm surprised!
You're really strong!
What is this? I like it!
You look great!
You look like a man!
You're right!
This is a one-time job.
Paka is easy to handle.
Let's keep doing this in the back row for 24 hours.
Oh, my head!
Ryo!
Perfect, Ryo!
You're great!
You're amazing!
What is this?
Ryo!
Great job, Ryo!
What a perfect job.
Ryo!
Great true job!
I guess we have to shoot him.
Ryoichi, are you okay?
I'm a little tired.
I'll give you a massage.
Do your best.
Please make our log house soon.
Of course, Tomoe.
-Oh! -Revive!
-Yay! -Yay!
-Good luck! -Good luck!
To Be Continued
Here's your lunch.
See you later.
Are you leaving already?
I'm on a business trip.
Another convenience store lunch.
I used to love homemade lunches.
The level of lunches has dropped
due to the lack of perfection in the house.
Oh, this again.
I have to eat more poppy bread and butter
every day.
But I can't find it.
My dad is too stingy to make a living.
These days, no one supported me.
I feel like I'm forced to work,
being forced to do this.
If you keep doing this,
you'll beビったt.
I soon felt like a senior was being manipulated.
Nakagawa-kun, seems like you didn't want to lose the first position.
You know what I mean? You're envious of me, though. Do not be Dangri.
I'm so tired.
Senpai! Ryotsu-senpai!
Ryotsu-senpai!
Senpai!
He's still not here, that Ryotsu guy.
He's so tired.
It's only a little while, but he's still working hard.
I wonder when he'll finish it.
I'm tired of nagging him.
Oh, I'm so tired!
I worked so hard to get the first place in the poll.
Just a little more.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't mean.
What's wrong? Did I say something?
It's nothing!
Don't worry about it.
Just a little more. I'll do my best.
I'm glad. I didn't hear you.
I'm glad you're an idiot.
I can hear you.
I'll do my best.
Watch me.
That's so great!
It's finally done.
Our villa!
It's awesome!
It's so pretty!
The curtain windows!
The bath is bigger than the ridges.
Hey, let's stay here tonight!
Agreed!
I'll teach you how to get angry at me.
This tree smells so good.
It feels like I'm in a hot spring in the mountains.
But he's surprisingly good at making such a great log house.
He's really good at it.
Yeah, he's been working hard on it.
I think I should rewatch it.
Komachi!
What?
You're in love with Ryo Tsukankichi, aren't you?
No, I'm not!
I'm so happy!
No, you're not!
Everyone, be quiet!
The special seat is 5,000 yen.
The camera and video are 1,000 yen each.
Come on!
Let's go!
I'm in heaven, you stupid girls!
Come on!
Did you see that?
This is what a real man's job is!
What are you doing?
You're a jerk!
Ouch!
My ear pads are all messed up!
I don't have any tires!
Huh?
I won't forgive you!
We're still going to get revenge!
I won't forgive you for bullying a weak woman!
You're not weak at all!
Wait a minute!
If you get hated, you'll be the number one.
New Year's Eve at the Chief's House
New Year's Eve at the Chief's House?
Huh? I haven't heard of it!
Why didn't you call me?
Chief!
I'm going to go right now!
Please leave the Osechi food!
Next time on New Year's Battle Carter!
Please take care of me!
New Year's Eve at the Chief's House
♪ I tried to stop the clock ♩
♪ Because time will pass ♩
♪ Don't stare into the distance ♩
♪ Just laugh and stay alive ♩
♪ Even if today starts raining ♩
Even if it's a long day, tomorrow will be clear
Bye bye, let's wash our hands
Goodbye, the unpleasant things
Oh yeah, let's live the way we like
There are good things
Outside the door, the sun is calling