Translated by Releska
I looked at the sunset floating in the river
I kicked a stone and it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym I was saving money for
I was laughed at for being a kid
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There are only patsushika and kameari
The cityscape that doesn't change even one yawn is strangely kind
From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi
To the taishakuten, the sunset falls
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again because of the patsushika and kameari
I realized
I'm an idiot
'Cause I'm an idiot
A本抹け in Canada
To the Tungari-boshi
You're so annoying!
Reiko is on a trip, and the chief isn't paying me.
Why do I have to work in this damn hot place alone?!
Oh, right! I think the ice pillow fell off...
Huh? What's this?
Hey! This is the magic circle I found in Haru!
I totally forgot to hide it so the chief wouldn't find it!
Yay! I'm so lucky!
I'm so lucky!
This is the blessing of God!
Huh? Wait a minute.
I think the best time to get a cold is on the 60th.
49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60?!
What?! If I don't change it today, it'll be a year!
I think the ice pillow was about 1000 yen.
I can't afford to lose it.
What should I use it for?
I'm so lucky!
It's my death!
I'm so glad.
I'm finally awake!
Maria, where are you?
I should've slept a little longer.
What?!
It's the old man from Hondara!
What happened?
I'll take you to Canada.
What?
Actually, I'm going to make a division in Canada.
I'm going to travel with Ai.
Besides, why do I have to go with you?
I could go with you, Ryo.
It's okay if you're with the king.
Ai won't say it like that.
I brought you here.
Ah!
You've got to be kidding!
Is this your job to kill me with an anvil?
Huh?!
Ah!
Hey!
I have to change this sword by the end of today!
No way!
I can't make it with 100,000 yen!
Excuse me!
Let go!
I have to change the sword!
No!
Wait!
Sir!
Uwa!
That's why I said no!
Hey! You brought me here while I was in despair!
Why did you give me 100,000 yen?
Don't be so excited.
If you go to Canada, you'll only get nice things.
Nice things?
The village where I bought land for my wife has a big dog in it.
What?
It's not a dog with a love pad. It's a live dog.
And it has F-cup and G-cup.
What? A live dog?
I've been to Canada before.
What? I've been to Canada before.
It seems he downwards.
That's why I'm so excited to have a life like my wife!
What? I've been to Canada before.
I've been to Canada before.
But I can't imagine living in Canada.
If I was given the chance, would I have been able to do it?!
You should be in a amidst of many people.
I'll wake up and give you a ride.
But there's nothing I would do if I ever have to.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I love you, I'm sorry to hear that.
My dream is to make the Honda-ra Kemp the best fighting game in the world!
Ah, we're here.
It looks like we're going to change planes from here.
Hey! Is there really a Nama-chichi here?!
Nama-chichi?
Ryo-sama, what's a Nama-chichi?!
Well, it's a Nama-chi, no, an egg-chi.
It's a Nama-chau-na.
I was invited to a date.
What is it? What is it?
Hey, where are you from?
Aren't you from Alaska?
Is this place okay?
Well, there are a thousand of them.
Well, it's okay.
Wow!
I can't believe you can build a building on ice like that.
Don't you think you got tricked?!
Who on earth bought it?!
Well, I think it was Hanyu who said it, right?
What?!
Ah!
This is a fake real estate company with a chip on it!
Ehh?!
We were perfectly beaten, huh?
I bought it because it was worth 5 million yen.
Did I get fooled?
Oh no! It's a disaster!
What did you do?
Where are the F-cup and G-cup girls?
That's...
You bastard!
Stop it!
What did you say?
You bastard!
You're going to sink into the sea of ice!
Stop it!
My last...
There's a passport in there!
What's a passport?
You can't go back to Japan!
I lost 100,000 yen and I'm in this place because of you!
What are you doing, Dad?
Hey, that's my passport!
I'm using this passport!
No way!
It's a different picture, so I'm not going to use it!
What are you doing?
What?
Dad!
Look, it's me!
It's completely different!
No way, Dad!
What are you talking about?
Show me your passport!
Look, it's completely different from the picture.
The judge was in a panic.
It's basically you, Maria!
Anyway, give me your passport!
You can live here by yourself!
No!
Give it to me!
Don't bring your face closer!
It's hot!
I'm begging you!
No!
Don't say that!
I won't!
Please!
It's too much!
Give it to me!
Give me back my passport!
Give me my passport!
Oh, my!
Good girl.
I'm begging you!
Bring this one over here!
Come here!
Now we are friends!
You!
You dropped it on purpose, huh?
I didn't do that.
You only have 30 yen.
What do you want?
I don't have any.
You're so naughty.
You're a good boy.
You too.
What's wrong with you?
You're a good boy.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
We're not fighting.
We're just going to die.
We're not going to die.
What's that sound?
It's a helicopter.
The sky didn't let me go.
Help me.
What did you do?
I thought I heard Ryo's voice.
I can't believe I'm in the north of Canada.
Help me.
I didn't notice.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to make you notice.
What are you doing?
Ryo.
Reiko.
I need a medical check.
.
A isso - I-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-iiii....
I need a medical check.
I need a medic.
Help me, will you?
I'll if you save this place.
Thank you, for helping me.
I didn't think Ryo would be here.
I was fooled.
I thought a real man would make a company.
What are you talking about?
You were caught by a live father and you came back.
Live father?
No, I mean, live father, not live father.
I was just kidding.
By the way, what are you doing here?
My father went to Bahama to play.
So I'm using my courage to do business meetings and inspections with the companies in my line.
Oh, you came here to play.
I'm going to enjoy my vacation tomorrow since I've finished my work today.
Oh, right.
Why don't we go skiing together tomorrow?
Sounds good.
I'm not in the mood for that.
Father...
Uncle, I'm going to let my company find the land of Shibu.
So don't be depressed.
We'll be stuck here for days until we get our passports.
Let's think this is a vacation and play, father.
Okay, I got it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
When it's decided, let's go play.
You only brought the major items.
Hon Dara has a lot of fun.
Okay, let's play.
Father, you're quick to recover.
It's my first time to be born to like something.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay.
It's not too late to be excited.
I'll make you pay for your grudges.
Uncle, relax and lower your waist a little.
Is this the way, Reiko-dono?
Yes, keep it up.
You liked the ski in the summer and that's why...
...you came to Canada to learn about beauty.
I'm glad you're here.
Hey!
Big jump!
Front first spin twist!
Ryo-sama, you're amazing!
Why are you so good?
I was only a rich man when I was born in Tokyo.
We, the common people, have trained in the snow in Tokyo.
We wore skis made of bamboo and trained with our bare hands.
That's why we're self-proclaimed as the dog-slaughtering law.
But we can't be defeated by those who are skilled.
I'll teach you how to ski.
Don't try to avoid me!
I'm from Reiko!
How dare you say that I'm going to teach you how to ski?
What?
You're challenging me, a budokan!
Wait a minute.
I'm going to remove the skis.
Let's try the hondara sword!
What a good skier.
You can call me a self-proclaimed law.
You're a self-proclaimed law, too.
Then I'll teach you how to ski.
We'll learn to ski faster when we're together.
Don't say that to Reiko!
All right!
Hehehe.
First, you must ski 1,000 meters at a time,
No way!
What do you mean, no way?
You're going to be a teacher!
I don't have any feelings for you!
That's enough!
Get off me!
Where are you going?
Just do it now!
Are you going to be all right, Dad?
No need to worry.
It appears Ryo-chan.
Can't worry about being a teacher.
Can't you get on the lift?
I'm not good at an expensive place.
This is your chance to clear your revenge!
Get off the lift!
Go fix it!
I got it!
Let go!
Let go, idiot!
Then so that's why the game is so long, can't I!?
Hey!
You bastard!
Don't move!
Shut up! I'm going to sit there!
Don't come up!
I said we can't sit here!
Then get off!
You bastard!
It's so hot! I'm scared!
You bastard! Hold my hand!
Are we going to slide from here?
That's right.
We're almost at the right angle.
That's why we're going to practice the right angle.
I don't even know how to turn or stop!
I'll teach you while we slide.
No!
I'll give you a good lesson this time.
Go now!
Good job!
Next is the right angle.
And then...
Like this!
See?
That's right!
You're a real man!
What's wrong?
I'm cold from the snow.
You're a pathetic dancer.
Go and get it done with the tree.
I got it.
I didn't think I'd be imitating you in the countryside.
Oh, I'm getting cold too.
Stop it!
Don't come this way!
Don't grab it!
Stop it!
I can't stop you anymore!
You're all idiots!
Let go of my hand!
Don't come near me!
What are you doing?
*Screams*
Now, the Japanese consulate is contacting us, and the passport will be available by tomorrow.
That was faster than I expected.
What should we do? We can go back to Japan by tomorrow, but should we get a ticket for the plane?
I think it's a little more painful, but it seems like they came out quietly. The chief is very...
Huh? The hunter is so inconspicuous.
There is a local hunting party. There are many bears around here.
I see.
That's quite a lot, Reiko-dono. Thank you for deciding the branch of Hondara Prefecture.
No, no, it's not that big of a deal.
It's decided?
We will put a dojo in the training room of this hotel.
That's good. Now we can go back to Japan with peace of mind.
I and you will stay.
What?
You two will be the chiefs.
Ai, you can live here as you wish.
But, father, I don't want to be the chief.
We can live together, so it's fine.
That's true, but...
Don't joke around. I didn't hear that. Why am I the chief?
*Screams*
Is it a yes or a no?
Noooo!
Beautiful!
Nooo!
Which one?
Nooooo!
Nooo!
Which one?
Nooooooooo!
Beautiful!
I said yes!
It's done.
Reiko-dono, would you like torell tea in the training room?
Yes.
Are you alright, Ryô-sama?
I was weak when I skied.
Maria, tell me how weak father is.
Huh?
If you keep this up, you'll become the head of the law department and live in Canada!
B-But...
Maria, you were tricked too!
Tell me, Maria!
Yes, if you say so...
I remember when I was training in Yamagomori, my dad once bit my head from behind.
And he said I was really bad at it.
That's it!
If you bite me again, I won't tell you to make fat in your body ever again!
I can use this one.
You have to sew it up properly. It's not good to take it off halfway through.
Yes.
But it's real, it's real.
Hide here.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
I'll bite you as hard as I can.
Here it comes.
Oh my god!
Watch out!
Get out!
What the?!
The hunters are here! Stop it!
The beard hounds are around us too often.
And they scare me.
Leave me alone.
I've lost my sleep for days.
All right!
Whoa!
You can't grab it just by staring at it.
Wait! Listen to me!
Yeah!
No!
My head!
I can't jump in the air!
That bear is Ryo-chan?
Yeah.
So you were trying to trick me?
I got it. I'll get you out of here right away.
I'm getting back on you!
Don't shoot! I'm a human!
Don't shoot! I'm a Japanese policeman!
I have to run to the mountains!
footage 2
5 Minutes Later
I've captured all the bears, but I don't know who Ryo-chan is.
It's me, for real.
Oh, no! I was screaming, so my voice got hoarse.
All of them are normal bears.
I understand that too.
I'm sorry...
You're such a bad father! Remember that!
Example!
"Ryotsu Kankichi Junsacho has an order from the president..."
"to go to a restaurant next to the office and do a special job..."
Why do I have to work part-time jobs that I can't even make money from?
If I had to do that, I'd better write a letter of apology at the end of the day!
Next time, "Limi's Revenge Recipe"!
See you then!
Subtitled by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
There are rumors that I'm a woman who can't fall in love
But I have so much I want to do
I want to ride a bike through the vast desert
More than a bird
I want to be free
The speed of the full moon
Changes the lady's dream
My love, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
The future of the panorama
The dazzling light that shines on us
Do you understand?
I'm sorry
Please wait for me
Translated by Dreadopp and Zedopp