They say lives.
They say more lives.
They say more people.
When you watch TV,
brighten up your room,
and take a look from a distance.
The people who don't have money,
come to me.
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
It will be alright somehow
Come to me if you don't have a job
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red cloud
It will be alright somehow
Do you understand?
Do you understand? Do you understand?
If you understand, then quietly follow me!
Bonus Soda Battle Seven
Now, we will start the 35th Ryoutsu-Kankichi Bonus Soda Battle Strategy Meeting.
This year's strategy...
"The
Hm?
Then, let's start the operation!
We are the ones who will win this year!
Yeah!
That's dangerous!
Ryo-san took a day off yesterday, and he's going somewhere!
What?!
The public in the store is probably very frustrated by now.
With these, they will be able to get bonuses anywhere in the country.
Then, you'll be able to keep up with them.
Momo
I was on a vacation before I knew it.
I borrowed money from you two days ago...
You're so stubborn.
Ryo, you're not stupid either.
We predicted that you would come again this year,
and we were in a hurry.
I-Is that so?
Damn it!
Ryo, you're so stubborn about things like this!
What are you going to do, Kuramo?
If this goes on, I'll lose the bonus battle without doing anything!
Mom!
Takashi! Takashi!
Thanks to the viewers' cooperation,
the mother and child who had been separated from their parents
are finally reunited!
Thank you so much!
We are sending you a live broadcast of the TV release investigation.
We have recruited a client.
Your request will be sent to us right now.
This is it!
What's wrong, Kuramo?
We will change the strategy for this year!
The name is...
"Give me your tears! The strategy of the Great King of the Land!"
I will never let you escape, Ryo!
What should we do now?
I have borrowed money from the inside,
so I won't be able to drink and eat for a while.
What?
Isn't that him?
I'm sure it's him.
I should contact him.
What?
Is there something on my face?
Huh?
Ah!
What's going on?
Huh?
What?
What's going on?
Why is my face on TV?
His name is Ryo Tsukankichi.
He is the benefactor of the client Ozaki's life.
What?
I want to thank him with my eyes.
Please!
Everyone in the country, please find Ryo!
He's a bad actor!
Hello?
I was watching TV just now.
I saw Ryo Tsukankichi here.
What?
Don't report him!
I was watching TV just now.
I saw Ryo Tsukankichi here.
Stop it!
Hello?
I saw him on TV.
I saw Ryo Tsukankichi here.
Yes, he's here.
Hello?
Ah!
Oh, no!
He'll find out I'm here!
Hey, wait for me!
Please let me in!
I want to meet him, Ryo!
Stop it!
It's dangerous!
Kill him!
I'll eat something.
Ryo!
What?
Mr. Tsukankichi Ryo!
We have a guest of honor to help us out!
I'd like to ask for your cooperation.
Huh?
F-fine!
Ugh!
See ya!
Everyone in the country, please!
Please find Ryo!
Mr. Ryo!
Mahjong projester: Yes Yes!
No way!
Damn it, there are too many people in the city.
I have to go somewhere where there are no people.
Sugii, more and more information is gathering.
It seems that we can find it surprisingly quickly.
No, the opponent is Ryo-san. I can not be careless.
Use the newspaper and the Internet fully.
Use anything that can be used.
We will be the winners this year!
We are the winners!
The game is over.
I will be the winner.
I came to a very strange place while avoiding the eyes of the people.
That is...
The police station, huh?
There is no one here?
There is no trace of people for many years.
It hurts!
Hey, sir.
What is it?
Sir, do not eat.
Hey, sir.
Well done!
Finally, a policeman has come to this village!
What?
What's wrong?
After the before deputy chief died at the age of 95 ten years ago.
Since then, there has been no policeman in this village.
He finally came here.
Oh, no! No!
I'm not here because I didn't recognize him.
I mean, he did not recognize me.
Everyone!
A policeman has come!
They're here!
Hey! Wait! Listen to me!
Ugh, shit.
Hey, everyone!
The people of our village are here!
Before they report us...
I have to get out of here somehow...
Hoi!
Hey!
What's going on?
Huh?
It's just the old men and women.
We're going to prepare for the welcome party soon.
Wait for us.
Huh?
Come on, come on.
Let's drink.
There's a lot of food.
Don't hold back and eat.
Here.
Ah, ah.
Huh?
They're so flashy on TV that I can't recognize them.
Come to think of it, there's no TV in this room.
Hey, you guys.
Don't you watch TV much?
No, I don't.
I watch it properly.
I see.
Once a year, we all watch Kohaku.
What?
Just once a year?
That's enough.
By the way,
how many TVs do you have in the village?
There's only one that's as good as the public.
And it's color.
It's amazing.
Oh, I see.
Hmm...
Huh?
Then, until you get a bonus,
it's not a bad idea to hide here.
Okay.
If that's the case, I'll drink it.
It's delicious.
It's our local sake.
Come on, eat your food.
This is delicious.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
You don't have to worry about food while you're in this village,
Mr. Surrounder.
Really?
Yay!
Instead, stay here all the time,
Mr. Surrounder.
Yeah, I'm here.
I'll bring it to you.
Mr. Surrounder,
let's eat breakfast.
Oh, sorry.
Huh?
Oh, this looks delicious again.
I got everything from this village.
Mr. Surrounder,
a terrible thing happened.
Come here.
What?
An accident?
This way, this way.
Mr. Surrounder,
hurry up.
I didn't expect an accident in the middle of the mountain.
The chicken bird suddenly fell.
Why do you call me?
I'm not a guard.
Mr. Surrounder,
you saw me.
Is there someone at home?
No,
everyone in the house is out.
Then, are you a thief?
No way.
Idiot.
There's no one here who does such ill deeds.
There's someone here, after all.
I'm in the kitchen.
Don't move!
You're a cow's nose.
What?
What was that?
It was Hanataro who used to live in my house.
One day he suddenly jumped out of my house and started to fight with his friends in the village.
What a cow!
You were supposed to be fainted!
Damn it!
Did you get away?
Hanako!
He was also fainted.
What happened?
Hanako was on the path of evil!
Sir, please do something.
I'm not a health center.
You guys do something.
I should have closed the door.
I was beaten.
Did they do it?
I even brought a game and a plastic model to kill time.
Keep up with me.
All right.
Tomo!
Good night, Tomo!
I'm feeling so good!
Good night!
I understand your feeling.
Taro?
Yes?
You're so cute.
I'm Durchu.
What's wrong with you?
Don't think you can get away with this by making me angry!
There, there, there!
Idiot! You got caught!
You can't beat a human after all!
Oh, thank you, thank you!
You caught Hanataro so easily!
You're really something, Omawari-san!
Please stay in the village for a day at least.
If you keep standing here,
you'll end up with steak, tonkatsu, and roast chicken!
What's going on?
I thought I'd get a bonus the day after tomorrow,
but I can't get any information about Ryo-san.
He must have run away overseas!
He must have gone to Kukoya Port,
and if he goes to Kukoya Port,
he'll definitely catch the eye of someone!
He's disguised.
Even if he's disguised,
he can't hide his connected eyebrows!
Ryo-san's face has its own features.
Then where is Ryo-san now?
He's hiding somewhere in the countryside,
somewhere where the TV doesn't work.
That's it!
This is the last sighting information.
Should I set up a net in Ichikabachika?
What?
It seems like he got killed by the autumn typhoon.
He won't watch TV anyway, right?
But I can't let him get better by the new year.
The villagers will all watch Kohaku.
Oh well.
How's that?
Did you get it?
Oh! It's perfect!
About what he just said,
Akimoto-sensei is...
It's been a while since I watched TV.
Today you've won a civil service educational bonus.
What?
That means you've forgotten something important...
Oh! You want me to have my bonus today, too?
This is not the time for this!
This is terrible!
Those boys are coming for you!
Damn, you're not coming for a while.
I'll borrow a tractor from the village.
Sir.
Yeah, that's just right.
Where are you going, sir?
Where?
I was thinking about something.
You'll stay here forever, won't you?
You're not going to take a break, are you?
No, I'm just going out for a bit.
I'll be back soon.
You're right.
You're the village's resident, aren't you?
You'll stay here forever, won't you?
If you need me,
I'll go to you.
Actually, I received an order from the main city.
I'm going back to Tokyo.
I've been doing all sorts of things.
You're not going to abandon us, are you?
You're not making a promise.
No, I'm going to be a prisoner of the village until I die.
It's not the end.
Hey, you bastard.
Oh, you're it!
It was nice getting around.
I'm not done yet.
"The
tunnel is too far away."
"Huh?"
"Ugh!"
"What? Are you going to dig a tunnel?"
"Alright! We got out of here successfully!"
"Let's go to the bank!"
"Ugh..."
"Ugh... The roundabout..."
"I'm in trouble..."
"Huh?"
"Ugh!"
"W-What was that?"
"It was the sound of someone knocking on my door..."
"I got it!
"I got it! It's a bonus!"
"It's a bonus!"
"You can get money in any bank, you know."
"It's become convenient."
This voice is...
Hand over the bonus to us!
Why are you guys where I am?
Based on the sighting information, we analyzed your movements.
Damn it!
You're being obsessive, Ryo-san.
Now, hand over the bonus.
Bonus?
No!
The pig got the bonus?
Hey, that's my bonus! Give it back!
Hey, wait!
We're going after him, too!
I won't let you get away!
Why would a pig run away with Ryo-san's bonus?
Ryo-san's bonus is...
What's that supposed to mean by "what's he doing?"
Hold it right here!
This isn't going to end well!
Is it time to wait for someone else?
Does that sound about right?
Hold it right here!
W-What's this voice?
It's Mr. Omawari!
It's over!
It's all over now!
Wait up!!
What the?!
Wait!
Digan!
The trash can...
My house is...
My garden is...
What are you doing…?
The hot springs are...
Ow!
Ouch! What's going on here?!
Oh no! It's a cow!
Nice!
Crap! No way!
The cow ate the bonus!
The bonus was eaten!
The village is in a mess!
I knew it. I'm glad that the neighbor came back.
Yeah.
Damn it! I couldn't win this year either!
You're going to lose!
The bonus...
My bonus...
My bonus is...
To be continued...
So I walked around the black street of Ake-do-gai
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a wall over there, there's definitely a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What? The land of Minokishi-ji's inheritance sold for 100 million yen?
This is a piece of sand from a sandstone, a piece of clay from a shelf, and a wet hand
This 100 million yen, I'll use it big!
Next time, 100 million yen from a sandstone!
Thank you!
There's a wall over there, there's definitely a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!