"When you watch TV,"
"make your room bright and try to look away."
Come to me, the one without money!
I'm not here, so don't worry.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
It'll be alright eventually.
You understand, don't you?
If you understand, then come to me quietly!
"The
Honda!
The weather was great!
The two nights, three days of luxury,
the journey of Izuhakone, the pair, the Gosho experience!
This is also a good life of my daily life, isn't it?
Um...
I'm not the one who got that right.
Besides, I was going to invite Nata-chan, not you,
but you said no.
Say something, Honda!
No, I didn't!
The train is coming.
Please wait inside the white line.
Oh, the timing of the train...
What the hell is this?
Huh?
It's a train!
Yeah, it's a luxurious train...
Wait!
Hm?
Wha-what the hell?
Don't get on this train!
Hey! What are you doing?
This is a special train!
Ordinary people can't take it!
A special train?
Got it!
Huh?
What is it?
A smooth cosmos!
A train journey to the sun,
Shipopo Shipopo Shiposhiposhipopo
Come on everybody
Shipopo Shipopo Shiposhipopo
What's up with that old man?
What's so rude?
Listen up
The president of the Gosho-Gawara Group
Gosho-Gawara Kingorohno-suke
Saemon-Taro-sama will be the president
Masaaki
I'm sorry
President
I was mistaken
I was trying to get on the president's train
I did it
Hello
I'm the president of Gosho-Gawara
That's great
As expected of the president
Wonderful
I'm impressed
That's right
What are they?
I think it's Gosho-Gawara Group
It's a top-class company in Japan
that makes space rockets from Trump
The president there is a very good man
I see
President and his subordinates
The rate of employment is high
They all work hard
I forgot something important
What is it?
It's a station lunch box
The lunch box
It's over there
Masaki
Yes, what is it, president?
I've got one
If you're full, it's time for dinner
Ben Ben Ben
I love lunch boxes
It's a station lunch box
Give the president a station lunch box
Yes, sir
President, it was a fantastic lunch box
Which should I choose?
This is mine
I'll pay for it
Give me everything
What?
I sold it
At least it was just a drink
What?
I'll pay for it
What the hell
What?
I found one
Bells ringing, bell-marking.
Let's have a great lunch!
Bravo!
Hey! Don't take everything!
Just one! Come on!
Wow, what a great view!
Senpai, look at this!
It's a great view!
I'm so hungry that I didn't have lunch.
No way!
I still haven't had lunch!
It's still lunch time.
Oh!
There is a tennis court!
There are so many girls.
I wonder if they are girls.
There is a cute girl!
Yes!
Hey, you're doing it!
You're young, aren't you?
Senpai, you're hungry, aren't you?
Even if I don't have lunch, I'll come out when it's time.
Now I'm hungry.
Let's fight one more fight!
Don't you dare!
Come on, Senpai!
Go ahead, take it easy!
I just want to have lunch!
Don't fight!
If you don't want to go in,
You're an idiot!
I'm saying, don't fight!
Take it easy!
Ah, they are the same as before.
They were also here.
Boss, I'm ready.
How is it?
It suits you very well, boss.
What a cool guy.
He doesn't look like a tennis player.
Oh, I have an idea.
What is tennis?
Is it a ball in the hand or a ball in the hand?
Aim for the ace, ace, ace, ace.
That's a great idea, boss.
Hey, Horashi.
Let's go to the bathroom after we get home.
That's a good idea.
Oh, I have another idea.
What is tennis?
It's a game of girls.
Don't do it anyway.
Then teach me how to play tennis.
That's great.
No, that's not what the boss wants to say.
Is there a female coach here?
No, I'm the only coach here.
Oh, no.
Find a female coach immediately.
Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
A female coach.
What are they doing?
They're making a fuss.
It has nothing to do with us.
Hey, you guys.
What?
Is there a female tennis coach or someone you know?
What is it?
If you know, bring me a big ball.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
Please.
I'll pay you any amount of money.
What?
If it's a female coach, any one is fine.
Is there one here?
Leave it to me.
Oh, okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm a coach, Ryo Tsukanco.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
What do you think, do I look good?
What's the point of being a female coach?
You're just a female player.
In short, I just need to look like a female coach.
That's enough.
Senpai, it's too much.
Is that so?
Masaki.
Yes, sir.
I made a wig.
It's wonderful.
When a female coach arrives, you must tool myself with "What can I do?"
So let's try it together.
Huh?
Take a look over here, it'll do.
Was it your taste, that woman?
I didn't know I had such a taste.
Nice to meet you.
What the...
What's the matter?
I'm back. Please return it.
I'm going to hit the president's racket.
What? Then I won't be able to play tennis.
What if you hurt the president?
I don't want to play tennis.
If you want money, do as I say.
I got it.
Here we go.
Take this.
Did I hit it?
Too bad. It's out.
It's a great shot, president.
Professional.
No one can take it.
I can't lose to anyone in tennis.
What? That was out.
President's shot was out.
You don't want money?
I got it.
I got one.
I saw it one day.
On the TV, the ball comes and goes.
It comes and goes.
You know what?
So, I don't want to play tennis.
Let's play tennis and start over.
Come on.
You can't beat me.
Good game.
Go to the Natsuma четting.
A man who is at the top of the game.
Are you okay, Senpai?
I've come up with a good idea.
I can rally if I use this.
I see. So that's how it works.
Let's go!
Captain, now!
Captain!
This is really tennis.
I've finished one round.
Tennis is really fun.
I want to play it again with everyone.
That's it!
Thank you!
I'll never do it again.
I can't stand it.
This stupid tennis.
You eat a lot.
I moved my body yesterday.
It must have been hard.
But you got a lot of money, right?
Yes.
Let's play as much as we can today.
Let's play as much as we can.
They're so early in the morning.
Hey!
How was yesterday?
Are you going somewhere?
The president suddenly said he wanted to play golf.
I'll come with you.
It's about him.
Don't make a crazy request like yesterday.
That's a good idea.
Maybe we can play the game later.
If I'm an important person,
this is my chance.
He's going to make it.
I'll when I'm gone.
When I'm done, I'll start playing.
If you come, please.
But that's...
A big chance.
You made another loan?
Of course.
One is up.
One shot.
I'll show you, hototogi.
Hohohohekyo. That's a good one.
Ha!
The president wants to get a whole-in-one.
What?
Follow him.
Uh...
Here you go.
Koshokawara.
What did you do?!
Zip.
It's Ikeboccha.
Leave it to me.
I can't do it. I'm going to go over.
President, thank you. I'm a new member.
I want to ride a horse and run as far as possible.
Run, run, run.
It's a horse. President is very generous.
I'm very generous.
What? I just started golf.
Why do we become horses?
Because the real horse doesn't listen to the president.
Aki, Kashi, Yamawa, Akai, Momiji, Gari, gather everyone.
Momiji, Gari.
Isn't that something different?
I hope the president agrees.
Speaking of Izu, Izu's踊り子 is the best.
Izu's踊り子.
Next year, this month, tonight, this moon.
No, this is a temporary horse.
I can't notice it if I stay quiet.
The sea is wide and big. I envy Hana-chan who is fishing all the time.
I'm going to fish this time.
Speaking of fishing, I want to fish.
I want to fish if I'm from Kyushu.
The president is very generous.
But how can I fish?
Leave it to me.
Welcome.
Dad.
What should I do?
Everything.
What?
With this.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm tired.
I will go.
The rest is up to you.
I'll stay beside you.
Really?
I did it!
The president is right.
Congratulations!
Ba-tai!
I'm a genius fishing master!
You're great!
Next is octopus. Chuchu Chuchu Octopus!
Next is octopus! It's octopus!
What? Octopus?
I bought one from the store, so I have something.
What? What? What?
Well...
Here it is, boss!
Bonzai! Bonzai!
Let's catch some suzuki.
Next is suzuki! Suzuki!
Suzuki? Oh, no. I don't have suzuki.
I don't have suzuki.
Ouch.
Pardon me.
What's wrong?
Are you familiar with fish?
No, I'm not.
I see.
I guess that's enough.
Well done, boss!
Bonzai! Bonzai!
The wind is getting colder.
Should we go home?
Well, let's get the car ready.
I want to catch a big fish and go home at the end.
What? What?
I want to catch a shachi.
Shachi, shachi, shachi, shachi, shachi.
Shachi?
It's a shachi.
You didn't prepare a shachi, did you?
Of course.
You think we can catch a shachi, you morons?
That's why I told you that I don't know much about fish.
If we don't catch any, what will happen?
We're all going to be in the restaurant.
We'll be lost in the last days of our jobs.
Then, how about my car?
We can't pay for it!
What?
I have three daughters in China, boss.
Who the hell is this?
Hello?
It's me, boss.
What do you want, Honda?
I'm in a aquarium called Oizu Marine Park.
I'm doing a great show.
What do you think?
I don't care.
It's a shachi.
I'm doing a great shachi show.
Shachi?
Where is it? Tell me.
What?
What did you say?
You want me to lend you a shachi?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm not going to tell you.
This is the rental fee.
Please take it.
But how can I take it?
You're here for that.
This is it.
What?
It's a jet.
Get in, Honda.
Okay.
Ryoji's husband, get in.
I did it.
Give me the water.
Okay.
I'm hungry.
I can't drink water yet.
I don't have a shachi yet.
What should I do now?
I don't know.
I don't know what to do without Masaki.
Boss!
Masaki.
Boss.
Look at that.
Honda, go straight ahead.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's a shachi.
The car is here!
Oh!
What?
What's going on?
I don't know!
Maybe it's because it's Sho's car
It's fun!
The car is big!
Is it my car?
The car is coming this way!
Your majesty!
It's dangerous! Let's escape!
Wait, the car is going to get us soon
We're going to be so happy
Your majesty!
Is that the car, your majesty?
Boss!
It's over.
Everything is over now.
Boss...
Are you okay?
Do you want to fight?
Masaki.
Yes?
The pick has come up.
Good bye, good bye, good bye.
Good bye, everyone.
I knew it.
I'm fired.
Wait a minute, Goshogawara.
They've been with you until now.
You're going to fire them with just one failure?
Is that what the president of a big company does?
Hey, it's the money I got from tennis yesterday.
I don't need this kind of thing, so take their heads off.
I have no intention of taking their heads off.
I'm just going to go back to the hotel because it's cold.
Boss!
I'll have to pay you back.
Happy, happy, happy, happy, happy.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Good job.
Mr. Kare, let's have a party tonight.
Good bye, good bye, good bye.
Thank you very much.
Why did this happen?
Then pay me back, you idiot!
Boss, why did you do this?
Why did you do this to me?
Help me!
Call me!
Hello?
Are you in the hotel?
I'm going home now.
I'm going home and I'm getting out of here.
Come home, you idiot.
You're always Italian.
I felt a strange feeling
That's why I tried to walk on the black tile of the arcade
Everyone was a child at least once, but everyone forgets
The politician with a great face and the blue aunt above her eyes
Turn around and see that corner
Everyone can see everyone
There is a turtle over there, there must be a turtle
Come on, everyone
Let's go
To our town
Thank you!
The prize money of the competition of WIN is 10 million yen
You're a new violinist, but you can't go to Narita without your wallet?
Leave it to me!
I don't want to be a fool who can't win such a big prize!
Next time, "Troubled turtle and Narita"
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Come on, everyone
Let's go to our town