When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
"The End of the Rain"
It's like someone is calling you
Looking back, I walked
"Mom, please help me"
At that time I felt
A strange feeling
So, I took the cable car
And walked only in black
"The End of the Rain"
Everyone was a child once
But they all forget
Politicians with a proud face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
You can meet everyone
"The End of the Rain"
There is a turtle
Here is a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
"The End of the Rain"
I'm back
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Oh, hey!
I got this for the lottery!
Huh?
Pierre Nishikaguchi?
Sounds like a mansion.
What a snob!
You don't know him, senpai?
He's a hot topic right now.
Who is he?
In the old days, he would go through the Berlin Wall,
the top of the Vanli,
and walk over the wings of a flying jet plane.
He would live inside a box that was buried for a month.
He's a magician who sells magic.
Isn't he amazing?
He's like Superman.
What are you talking about?
He's a magician, so he has tricks.
But he's quite worth seeing.
Let's go see him next time.
He looks interesting, Ryo-chan.
I'll watch him for the sake of the story.
The next morning
Ladies and gentlemen!
The father and mother!
The Ultra Super Miracle Magician,
Pierre Nishikaguchi!
Welcome!
I am the true magician,
Pierre Nishikaguchi!
Amazing!
What's going on?
He's coming out of that tiny box!
Isn't that surprising?
Huh?
I think on this stage,
there should be a hole for the stage.
A hole?
So, open that box,
and go through that hole.
Welcome!
I see.
He's using tricks to fool the children.
The magician of the century is going crazy.
I can't wait to see what happens next.
The first part is hypnotism.
Anyone here want to help with the hypnotism?
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
I'll help!
Yes!
Then, that person!
Hey!
Hey! I was faster, you bastard!
Senior?
Yes.
You're getting sleepy.
Then, count three.
You're a rabbit.
One, two, three!
You're Fujii Takashi.
No.
No!
You're completely stuck!
He's a cherry!
What?
He's got a big voice!
You can tell if he's a rabbit or not
based on the cherry placed on his back seat.
It's all up to you. It's a classic technique.
Then, this person, please come on stage.
Interesting, isn't it? Let's have him play.
You're getting sleepy.
It's nothing at all.
Ryo-chan is very challenging.
I hope it's not a fight.
See, you're getting sleepy.
Muu-kun.
You're getting more sleepy.
You're getting...
I'll give you money.
He's getting sleep-deprived.
He's really something.
You're Suzu-me-chan.
Let's fly around the sky.
How much is it?
1,000 yen.
I suddenly woke up.
What's that?
Why did you wake up?
I knew it.
Just a moment.
He's getting sleepy.
I'll try again.
You're getting sleepy.
You're getting...
3,000 yen.
10,000 yen.
You're getting sleepy.
5,000 yen.
10,000 yen.
You're getting...
6,500 yen.
10,000 yen.
You're getting sleepy.
You're getting...
I got it.
You're a dog.
You're getting a dog.
You're getting sleepy.
Next is the 55th grader.
I'm going to fly.
I can't believe Ryo-chan will become so bad.
He won't.
I didn't believe it at all.
He's really into it.
He's a real man.
The second part will start.
It was pretty amazing, wasn't it?
I have some business, so you guys go home first.
What are you talking about?
I'm here to take the 10,000 yen I promised you!
You're a really simple man.
That conversation was the spell of hypnotism.
You've been perfectly hypnotized.
You're a jerk!
30,000 yen, 50,000 yen, 10,000 yen.
You have such a spell?
You're not even in a hurry to give me money!
You bastard!
I get it! I get it!
You're so stupid.
What's this?
It's just a hair clip!
I gave you the real one.
Don't use magic, you bastard!
I told you not to use magic!
Stop using magic!
You medicationista!
If you do that, I'll tell everybody that you have hypnosis.
What?
What's that?
What's that!
If you'll not close your eyes, I'll get rid of your hair clip.
This key is because you kindly gave it to me.
I just wanted to let you know.
What are you talking about?
I don't give a fuck.
Oh, nice to meet you, grandma.
What are you doing?
What?
Don't move!
It hurts!
You bastard!
Do you have a key?
What a stupid power.
Let's call it "Kairiki".
Hey, I've always wanted a partner.
Would you join my team?
Don't mess with me!
I'm serious.
Of course I'll pay you monthly.
What are you talking about?
You're using people's money and you're saying it's the last day of the year?
It's the end of the year.
You're going to have to pay me back anyway.
No, no.
I'm telling you it's real this time.
Right?
How is it?
Hey, Ryo-chan, this is for you.
Look at this guy.
He's definitely a senior.
Right?
He was told to rest in the cold, but he was still sick.
Now, it's time for the climax of the magic show.
Pierre Nishikawaguchi and the man from Brazil, Mogambo,
will pass through the wall that used to be used in prisons.
We'll send you the miracle of the great magic on live.
Let's interview them.
Let's do it.
Pierre-san, we're going to start the show, but can you say something?
Hmm...
You seem to be very focused.
Well then, Mogambo-san, can you say something?
Mogambo!
Well then, let's watch the moment of the miracle.
Will it succeed?
Hmm...
Watch out, watch out.
Ah!
And after this...
What's that?
Here, I'll help you.
He's fast.
I used to be in the Ranger Corps.
What a great past.
Well then, let's open the curtains.
Don't you think it's better to dig a hole in the front?
Isn't it a fraud?
It's a magic.
By the way, you seem to be walking on the wings of a flying plane.
What kind of trick is it?
That's my miracle power.
Don't look at me now.
That's wearing powerful shoes with a heel.
Is that all?
I was always alive.
Then, keep it in the box for a month on the ground.
That's...
Don't say that. I'll guess.
Get out of the tunnel I dug in advance and go somewhere.
When the box is dug up, I'll go back to the box.
That's right.
While I was hiding, I was hiding in the forest so that no one could see me.
I was lonely and lonely.
It's pretty plain and boring when you imagine it.
To create a miracle that seems unreasonable from the first sight.
Day and night, endless research and effort.
Magician is a person who works hard and logically.
It's over if the magician talks about hard work.
More than that, time is fine.
Is it okay?
Oh no!
It's finally the moment of the miracle.
3, 2, 1, open!
Yes!
It's really wonderful!
Excuse me.
The viewer said that he wanted to see a place where you can pass without using a curtain.
That's right.
Please show that scene in front of you.
What?
I want to do it without a curtain.
I'm digging a hole in the ground.
Nice!
Greg will see that.
It's closed.
Well, I've already broken.
Ah, I understood!
Of course, it's possible to do without a curtain, but the planning time is already past, so
If you don't mind some time ekamacho, the producer now said OK.
If you don't mind, save it.
How much does it cost?
Oh, about the room?
Because of this wall.
- A wall... - Alright, ¥3000.
- ¥20,000. - ¥50,000.
- ¥20,000. - Too high.
- What is it? - Eh?
Oh, no. The girl's son-in-law is going to do the wall-pulling for me.
Eh? Really?
This is amazing!
- He's going to do the human wall-pulling without a curtain! - ¥80,000. ¥20,000.
- ¥100,000. - ¥20,000.
The magic of the past, present, and future!
The human wall-pulling!
I'd like to send you the curtain-less version again!
The wall-pulling!
I'm going to change into the teacher, Pierre Nishikaguchi,
and do the wall-pulling magic!
The wall-pulling!
Will Ryotsu be able to do the wall-pulling?
The result is in 90 seconds!
"The power of the human wall-pulling!"
Elohim! Essaim! Elohim! Essaym!
Tonhirakoppe! Tobidabojo! Tamore! Tamore!
Kabenukete! Tamoure!
The reality is...
Kabenukenukedabuchya! Erashou! Kabenukenmurela!
Kabenukenmurela! Erashou! Kabenukenmurela!
We are going to freeze and then do the wall-pulling.
Ouch!
Just like this, I got out of the hole!
As you can see, I got out of the wall.
If you get used to it, you can get out of the sand even more.
Amazing! It's amazing! It's like a miracle!
I got out! I got out of the wall!
Alright! I can do it!
You're so strong!
I feel like I really got out of the wall.
But, is this magic?
You're so small!
You're more like a disciple than a teacher.
You're so big!
It's natural that I'm bigger than you.
But...
I'll tell you just in case.
I didn't intend to become your disciple.
I just wanted to tell you as a good disciple.
David Copperfield has erased the Goddess of Freedom again.
What?
The electric field's kappa is floating?
You're a magician, but you don't even know David Copperfield?
You can fly in the sky, and you can erase the train.
You're the world's best, the best, the best magician of the million-year-old!
What?
Yes!
It's flying even more than usual!
Damn it!
You're so cheeky, and yet so cheeky!
The other day, you two successfully got out of the wall.
What kind of magic are you going to try next?
Well, that is...
If our rival, the electric kappa, has erased the Goddess of Freedom,
I will...
I will make a peace sign on Nara's temple!
Well then,
Miracle Magic: Pierre Power!
Miracle! Kuru Kuru Kuru!
Peace! Peace!
Peace, kuru kuru, kuru kuru, kuru, kuru kuru...
Easy peasy!
You're fooling around off your own.
Dear Riel,
What magic are you going to try next?
If our rival, the electric kappa,
can fly in the Grand Canyon,
I will become the wind of Saku Tottori!
Whaaaaaaaaat?
This is not magic!
This is the miracle magic of Pierre Nishikawaguchi, who is as strong as a steel shovel!
If you want to do it, do it yourself!
Yes! Turn around, turn around!
I'm gonna get you!
Mogi!
Alright! Now we're gonna have to escape!
Escape from the Ikezu!
Escape from the train!
Escape from the hell of the Shakuen!
Is there such an escape?
I don't care how much you pay me,
I'm gonna pay you back with my life!
I'm quitting!
No way!
You just got popular!
You'll be on the CX for two hours this time,
so we'll work together to escape from here!
I'm the only one who's strong!
I'm gonna go back to the police station!
I'm gonna pay you back with cash!
Don't say that!
I don't want to.
Why not?
Alright! Then I'll ask you one last time!
I'll ask you one last time!
Alright?
I'll pay you back ten times as much as you've done!
That'll be 100 times!
Alright!
It's starting, Reiko!
It looks like Ryo-chan is starting to lose weight too.
Right.
Hello, everyone!
Japan's number one magician,
Pierre Nishikawaguchi and his disciple Mogambo
are here to send you a miracle escape!
Unfortunately, Mogambo has to retire
and will return to Brazil!
Pierre, this time,
it seems like a big escape!
Well,
at the start,
the box with Mogambo's hands and feet
will explode!
At the start?
Yes.
And Mogambo, who escaped the crisis,
will escape through this tunnel.
However,
there are many traps waiting for him
in this tunnel.
And Mogambo, who has successfully reached the goal,
will be able to get a prize of one million yen!
I see!
But!
It's not just this!
If you don't press this button at the end of the escape,
the explosion will happen at the end of the escape!
A big explosion?
This seems to be a big deal!
I see!
Wait for me, 1 million yen!
From just a moment,
the start point has been completelyonen Apollo!
Will he be safe!?
1 million yen!
"Waterfall"
-Oh! I just saw Mogambo-san!
Apparently, he's fine.
-What is it?!
-Sli... Sli...
-Aaaah!
-Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya!
-Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
-As expected of Mogambo-san! You're good!
-We're still in the beginning.
-Nya? Nya?
-Aaaah!
-Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya! Nya!
-Aaaaaah!
-Eh?
-Aaaah!
-Mogambo-san is doing well!
-No, but we're only one minute behind the time limit.
-Aaaah!
-Aaaaaah!
-I can't see! I can't see! I can't see!
-Shh! The baby is sleeping!
-One million yen! One million yen!
-Move!
-Aaaah!
-Aaaaah!
-Ugh! Uuuugh!
-What the hell is this?!
-Uuuugh!
-Aaaah!
-Here we go!
-Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
-Ouch! Ouch!
-I was hoping this would happen, so I was trying to avoid the low-intensity
-Nice!
-Aaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaaaaah!
-Aaaaaaaah!
This is it!
If you don't have it, make it!
Help me!
I'm going to make you pay for what you did to me!
The first time in history!
The miracle escape from Tomahawk!
It's about to start!
Help me!
No!
I can't escape!
What's wrong?
Komachi suddenly became a star!
Looking right or left, Komachi Komachi is booming!
Wait!
This guy might make a lot of money!
Next!
Komachi Big Break!
Don't miss it!