Tears in the Modern World
When you watch the television,
clear up and separated the room!
People who have no money!
Come to me!
I don't have anyone, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
You'll be able to do something somehow
Those who have no job, come to me
I don't have one, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
Ah, it's burning
You'll be able to do something somehow
You know it, right?
You know it, you know it
If you know it, then just shut up and follow me
Huh?
You know me too well
Ah, what a nice day.
Summer's just around the corner, isn't it?
You're right.
Ah...
Huh? Ryou's neck's gone.
Ah-ha!
-Yay -Yay
It's dangerous. It's a two-seater.
You guys!
Look at that!
Ryo-chan, you're fast.
You two, the two-seater is dangerous.
You can't do that.
Yes, yes, I understand.
It seems like he's not reflecting on himself.
It's like he's just talking.
Well, it's not the age to be careful.
Ryo-chan, you're good at understanding things.
I remembered.
I was looking at them.
What?
What are you looking at?
I found it. This is it.
What is it?
These scars.
It was when I was in junior high school, like them.
Azakusa!
I want to see you, Azakusa!
Krillin, you were here in high school, too?
Yes, we went to Nagoya with my friends.
Yeah, I was.
Let me think about it.
You came for Misa-kun's birthday, didn't you?
I thought he was going to fall.
There.
We have to take a look at this.
But it's Osaka, so it's gonna take a lot of trains.
If you could make it in Sensoji's Keidai or Hanayashiki, it would be nice.
You're so picky.
Hanayashiki is too small to make a pavilion.
It's not a pavilion, it's a pavilion, dad.
Shut up!
Whoa! It's on!
Hey, Tonpei, Chikichi, you guys get on too.
Are you alright, Kankichi?
It's an old man's motorcycle, so it'll be hard to break it.
Hurry up and get on.
Okay.
Can you drive?
Leave it to me.
You're gonna get hurt by a bicycle.
Let's go!
Go!
Easy, easy.
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't.
Can't you stop?
You can't drive like that!
Kankichi, this is bad! Stop!
That's...
What's wrong?
I don't know how to stop.
Stop! Stop!
Kankichi!
There's Sumida River ahead!
You guys, get off the road!
No, no, no!
That's the scar from that time.
Did you jump in from here?
So what happened?
The aquesta was aligned with me.
I got into the net of the fishing spot.
If I had not been there, I would have been on the Natti Line.
We wereagnered.
But the man who was younger than us was a nice guy.
Eat.
Due to his despondency, he took us by motorcycle.
And drove around the area with us.
Hey, get me next time!
I'll be the next one!
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
Hey, Dad.
Let's buy a color TV.
Color?
You idiot!
There's no color TV in Tsukudaniya.
No way!
I bought one for Tsuyoshi and Satoru.
It's already half the class.
The only thing that's left is color.
Huh?
The word "color" that appeared on the edge of the screen at the time
looked very uncomfortable to me.
Hey, Dad.
Shut up!
I don't need color.
If I watch that, I'll have a bad headache.
Tch.
But,
I really wanted to watch this much of the program in color.
What is it?
Well,
we were in puberty at that time.
It's a legendary program.
We really wanted to watch that in color.
We talked to the electrician's son
and went into the store at night.
Hey, Shinji,
I hope you're okay.
It's okay if you stay quiet.
We go to bed early.
Yes.
Wow!
Shin Pirobont!
It's different from color, isn't it?
Check the channel.
Yeah.
This...
Shabu-Shabu-Dabu!
Hey, wake up.
What's this? It's so late.
There's a strange sound coming from the store.
Could it be...
What? A thief?
I don't know.
Alright!
Someone's here.
It's you.
You bastard!
Get out of here!
What's wrong?
Sir, it's a thief!
What?
Wait!
He's alive!
He can't escape anymore!
You're Shinji!
I guess this is the fifth time I've been taken to the workshop.
You've been taken to the workshop five times a year?
How many times have you been taken to the workshop?
15 times?
16 times?
I guess you're right.
It's fine.
I don't mind that.
What else did you do that made you feel bad?
Well,
I guess the thing that left an impression...
Please pay attention to Janet Lin, the figure skater's beautiful performance.
You're glad you bought the color TV, Dad?
Well, well.
Geez.
The Olympics, the Olympics.
They're on TV from morning to night.
Those two are...
It's growing, it's growing!
We did it!
The Japan HINOMARI Air Force has won the Olympics!
As expected, the Sapporo Olympics made us so excited.
Go!
Chikichi!
Chikichi, this way!
Wait!
I'll catch you!
Let's go!
Go!
Shoot!
Well, this is just a daily routine.
The only time I couldn't do it was when I imitated the HINOMARI Air Force.
Now, it's done.
It's a wonderful jump.
So cool!
I'm satisfied.
Let's slide now.
Yeah!
Who can fly the farthest?
Let's compete.
The one who wins is the lunch box for three people.
All right.
No.1.
Tompei, here we go!
Go!
I failed to land.
I failed to land!
You suck.
It's because you did this.
Now, Kasaya, Kankichi,
I'll aim for the firing line.
Let's have a look!
This is amazing!
How's that?
Sorry.
Oh, that's my faze!
You brought more than enough letztment.
You're very fast.
You can go fast, too.
A few dozen pigs were in a riot in the streets of Asakusa.
This was to be seen.
Of course, it's the police's business,
so the rich is waste for their father.
Don't put people in trouble.
I'll be back soon!
It's cold... I'm starving...
Hey, you're being chased again?
Hey!
Thank you, sir!
It's so delicious!
You're so naughty!
The End
Three people on a motorcycle fell into a river...
They snuck into a store and got mistaken as thieves...
The End
They imitated a jumper and made a piggy run...
I see... Ryo's middle school days were really rough.
By the way, we also did a chicken race on our bikes.
Huh?
The other guys were the bad boys from the middle school next door.
If you want, I can do more.
I know!
I get what you mean!
Make sure you get everything you want, okay?
Please do, Kankichi.
The technological revolution is so important.
I know. Just leave it to me!
Then, let's start.
It's easier to slam the brakes than to run.
Ready?
Start!
Go!
Ah!
Kankichi!
Kankichi! Are you okay?
Hehehe!
I was in trouble at that time.
That's not the problem.
You have to laugh.
Yes, yes. There are others.
Are there more?
I'm afraid to ask.
Many of our school students are quiet.
They were targeted by the bad students everywhere.
One day, I found my students who were involved in them.
You're amazing!
You bastard!
Now, let's get out of here!
Yeah.
You bastard!
Hey, you again!
Ah!
Hehehehehehe
Ouch!
Damn, you made me get hurt!
You're overdoing it because you're so energetic!
But, but...
Not but!
It hurts! It's not a woodpecker! Stop it!
I can't tell by your mouth!
Ouch!
I'll entrust you to Gokurakuji and be a boy!
Ouch, ouch, ouch! I hate boys!
Haha, well, well. There were only three of us.
That's right! It's three against one!
E-V-E-R-U-L-E-Y!
Hmm...
Hey, Kankichi-kun, do you know that short-term is a loss-time?
Short-term is a loss-time?
When you get short-term, you make a huge loss.
Even if you fight, it's not for the best, right?
But, I can't run away!
However, I think that's too much to say.
It's too late.
I had a weight of a thousand times.
What do you mean?
He was aiming to become a champion.
A champion?
Huh? He was boxing?
Well, yeah.
He made his debut in high school, and won all five championships.
He was being expected to be the champion.
But, he was still a rookie in the East Japan final.
Oh...
He was forced to fight 5 guys during the night running.
Ouch!
Ouch...
At that time, if I had a little more distinction, I would have escaped.
I realized that was the right decision after becoming a police officer.
I understand. I will never fight again. I promise.
I see. You said it well, Kankichi-kun.
Yeah.
- Kankichi was bununjiru.
You were at fault.
- Kankichi Kunt Gaupen The
Please don't say gently angry.
- Kankichi Kunt Gaupen Don't you enjoy volume
OK, I understand.
Let's go together.
- Kankichi Kunt Gaupen
Kichi-kun...
I promised I wouldn't fight!
You're so stubborn!
Get out of my way! I'll forgive you if you do!
Get... out of my way?
What are you guys doing?
Crap! Run!
Damn it! This guy's so lucky!
Kichi-kun!
Is something wrong?
It's nothing!
You've put up with it, haven't you?
Well, at least at that time. But...
What did you say?
Tonpei Chinkichi...
Yeah, I said if you want to help, come to the river!
Damn it! They're not just me, but two of them!
I'm counting on you, Shinji!
If Kankichi doesn't come, I'll throw him into the river!
Kankichi will come for sure!
That's right!
What do you think of that waist?
Kankichi is not a waist!
Hey, I... I'm sorry for breaking the promise...
Kankichi!
You're good!
As expected of Kankichi!
He's not a waist!
I'm not a waist!
Damn it! Where are you, Kankichi?
Show us your true form, you slug!
Who's a slug?!
Kankichi!
You bastard!
You slug!
Where are you going, you moron!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
He's been going around in a terrible way.
Tatsumaki, huh.
I see.
You're Tatsumaki, right?
Y-Yeah.
Right?
Y-Yeah!
Then, I'll have to go back and write a report.
Men have times when they have to do something.
But, you have to do it in moderation.
Yes!
That's how I learned to be patient.
Patience?
From your seniors?
No, that's not the most appropriate word for Ryo-chan!
What are you talking about?
Even if the chief gets angry, he's still patient, isn't he?
Hey, they're here again!
Hey, you two, get in the car!
I told you, you can't do this!
You're always like that!
You're always so noisy!
What are you doing?
What's with the patience?
You're getting angry right away.
Wait!
Wait, you!
You!
Why are you doing this?
I told you, you two are in danger!
You!
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Excuse me, may I?
Welcome!
A little roll, a little roll, a little roll, a little roll,
I wonder what to do with any roll?
That's right, do you have a California roll?
California roll is not available.
This is not America.
Excuse me, sir.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Welcome!
Please, I'll have a kushigaki, a kakiage, a katsuage,
What would you like?
What do you recommend?
Take care of the katsuage,
Huh? Is that a gag?
Yes, you too.
I don't understand.
Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh? Really?
Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome!
Please!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome! You're welcome to this room!
Ryoutsu, Tamekichi, are you my late grandfather?!
Why are you here?
Are you drunk and coming to earth from heaven?
Do people really come back if they're drunk?!
Next episode: Good afternoon, Master Gosen!
Thanks for watching!
Kameari
Ah, I'm sure it's Kameari
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!