This video is a derivative work of Touhou Project.
Ah~ The summer has come again this year!
It has come, it has come!
It has come!
I'm going to the south wind
Otsu!
I'll skiski with shaved ice!
I haven't done this in a long time!
I'm sorry.
Shaved ice, give me some strawberries.
Here you are.
Huh? Since when did you start making shaved ice?
Since this year.
Shaved ice is easier, and you don't get angry.
That's true.
I was thinking of throwing that away.
Throwing it away? That's a waste.
You can still use this shaved ice.
Well,
it's the flow of time.
Here you are.
If you don't need it, I'll take it.
Oh, no problem.
Grandma!
Hm?
Give me some shaved ice.
I want some melon.
Here you are.
You guys,
if you don't study and wait for your vacation,
your mom will scold you.
Ryo, are you sure you're going to sell oil in a place like this?
I'm not selling oil!
I'm eating shaved ice.
Does that mean this is my last night at home?
you can hardly talk inside like this.
He ate.
If you eat something cold,
you're gonna get diarrhea and sleep.
If you have diarrhea, you're gonna get stage 2.
See you later.
Yeah!
Go on, take that!
I'm just a worker who's wandering in a hell of a world.
Ryo-chan, what's that?
It's an ancient ice-shrink. I got it from a candy store.
An ice-shrink?
You can get anything you want, right, senpai?
What are you going to do, Ruki?
You know I'm going to make shaved ice, right?
In the winter, I'll make a kotatsu with a mikan.
In the summer, I'll make shaved ice with a salt bar.
I can even make katsubushi with this.
I can't help it.
Senpai, what about ice-shrink?
Ryo-chan bought it from the supermarket last week.
There's this pen-kichi.
No!
You can't use a toy like that!
In this era of gourmet, shaved ice has to be real.
I wonder if shaved ice is also real.
It depends on the time and place.
I've been showing off this shaved ice machine until last week.
I'll make it right away.
But Ryo-chan, if you say it's real, you can't use ice from the fridge, right?
Huh?
If you say it's real, you have to use ice from Mont Blanc or the South Pole.
The South Pole ice?
There's a branch of Nakagawa Continent in Greenland, so I can use the North Pole ice.
That's it!
The gourmet shaved ice is from the North Pole, not the South Pole!
I bought that ice. Please share it with me right away.
Oh, okay.
I'll be right there.
I hate waiting.
Okay.
Then, I'll take a break.
He's getting serious.
What?
It's noisy and I can't sleep.
Senpai, the ice from the North Pole has arrived!
Huh?
Hurry up! The ice has arrived!
It's here!
Where is the ice?
One whole dumpling?
Yay!
This is all mine!
Here, take the ice. It's 10,000 yen.
This way! A little further!
Ow, ow!
Ah!
You're too noisy!
Ow, ow, ow!
What happened?
Come on, you're too noisy!
Ow, ow, ow!
This is bad.
No, no, no.
Ow, ow, ow!
Hey!
Ow!
What's that?
An altar?!
An abomination?!
Ah, it's Ryo.
A museum!
It's shining different after all!
Come on, Ryo.
Can you give me some too?
No!
Why not?
Just a little!
I'm just kidding.
I bought this precious ice from Mizeni.
I'm not going to do it for free.
You're so stubborn.
No matter what you say, I already paid 10,000 yen.
The ice is all mine.
The ice from the fridge suits you guys.
What a precious sound.
Compared to that, oh, what a wonderful sound.
It's like the sound of a hornet's cry.
This is the traditional Japanese ice.
I'll pour the syrup on it.
It's done.
The ice is as delicate and beautiful as the blue snow.
First, I'll take a bite.
It's delicious!
I knew the real thing was different.
And in return,
the smell of the water and the fridge is mixed together.
This smell.
It's really pleasant.
This is delicious.
It's full of the old-fashioned romance.
It's a bold and beautiful ice.
Otherwise, it wouldn't have been born.
This is the world's most expensive ice.
No, rather, this is the only one that should be called ice.
The ice that I made for free in the fridge is no longer ice.
Until yesterday,
I ate the best ice that I made with this pen-kichi-kun.
That's right.
This time, let's make it luxurious with milk.
What?
Take this!
Don't steal the ice on your own.
I'll arrest you.
Isn't it a little good?
Thanks to this ice,
I can organize the traffic.
Look, the car is moving.
Hurry up and get to work.
Oh, Kei-chan.
I think this is it.
It's SO good!
It melts in your mouth.
Episode 4
It's so good.
utilities
LUXURY
It's the perfect texture,
but be careful.
Hmm, it's beautiful.
Oh, that's real delicious!
The shining of the rose and the softness of the tangerine.
The sound of the ice popping is the elegance of Venus's whisper that woke her from her sleep of millions of years.
Fantastic! This painting is a rose-colored shadow.
I'm going to eat it all up!
The city is so cold that I'm getting dizzy.
But it's a bit hot when it's the 70th drink.
You're getting tired, aren't you?
That's not true.
Is this the ice?
It's cold.
It's dangerous, so get away from here.
It feels good.
Damn it!
Hey! That's my ice!
Don't stick to it!
I paid for it and bought it!
It's my food for a week!
Delicious!
The strawberry flavor and the milk topping are perfect!
I ate it all up and my head is getting numb!
Are you okay, senpai?
Don't push yourself too hard.
I gave it to the neighbors.
What kind of rule is this?
If you think this is just water, you can put in as much as you want!
Two-thirds of a human body is water.
There's still a little bit of luck left.
Okay, I'll give you a special service.
I'll give you this authentic ice cream.
I'm already done eating.
That's right.
I don't need it.
You take responsibility for it.
Okay.
I'll eat it all up!
I'll eat it with all my might.
What are you going to do, Tsunori?
It's obvious, right?
I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to get sick of it because it only tastes like strawberry and milk.
I need to change the sauce with ketchup while I have my coke.
On this side, I'll mix natto with eggs.
I will also add a vitamin drink to the à purée .
What do you think?
It looks delicious, right?
Will you really eat it?
Of course I will!
It's hot.
I'm going to go through a period of slowing down.
I just want to be able to eat a little more.
I'm going to stop eating the ice cream.
It's getting cold.
I'll drink some tea and warm up.
Alright, it's warmed up.
I can't take it anymore. I can't eat anymore.
What are you going to do, Nakoriya?
I'm going to make rice balls and eat them later.
What's this?
Ryotsu, is it your doing again?
What? I didn't do anything.
Idiot! Come here!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
My ears are getting numb!
What's this ice?
Your phone is still ringing.
This is...
a stage equipment prepared for the chief.
For me?
Yes.
This ice is...
a special gift for you.
I'm going to sing a karaoke song for you.
Don't try to fool me!
This is the ice from the northern region...
imported from Greenland.
Ryo-chan bought it from Kei-chan for 10,000 yen.
Ryotsu!
Would you like some, chief?
No!
Get rid of this ice!
I'm going to kill you!
K-kill?
Shut up!
If this ice is still fresh and clean by tomorrow,
you'll have moved to the North Pole Expo!
T-the North Pole Expo?
We have that kind of thing?
We're doing this for you.
Got it, Ryotsu?
The North Pole Expo
Oh, I can't eat all of this today.
Oh, this is it.
The ice cream Ryo bought.
It's a real North Pole ice cream.
If it's so noticeable, it's easy to be rumored.
What are you going to do?
I was going to make it into shaved ice and eat it.
Shaved ice?
If you make this much ice into shaved ice, you can do ski.
That's it.
This hot summer ski.
I'm going to take it.
You can think of it as rental skiing and rental snowboarding.
The money will be earned and the ice will be cleaned up.
It's a real miracle.
Let's get started.
I'm going to do it.
What is this?
Even if this hand is mine...
What are you going to do next?
I'm sure it's going to be about money.
The origin of Ryo's power is just a profit.
Good job, take it to the rest.
Ryo-san, leave it to me.
Next is the seat.
OK!
This is the Asana Island!
Now we know the route.
Kankichi, what are you doing with that ice?
We've done a lot.
Ryo, I brought a ski and snowboard.
Yeah, come with me!
OK!
OK, now we're ready.
You did a good job.
Welcome to Ryotsu Snowland.
The business starts now.
What is Ryotsu Snowland?
Come and take a look.
Snow falls in the summer of Katsushika.
The city's oasis is like a desert.
Karuizawa is a lowland town.
You can ski and snowboard in the middle of the summer.
You can even play bobsleigh.
Come on, let's go!
Let's go in.
Yeah, it's going to be fun!
Me too!
The traffic jam has been resolved, but there's still a long way to go.
Here's the rental.
The delivery is not allowed.
The group is 10% off.
The kid, the girl, the old man and the grandma are 30% off.
How's that?
That snowboard.
Yes, yes.
Welcome!
Yes!
Here you are.
Thank you.
I think this will cost a few million yen.
That's right.
Let's get out of the store.
Come on, come on.
Snowland's signature ice sushi.
Father and mother cry and rejoice.
Squid in a snowboard.
Kids' favorite, egg fried.
If you don't eat this, there's no point in coming here.
Then take one, snowboard.
I want an egg.
Here you are, snowboard.
One egg.
We'll eat the eggs.
Wow.
Curse.
It's great.
The rice is frozen in時候 ice.
That's right.
The sticky rice should be chilled and it will last a long time.
How do you eat it?
Just like this.
You have to put jam on it and eat it.
It's delicious.
This is jam made of salt.
If you don't like a raw pizza,
how about some frozen curry that surprises even Indians?
Come on, everyone.
Even curry is ice.
I want that.
Curry!
I can still go as far as I want.
I'll give you the food you dropped.
If you hit me, I'll throw a car and a ball at you.
I'm a smart pitcher who likes to throw.
Give it to me.
Me too.
Don't push me.
The ball is 200 yen.
Me too.
I'm already sold out.
I can't keep up with this business.
What?
What did you say?
The amount?
He made his own snow land in the park.
He's collecting customers.
He rents skis and snowboards and makes money.
What?
He's a genius.
I know.
If they're making money,
I'll buy another snow land.
What is it, Chief?
You're making money by making these things in the park?
It's nothing.
I'm not just going to clean up the ice.
I'm going to make a place where I can meet the residents of this area.
I wanted to make a place for us to hang out and make people happy.
That's all I wanted to do.
Then what is this?
What?
Ryozu! I know you have money behind you.
Give it back to everyone!
No! I don't want to!
Wait!
Time out!
That was close!
Ryozu!
I'll take it! I have an egg!
Wasabi!
Wait!
Damn it!
No!
Ah! It's DC!
Stop!
Ouch!
Watch out!
I'll give the camera to anyone!
You!
Prepare yourself, Ryozu!
What? You're not going to do that?
You're naive!
Ouch!
Ah...
Aaah!
It's falling!
Ouch!
силь은 피가
아
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Otsu!
Aaaah!
What's that?
Huh? Where did everybody go?
It's time for the next round.
Ah, Ryousha!
Aaaah!
It's strange. Nobody's here.
S-Sire!
Help me!
Aaaah!
I protected you.
I'm returning this money to everyone.
No! It's mine!
A-Action!
Thank goodness. I could use all the ice.
He's a smart guy who can use all the money he's made.
I wonder if it's his instinct to do so.
Shut up!
Oh no! I'm in trouble!
I'm in trouble!
I'll get in trouble if I make Reiko angry!
Stop it!
The high-speed road will be thrown away!
The mini-patto will be sucked away!
The highway will be reversed!
That way, I won't get my wife back!
Next time, Reiko's Raging Inferno!
See you then!
Let's smile at any time
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
Even if anything happens
Smile cutely, okay?
It's okay to go out with a face that's nothing
Hey, smile at me
You're not bad
With the same attitude as before, yeah!
When?
But, smile, okay?
It's not beautiful when women are serious
You should smile right away
If you're not a kid