♪ When you watch TV ♩
♪ Make the room brighter and look away ♩
♪ It's after the rain that someone is calling ♩
♪ You walked while looking back ♩
♪ Your hand was on the chair ♩
♪ The mysterious feeling you felt at that time ♩
♪ So with a black side of the fence ♩
♪ I walked on the outside of Ake-do ♩
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
Politicians with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Do your life again!
Don't run away!
Go! Go!
Leave it to me!
Bastard!
Honga! Don't lose!
Don't underestimate the police!
I'll arrest you!
Bastard!
What are you thinking?
Ohara is trying to disown you
What should I say?
Excuse me
Today's lecture was a little long, wasn't it?
Without you
My life would be a lot different
Yeah, it was hard
I was about to be fired
Oh, my God
Well, it doesn't matter what happens
It doesn't start
Life has to be positive
Ha ha ha
How bad are you?
Well, I'll shoot you!
Oh, a knock-out board
Senior, I did it!
Your favorite masterpiece!
What? Really?
This one!
Yes!
This is the revolution of PC games!
Ryoji, what are you talking about?
It's a revolutionary PC game developed by a company in Nakagawa
It's not like you used to raise a girl or a pet
This is a game to raise yourself
Raise myself?
What does it mean?
In other words, input all the data of the person himself
and make it into a game character.
That way, the person's future can be simulated on a computer.
There's a lot of side characters, and it's hard to understand.
So it's a life game on a computer, right?
That also means that you can understand the future that's very close to reality.
I don't even know what to say to the manager. Let's actually try it.
Let's do it.
This game already has all of the data of the senior as a sample.
When you start the game, the main character will appear.
Oh, it's exactly like Ryotsu.
Exactly. This is me.
What?
For example, let's say you dropped money in front of the senior.
Then...
I closed it! I lost 5,000 yen!
Lucky!
Hey!
The police officer is also there.
Do you think you can conquer the secret?
No way! Calm down!
This is a game! A game!
Oh, I see.
Damn it.
Hey, what's this number?
It's the current happiness, assets, and position numbers.
I picked up 5,000 yen, so the assets are 5,000.
Happiness is 10.
I see. The position hasn't changed.
There's a continuation.
Oh, the manager is here.
Oh, Ryotsu.
Ryotsu, what were you doing here?
M- Manager! No, nothing.
Nothing is wrong.
It's a nice day today.
The excuse is exactly the same as Ryotsu.
Because they have the same personality.
I saw it, Ryotsu!
Do you think a policeman can conquer a secret?
M- Manager, calm down!
The lines are the same.
Really?
I'll take care of this.
Oh, my God!
Oh, damn it.
The happiness and assets are back to zero.
Of course.
I'll marry a rich girl and increase all the numbers.
No, I have my own.
Speaking of rich girls, Reiko.
Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
You want to be rich, right?
Oh, my God!
These numbers increase so quickly.
I have to do this.
In a month?
That's impossible.
The company started with a copy of my wife's unique work has gone bankrupt.
Gah, what the hell!
Then it is a comeback as a policeman!
I have no idea.
I don't know.
What?!
Ah! The police are being arrested!
Hahaha! This is good!
Even though it's a game, the burden is greatly reduced!
Hahaha!
Ah, look at this!
He's starting a bank robbery!
Give me the money!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Even if you say that, the character is moving on its own!
Oh! He stole 3.3 billion yen!
You idiot!
Ouch!
Ah! I won't work for the rest of my life!
Hahaha!
What a guy!
He seems to have completely tasted it.
Ryotsu! Be quiet and confess!
I don't want to!
Hey! Are you waiting, Ryotsu?!
The chief's persuasion is still not enough.
How cheeky! Don't make the game and reality together!
Ah, look! This time he has a gun!
He's going to attack a cashier.
Give me the money!
Ah!
Ah! I was shot!
In 2005, the law changed and the defense was strengthened.
Don't predict it on your own!
It's game over.
Hahaha! This is quite interesting!
Nakagawa-kun, you're doing well!
I'm sorry!
Don't do this!
I'm the only one who's too pathetic!
Everyone, join us!
It's okay. The data is perfect.
Me too?
That's right. And everyone starts at the age of three.
But the era of birth is different.
It's okay because it's linked properly.
Wow, cute!
Hey, Ryo-san.
I wonder if you could start at a different time than now.
If you don't, it's boring to see my future.
I see. You're right.
Alright, I'll start as a rich old lady.
And then, I'll start as a poor person.
Eh? Why?
I'll let you guys experience the pain of growing up from the bottom.
Then, I'll start.
Start!
I don't know where my home is.
You're going to get lost in your own garden?
I'm not used to it.
Papa! Papa!
He's out of the house.
What?
What's going to happen to me?
It seems that he was picked up by a kind person.
And when he grows up, he becomes a police officer.
He's an ordinary man, but he's living a happy family life.
What? You're still the same as you are now.
Well, I guess I'm just like this.
I've made you live in a rich family.
Alright, next is Reiko.
Oh, you're three years old, Reiko.
Wow, I'm poor for what I'm wearing, but you're so cute.
No matter how cute you are, you're so poor.
Wow, great!
This is the ideal girl I've been looking for.
Hey, you, would you like to appear in a movie with me?
Mama!
You're a beautiful girl, but you're a debut as a child actor because you got caught in the eyes of a movie director.
That movie was a huge hit by chance.
Reiko is a national star.
Hey, hey!
And she's also a world-class star in Hollywood.
After that, she was liked by the US President.
And she's going to be the secretary of the White House.
This is even more amazing than it is now.
You're so talented and talented.
No way.
Damn it.
Alright, then I'll make you more and more hyper ultra special poor.
It's from where you're living in a pipe.
Isn't it a little too cruel?
This is enough because reality is too blessed.
Oh, a roll of money.
Oh, where's Amuko?
Wait a minute!
I'll go.
I'll make sure no one comes.
No one can get close to this.
That's terrible.
Oh, construction has begun.
Hey, you.
Yes, president.
That girl.
Hey!
Can you forgive such a convenient thing?
All right, it starts from the point where you're drifting in the sea.
You, that girl.
Why do you always do that?
Why do you always find such rich people?
Oh, yeah.
It seems that no matter what the setting is, Nakagawa is destined to be rich.
You were born under the star of luck.
Even I'm afraid of her.
Hmph.
Not funny.
Then the next is the head of the club.
You idiot!
What on earth are you doing?
Mr. Tonda.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ohara.
Mr. Ohara?
What do you mean?
I see. The game is still running as Senpai said it was.
What?
If he's not here, am I the president?
That's what I think.
I want to see more. Show me the rest.
Okay.
Wow! He's even working as a police officer!
What?
What do you think, Ryo-tsu?
My ability is just like yours.
Who said don't play games and reality together?
Idiot!
It's proof that your life has changed because of you!
You pervert!
No! Don't say I'm a pervert!
Then, what will happen to me without Senpai?
That's right. I'll show you, Ryo-tsu.
I'm going to the head office of the traffic department.
Really?
It's a great deal to meet you, Ryo-tsu.
Senpai, you're so mean! You're a pervert!
No way! I'll say whatever I want!
Then, let's see other people.
How about Sakonji?
No!
After winning gold medals at the Olympics, he was a great player in the K-1.
He never got into the game.
It's a life of bickering.
You devil!
Ouch! What are you going to do, President?
I'm not asking what I'll do.
Everyone is unhappy because I just met you.
It's just a game simulation.
But it's like reality. Take responsibility!
That's nonsense!
Then, how about you try it if you met Senpai before?
I agree.
It may not be just Senpai.
Then, what about you, Komachi?
Let's try it.
I met a senior who was a junior in my neighborhood when he was 3 years old.
After that, I married him because I had no other partner.
I built a building by destroying the lawn of my house, but it failed.
I have no place to live because of debt.
No way!
Look, Ryozu, it's all your fault.
It's not like that.
There may be some people who have become unhappy even if they don't meet me.
Then let's look at the others.
Then, what is the model of Ozaki?
He is the president of a large gang chain.
Then, what about Ryo's aunt?
She won the All Japan Ryo-bo-san Contest.
No way! What about my father?
Ryozuya is a big company and is the president of Asakusa Shopping Association.
Then, what about that dog?
It was picked up by a rich man and sold for a lot of money.
Don't say that.
Then, what about the bride?
What if I don't meet a bride?
Are you a bride?
Look at this.
The bride is the same as before.
But look at this happiness.
It's 62% from 60%.
It's 2% up.
It's all my fault.
It's not like that.
Maria.
Please.
If I were a real woman, I would be with Ryo.
What's going on with her?
What's happening with her?
Then, I'll go.
I'll be in your care.
We got married for free.
It's love.
That's right.
Happiness is increasing.
Thanks to Maria, we arrested the culprit of the important international mission.
We even got a 300 million yen lottery.
We even got a prize.
We even went to the police department.
Everything is going well.
Besides, thanks to Maria,
we won't be a nuisance to the people around us.
There's nothing good.
Maria is happy.
Ryo.
How about you marry Maria?
That's a good idea.
That's right, Ryo.
That's great.
Ryo.
Let's get married soon.
That's right.
What?
You can't do that.
Because you are...
Because you are a man.
Yes.
That's right.
It's a good thing.
That's right, Ryo.
It's for everyone.
Congratulations.
Maria.
I'm glad you're here.
we don't want to get married.
Help us.
Wait, Ryo.
Let's build a happy family with me.
No, stop.
Let's stop this alliance.
Let's move on.
Next story!
The man with the seven-colored voice
Senpai, what's wrong?
A terrible growling voice. Did you catch a cold?
No, I went to karaoke last night and sang for 12 hours, and my throat was cold.
12 hours?
That's crazy.
But it's a great voice. It's like listening to a old song.
I was surprised when I woke up in the morning.
Are you okay? Senpai?
What's this?
Ryo-san seems to have a lot of damage.
He was just a normal human.
Of course.
Ryo-san, what's that voice?
What's wrong?
It's just like Chief Ohara.
That's creepy.
Is it that similar to the voice of the chief?
Anyone can hear that voice.
Good morning, everyone.
What a coincidence.
It's true.
Yes, this is the Parkway Exhibition Office.
Chief, Chief Ohara hasn't come yet, but...
Give me a minute.
Hello, it's me, Ohara.
That voice is the chief.
What do you want me to do?
Ohara, what's with that attitude?
If you have a problem, come here, you stupid chief.
I don't forget, I'm the type to take care of things.
Oh, good.
I'm Ohara.
That's terrible.
What?
You don't care?
All right, I'll run around with the chief's voice.
Senior.
I don't know.
Here, morning sushi.
Chief Ohara.
Yes, it's Ohara.
Ten special sushi, please.
Please.
I'm on a big call.
Yes, sir.
Oh, this is Chief Ohara.
Excuse me, but please send the plamodel of the Radicon helicopter and the battleship Yamato
and the combat-like figure set to Ryo's place.
Of course, I will pay the full loan.
Why?
That is a reward for the daily work of Ryo's chief.
Stop it, Ryo.
That's right, senpai.
Shut up.
You're going to get a lot of grudges.
Alright, I'll call the police next time.
Look, Ryo-san.
I'm going to do something bad.
Shut up!
Ah!
His voice changed again.
This time, it's the president's voice.
Huh?
What did you say?
It's true.
That's strange.
What's going on?
I...
I got a stomach ache from suffering.
Ah...
It hurts.
It's obvious.
If you tighten your neck, you'll die.
I don't know that much.
Ah, it changed again.
His voice got louder.
What?
I see.
I know how to do it.
How's that?
Your voice got louder again, right?
It's true.
When you touch this part of your throat, it changes.
When you lower one finger...
Ah.
When you lower one octave, it changes.
It gets louder.
And you can adjust your voice with the balance of left and right.
That's amazing.
He has a seven-colored voice.
All right.
If I do this...
Ah.
I bought a new Ferrari.
I'm sick of it, so I'll give it to you.
How's that?
It's like Kei-chan.
You can do good things.
And if I do this...
Ah.
Oh, it's like Ryo-chan.
He's a manly and popular idol.
Ah, it's Reiko-san.
I don't like it.
Next.
I'm a life-saving band member.
It's Terai-san.
Am I that kind of voice like Hayashi or Kobuhei?
And...
Hey, hey, it's Gouki's Honda.
I'm going to beat you up.
Hey, Saori.
Help me get out of here.
Ryo-sama.
I'm Maria.
I don't know what to say.
Good morning.
Ah, Chief.
Oh, what's wrong, Ryo-san?
What's wrong with you?
Good morning.
Oh, Chief Ohara.
I'm waiting for ten sushi.
What?
I don't remember asking for that.
But it was definitely the voice of the chief.
Even if you say that, there's nothing I don't remember.
Don't say that.
Well, then...
Chief, I brought a gift for Ryo-san.
What?
Chief, you have a good point.
Don't be silly.
I'm not supposed to do that.
You're getting embarrassed again.
No, no, it's not me.
What?
But on the phone...
Ohara.
Ohara?
Chief, this is just the right place.
Something strange has happened.
Ohara.
Huh?
A decision has been made on the end of the sea,
so I decided to ask you to tell me right away.
What?
Chief, why did I have to go to the end of the sea?
I said that on the phone.
On the phone?
What did you say?
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-san.
Do you know something?
Ryo-san, did you do it?
No, I didn't do anything.
What?
You sounded like a woman.
I became a man with seven voices.
What?
What do you mean?
Ryo-san, you can't run away like that.
So, this is what happens.
When you do this...
Stop, Nakagawa.
Stop!
That's my voice.
And then, when you do this...
No, you should stop, Nakagawa.
Don't move, you!
I won't leave you alone.
You idiot!
I'll cut your head into pieces!
Like this, Ryo-chan used the seven voices freely.
Please pay ten people for the special sushi.
I'll get the money for the ramen too.
Ryo-chan, are you ready?
You're the one who's going to the end of the sea.
You're the one who's going to the end of the sea!
Please stop, chief!
Shut up, you idiot!
You're so mean!
My eyes are spinning!
I won't forgive you this time!
I'm so happy!
You idiot!
You're the worst!
That's my voice!
I don't know what's going on!
Nachi!
Help me again!
You idiot!
You piece of shit!
You little black grunge!
Shut up!
My eyes are spinning.
This can't be happening.
Why are you doing this to me?
Put up your hands.
Shut up, chipmunk!
Shut up, idiot!
And here we are.
♪ I don't care anymore, I'll solve it as I like ♪
♪ Everyday is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ Heart is flying, Monday ♪
♪ Monday Monday No Problem ♪
Why do I keep getting unlucky?
According to the fortune teller, today is the worst day of my life?
I see, if today ends, this misfortune will end.
Next time, "The Worst Day of Life"!
See you then!