Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating on the river ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging on a tightrope ♪
♪ I was laughing at the fact that I was still a child ♪
♪ Even if I try to cheer up somewhere ♪
♪ I can only get angry ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes is so kind ♪
♪ The crows are crying, so the rain is getting heavier ♪
♪ Are there any grilled chicken? ♪
♪ From the tap of the hat ♪
♪ The sun is setting ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be the same ♪
♪ It's a happy year, so I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm the stupid one who noticed ♪
I have to drops my eyes all night.
Hm?
No good. Yep, I got the wrong room.
Oh! Ryo, where are you going?
Reiko?
Then this place is the exit before the park.
The Exit Full of Women
You're dressed up again.
There he is, the gorilla boy.
You don't have to come.
What?
You're late, Kankichi. You're completely late.
Sorry, Matoi.
Why are you here?
What happened to the others?
The chief is on a business trip abroad.
I didn't hear that.
He suddenly went to work.
The monk fell off the stairs at home last night and was hospitalized.
So, Nakagawa-san said that the company was suddenly busy and he would take a break for a while.
Really?
Only Ryo-chan and I can't do anything.
So why are you here?
Well, let's go to the exit.
You're the ones who did this.
I came here on purpose.
It's natural to make it easier to work even a little.
What?
Yes, yes. Let's start working with this.
Damn it.
What the hell?
What are you doing, Kankichi?
That's my line. That's my line. Don't use it without permission.
I see.
What happened?
I thought no one was using it because it was so dirty.
No way.
What was in the drawer?
It was just trash.
That's my collection.
Where did you put it?
I threw it away.
What?
That's the rare thing I've been collecting for tens of thousands of yen.
Well, on this occasion,
I'll give you a chance to work seriously.
You don't need a desk anyway, do you?
I use a desk, too.
It's only when you're writing a draft.
Right.
So,
your desk is enough.
Wow, what a great orange box.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm the best at this time without the director.
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
We've come to play.
Are you all right?
Let's have tea.
Some Sashi.
Thank you.
Huh?
Why is the floor here so mushy?
I don't know.
How... can I use it?
Help!
Watch out, kid!
You idiot!
Out of the way.
Ah!
Gah!
Are you okay, Ryo?
Ugh!
I'm just fooling around in there!
That's right!
What?
I don't want to live in a place full of women!
Ryo, where are you going?
I'm going on a patrol!
You're not going to skip school, are you?
I'm sure you're going to a pachinko.
I said patrol, so I said patrol!
You're so suspicious of people.
It's not funny.
Let's change the mood.
Wasn't it a patrol?
Gah!
Matoi, when did you...
The director asked me to do it.
He said you'd skip school so don't look away.
Director?
You're such a nuisance.
Ah, Yumi Morioh is flying in the sky!
Eh? No way!
No way!
Ah!
Hey, Kankichi!
Ah, but I can't help being followed around in the middle of the night.
Ah!
That's...
Money!
Haha!
Yay!
I'll take it back.
Matoi!
Oh, dear.
I didn't expect to get caught by such a simple hand.
Yes, patrol well.
This is a dog walk.
Oh, dear.
What a boring day.
Let's go back to my room and play a game.
Sakonji, let's play a game.
Sakonji, are you there?
Sakonji-san isn't here.
Huh?
He's supposed to be at the Judo training camp in Izu from today.
Ah, I see.
I guess I'll have to go with Honda.
Honda-san is going to Shirobai's Shido in Tohoku.
What's he going to do?
Huh?
I've met Hojo.
Hojo-san will stay at a hotel for a study session.
Uh, maybe someone else...
Today, there aren't many people either,
either on time or at night.
What?
"Occult Club"
Shut up, all of you!
It's in the way of business!
It's fine.
It's break time anyway, so...
You still have your rejoining.
I have to deliver the
check!
Huh?
Hmm...
Ah, I got the kanji wrong!
Eh?
I really can't believe it!
It's your fault we were distracted!
If you want a break, then let's take a break!
Hey, don't blame others!
Why do I have to be ordered by you?
Everyone, let's take a break to calm down!
Yes!
Reiko-san is right!
Let's all go!
Yes!
Hey, you!
I'm more important than Reiko!
They're so noisy!
It's like that when women gather.
It's the same abroad.
Women like to talk.
Women...
Hmm?
It suddenly became quiet.
Yeah, what's wrong?
Hmm...
If it's quiet, I don't care about it.
Is that so?
Isn't that wrong?
What are you doing?
Ah, it has nothing to do with you.
Shishi!
I don't care if you tell me what you're doing.
Hmm?
What are you making a bag?
I'm making it with a hair tie.
I can't go ahead from here.
Hmm?
Let me see.
Ah!
I see.
Hey!
Shut up and look!
Here.
It's amazing.
I'm reducing the number of eyes like this.
And I remove one by one.
And I knit them.
Look, naturally, the end is curving, right?
Awesome!
It's elegant.
Wow...
Look.
Oh, thank you!
It's like a professional did it!
Hey, how do you make this?
It's not in the book.
Hmm?
Ah, is this a beeswax?
Mark?
It's easy with flowers.
You know how to do it?
Yeah.
You make a ring with the beads,
and then you wrap it around like this,
and then you do this.
And you have an aura!
Wow!
That's amazing!
You can make it with such a thick ring.
Ryo-chan is basically a master of craft.
Can you watch this too?
Sure.
I can't believe you could do something like that even though you're an angel.
I can't believe it.
It's about time for lunch.
Agreed!
So, what should we have for lunch today?
I brought lunch.
Let's eat lunch together.
Of course!
Okay.
Here we go again.
Ryo-chan,
here's some for you.
Huh?
Oh!
Th-this much?
I got a lot of help yesterday.
Here's a thank you.
Oh, I didn't know this was...
Teacher!
This is for you!
Thank you for the lunch!
You're like a female teacher.
Then, thank you for the lunch!
It's good!
Really?
Try this!
Thank you.
This is delicious.
How did you make this?
Do you like it, Ryo-chan?
Yeah!
I want you to tell me what happened yesterday.
Sure.
Yum!
Hey, Reiko.
I'm making dessert.
But you didn't decorate well like in the pictures.
I can't do it.
Oh, this is a little difficult.
Which one?
Oh, I've made this before.
I'll make it.
I wonder if it's like this.
Amazing! It looks delicious!
I can't believe it.
How can you make something like this?
I taught Ryo-chan how to make dessert before.
He mastered it in no time.
If you have materials, I'll make more.
What?
Well, you'll see.
Thank you for waiting.
Beautiful!
It's more beautiful than in Japan.
It's wonderful to cut fruits.
My grandmother, who rarely praises people, praised her for her knife skills.
She can do anything unexpectedly.
Except for work.
Useless!
Ü meng cek!
Interestingly, she couldn't write it well even though it was in Japanese, but in Japanese she founded an empire of Japanese women.
Yui
Yu
I can't do it.
Beautiful!
Looking delicious!
I got an extra bowl of sushi and ingredients to share.
Can you exchange them?
Yes, I made a lot.
That's why I made it.
Me too.
Come on, eat more.
Which one should I choose?
It's been melting in my mouth.
It's good.
Here, it's done.
It's beautiful.
Next, I'll do it.
Okay.
I did it.
It's done.
What?
Is it done already?
It's a handmade dress.
I thought it would be a little more difficult.
I'm glad you taught me.
Yes, I'm grateful to Kankichi.
Kankichi.
Until now, he didn't call me by my name.
Hey, hurry up and wear it.
Wait a minute, Komachi.
What?
It's not good.
Before I saw it.
No.
If you're there, say you're there.
I've been there since a while ago.
Come on, hurry up and wear it.
I understand.
It's a mess if Komachi says it.
If it was before, he would never have laughed.
That's right.
Something...
Komachi said.
If it was a woman, she would be a good wife.
What?
Hey, what are you saying, Komachi?
That's right.
What are you thinking?
But you're good at cooking and you can sew and sew.
Besides, you're good at shopping.
I bought good things for cheap.
Right?
Even Matoi-chan.
You guys forgot the important thing.
I'm not good at cleaning and washing.
You've seen my room, right?
Oh, I see.
But recently, there are more and more women who can't clean and wash.
The garbage house on TV.
Kan-Kichi is not that bad.
Stupid.
I've been wondering about it for a while.
What are you making?
What?
Table cloth.
It's better to have it when we all have a meal.
Rather, what you're doing is what you're doing.
Hmm...
What?
The only problem is your appearance.
Huh?
Hmm...
Why don't you try makeup?
Huh?
Good job!
Hey, are you serious?
I'm serious!
It's okay. Leave it to me.
Hey, stop it!
Hmm...
Apply foundation well.
It's better to put in shadow.
Hmm...
No, stop it.
Is it this bad?
Hmm?
What? What's going on?
It's hot.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Ah,
?
Huh?
What is this?
What?
I'm sorry.
The face of Kan-Kichi is thick,
so I thick up the make-up.
Please, let me do it again.
In the case of Ryōchi san,
this thick eyebrows are the neck.
And her eyes are also scary.
Let's make both eyes and make it gentle.
I think we should do it in the week.
Let's put on some beard.
It's gonna work out.
How about this?
Is this Ryotsu?
It's totally different from what I imagined!
It's much better than before.
This is...
Me?
I thought you were reading a book.
It's a fashion magazine.
I'm not sure about makeup.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I bought this.
The makeup you asked for.
Oh, thank you.
I got this at the shop.
I bought it today.
I heard there's a fashion magazine presentation.
Alright, let's go!
Let's hurry!
I'm totally into Kankichi.
I'm a little worried.
I've been studying makeup for a few days.
I'd like you to see the results.
Ryo-chan, you're completely talking like a woman.
You're such a talker.
Why am I the one who's on the experiment table?
You don't usually put on makeup, do you?
Leave it to me.
Let's go.
Let's see.
I'll put on makeup.
Here it goes.
Wow, Matoi-chan.
A beauty like you!
It's like magic.
Is this really me?
Well.
Tell me next time!
I'll tell you soon.
Wait, I didn't study makeup for you two.
You have the first purpose?
Yes.
So I can be beautiful.
In Matoi's case, she's beautiful, so she doesn't have to suffer much.
But in my case, I can't do that, so it's hard.
It's okay. You can do it.
We'll help you.
We'll help you, too.
Thank you, everyone.
I think I'm doing something wrong.
What? A gorilla?
Yes, a gorilla is running away and is in the room.
Okay, I'll do something about it.
It's his turn.
Are you two there?
Chief!
Kan-Kichi is in the back.
It's an incident. Go out right away.
Yes, but...
What are you doing?
Call me right away.
Yes, I will.
One, two, Kan-chan!
Kan-chan?
Yes, sorry to keep you waiting.
It's been a long time, Chief.
Are you Ryo-tsu?
Yes.
I can't do that.
Shut up!
I have to do something about it.
Come on!
Get the gorilla over there!
Am I alone?
Of course.
No way.
It's terrible.
Kan-chan is alone.
How can you make me look so dangerous?
You're a weak girl.
No, I'm a man.
Ryo-chan is now becoming a woman.
I don't think it's possible.
What should I do?
Help me, someone!
Someone, help me!
Boy?
Yes.
There's a 3-month-old baby in that room.
So we can't use the
"Sailugidan" .
Someone has to rush in and help.
He's sleeping now.
If he wakes up and starts crying...
Someone, help me!
I'll do it.
Will you do it, Ryo-tsu?
Yes!
You can't abandon the baby as a woman.
My maternal instinct is weak.
What?
I'll do it.
Komachi, Naoko, follow me!
Yes!
Alright!
Alright...
Good boy.
Oh no! He started crying!
No!
Alright, alright!
I have to run away!
Oh no!
What should I do?
Kan-chan, this way.
Komachi, hurry up!
I'm counting on you.
Got it!
Be careful!
Uh...
Ah!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Kan-chan, hurry up and hold on to me!
No, I'm wearing a skirt!
It's not the time to be embarrassed!
But...
Huh?
What?
Stop it!
You're not my hunter!
Surely not.
I'm your child.
Can you stay calm?
Get out of here!
Hey, you!
Stop!
What are you doing, Kanata?
Stop it!
What is this?
Stop!
Don't do this, Toko!
Good work.
We are going back to work.
Thank you for your concern.
Welcome home, everyone.
Welcome home.
What happened to Ryotsu?
I can't see him.
Where did he go?
Well...
He's become a good bride.
What?
I don't want to live like this anymore.
Help me!
Thank you very much for your though.
I'm really sorry, but can I walk with you?
Could you stop me?
I had a vision when we met.
There's nothing like a dream.
I have never thought things would turn out like this.
I want to go home.
I saw it
Everyone was a child once
Everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above his eyes
Look up
That corner
Everyone, everyone can see
We can see
Let's go!
There's a wall over there
I'm sure there's a wall
Everyone come to our town
Let's go!
There's a wall over there
I'm sure there's a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Let's go home!
You took the customers from the shopping street?
I'll take it back!
Leave the business stuff to the Ryotsu Saba
I'll give them crazy ideas!
Arai!
Come to Kameari Shopping Street.
I'm counting on you!
To our town
Thank you!