Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle of the sky ♪
♪ I'll fly to the place ♪
♪ where the love stone was cut ♪
♪ I wonder if I'll go there ♪
♪ after jogging ♪
♪ I was laughed at ♪
♪ for being a bad boy ♪
♪ Even if I'm in a good mood somewhere ♪
♪ I can't help but grumble ♪
♪ and grumble ♪
♪ The cityscape is kinder than usual ♪
♪ Because the crows are crying ♪
♪ the bird is singing ♪
♪ Are the yakitori and hobari here? ♪
♪ From the tapestry of a tattered hat ♪
♪ to a large-scale store ♪
♪ the sunset falls ♪
♪ It'll end tomorrow as well ♪
♪ But I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm relieved ♪
♪ because I'm a fool ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Battle Shogi
I played with Kei-chan three times and won three times. Ryo-chan's chess skills are also quite good.
I'm confident in chess, but...
Hahaha. You can play against me at home. The match cost is 5,000 yen.
Eh? I'll hold back.
Then how about you guys?
I'll hold back too.
I also pass.
Well, I'm not proud of it, but I haven't lost in chess since I was a child.
I haven't lost in chess since I was a child.
But there are some people who are better than you.
Ohara-buchou is so talented that he won in the main school's chess competition.
That's right. The captain's chess is full-scale.
What? I'm not good at it.
You're very confident.
Of course. Chess is the life of the flutter.
Like that captain, I'm so stubborn...
Ohara-buchou!
I want to say that I'm not good at chess during my work, but I'll play against you.
Are you going to play with your senior?
Wow! This is a very interesting match.
It's not interesting just to play.
If I win, I'll have lunch over there for a month.
All right.
All right. I won't hold back.
Ohara-buchou
I'm going.
You can come from anywhere.
Ohara-buchou
The captain's expression has changed!
The captain is serious.
Ohara-buchou
Chief, one more time!
It doesn't matter how many times I do it.
- Again, Ryo-san? - One more time!
- Senpai, that's... - Hey, one more time!
Ryo-chan.
One more time!
- Stop it already. - Damn it!
I can't beat that chief no matter how many times I do it.
I'll drink to my fill today!
Chief.
Wait a minute.
Wait for me.
I'll give you 500 yen if you wait.
It'll double from the third time.
Okay?
No way.
Damn it, it's better than losing.
What are you doing, old man?
You can't tell, can you, old man?
Do I look like a cult?
Chief.
You're going to get in trouble.
Calm down, old man!
What?
What's up?
What are you talking about?
Who do you think you are?
You don't know my name?
You're so annoying.
I'm the king of the Ennai Shogunate.
Oh, it's me.
The child who was silent started crying.
Oh, good, good.
Good, good, good.
You're so annoying.
You're going to get in trouble.
But...
He's really good at it.
The king of the Ennai Shogunate, huh.
You're no good at personality,
so you're not good at Shogi.
Your Shogi is the best.
If you're upset, find a base.
Come to me step by step like this.
Then, with a special service,
I will show you my special skill!
I will cast a lightning storm!
Dragon's Mouth!
That's awesome!
This might be the real thing!
Please!
Make me your apprentice!
I really want to beat the chief!
Idiot!
The spirit of Shogi is the spirit of Fu.
Fu is Fu, meaning "to lose".
The spirit that wants to win will cause a disaster.
What?
Shogi starts with Fu and ends with Fu.
No matter how strong you are, you will eventually lose.
Master, I ask you again!
Please make me your apprentice!
Please, Master!
Do you want to be my apprentice?
Yes!
Then, first...
I'll start with the bath!
What?
If you blow...
I didn't think there was anyone who used a bath like this.
Master, how is the floor?
It's hot!
If you blow, I'll clean the toilet.
Oh, my!
This is a mess!
If you blow, come to my room!
Yes!
Master, I think I can teach you Shogi in earnest!
Master, I'm coming in!
You're here.
Yes!
Next is the inner color of the inner pot.
What?
The bath, the toilet, and the inner pot...
I'm here to help you with Shogi!
Are you dissatisfied?
Because you always make me do things that have nothing to do with Shogi...
You idiot!
You!
You poor thing!
You have no skills at all!
I'm here to teach you the spirit of Shogi.
The spirit of Shogi?
As I said earlier, the spirit of Shogi is the spirit of the nation.
The nation begins and ends with the nation.
Think about what you've done so far.
What have I done?
Well...
First, I've done the bath, then the rice, and then the toilet.
And then the last one is the inner pot.
That is, the nation begins and ends with the nation.
What?
Don't make me look stupid!
Are you dissatisfied?
Of course!
If you don't teach me Shogi anymore, I'm going home!
If you're going to say that much, I'll teach you.
I'll teach you.
Let me teach you that.
If I teach you that much, will you?
Of course I will.
Why don't you become my servant?
I'll teach you.
Oh, I gotcha!
Something's wrong with all of them.
That you can't laugh.
I can see it from so far away.
I'm scared.
Come on, boiling.
Gah!
Splendid!
You are the successor of the battle shogi that I have been waiting for!
What is battle shogi?
Look at this.
Battle shogi is a new game that combines traditional shogi and fighting.
The rules are simple.
You use a piece of iron to win.
The loser will be blown away by the explosion.
You cannot win with your ability, but this battle shogi is not a dream of a world champion.
World champion?
I am not crazy.
You are born to play battle shogi.
If you win, you will have a lot of prize money and a lot of money for the commercial.
You will also be a champion in the Olympic Games.
If that happens, I may also have a rich life.
Master, please teach me battle shogi.
The training is tough.
I will never cry.
Good for you.
Let's aim for the victory of battle shogi together!
Master!
This is...
No way...
You're going to win a battle shogi game that I have been planning.
Master!
- closet door - - toilet
- - toilet
- Goodcamp
Episode 1: The Battle of Nagasaki
Come on!
It's a match! Dynamite Nagasaki wins!
It's not a match, it's more like a combat.
This is perfect for Ryo.
This is not a match, it's more like a combat.
It's Ryo's turn.
Strong Kondo enters the red corner.
Ryo Tsukankichi enters the blue corner.
Ryo's turn.
Ryo, you can do it!
Ryo, you're going to win!
Kankichi, don't lose!
Listen, Kankichi.
If you use the techniques I taught you, you'll win.
Time limit 1 match.
About Ryo's position...
Sente Aoi!
Time limit 1 match.
Start!
Let's go!
Sente Aoi!
Kankichi, use that!
That's it. Use that.
Fire!
Kenshin오 Inazuma!
Okay!
That's it!
OK!
It's a match! Ryo Ryo and Kanchi win!
Amazing! Ryo won!
Good job, Kanchi!
You idiot!
The second round! Red, Ryuo and Watanabe vs. Blue, Ryo and Kanchi!
Say my name.
Ryo, you're in trouble!
It's a match.
The power of Shogi is greater than Ryo's.
You're totally in trouble.
Don't hesitate, Kanchi.
This is the only way.
Higidaifunkacchabudai!
He's rearranging his moves as if he's the winner.
What a cowardly move.
The rules of battle Shogi are OK.
You start from the moment you rearrange your moves.
OK!
It's a match! Ryo and Kanchi win!
Amazing! It's a big turn!
The first round is over!
Red, Ryo and Kanchi vs. Blue, Dynamite Nagasaki!
You're strong! You're a killer!
What?
Daigai!
Ryo, how many moves?
Two!
Look at that!
So far so good.
Everything is so fast, Ryo.
I'll get you if you play seriously.
What about this?
Are you А déjà vu?
You fool!
What?
Ote!
Good job Ryo-san!
Ryo-san!
Good job!
Ote!
OK!
The two who are left in the final of the World Championship is...
The original Kamen Rider, Ryo-tsukanki!
You're the world champion Ryo-san!
Ryo-chan you're wonderful!
Senpai, do your best!
Just do whatever you want.
Kankichi, you can win with any hand you want!
The day has finally come.
The opponent is that fated rival.
And the opponent of this battle is...
The supreme Shishida Ryusei army!
Nagareboshi Ikketsu!
Kankichi!
Don't be careless.
The opponent is me.
The man who drove us into retirement.
Master!
Shoukaku, it's either you or me.
The one who loses this match will retire from the battle.
OK?
I'm looking forward to it Ikketsu!
And I can't let it be!
Hehe...
Hehehe...
You're already dead.
What?
That's right!
OK!
In that match, I defeated the One Iron Sky Thunderstrike!
*Strike*
*Shot*
*Urace will come *
The fact that you were able to establish a bond between me and my disciple all this long;
it is truly an eternal pact!
Master, I will take that revenge for you!
You can destroy that as much as you want to.
The final battle will be held here, in the special ring built on the Sumida River.
The winning piece used in the final battle is 100 kilograms.
The battle on this river where there is no place to run or help is exactly the battle between Musashi and Kojiro on Ganryu Island.
-Hakushii! -Ryo-chan!
-Ryo-san! -Will Ryo and Musashi win?
The winner is Nagareboshi Kojiro!
Kankichi, come at me as hard as you can!
If the winning piece is in the ring, then I won't be able to use the cat's eye, the mid-air spin, or the big wave chabudai.
Hehehe.
Hahahaha.
You're already dead.
Wow! The final line of the Nagareboshi-I-Tetsu is already out!
The final line of the Nagareboshi-I-Tetsu is already out!
The battle is already on fire!
I can't even open my eyes!
Oh, no! Nagareboshi-I-Tetsu has taken over the corner of Ryōzu Kankichi!
Ugh...
Damn it.
Yeah, it's pretty tough.
You seem to be using your stamina more intensely than me.
Take this!
Sky-Fall of the Sky!
Big Wave Chabudai!
T-This is...!
A giant whirlwind created a huge whirlwind!
That's right!
The first one!
It completed that giant whirlwind!
See?
Kankichi, that's a dummy!
What?
Ryo got caught!
Ryo-chan!
んでfinitive
This is intense!
Attack them!
Kankichi!
Stand up!
Don't stop, Kankichi!
Stand up and find your glory, Kankichi!
I promise to finish you off!
If you're not here,
then I'm gonna let you win!
Hmph!
It's a waste of time!
He stood up!
Ryo Tsukakichi!
He's gone to hell!
Now it's my last chance!
What?
What was that, Ryo Tsukakichi?
He was wearing a silver ring underneath his grave!
Hmph!
He's gone!
He's the one who's screaming as he's destroying a metal device!
The game starts and ends with a fail!
Let's go, Hi!
Shinku Datsunaki Otoshi!
Ryujin no Mai!
I won't let you do that!
Shinku Inazuna Otoshi!
The Great Uzu no Naki Version!
What?
Whoa!
Let's go!
The game's on!
Ryo Tsukakichi wins!
Ryo-san wins!
That's awesome, Ryo-chan!
Senpai, you're the best in the world!
Kankichi!
You did it!
You finally paid for your grudge against the stone.
Let's see!
What?
What's this?
W-what just happened?!
The iron rod cracked due to the impact of the battle!
S-s-save me, please!
I'm sick of this game!
To Be Continued
10 games, 5 times, 3 times, rock, paper, scissors, go!
10 games, 10 games, 5 times, 3 times, rock, paper, scissors, go!
Always sandals, always scandals, don't worry about it
Play the tunnel, everyday
Tiredness, I rolled it up in the end, threw it in the hole
Thin-legged instinct, a
stupid whipping instinct
Am I a fool?
I'm graduate, and I'm poor, not bad, right
Just do what I want to do
♪ That's what I'm talking about ♪
♪ Ya-mura koji, bura koji, paiko paiko paiko no shurin ga ♪
♪ Shurin ga no kurin dai ♪
♪ Kurin dai no ponpoko, kiiro ponpoko na no ♪
♪ Choukyuu mei no chousuke! ♪
♪ Director Kazuchi has developed a machine that can carry all kinds of heavy objects! ♪
♪ It's called the Super Power Assist Suit, Otasuke-kun! ♪
♪ Well, first I'll test it out! ♪
♪ Shwaa! ♪
♪ This is Ryo-san's Zenigami moving van! ♪
♪ Next time on Tetsu an Ryo-tsu, Yoroshiku na! ♪
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, it must be Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
♪ Thank you! ♪