Translated by 方 Hou
When you watch t-t-tv
Look into the deep blue sky
♪ Try to get away from me ♪
♪ I look up at the starry night ♪
♪ Floating in the river ♪
♪ When I kick the pebble ♪
♪ It flies to the shoe ♪
♪ I wonder if I'm going to the gym ♪
♪ Where I used to do my savings ♪
♪ They laughed at me ♪
♪ Saying I was still a kid ♪
♪ Even if I try to cheer up ♪
♪ I can't help but feel a bit sick ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes ♪
♪ Is strangely gentle ♪
♪ From the water in the Tungari-boshi ♪
♪ To the Taishakuten ♪
♪ The sun sets ♪
♪ Tomorrow will end like this ♪
♪ Katsushika and Shibamata ♪
♪ I lost my happiness ♪
♪ I realized ♪
♪ That I'm an idiot ♪
♪ For some reason ♪
Let's all
celebrate our happiness
and drink!
That's it for today!
Is Keisha hanging out with us?
This is not cool!
♪ ♪
As a guest!
Phew, I'm glad the wedding is over.
Yes, this is Nakagawa.
Yes, this is Keiichi.
Eh? Nakagawa group emergency meeting?
Keiichi, what is this about?
I don't know either.
But my father, who was supposed to return in 10 years, is coming back.
Something serious may have happened.
It's about time. Is President Ryuichiro really coming?
Oh!
Father!
It's just as planned.
President, it's been a while!
You're wasting your time!
I told you to stop greeting me!
But there's another reason why I was invited today.
Actually...
What's the point of ringing your phone during a meeting?
Turn off the power within 3 seconds!
Good.
Huh?
Who is it? Who hasn't turned off the power yet?
It's me. It's time to refill the nutrition drink.
Wait 15 seconds.
It's here!
Well, actually, yesterday,
a large project was submitted by the Japanese-American Commission in New York,
but
Nakagawa Group, who had never lost a single time before,
lost to Ibishi Group, its rival.
Moreover, the difference in the import and sales amount with Ibishi Group is $1,000.
It's a $100,000-dollar super-big business,
and the difference is only $1,000.
Do you understand what this means?
I-I can't believe our import and sales amount is being transferred to Ibishi Group!
That's right.
The ones in charge of the import and sales are the ones gathered here.
In other words, our job in Ibishi Group is to
transfer the information to the Japanese-American Commission.
You have to find the traitor!
N-No, I'm not!
You're suspicious because you're an Akashi!
We're the ones who have taken advantage of him!
A-Everyone, please calm down!
Shut up!
Now that a crack has entered the Ichimaiwa Nakagawa Group,
I'm going to find the traitor thoroughly!
That's all I'm going to do until I stay in Japan!
Father...
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. President!
Nakagawa.
Ah, yes. What's wrong, President?
Huh? Mr. Nakagawa, your face doesn't look good.
Well, Ryozu messed up yesterday's wedding.
Oh, no, no! The senior took care of the wedding well, and it was very exciting!
Oh, I can't believe it!
It was hard to get drunk in the end, though.
I thought so.
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning, Mr. Ryo!
You can't help it if you make a rumor.
Well, yesterday's wedding was very exciting.
Y-Yes, Senior.
Well, you can't call me "Senior" for the sake of others.
That's right! Mr. Ryo became a good friend with Ms. Nakagawa!
Oh!
The wife of my brother Kinjirou is my younger aunt's younger cousin's unmarried wife's second young man's younger brother's daughter's daughter's wife's younger brother's young man's second young lady's younger brother's daughter's younger brother's younger mom's younger daughter's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's older wife's younger sister's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger daughter's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger brother's younger daughter's younger brother's younger.
Ah...
That means Nakagawa and I are gia Arbeit.
In other words, we're going to be family in marriage.
You can't explain the distance yourself.
I'm not far away from your family.
Well, Kao, from here, I'm going to call you Kei-chan.
What?!
Kei-chan, call me Nii-san from now on.
Oh...
Ryotsu, you're not Nakagawa's brother, so you should call me Nii-san.
Chief, don't talk about your family.
Then let's do this. Call me Mr. Neighbor.
Mr. Neighbor?
Kei-chan, if you have any problems or problems, you can talk to me.
Hahaha!
Nakagawa seems to have a problem with his family.
Yes.
What's that?
It's a book about Nakagawa Group.
What's wrong?
We need to know more about Nakagawa Group, as a relative.
So as a relative, I put together the main points of the group.
That's...
He's really good at this.
Because he's Ryo-sama.
Railways, drugs, cars, and communications are growing well, but the problem is that 163 subsidiaries of real estate and securities, etc.
This is bad.
The business profit is down last year.
I don't know that either.
You can't just leave this as a relative.
No, I don't mind leaving it.
I'll get into the company and put in the money.
What?
I've saved several companies in the north town. Leave it to me.
But...
If I go to the company suddenly...
Don't worry.
I've made a name for it.
A relative?
You can tell by looking at this.
Even this?
Ryo-sama is amazing!
Right?
Nakagawa, wait.
Yes?
If you don't stimulate him, you'll have to destroy the company.
You should do as he says.
But...
You have to trick him into giving you a job that he can't do.
I see.
That's safer, isn't it?
Senpai, I've found a job I want you to do.
What company is it?
It's a company in Kachidoki.
Kachidoki?
I'm good at waiting.
Nakagawa, I'll do my best.
As a relative.
Y-yes.
You're Ryo-tsu Kankitsu, aren't you?
I heard from Keiichi-bocchan.
I'm the president, Kurokawa.
Nice to meet you.
Me too.
And my job is...
I can't do anything without you.
Yes, I'm a Superguard Storekeeper.
Superguard Storekeeper?
That sounds like a cool job.
Damn it!
What do you mean by Superguard Storekeeper?
Isn't it just a joke?
Nakagawa, you're trying to trick me.
If you want to do it, I have a plan.
What? You want to do business?
But...
Look at this.
A relative?
A relative of Nakagawa Group?
Keiichi-bocchan's just a senior.
I'm Nakagawa's great relative.
I want to rebuild this Akaji Company,
which is said to be in Nakagawa Group's luggage.
As a relative.
But Keiichi-bocchan...
Shut up! Are you still the president?
Please give me some strength.
I want to make this company the first company of Nakagawa Group.
Will you help me?
Yes.
All right.
If you do, I'll start with improving the luggage department.
First, I'll change the company name.
What?
Nakagawa Wing's Luggage Storage is a lame name.
Oh, right.
Let's make it a luggage container with a connecting eyebrow.
Hehehe.
All right, Kurokawa.
Let's get started.
Where is it?
Huh?
A relative of Nakagawa Group?
That's right.
Let me show you the evidence.
Kurokawa.
Yes.
Hmm?
Here! Here!
It must have a name, right?
I-I got it. I got it.
So, what kind of a relative do you want?
Hmm.
The president doesn't know the power of his relatives.
Hmm?
A farmer's company can't be run by the president alone.
The relatives are against it, and sometimes they can't make a decision.
I'm the one who takes care of all the relatives.
In other words, I'm the best in the shadows.
If I say I'm Kuro, the relatives will always be Kuro.
In other words, if you make me angry...
If you make me angry...
I'm scared.
Huh?
Really?
Yes.
What are you hiding?
I'm having a meal with President Ryuichiro Nakagawa when he comes back.
You're kidding, right?
I've never had a meal with President Ryuichiro.
It's not a lie.
When President Ryuichiro came back half a year ago,
we ate standing soba for 15 minutes side by side.
Oh.
President Ryuichiro is certainly busy, but he's very busy in Japan.
I heard he can't eat.
And he's been with me for 15 minutes.
That's how much I'm trusted by President Ryuichiro.
In other words, I want you to listen to me as President Ryuichiro.
I understand.
Please don't hesitate to say anything.
My relative's uncle.
Ah, I see.
Then, I will consult you about the delivery of the delivery ticket.
By all means.
Yes.
I think I can use this idiot.
Eh?
The profit of Nakagawa Omuyu Delivery Warehouse is rising?
Yes.
After changing the name of the delivery ticket of Tsunagari Mayuge,
we increased the turnover of the delivery service.
Finally, we reached 300,000 places and became the top of the industry.
It's my senior's doing.
You imported 100 million tons of grain from overseas?
Yes.
It seems that we have all the profits.
The L2 phenomenon is also declining.
It is dangerous to get into the grain from now on.
You may be President Kurokawa, but I wonder what your senior will say.
The warehouse is full of 100 million tons of wheat.
I'm sorry to say this, but the president is not in charge of our company, but the president.
The president?
Yes.
He is Ryotsu, a relative of the Nakagawa Group.
Eh?
The senior is the president?
Mr. Kurokawa.
Oh, this is the president.
Oh, I see that you're here too.
Perfect.
Look at this.
The price of wheat and corn is rising rapidly between Europe and Russia!
It's skyrocketing to the double price I bought.
Even if you look closely, it's a profit of 30 billion yen.
Hahaha.
Damn it.
I was going to give Nakagawa Group a big blow.
Well, that's how it goes.
I was really surprised by the strength of your bad luck.
But I thought Kurokawa was an unbeatable man even if he hit the stone bridge, so I made him the president of the freight company.
He has changed, too.
Everyone is doing it for the sake of the senior.
It's all because of President Kurokawa.
Then...
Keiichi, I'm going to leave the company for a while.
Eh?
I'll leave the rest to you.
Ah...
Hm?
Oh, it's time to refill the nutrition drink.
Ah, no.
I've got the usual habit.
This way.
Ah!
Hey!
I-it's over.
What?
You're quite an overbearing guy.
Nakayama-kun has been working for me since today.
Y-yes.
Nakayama, huh?
I feel like I've met him before.
I-it's our first time meeting.
I see.
You look like someone.
I remember.
Uh...
Yes.
Damn it!
He found out!
That mustache is cool.
I look like I'm going to grow fast.
Mustache?
Kurokawa, go buy some at Kappa Pashi tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Ah, this sound...
Oh, it's time to refill the nutrition drink.
Eh?
Ah...
E3
P4
Y3
Ah
There went J10.
What wrong with that face?
Huh?
Is it often in conflict of affection?
I-It's not!
As expected of a chairman,
everyone thinks you are different.
I see.
You're a pretty good guy.
It's a waste of time to leave you as garbage.
No, no.
I liked it.
Nakayama!
You do my driver.
Eh?
Yes.
This is a good opportunity.
President Ryozu.
What?
The president has earned 3 billion yen with wheat.
How about investing it in a stock market?
Sounds good. I'm in the best position right now.
Do you have any good stocks?
How about a tilt policy?
Right now, I'm not sure, but I'm sure it will go up.
I have information that it will go up.
The tilt policy is a company that is about to go bankrupt.
What do you intend to do, Kurokawa?
All right. I'll buy all of the shares with 3 billion.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
But I don't know how to invest all 3 billion.
Do you want to talk to the president?
Yes.
I understand, president.
I will contact the stock market company immediately.
I'll buy all the shares with 3 billion.
I'm counting on you.
This time, I'm going to close the company.
What?
The tilt policy is developing a special drug for water?
I can't stop laughing.
This is all thanks to Kurokawa's advice.
Kurokawa seems to have completely missed the target.
But Ryozu's bad luck is also considerable.
What?
Ryozu earned more than 10 billion yen in stock.
That's a terrible bad luck.
He made Nakagawa Group, the top profit company, grow in just one month and a half.
That's amazing.
Ryo is amazing.
No. This is the usual pattern of Ryozu.
At first, everything will go well.
But at the end, there will be a big loss.
Nakagawa, you should do it quickly.
Yes.
I thought so too, but it's too late.
I've already earned 10 billion yen and went to the United States for a talk.
But I can't get through the translation.
I have to make more and more contracts and import everything from the United States.
He can't speak English, can he?
He seems to be making a contract without saying "yes" or "no".
If it's Ryozu's determination, he seems to be able to make a contract with aliens.
It's not that much of a determination.
Thanks to him, the company's warehouse is full of junk.
He's stuck in the process of processing junk that can't be put in.
Finally, the white ant has begun to bite the pillar.
Drive for an hour.
Yes.
Ryozu will return from the United States tomorrow.
What does he want to do in Narita?
That's...
Isn't he the president of Ibishi物産?
The black ant finally has its tail.
President Ryozu, you should be back tomorrow.
Get your work done quickly.
What are you doing in a place like this?
No, nothing.
That's a camera, right?
Yes. I like photography.
I like photography, so I took a chance.
That's right. Then take me.
I wanted a portrait to hang in the president's room.
That's right, President. That's convenient.
No, it's a good idea.
Then here.
Here, here.
Yes, President. It's cool.
President, a little more to the right.
Like this?
Yes, it's okay.
It's perfect, President.
President, is that so?
It's perfect, isn't it?
After the 100,000 American cars, there's a tea mushroom in Nata and Coco.
Senior, you should stop investing in dangerous things.
What are you talking about?
The world is turning its axis around me.
But...
What? I'll double the Nakagawa Group.
I'll be a power.
As a relative.
To get a big blow to the Nakagawa Group.
And then...
President!
I-I knew it was dangerous to sell dangerous things.
Idiot!
There are advantages because no one else does it.
24 hours of business without working all year round...
What are you saying?
That's why I'm installing full automation equipment.
The advantage of the machine is that it works without rest.
But there's no time for maintenance.
If something happens to the machine, it'll be a big deal.
Don't worry. I'll take a good look at it.
I brought a fire.
It'll be a big deal if there's a fire.
Turn off the fire quickly.
It's too late, President.
Let's run away.
What?
I've earned 100 billion yen.
You did it again.
What's going to happen to Ryo?
It's such a big loss.
Of course, the Nakagawa Group will be released.
It's a serious cause of injury.
Stop it.
Hey, Kanzaki!
Shou, just sit down.
I'll wait until you get to the president's desk.
But regarding this case, the blame doesn't matter.
But the накagawa group's name...
More importantly, a traitor found out thanks to you.
What?
Who are you?
The traitor is...
him!
It's him!
Huh?
Satsuo, stop making bad jokes!
What's the basis for that?
Here's the basis!
Huh? What's that?
Kurokawa went back to the Ibishi group
and organized the next major incident.
It's a mess!
Are you still going to cut the shira!?
Hey! Driver!
Damn it...
What?
Kurokawa!
The headquarters and the special dispatch are both here!
The cannon is being sent out.
Do you want to come with us?
This is a piece of cake!
Wow, you saved me, Ryu-chan!
Ryu-chan?
I look forward to working with you as my relative.
Relative?
I've never heard of that.
Huh? You weren't his relative?
What did you say?
No, I mean,
my brother's...
My brother's wife is the son of the sister of the old woman in Nakagawa's...
Huh? Time's up.
Ah!
Well then, we'll meet again in ten years!
Farewell!
Dad!
Take care!
Kei-chan.
Hm?
As your relative, would you introduce me to someone?
As long as my father doesn't recognize me as a relative, that's a little...
Kei-chan!
That's a sure thing to do...
Hey, wait.
Don't run away, everyone!
You're my relative, aren't you?!
I know you're cold, but as a relative, you're econesic...!
In Ag cottage
In Ak cottage
Woah...
Surprised.
No.
Shaking.
Tired.
♪ The last energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday ♩
♪ Draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ The planet of the turtle will turn into a circle ♩
♪ This is good, right? ♩
♪ There is no excuse, right? ♩
Next time
It's you again, Professor Tondemo!
What?
You sent a video that you need for tomorrow's lecture
to someone of your daughter by mistake?
I don't care, but why are your daughters in such a place?
Next time, "48 Hours World Tour"!
See you!
"48 Hours World Tour"