Last
"The
When watching TV, make the room bright and look away.
If you don't have money, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky.
White clouds
I wonder what will happen.
I know.
I know. I know.
If you understand, come to me quietly!
Look at the blue sky.
"The
It's all done.
It's a unique job for a senior.
But it's not enough to make you get older.
We have to find another part-time job.
Ryo-san is the type who uses as much as he can and gets to the last minute.
Leave it alone.
That's right.
Ryo-chan is busy looking for people.
I think that's part-time job that Ryo-chan's cleverness can make.
Really? I'm not going to be lazy.
Introduce me.
Yes, but there's something I want you to do instead.
Good morning.
Chief.
I'm not working.
You're not working?
No, it's nothing.
It's about me.
Anyway, you've asked me to do something, haven't you?
What was it?
What's that look on your face?
Did you forget?
No, I didn't.
Ryo-san, Chief.
I'm going to give you a hand-made hand-made model for your granddaughter.
Oh, I see.
Of course, I won't forget anything.
Leave it to me.
Daisuke loves the ship.
I'm really looking forward to it.
You must keep your promise.
I know.
Please trust me.
I'm going to make Ryo-san a part-time job.
From today to the Christmas Eve of the actual show,
I can become a one-man cake chef.
You can do it all by yourself.
How about it?
Will it be a one-man job in a week?
Ryo-san.
Yes, please.
First of all, the basics of cake.
Making meringue.
I'll mix it with this.
Easy peasy.
No, no.
Faster.
Like this?
It's still too late.
Damn it.
Let me hear the snap of your wrist.
What is it?
Faster, rhythmically.
I'm going to do it.
No, no, no, no.
That's right.
You're stupid.
What are you going to do with all of them?
Sorry.
Can't be helped.
Use an electric mixer.
Let me do it from the beginning.
How is it?
Oh, it's good for the first time.
Right?
I made something like this.
It's a Japanese-style cake.
A Japanese-style cake?
Yes.
I arranged plum and shishamo and shumai.
I put miso on the whole instead of cream.
And when I cut it,
it's a natto sandwich.
How can this be sold?
Next is this.
Curry cake.
What?
I'll put real curry on it.
Curry?
Yes.
I'll put yakisoba inside.
I'll put curry on it.
You can taste both curry and yakisoba.
No.
And.
Sushi cake.
I'll put sushi on the chocolate eclair.
Not only for Christmas and birthdays,
but also for a year.
The cake will sell.
No, no, no.
How can it sell?
I knew it.
Then.
How about this?
This is a decent cake.
It looks good.
But if you put this on the cake one by one,
the fireworks will go up.
The fireworks can go up to rocket fireworks.
Maybe I can make it.
Right?
Leave it to me.
Now,
if you put this one by one,
you can enjoy Christmas with your family.
Please enjoy the fireworks cake.
Please give me that.
Me, too.
Yes, please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I didn't expect it to sell so well.
Thanks to Ryo,
a special bonus will come out.
Ryo, Ryo,
I heard the popularity of fireworks cake,
and I got an amazing order.
Make a 10-meter-high cake
for the garden party.
Really?
I was surprised.
This is what I said.
And next.
Please give me two fireworks cakes.
Two.
Two further.
I will pay for him.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'll have two fireworks cakes, too.
Oh, Ryou.
Ryo, you are so popular.
Very.
I heard it from Chief.
He said he improved the cake making skill too.
I gave it to you.
Well, well.
Ryo-chan, I told you I wanted you to help me.
I did.
What can I help you with?
Making cakes.
Cakes?
Yes, on the day of the event.
I introduced you to the cake shop, but you didn't do it?
As you wanted.
Ryo-chan mastered making cakes in a short time.
Well, if you have the kindness of my hands, then I can do it.
Right? So help me on the day of the event.
I got it.
Instead, give me a part-time job.
I'm a professional, after all.
I know.
This is Ryo-chan's husband.
It's a cake shop that's working part-time!
Eve and Otohime are on a date, right?
Yes.
Nana-chan forced me to open the serial schedule.
So I had to enjoy it.
I'm sorry.
I have to give you a special treat, so I have to give you a special treat.
I wonder what's better.
After all, it's better to keep the standard, right?
There's no such thing as a course like that on the magazine.
It's like going to see a couple.
Is that so?
Then, is there another unique course?
Leave it to me.
I'll teach you where to get a good mood with just the two of you.
Really?
Senior, thank you.
It's delicious.
Okay, it's over.
The day is over.
To the amusement park with Eve?
That's right.
I was told that they don't take me anywhere every year.
This year, I'll go.
Ryo, you know what I mean, right?
If you go somewhere, I wonder if the children will be happy.
Tell me.
That's right.
I have a feeling.
If you go with me, the admission fee will be free.
Really?
That's great.
I'm counting on you, Ryo.
Leave it to me.
Chief, please come to the Christmas party at my company.
Please come with your grandchildren.
Oh, that's boring.
No, I'll be glad to participate.
Reiko, too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm a little bad at Eve.
By the way, you said you were busy at Christmas Eve every year, right?
That's right.
I have something to do.
I'm sorry.
It's a shame.
This year, I'll go to the garden at the company.
I'm going to prepare a special cake with a height of 10 meters.
Oh, that's great.
Is Mr. Terai okay?
It's a shame, but I'm going to the amusement park with the children this year.
It can't be helped if it's a family service.
Reiko's help for the cake shop part-time job.
I have to put the Terai family in the amusement park.
It's a party in the middle of the night.
This is enough for me to have a lot of body.
I'll do it with the help of the family.
Well, I'm sorry.
I hope you don't mind.
It's a pity.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the amusement park.
It's a shame, but I'll have a lot of body.
It's a shame.
I'm sorry.
I'll go to the amusement park.
I don't want to go.
I have to go.
Good bye!
Looks like we'll be able to get in by the evening.
Ryo-san, are you ready to set up the fireworks?
Leave it to me. I'll go set it up before I decorate it.
All that's left is to put this switch in and it's done.
It's done.
If I put in 10 pieces, I'll get one of them.
Now, should I get going?
I have to go to Reiko's after this.
I'm so lazy that I can't sleep at night.
Oh, I see. This is inside the cake.
If only I could sleep for a little bit...
Mmm, it's good!
I'll go to bed now.
Okay, there's no one here.
Okay!
Good!
Let's go!
Hurry up! We won't make it by the evening!
Alright, we have all the materials.
Now let's all do our best again this year!
Now we've finally got 20 of them.
It's noon.
Ryo-chan did say that in the morning she'd be coming.
Huh?
Reiko-san!
What are you doing?
Making Christmas cakes!
That went MICHEAL!
I thought it would smell like something.
But why are you here?
My home is under renovation.
So I'm using this place.
I have to make 200 of them today.
200?
Reiko, alone?
Yeah.
Ryo-chan was supposed to help me.
She's a bit drunk, isn't she?
You can't trust someone like that.
Huh? Reiko, your face is a little red.
Yeah, I think I'm a little hot.
Then we'll help you.
Okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
Reiko, what should we do?
Let's start with the BUSHED NOEL's dough.
Let's make it more and more complete.
This one.
BUSHED NOEL.
I think they decorate it and then roll it up like seaweed.
How do you deco...
Reiko!
Are you okay?
I'm so hot.
I have to go to the ambulance.
Okay.
I have to deliver the cake.
It's a big deal.
It's a very important cake.
But where can I deliver 200 of them?
Huh?
This is...
Dahlia's old home, 37.
Santa Maria's private hospital, 40.
That's...
Right.
Reiko wanted to deliver the cake where it's written on this note.
Right. Reiko wanted to deliver the cake where it's written on this note.
Right.
Reiko wanted to deliver the cake where it's written on this note.
What are we going to do with the cake?
We have to do it ourselves.
The recipe Reiko wrote should be somewhere.
We can make it based on that.
Right.
It's a day of Ibu, but it's overflowing.
Let's send a dispatch to the traffic police.
Reiko, don't worry about the cake.
We'll do something about it.
Christmas presents.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ibu, Ibu says it's empty even if it's a temple.
It must be empty, but is that all right?
Mr. Honda is numb.
Me, too.
I can't eat it anymore.
I'm coming.
Hi, Bobby!
Jodie!
Long time no see!
Thank you for saving me!
Ryo is missing.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, everyone!
As expected of the "all of us"
You guys wait outside!
Now let's start.
Papa, make the "no need" part thinner!
You're good, Scott!
Maria, how is Reiko-san?
She seems to have a bad temper.
It seems that her health has improved a little after being beaten.
I'm in trouble. I don't know about this.
What's wrong?
I can't read the details of Reiko-san's recipe in foreign languages.
It's not English. It's French.
I don't know unless I write this myself.
But Reiko-san is in the hospital.
Yes, that's right.
Then, can you put cocoa in the whipped cream?
Like this?
Okay. Then, mix it.
Okay.
It's too late, Reiko-san.
I said it's just here.
Papa, come on in.
Let's go in.
Let's do that.
It's getting crowded.
Yes.
Can't you catch it?
Are you okay, Honda-san?
I'm okay.
It's okay. You should be careful not to catch a cold.
Okay.
It's a date course as the guidebook says.
Senpai.
It's a grand party.
By the way, have you seen Ryotsu?
No. It's strange.
He said he would come as soon as I finished the deal with Reiko-san.
He promised Daisuke a present.
Grandpa, it's delicious.
Oh, is that so?
That's strange.
Senpai shouldn't be caught by food.
I prepared roast beef for Senpai.
I made 200 cakes.
I made 2000 cakes.
I repeated everything.
I sprayed a lot of powder.
Look at them.
Are you okay?
Good job!
Thank you, everyone.
I just have to deliver the cake.
But all therophiles are scattered all over the place.
Will we be in time?
No worries.
I'll use
Let's go!
I'm going to go!
If you insert this sword into the cake and touch the switch inside,
the rocket-type fireworks will fire!
The person who hits it perfectly will be given the cake!
Wow, what a great ship!
It looks much better than any of the others.
Then, let's start with the first entry.
Please check the number card you have.
The first entry is this!
Number 214!
Number 214...
It's wrong.
Me too!
That's too bad.
I got it!
Yes!
Congratulations!
Then, take the sword you like and insert it into the cake!
I slept well...
Oh no! It's completely blocked!
Everyone must be worried outside.
I made an appointment with the chief and Reiko.
And I also made an appointment with the temple priest.
That's too bad.
Next!
Number 75!
It's the poor man.
Number 175!
Grandpa, I've forgotten it too!
Let's see if I can hit the sword next time!
Yes!
Th-This is...
größе!
Have I been taken to the seaside?!
Stop! Someone is here!
Stop!
Please stop it!
If this happens, I must eat all the cake and get out of town!
What the hell is this?
Why do I have to do this?
My whole body is shaking.
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
I have to get out of here.
I got it wrong again.
Please guess the next one.
The next number is...
It's Christmas, so I made the helicopter look like Santa Claus.
You painted it red?
Bobby.
Why don't you put on a bell?
I really look like Santa Claus.
I got it wrong again.
You're not good at switching.
That's true.
But you're not coming.
I always keep my promises.
That's how it is.
What's that sound?
That's...
Santa Claus!
Merry Christmas!
It's not Rieko this year.
It's the PG Hitter!
Wow, that's amazing!
Ryo, this time is...
I was told to get on the Ferris wheel, but is there something wrong?
Rieko, you finished the delivery.
Thank you, everyone.
Rieko, please rest.
Tonight, we'll be on the way out for you and Rieko.
It's Christmas, but it's not a good idea.
We'll have a mini party together!
The next number is number 175.
Yes! I finally got it!
Grandpa, you're amazing!
You did it.
Yes! Number 175.
Congratulations.
Now, will you be able to hit the rocket-shaped fireworks switch?
If you do, all these luxurious gifts will be yours.
Now, please.
I'll do it.
I'll take a half-shape for Daisuke.
Nana, I'm sorry.
I dragged you around so much today.
It wasn't fun at all, was it?
No, it wasn't.
I was happy to spend Christmas Eve with Honda-san.
Nana...
With the schedule you set,
I wonder if there's anything else...
Today was tough.
But it was a comfortable day.
Let's have some coffee.
What?
That's the half-shape I made for the president's granddaughter.
Shit! I didn't have to eat anything!
I did it! I'm out!
What? It's my old place, isn't it?
Shit!
I did it!
Ahhh!
Ahhhhhhh!
Merry Christmas, Ryozu.
Ah!
It's so beautiful!
This is what Ryou-san said!
So this is what you were talking about.
You're welcome to come.
Ah, it's snowing!
Papa, this is the first time I've seen a Christmas like this!
So pretty...
I wanted to show you this, so I planned to come here.
Hold my hand!
That's too bold.
It's perfect.
A winter Christmas on a fireworks show.
Nana-chan.
Okay.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Honda-san.
Nana-chan.
Thank you, senpai.
Here, it's from Ryo-sama.
Wow! This is the second one in a row!
Why am I the only one who hates Christmas so much!
What?
The night after the rain that seems to be calling someone
I walked while looking back
I walked home
My mother waved her hand
At that time, I felt
A strange feeling
So
I tried to walk
On the Ake-do-gai tile
That was black
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgot
Politicians with great faces
And blue-haired old ladies
Turn around and look
At that corner
You'll see everyone
Let's go
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Yes
Everyone, come
To our town
Thank you!