Translated by Shion
I watch the rising sun in the middle of the river
When I kick the stone, it flies to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I used to go to
I was laughed at for being a naughty boy
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, it's a pity that I can't
The cityscape that doesn't change a single yawn is strangely kind
From the stream of the Tungari Boshi
To the Kaishaku Tengen, the sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness because of the Katsushika Shiba
I realized that I was a fool
Because I was a fool
Ryouzu Kankichi
You bastard!
I'm sorry
Ryou
Maria! Catch him!
How dare you!
Forgive me!
Yes, Mr. Ryou!
Get away, you bastard!
You're tough, Maria!
It's a pleasure to help you
Ryou, who is this?
He is a wedding thief
I was at the Asakusa's childhood friend's wedding, and I was caught.
So you're wearing a wedding dress, too?
It's wonderful!
Yeah, it's hard to go.
What are you doing with a Japanese dress?
I'm going home to the tea party.
You look good in it.
I'm happy, Ryo-sama!
Stop it in front of me!
I'm embarrassed to go home with this kimono.
You can't wear it?
Yes.
What should I do?
My parents live nearby.
I'll ask my mother to fix it.
You can meet your mother?
That's great!
I'm not going to.
Let me say hello to your parents.
What are you talking about?
I'm just going to fix my dress.
You're going to?
No.
I'm not going.
You're not going?
No!
Don't say that!
My parents live in Tsukudaniya.
Hey, it's me!
Are you there?
I can't believe you're opening a shop.
Do you have money here?
You forgot to pay the deposit.
What are you thinking?
It's a troublesome place, so get out of here.
I see.
Hey, father!
And mother!
You left the pot on the stove.
Ryo?
Yes?
The customer...
Oh, it's you, Kan-chan.
Hey, aunt.
Long time no see.
Oh, no.
Leave it to me.
Okay.
You quit your job and came back to the shop?
Yeah.
Just today.
200g is this much?
It's a little extra.
Nice service.
How much?
What?
It's not written anywhere.
I'm in trouble.
100 yen is fine.
Really?
Yeah.
It's a service today.
It's a shop that I'm doing as a hobby.
Even if it's broken, it doesn't matter.
Then 100 yen.
Thanks.
Kan-chan, the person in the dress earlier,
is she your wife?
No, no.
You're a fool again.
Hello.
Long time no see.
You look like a silverfish.
You're still alive.
Are you still alive?
You're still talking about yourself.
Did you become a cartwheel and go back to the store?
No, today...
Kan-chan is getting married.
Really?
No, no.
It's a coincidence.
Good.
I thought I wouldn't be able to marry for the rest of my life.
So I'm not.
I'm done here.
I'll take care of you.
You're a little over the top.
How did you deceive me?
That's mean.
I mean...
It's so hot!
Really, really hot!
What would you like?
300g of clams.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Ryo-sama, how much is this?
It's 100 yen for today.
Okay, 100 yen.
That's a good service.
It's different from Gin-san.
Really, really!
If it's so cheap, I'll take this and this.
Oh, right.
Kan-chan, when Gin-san returns,
tell him that the next trip to the Kero-kai
is decided on June 29th.
June 29th, okay.
Okay, good luck.
I'm so happy that I didn't have to go to the first class.
Gin-san, Gin-san!
Huh?
I'm glad Segare-san found a good wife.
What is that old woman saying?
What is it?
Huh?
Welcome.
What would you like?
I'd like a pot of inago-tsukuda.
Okay.
Are you free tonight?
If you're free,
why don't you and I go to the Kawasaki Kepa-jo night race?
Oh, Dad!
Huh?
Kankichi!
Why are you shopping at your own shop?
Geez!
You met him for the first time, didn't you?
Everyone in my office calls you Maria.
Dad, nice to meet you.
Oh, me too.
By the way, Kankichi,
what's wrong with Mom?
Listen to me.
The shop was empty.
Oh, you're late.
Oh!
Oh, I'm home.
Kankichi!
Come back home!
Mom!
I'm so happy!
Stop it.
Where have you been?
I was shopping.
If you get to the shop,
I'll ask you to help me get my kimono.
I know.
Hey, Maido!
Dad, Dad!
Who's that cute girl?
She's Shono's colleague.
Rumor has it that she's Kankichi's...
Oh, I see.
I knew it!
She's so cute that I can't help but ask her.
I'm sure she's cute.
Mom, are you done?
I'm almost done.
All right.
This is enough.
Thank you.
By the way,
do you like Kankichi?
Yes, of course.
It's not a dream.
Hey, Dad!
Come here!
Why?
Dad, you know...
What?
Mom, I'm serious.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you like him,
it's 100% sure.
I'm sure he's determined to take over this shop.
As expected of the eldest son.
He's thinking about what's ahead.
Ms. Maria,
I'm counting on you to take care of Kankichi.
Please.
I'm counting on you.
Please, take care of him.
Why are you saying that?
Maria,
if you're done, let's go.
We're going to send you to Sensoji.
That's right.
Come on.
Yes.
See you.
Thank you.
I'll be back.
Yes.
Oh, I forgot.
Kankichi,
did you decide on the date?
What?
I decided on June 29th.
Oh, June 29th.
Is that so?
You're a big guy.
I always decide when I have to.
Mom,
let's say goodbye with "Banzai."
Yes.
"Banzai!"
Stop it.
It's disgusting.
Maria, let's go.
Yes.
"Banzai!"
You're so lucky.
Yes.
You're so happy that you've decided to go on a trip alone.
That idiot.
What's her name?
Maria.
"Maria"
"Maria".
Maria.
How about this?
Here you go, father.
How does it taste, father?
It's delicious.
How about this?
How does it taste, father?
It's very nice.
I'll have some more.
And I started to help Tsukuda.
Father, can I have a taste?
Stop!
It's not as good as the 300 years of Ryotsuke.
It's still too sweet.
I'm sorry, father.
Don't cry, Maria.
The road to Tsukudani is long and steep.
Let's go step by step.
Father!
All right.
I'm done!
Life changes when a girl is born.
I don't like it when you smile alone.
If only she was a good mother and daughter.
Sure you do.
This means to us that the number of customers increases.
Good morning!
The wedding of Segare Muray Messi has been decided.
Let's celebrate from the inside out.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Gin finally feel better, doesn't it?
My mother finally escaped.
You, father.
Mr. Segare finally decided to work hard.
I've been looking forward to it since yesterday.
I know, Yoni.
Mother!
That Kan-kichi is finally getting married?
Well, if you think about it, he's only five years old.
He's been a destroyer for decades.
He's finally getting married to that evil woman.
If you're ready, please make sure to cry.
All right, I'll make sure to make that day come true.
Thank you very much!
The garden will be given to that phoenix.
What?
Wow!
Gin! Gin!
What's wrong?
It's a big deal.
They're going to hold a wedding parade at the store.
This is going to be a blast!
All right, I'll do it!
That's great!
Thank you!
Well, that's about it for today.
I hope you enjoyed it.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
Subtitles by Subdiver
Huh?
What happened?
Hey, Ryosu!
Why were you hiding from me about your wedding?
Huh?
What?
Your senior is getting married?
No way...
You're kidding, right?
Your father called me yesterday since the wedding day!
W-Wait a minute!
Who are you marrying?
I didn't ask him in detail, but the beautiful woman in Japanese clothes came to say hello to you last week!
I'm not going with the beautiful woman!
Huh?
Maybe...
Maybe what?
No, I went to my parents' house with Maria the other day.
What?
Haha, that's right!
After I introduced Maria, I was very rude!
What did you say?
It's hard, manager!
Didn't you say you were a man?
Come to think of it, I forgot to say that...
He must have been mistaken for a fiancee.
Then are we getting married?
Oh, I'm so happy!
Hey, wait!
That's not the way to do it!
We're both men!
That's right.
If you miss this day, you can't get married for the rest of your life.
Leave me alone!
But I'm in trouble because I'm in contact with the manager!
Maria, come with me for a while!
Okay!
Manager, I'll take the bus!
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah.
Asakusa! Asakusa, go!
Uh, this isn't a taxi, but...
If you say go, I'll go!
Ah, yeah!
Oh, come on, deal with it!
I got it.
Come on, deal with it!
I'll go now.
I'll go now!
I'll go!
Um, I was just speaking with your friend!
A friend?
My friend?
I didn't know there was such a thing as a friend.
This place is...
This place is my childhood friend.
Yes, Kankichi is the eldest son.
It's not a big deal.
But 5 hours is a bit...
Why don't you take a break for 10 minutes?
Like a big movie.
That's a good idea.
The budget will be quite expensive, but...
How much is it all?
It's already over 10 million yen.
What?
Do we have so much savings?
There's no way.
I know.
We didn't even think about marriage.
We didn't think about marriage.
Don't worry.
We can get 1000 people to join the wedding.
Yeah.
It's 30,000 yen per person, right?
It's 30 million yen per 1000 people.
If we raise the budget, we'll make 20 million yen.
I see.
As expected of you, old man.
The more you call, the more budget you have.
Hahaha.
We have a budget, so let's make the budget more flashy.
How about a parade in Asakusa in 5 minutes?
That's a good idea.
We can do a three-way carnival.
It'll be so much fun!
How about a parade on the Sumida River?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Let's call 500 people and have a party!
The ceremony will be held at midnight.
It's a 24-hour wedding.
That's a good idea.
What's this?
Oh, shit.
You're already doing business, aren't you?
You're making a festival.
You even made a signboard.
You're so good at the wedding.
You don't even know how to put it on the signboard.
You do it everywhere.
Whenever you see a signboard, you like to call it Mr. Ryo.
That's the lady who got a bardziej?
The
You..
You're funny, isn't it?
Shut up!
What's wrong with you?
Do you know where our parents are?
I guess it's the Gachon Museum in the Gachon Temple.
You're not the only one who has a rang-up.
Not even Mr. Ryo has one?
Not even Mr. Mr. Ryo has one?
What?
Not even Mr. Ryo has one?
Coven went out.
Good!
It's the appearance of the man you want to know!
Uh.
That's right!
Put this on!
With that in mind.
The size is just right.
The new work come to the school is okay.
At least it's a five-hour wedding.
It's boring to have so many changes.
My father has to talk to you.
Yeah.
What is it?
Maria is here too?
I have to introduce you to everyone.
Dad, when will I get married?
Don't be stupid.
What are you talking about?
I told you that the date was decided on June 29th.
June 29th?
That's the date of the trip to Keirokai.
What?
You misunderstood me.
But I'm going to marry her.
You can't do that.
Maria is a man.
You're kidding me.
That's ridiculous.
Then check it out yourself.
No.
This is...
It's a lie.
It's not true.
You still don't get it?
What is this?
It's the same thing as your father.
You see, the person you love is not in love with him.
This is more like it.
Maybe...
You have to stop it.
He's in love with you.
I'm not.
Get out of my way.
Don't worry about that.
Don't say that.
You'll get married soon enough.
So...
Get away.
I know you're crying.
The wedding is already decided.
You're the one who decided it.
I didn't say it was wrong.
What are you going to do?
I don't know that.
I don't care if you're a man or not.
Get married.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're giving up on the 30 million yen of the wedding?
What?
Oh, shit.
You're trying to make money at my wedding.
Let me go.
What are you doing?
It's still in the middle of the meeting.
It's nothing.
I'll be there soon.
I see.
So how much will you make with the expenses?
You don't say.
Yeah.
We can't quit either way.
It's been so exciting.
I can't help it.
Let's get it done at this point and get the ceremony.
We can make a lot of money.
But if we get caught, it'll be a big deal.
Don't worry.
I'll get it done.
I'm always ready to help you.
Absolutely.
Thanks.
See you later.
You're so sweet.
You almost did.
See you.
Bye.
Wait.
I've got something to tell.
What?
We will now head to the venue.
It's all thanks to all of you that we got married like this.
I wonder if it's really okay.
Don't worry, we've got our hands on it.
Everyone in Gocho,
I'm Ryosu Gan-nichi, the one who makes noise every time.
As expected of Kan-chan!
Sanja Festival, Sanba Carnival, and the fireworks festival.
It's going to be a big event.
Look, they're even broadcasting it on TV.
That's right! They're going to keep on moving!
They're going to take the house!
The cars will go to the shopping street and enter the Gachon Temple.
Here, the Gachon Temple is a place where thousands of people can be gathered.
It's faster than the time of the year.
Let's start with the banquet.
In reaching the Gachon Temple, the
івa-ko many of us got together.
They're getting excited!
- Awww!
Ahhh, I'm so happy!
So, Kan Zoom, can't be here any more?
Aㅏㅏㅏㅏㅏㅏ
Excuse me, everyone!
This was all a surprise!
Surprise?
Oh, indeed, I got a little tricked!
You guys are good at fooling me.
I can't marry you.
You guys fooled me.
I was surprised.
You are all lying.
What are you thinking?
I'm not going to lose.
It was a good chance for us to meet.
Don't fool me.
You guys are good at fooling me.
You guys are all lying.
I'm sorry.
Did you fool me?
Mr. Ju.
He's unconscious.
I'll pay you back.
No. I won't pay you back.
I caught a thief the other day.
I failed to leave it to him.
I don't know.
Mom, let's go home.
I can't believe he's a snob.
Dad, let's go home.
Let's go home.
I can't.
I won't pay you back.
I can't pay you back.
I won't.
A ten-year-old policeman from the police station will come to the police station?
Leave it to me.
I take care of you.
You won't be embarrassed.
I'll teach you to be a policeman.
Kyo-san's Newcomer Training.
I look forward to working with you!
♪ I hear rumors that I'm a woman who can't fall in love ♩
♪ But there are so many things I want to do ♩
♪ I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle ♩
♪ I want to be free like a bird ♩
♪ A lady's dream that changes at the speed of a telescope ♩
♪ I want to love ♩
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♩
♪ The future of the panorama is so bright ♩
♪ You understand, right? I'm sorry, wait for me ♩
♪ I want to be free like a bird ♩
♪ I want to love ♩