"It's time for my sister and I to meet"
There comes a day that floats on the ocean
I look at the sunset floating in the deep sea
When I kicked the love stone, it flew to the shoes
I wonder if it's a joke
I laughed as it was
Even if I'm in good health, I have a bad luck
The cityscape that doesn't change even a single nightmare is very gentle
From the water tank of the Tungari Boshi
The sun sets to the sea
Tomorrow will end like this
The happiness of the Katsushika Shiba Mata
I realized it after losing it
Because I'm stupid
"Hondara's Alternative Facts"
It's a nice day
I want to go to work, take a lunch and go for a drive
If the running is not good, it's the driver who drives
Is true
I think so too
Yeah, when I thought you were running around,
I thought you were driving a Honda.
You're right!
Handling on!
Ah...
How is it? Is it good?
Yeah, it's good!
It's a great combination!
Oh, that's good!
Here, one more bite.
What do you mean, "Ahh"?!
It's obvious from the card!
There's something embarrassing about it.
Why do you have a wife like Kyoko in such a weird man?
She's not as young and beautiful as Maria's mother,
and she's very stylish, and she's a professional cook.
Ah, I'm getting hungry just by looking at her.
Nakagawa, put her next to me.
Yes, but what?
I'll teach you instead of Ten.
Darling, say "Ahh" to me.
Ahh...
What?
I'm sorry. Who is it?
If you're going to be so nervous, do it at home.
What?
It's been a while, Ryo.
Kyoko, how do you like this?
Ryo, how about a bite?
Me, too?
Then, no problem.
Senpai!
Yes?
I'll pay you back.
Ah...
Darling, be careful!
Sorry, my hand slipped a little.
Ryo!
Stop it, Nakagawa!
Senpai, are you okay?
I'm not okay!
I'm sorry, Ryo!
See you later!
Hey, you did it on purpose, didn't you?
You're too late!
Damn it!
I'll make you pay for this, Dad!
Watch me!
Honey, I'm going to the dorm.
I'm going to the dinner party, too.
I'll go shopping and go by night, darling.
I'm looking forward to the criminal's cooking.
A dorm full of women?
Isn't that MD?
What are you going to do with that?
Well, you'll see.
Mom, it's me, Zeon!
Yes, it's Kyoko.
Hey, lady, it's me.
Oh, Ryo!
I'm sorry about yesterday.
No, it's nothing.
By the way, what are you doing now?
Well, darling is going to the dorm from today,
so I'm going to buy some food.
Then, it's the Shimonoseki Fugu.
Fugu?
Don't you know?
All the fighters in the fighting team eat Shimonoseki Fugu
and get stronger.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I have to go to Shimonoseki and get it right away.
Thank you, Ryo.
You're welcome.
I'm glad to hear that, darling.
Oh, by the way,
which hand do you use when you shake hands?
Right hand.
Oh.
Which hand do you use when you throw a Southpaw?
Left hand.
But why do you ask me that?
Oh, I forgot.
By the way, lady,
do you love me?
Of course. I love you.
What do Kawa and Furui do?
Oh, they jump into the pool.
That's right.
Which hand do you use for baseball?
What are they up to?
What's that?
I collected only the voices of Kyoko-san on the phone just now,
put a number on it, and edited it.
What are you going to do?
For example, if you combine 4, 5, and 9...
I love you, Ryo-san.
Oh, we're talking properly.
Because it's MD, you can get your head out of anywhere.
You can take out any part of the conversation and combine it,
and it's digital recording, so your voice is real, right?
Yes.
Say something, Nagagawa.
Huh?
Um...
Hello, lady.
Okay.
16, 14.
Oh, hello.
How about your husband?
6, 15, 8.
Who?
Well, he's fine.
Wow, the timing is perfect.
Right?
I'll take revenge on that hondara dad with this.
You tell him.
F ries un hondara dad has a changed outfit,
In order to pass the international martial arts competition,
there are only two types of hondara dogs:
The hondara mice that can crawling through the ground,
as well as those who can come to the west beyond the horizon or beyond the planche,
or the hondara mice that can walk above the horizon,
So,
your homies must be hondaras,
if you are a typical hondara dog,
Yes, sir.
In that case, you'd better forget about your lover and your family during the gathering.
It's a phone call from the madam.
What? From Honey?
♪Ran, ran, ran, ran, ran, ran, ran♪
What?
Hey, Honey! I was so lonely!
Oh, boy.
6, 5, 4, 12...
Darling, we're almost there.
You're a lot faster than we thought, Honey.
I want to meet Darling as soon as possible!
What's wrong, Honey?
You seem to be in a different mood from usual.
Oh, no.
It's nothing.
Fugu!
What? Fugu?
Oh, no. I mispronounced.
Is Fugu Andy Fugu?
At times like this, it's 16, 16, 16...
I love you, Darling.
Oh, I see.
You're saying that Fugu is nothing.
Leave it to me.
I'm sure I'll win the International Fugue Championship!
Oh, well.
I guess...
I'm sorry to have fooled you.
All right. Next up is...
The New Fugue Championship
This time, several new members will participate.
Let's teach them a new technique.
You go first!
Huh? Me?
Then, out of the 999 special techniques of the Hondara sword,
number 773, the Gokinokken!
Whoa!
That technique!
Take a walk.
Y-Yes.
What's the Gokinokken?
What kind of technique is it?
Take a good look at the Gokinokken.
I... I...
It's a bad Gokiburi!
Look closely. It's just a toy.
But even a big man is not good at Gokiburi.
He'll pay for it when he's in panic.
This is the Gokinokken.
You're making up the most ridiculous excuse, and you're still playing the cheater.
Next up is...
The 7th special technique of the Hondara sword, number 774, the Inunoken!
All right!
Take this, Inunoken!
You're going to get beaten with the same hand!
That's the real thing!
What?
You got a problem?
Ugh!
Whoa!
That was just a toy.
But sometimes, you can use the real thing, so you have to be careful.
You're not going to stop me, are you?
Oh, I'll do it like this.
The next strategy is...
It's the original element of ever-changing love.
Hey, darling?
I know you're in here, honey.
What are you doing? Get over here!
Because I'm much better at this.
I'm so embarrassed. You're right here.
How come, honey?
Darling, raise your right hand.
Huh? Right?
Right here?
Bend your wrist.
Oh, right here?
Put your right leg in front of your chest.
Put your right leg in front of your knees.
Like this?
Yes!
It really looks like Yami.
Darling, put your left leg up too.
My left leg?
My head!
I can't hold it in!
He's such an idiot.
Next.
Darling, can you get me the flowers on the top?
Flowers?
That one?
But how can I climb that high?
I love you, darling!
Okay, Johan. I'll give it a try.
Okay!
He's so slow!
He's climbing!
He's really fast!
He's climbing.
It's not funny if he doesn't fall.
If this happens...
Darling, it's wonderful!
Are you serious, honey?
It's almost done!
He's so fast!
He's really fast!
That's fantastic, Johan!
I'm so glad I took this video!
I'm so glad I took it, MD!
Darling, jump down from here this time!
Don't be ridiculous.
I love you, darling!
I'll get angry! Hurry up!
Okay!
Give it up for Johan!
I love you!
I love you, Johan!
Darling, jump into the fire this time.
What?
I think I'm a little too stylish.
I love you, darling. I love you, darling. I love you, darling.
I'm going to get angry. Hurry up!
Yes, ma'am!
I'm tired of staying in the same dorm today.
You were so cool, darling.
I know, honey.
You should come here, too.
No!
Don't!
I went to the Shimonoseki to buy some fugu, but I was late.
Darling must be tired of waiting.
Honey, come here.
No!
What?
Don't!
No!
Show me your face!
I'm at my limit!
Darling!
What?
Why are you here?
Who's that woman?
It's you!
We've been talking about you!
Don't lie!
You're in this room!
Huh?
She's not here!
Of course not!
I just came here.
But you were with me all day today.
You were wearing a jacket.
No, I wasn't, honey!
Who are you?
Huh?
It's you!
What?
I was all alone.
It was dangerous.
Let's leave now.
What?
You two?
Good evening.
I guess everyone is your staff, huh?
Hey, let go of my beard!
Let go of me?
I'm not going anywhere!
You can go down!
Because I'm going down three times!
My house!
Why did you take me?
What did you do to me?
Thanks to you, Darling's students are doing great.
If this goes on, Darling won't be able to participate in the International Criminal Law Competition.
I'm in trouble, Ryo-san.
There's no other way. I'll participate as a student instead.
Really, Ryo-san?
The problem is not that.
The problem is this beard!
Beard? A beard will grow in a month.
That beard is not growing on its own.
That beard is growing on its own.
It's a "beard of happiness"!
A beard of happiness? What's that?
I hope nothing bad happens to me.
Is there anything wrong with shaving your beard?
Recently, I dropped one of my beards by mistake.
A few days later, I fell in love with my wife and became a woman.
Before that, I was in trouble with the bubble collapse and the Heisei rice riots.
All kinds of misfortunes happened when I dropped this beard.
Isn't that a "beard of misfortune" not a "beard of happiness"?
No.
My husband is a buddhist,
He was the one who raised me up,
And we got married,
Because I started to grow a beard of happiness.
Hmm.
I hope nothing bad happens to us at the International Law Conference...
The 117th International Law Conference is now on.
Now, let me hear a speech from the head of the Chinese department, Mr. Chou Nengten.
I am Chou Nengten, Reine.
What? Darling, you're not here yet?
I see. What should I do? It's about to start.
That's strange. I thought I'd go and take the lunch.
I can't believe that misfortune has started.
It's no good. I don't feel anything at all.
It was empty until just now. I can't make it to the tournament.
It can't be helped. I'll get off the highway.
Yes.
I'm not sure if it's because I fell or something fell.
Anyway, it's just a series of misfortunes.
This is all because I dropped the luck.
Hey, taxi! Stop!
Damn it! It's a bug!
This is also because of the beard?
If this happens...
Hurry to the International Legislative Assembly.
Yes, sir.
The government needs to take action.
Damn it! I got on the bus!
The first round is starting!
It started.
Please, Ryo-san. Can you do something?
Even if you say that, I'll...
Ryo-san can do it.
Please do something.
I'm in trouble.
Huh?
The winning team is the Airaiken!
Senpai, next!
Ryo-san...
Alright, I'll do something!
The Hon-dara-ken representative, Asato Bandai, and the Janken representative, Gu Jokiba!
I'm Asato Bandai!
No, you're not!
It's about whether you can win or not.
Then, let's begin!
Hon-dara-ken, Janken!
Tsubanomai!
I'm crying!
Now!
One!
The winner is the Hon-dara-ken!
You did it! You're just like me!
You're right.
Hon-dara's father is not easy to imitate.
Next, Hon-dara-ken representative, Ryo-tsu Kanki-chitai!
The baseball-ken representative, Yoyoi-no-Yoi!
Now it's my turn!
I can't drive. I'll use the subway.
I'll be there on time.
What's this?
I have an announcement.
The train has slipped into the banana river and has been out of service.
Ah!
Ah! What's going on?
One!
Until then!
What are you doing, Hon-dara-ken?
I knew it! I'm the best!
Oh my god!
Why is the magic door open?
I can't win!
Help me!
Ah!
The white monkey!
What?
Ah!
The egg! The egg!
Ah! It's a bear!
Don't come here!
Don't go!
Help me!
Ah!
Oh!
That was close.
You defeated 13 people.
The next Universal Champions Wins
Hon-dara-ken Representative Asato Bantai!
I'm busy!
Son-dama Shine!
Is...
Is he really human?!
Y-Yeah!
A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A!
If we're throwing away things like this, we'll be late!
It's the Enshita Sea!
I didn't know we were getting to the North Pole.
A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-!
A-Amazing...
We did it! We're in the final!
Japan! Asado's victory!
You're saying "get up, you!"
Hi, I'm Honodara Kenji, and I'm a commander of the Ryōchi.
I'm ready to use you!
Alright, alright.
Representative of the Imokon prefecture, Mecha Mecha Robusta!
Is that really possible?!
Hurry, you guys!
Let's hurry back to Japan!
It's an unknown ship. There's no signal.
Kama, attack.
Roger!
It's a ship!
Oh no! It's coming to our rescue!
Oh my, I'm doing it again!
I'll kill you!
I won!
I'm just a piece of cake if I win at Limokon.
Y-you won...
Awesome! With this, I'll have every Honodara Kenji in the final!
By "every"...
Senpai, what now?
Hmmm...
And now it's the final round!
The winner has to buy one.»
-and you'll receive 10 million yen.
What? 10 million?
I didn't hear that!
Then you'll put your father in danger!
That's not good.
Huh?
The prize money won't come out until the final.
Damn it, I guess I have a plan.
It's no good.
The martial arts competition will end at this rate.
Huh?
Another one has appeared!
Help!
I'll use this doll to trick them.
Really?
This is very difficult.
Then, I'll use the same sword, Asato Bantai,
and the same sword, Ryotsu Kankichi, to win the final!
It seems to have already started!
It's true that the movement was too fast,
so I was surprised.
I can't see it well.
I did it!
I finally surpassed my master!
What's going on?
There are two Asato Bantai?
Two?
What?
Where?
Oh, my.
Where are they?
Huh?
Damn it!
I thought I could get 10 million yen after winning,
but I came out of nowhere!
I see.
Come on, Ryotsu.
The real game is coming.
Yes!
Where do you want to go?
Huh?
It's for 10 million yen!
I can't lose!
I will show you the true strength of the Pondala Sword!
Let's go!
Come on!
What?
What's wrong with my tatsumaki?
10 million yen!
Ten million yen!
What's wrong?
How is it?
You are such a patheticSlug!
That's right!
I will destroy your business!
Save your business!
Well done, Ryotsu!
Oh, no!
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Well done, Ryotsu!
Byaaa!
And they're all bouncing
Debe-debe!
Magi-magi!
And they're all bouncing
And their faces completely go up
And everybody's all bouncing
And they're all bouncing
Don't make me laugh, you old fart!
Ah! What? Why did I become this small?
Next time, "Ryo-san's becoming small!"
I'm sorry, but please let me go back to normal!