Forged In
When it comes to watching TV
Try to look out of your room and try to look away
Searing the setting sun at a far-flungaway river
Nekatsu shikashiba mata
Shiawaseda resette
Nakushite
Kigatsuita
Wakana ore
Dakara
Nekatsu
Anitoshite!
Yueino No Shinani
This is Yueinou's Shinani from Ryoutsu-sama.
Please have this finished, in What a Long History.
Well, you're a beautiful woman, so you don't have to be so nice.
You're a beautiful woman, so you don't have to be so nice.
And you're a waste of money for Kinjiro.
And you're a beautiful woman, so you don't have to be so nice.
Go on, you're a good man.
How did you trick him, you bastard?
Dad, you drank too much.
What? You're a bad man.
When you're happy, you should drink thoroughly.
Right, Dad?
Y-Yes.
More importantly,
Kinjiro's brother is a police officer.
What?
Well, I don't think he's a good man.
Well...
Kinjiro, your brother, is a great lawyer.
And I think he's a great police officer, too.
Huh?
I think he was the chief of the Kazushika office.
Or vice-chief.
Oh...
Well...
You're a good man.
I'm sure you'll be a good police officer in the future.
What a wonderful brother you are.
Yes.
I'll be a good police officer in the future.
What?
Is that what I said?
You don't remember?
You're a bad person.
I won't remember.
I'll get it on my head.
What are you going to do?
Kankichi will come to the wedding.
But he's a great brother.
You're kidding me.
Well,
I'm going to invite Kankichi to the wedding.
You!
I'll think about it.
But look, if he comes to the wedding, he'll be in big trouble.
He likes matzubi, so if he gets drunk and gets naked, it'll be bad.
The wedding might turn into a divorce.
But you can't just ignore him, right?
We're brothers.
And if you find out later, you'll get angry.
Shut up!
If the wedding is over, there's nothing we can do about it.
Then...
Yes, the divorce is impossible.
We can ask for compensation and compensation.
Thank you very much.
Doctor, we have a call from your family.
Excuse me.
And we also have a call from the head office and the minister of civil affairs.
Got it.
Yes.
This is it.
The invitation to the wedding is here.
I gave it to them this morning.
What?
Did you give it to them on the day of the wedding?
Of course I did.
Damn, you're late.
Anyway, dad.
You said that about your brother yesterday...
Dad.
Dad!
Damn it.
Wait.
I gave it to them this morning.
It'll arrive tomorrow.
I have a problem with parents.
They'll never get it before the wedding.
I won't give it to them until the wedding.
I wish they gave me the answer.
Dad!
Aww, you did it again!
I love you man.
How about you and me?
We're good friends, buddy.
Never mind.
I'll remember it.
The wedding will be perfect,
I haven't gone to work yet,
Hey, daddy!
You're pathetic.
It's not me.
Hey, man!
What are you doing here?
I was just guessing.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Did you find out?
The 11th race is a battle between Kamioka and Yoshiyama.
Just this one point.
Thanks.
See you.
You scared me.
Hey!
What is it?
It's the 10th race.
You don't have to go to work.
Oh, I see.
The chief will be here soon.
What a guy.
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
No...
Excuse me.
I found it.
If I don't have this, Kankichi will come.
Don't worry.
I'll go to the Ferris wheel.
Are you touring?
Yes.
Honda and Otohime will go with me.
Sounds fun.
When is it?
Next Sunday.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There is a wedding on that day.
Don't say that.
Whose wedding is it?
It's my mother's, grandmother's, sister's, son's, wife's, sister's, sister's daughter's.
I don't know.
If you're a distant relative, you don't have to come.
Well, I guess I'll refuse.
Oh, right.
I found the invitation.
I found it.
The phone number is...
Keiko Kirigaya.
It's a different name.
What about Hanamuko?
Jiro Ryotsugane.
This one is also different.
It seems that she is a lawyer from Todai University.
She is from Todai University.
Her address is Taitoku.
Oh.
What's wrong?
My brother is also from Todai University.
He is a lawyer in Taitoku.
He is the same person as Jiro in this Ryotsugane.
Oh, it's a coincidence.
It's a strange name.
Ryotsugane.
Ryo-sama, is it possible that you read it as Ryotsukinjiro?
What?
Ryotsukinjiro.
Oh, I see.
You are a distant relative of my senior.
I'm sorry.
He is my brother.
What?
No way.
He is your brother, but he is not your senior.
You read it as Ryotsugane, right?
No, I'm sure it's the same address.
Then...
He is Kinjuro.
I didn't let you know that.
Damn it.
Ryo-sama.
It seems that something terrible is going to happen.
Nakagawa-san.
Nakagawa-san?
Senpai and I are relatives.
Kinjuro, you bastard!
Why didn't you tell me?
I won't forgive you!
You are so stubborn.
I just got it.
Make me some food.
Yes, yes. I'll prepare it right now.
Hey, have you eaten yet?
What's wrong with you?
I've been waiting for a mail from Ryo Kankichi.
You are...
Hey, Meiji.
Hey, Meiji!
Damn it.
Kankichi.
Ryo-sama's mother.
Maria-chan.
Where is Kankichi?
That is...
The
I thought it was this area.
Here I am.
My uncle will say hello to you.
Next is...
My middle school teacher...
Who is that?
Me.
Let me in.
Brother.
Brother...
Hello, brother.
Hey, Kinjiro!
Calm down, brother.
Nice to meet you, brother.
Brother, this is Keiko Kirigaya.
We're having a wedding today.
What do you mean you didn't invite me to your wedding?
Keiko's mother's younger brother's...
Oh, I forgot.
I received an invitation from a distant relative, but I didn't receive it.
There's no way.
I sent it to Niconico.
Don't lie!
I don't know how great you've become, but I'm not a bad brother who can't even invite me to my brother's wedding.
You misunderstood, brother.
Then why didn't you send me an invitation?
I've never had a sad day like today.
I thought I'd celebrate my brother's wedding no matter what.
What?
I told you, it's a misunderstanding.
That's right. I didn't even send an invitation.
You're so annoying.
Keiko.
Are you okay, Keiko?
I just sprained my ankle a little.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry for being a rough brother.
If you do this, I'll break your wedding as well!
My brother is always like that.
That's right. If I try to be happy, I'm always in the way.
What?
Even when I fell in love with a girl for the first time in elementary school.
Kinjiro, what are you talking about?
Stay close to her.
I took a photo of her in front of the futon I had put on.
So my first love didn't work.
You're sorry for putting on a sleeping mask.
That's not all.
Even when I was about to pass the university exam.
I'm sorry.
Keiko.
What did I feel for the past two days before I got the acceptance letter?
Thanks to that, the joy would have doubled.
It's enough. Please leave.
What?
Kinjiro.
That's enough.
This is how you are.
Right?
I'm not your brother anymore.
Bye.
To be continued
Kinjiro, can you give it back to me?
Kinjiro!
Don't talk about that guy anymore!
The End
Kinjiro?
The Whitebeard Bridge...
I have a memory of the Whitebeard Bridge.
That was before I entered elementary school.
I was watching a paper play.
That day, my brother was not there,
and I happened to be alone.
Oh...
I followed him to the paper play.
When I suddenly realized,
I was in a completely different town.
I didn't know where to go back to.
Anyway, if I went to Kawazutai,
I thought I would arrive in Asakusa.
And I arrived at the Whitebeard Bridge,
Dad... Mom...
Let's go home!
Brother...
Kenjiro...
I...
I was worried about you, but now I can't watch the pro-wrestling.
Nii-chan!
I still remember Nii-san's heart beating and the warmth on his back.
He's a wonderful man.
That's why he bought a house near Shirahigibashi.
It was a place of great memories for me.
Kinjiro-san, let's go to Nii-san's wedding.
Keiko-san!
Nii-san!
Nii-san, it's my fault.
Please attend the wedding.
No, please attend.
What? You suddenly changed your attitude.
Nii-san is a precious brother to me.
Please attend the wedding.
Please do it for me, too.
Idiot!
I can't say "Yes, I do."
If you're not my brother, I'm not your brother.
Nii-san!
Senpai!
Kankichi!
Oh, Fukuro!
This.
It's the invitation to my wedding.
My father took it out of the mail box of Ryo.
What?
I couldn't get a draft because I went to the wedding.
That bastard! I won't forgive you!
Oh!
Nii-san, the wedding is...
Of course, I'll attend it.
I'll make it the best wedding in Japan as my brother!
See you!
That's right!
Take care!
Are you the tough brother?
Nice to meet you today.
You're called the iron man.
Nice to meet you, too.
Well...
Uncle, the toilet is here.
I'll take a picture after the ceremony.
I'll collect them all.
Yes.
Keep an eye on the money.
Be careful with the money.
Yes.
The amount is here.
The ceremony will start in 10 minutes.
Come on, old lady.
You're so smart.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Is everyone here?
Yes, perfect.
Your wife is beautiful.
She's the best.
She's perfect for the wedding.
No way!
I have a request for you when you're getting ready.
What is it?
What are you going to do?
I'll make the best wedding in Japan.
Leave it to me.
Now is the time to be the main character!
I think so.
The times are about to change.
As for politics...
Enough!
It's too long.
It's over.
Thank you.
The next minister is definitely Mr. Kuroyama.
Who is he?
I don't know.
He must be his secretary.
First he gave up on the show.
I was really worried about him...
After all, it was better not to call him.
So I applied.
Not this time!
The next is...
The oldest member.
Kankichi Ryōtsu.
It's me.
I want to say something.
You're a good man.
What? I told you not to call me that.
I don't care what happens.
Even if you say that, I'm worried.
When he was a kid, his brother Kinjiro was a useless guy who was always sleeping.
Big brother...
When he got older, he became a model that was made of serious raw materials.
But from his brother's point of view, he's still a foolish brother.
You're the most foolish.
Please look. This is my father.
He actually has a good-looking face.
He became a guarantor because he was so good.
As a result, he crushed the perspective of the store.
Don't say that.
My relatives have a good life.
They have a good job, a good job, a good job, a good job, a good job.
They have a good job, a good job, a good job, a good job.
They are all good-looking and poor, but...
They are not doing anything good.
In addition, my relatives have a lot of old people and old women at the top at the age of 107.
They don't think much and just live a long life.
Next, please, Professor of National University.
Please...
Relax your necktie.
Do you feel good?
It's your home anyway.
Everyone, relax your necktie.
If you eat with your neck tight, the food won't pass through your throat.
I'm getting closer to the tempo of my senior.
Applause!
It was a wonderful classical performance.
But, the unbearable amount of money is a burden to the ears of the horse.
Oh, Nakagawa! Come here for a moment!
What?
This young entrepreneur is my subordinate.
Please greet him.
First, adjust the time. Connect it for three minutes.
I see.
You're using the temperature of the Akou of Nakagawa's treasury?
Well, uh...
I and the senior are...
That's enough! We have a job!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
After the retouching, the new priest will enter!
New priest! New priest! New priest!
The priest has returned!
The new priest is the chief of our village, the Arakuremono family!
This is amazing, professor!
The television is different from the Arakuremono family!
Amazing!
Now, everyone! Let's celebrate their happiness and drink!
Ah, that was supposed to be a bad idea by the new priest and the chief!
Don't say such a hard word!
Now, let's drink and drink and drink all the alcohol in the hotel!
Yeah!
It's fine to ride the new priest!
Yeah, he's a nice old man.
From today, he'll really become your older brother.
I'm glad to hear that he's a reliable old man.
Is that so?
I'm so happy! I'll take care of all the housework!
That's really helpful!
Kirinoya, please take care of the children.
No, thank you.
Of course.
Dad, let's drink already!
Huh? The priest is...
Ah, what a nuisance!
I think I drank too much today.
Professor, please wake up!
I can't drink anymore.
It's about time.
Okay, okay.
Now, let's go home, Dad!
My relatives are all dead.
President, are you okay?
Dad, I'm sorry.
My brother got too drunk and ended up in this situation.
Kinjirou...
Yes?
I've been to many weddings, but this is the first time I've had such a fun and warm wedding.
He's a good brother.
Kinjirou.
Yes?
Yes.
Please take care of my daughter.
Dad...
Ouch...
I've never seen such a happy father before.
I have to thank you, brother.
Ah!
Where's brother?
Mom, where's brother?
He went home with dad.
Eh? Really?
Brother...
Dad, it was a nice wedding, wasn't it?
It was the best wedding.
I'm worried about what's going to happen later.
Kankichi, stay up tonight.
That's right.
There's plenty of wine.
And fish, too. There's a sea bream that came out of the wedding.
I forgot to bring it all.
If it's decided, go home quickly.
I'm cold.
Kinjirou, be happy.
Get up.
Kankichi!
What are you doing?
Alright, let's drink!
Let's drink till morning.
Are you sure you're old enough?
I'm not losing to you yet!
Argh, kind of.
Hey, shut the door!
Why?
What should I do?
I'm right here, I'm gonna save Ryo.
What are you doing?
I'm being chased.
Kankichi, you're balanced too.
I'm just a little disappointed.
We're fighting for ourärisch muy well.
x ZO TRUST
x MY ARRIVAL
B algunos amigos
x AN source
Cheers!
Can I drink too?
No, please stop drinking.
Hoooo!
Why are you so mankind.
♪ The final energy ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday ♩
♪ Draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ The planet with a turtle will come ♩
♪ Draw a circle ♩
♪ This is good, right? ♩
♪ There's no reason to be good, right? ♩
Hey!
The wedding ceremony of my younger brother Kinjiro has been successfully completed,
and I, too, have become a relative of Nakagawa!
From now on, as a relative,
I'll build up a Nakagawa Group,
and make more and more money!
Next time, as a relative,
I'll be in your care!