You
Watch
TV
You
Your
Room
And
Get
Away
From
Me
You
Look
Your
Room
River
You
Look
At
The
Sun
That
I
When
Away
From
Me
You
To
Meet
Me
You
Suddenly
When
Get
You
Julia
Yeah
Music
Air
Yeah
Music
It's so sweet
From the water of the Tungari Boshi
To the Kaishakuten
The sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
The time will end, Kazushika Shibamata
I realized that I lost happiness
Because I'm such an idiot
I'm sorry
I did it! It's decided!
Good!
He's going to the final with an overwhelming strength
Well, that's the way he is
Speaking of this place Sagonji
Saori
The image has been completely settled
He is originally a strong fighter
Well, the final opponent is
Mr. Olbo is also doing his best
He started judo in earnest
He is still in time
Isn't that a sign?
He has improved a lot
It's time
That's it
Red fairy wins
I did it! I won!
Sagonji vs. Olbo
This is going to be a fun battle
Senior
But other martial arts are unknown
Because it is judo
This is Sagonji's victory
The career is too different
I have to try the game
That's right
Because there is also the fate of time
Right
Sagonji is a guy who can throw all his strength even if the opponent is a girl or a child
I won't
Red Sagonji Tatsunosuke
White Olbo Saigou
Come on
You've come all the way here
I'll fight all my strength
Sagonji
Let's start
I will go
I really do
BORBOO!
What?!
You've improved, Borbo. But you still have a long way to go.
I'll finish you off with one last blow!
Go, go, Bobby! Go, go!
What? J-Jody?
Do you know him?
Jody is Borbo's lover!
What?!
I-I see.
I thought you were a true fighter.
You've become stronger by lying so much!
Go, go, Bobby! Go, go!
Wh-What?
What happened?
One, two, three, four!
Borbo is the last!
Borbo won!
N-No way!
You did it, Bobby!
My legs just slipped!
Over there!
See? It's sticking out!
N-No, this is...
I see. You're sticking out like a cheerleader.
Tsukibé, you're a pervert!
No!
I can't believe you just did that!
My legs are stuck in the dopamines.
Even officer Watsons said it there.
I can't believe that you're a pervert.
I am the best fighter in the world.
I'm the man of the world!
My legs are in so much more control.
I won't let you win this time.
Hi!
Hi! Is Bobby here?
Hey, Bobby. Did you have a nap?
Jody, what's that outfit?
I came to Japan, so I thought I'd have you practice judo in earnest.
Where's the master of this dojo?
That's him.
Oh, you're the one who lost to Bobby in the Hanachi Bu.
Sakonji, Jody isn't in the wrong.
I-I know.
Come on.
Here I go.
You seem to be doing a little, but you're still too naive.
Don't make a fuss again.
I won't make a fuss about who the opponent is!
Are you okay, Jody?
This is the first time I've lost to a man this perfectly.
I-I can't believe this music!
I saw it! I saw it! I saw it!
Papa!
As I thought, Captain Bugryu!
Captain Bugryu?
Didn't Captain Bugryu say he would make a man who defeated Jody his wife?
What?
Don't be so reckless!
Bobby!
Jody! What's wrong? What's wrong with you?
I'm going to make this man my bride.
I'm getting ready for the wedding.
Jody!
Bobby!
Jody...
What the hell?
Don't worry about it.
I understand, Boss!
I think they were carried to the New Mexico Military Base.
I'm going to find them.
What's this?
It's a wedding hall under construction.
Captain Bugryu seems to be making a wedding hall in the base for the two of them.
Is that father serious?
Ryotsu! Please! Do something!
I know! This kind of ridiculous wedding won't be for anyone!
I'm going to destroy this wedding!
I'll do it myself.
Father, what did you do?
Father!
I'm going to destroy this village!
We have no choice but to buy materials from outside.
It's the second floor.
The window over there is Jody-san's room.
I see.
Is it really that room?
There's no doubt about that.
Shut up! You won't tell me, will you?
Jody!
Bobby! Is that you, Bobby?
Why are you here?
I came to bring you back.
Me?
No.
I won't forgive you.
Are you going to marry Sakonji?
It's your fault, Bobby.
If you had told me earlier
that you were going to marry Sakonji...
Jody!
What was that?
It's Daddy.
If he finds us, he'll kill us.
Run!
But...
Hurry!
Hey!
Don't be so slow!
Good night, Master.
Good night.
You guys...
Hey, we're here to help you.
Yeah, we should.
Hohoho!
We're here!
Hey, which is Sakonji's room?
She's calling me.
I don't want to be here alone.
I need to tell her where she can live in.
What do you mean, "this"?
Don't touch her.
I'll kill you.
Yes, I do.
But you...
You're not mine.
No, I didn't touch you.
Babe, everything is fine.
Happy?
Johnny!
What?
I'm teaching judo to the soldiers here.
Everyone here calls me "Master" and respects me.
Even the private ones are nice.
Ryotsu, what am I called in the Katsushika Shrine?
Hanaji Keio no Sakonji.
Right? I'm the judo master, Hanaji Keio no Sakonji!
As long as I live in the Katsushika, I will follow you, Hanaji Keio no Sakonji, all my life!
I wonder if you're right.
I've decided!
I will destroy the dirty image of the Katsushika and start over in America!
But you have to marry Jody for that.
You hated Namami's woman.
I noticed recently that Jody is not like Saori in the Doki-Memo.
What?
She has a hairstyle like this.
She has eyes like this.
She has a nose like this.
She has a mouth like this.
And she has a contour like this.
And finally, she has a skin color like this.
See! Saori is like that!
Ryotsu, this is a miracle!
I just changed everything!
You forgot something important!
If you live in America, you can't do Doki-Memo!
And Jody is jealous!
Even if she is a game character, she won't forgive cheating!
I'm ready!
I will forget about Saori today!
From now on, Jody will be my Saori!
Oh, Jody...
What is he talking about?
Is this Saori?
Oh, this is Saori!
Is he speaking Takumi's voice?
So, everyone is like this.
Utyнуть, who is he?!
Te-te-te-te-te-te...
Takumi...
I'm not talking about Takumi!
Somebody is talking about Saori!
I think she is speaking Takumi's voice.
I'm sorry...
What am I supposed to say?
Say something about Saori.
I don't understand what you are talking about.
Yes.
Yeah, we call it the Saori Project.
Alright! That's all for today!
Alright! Thank you very much!
Alright!
Th-this is...
......
A 20-piece Saori figure!
I'll give you a price of 15,000 yen.
What do you expect to receive here?
Nooooooooooo, Saoori!
Master, did you hear something?
Wha... what is it?
We just heard Master's scream.
I-It may have been my imagination.
I hope that's all right.
If you have something, feel free to tell us.
Master.
Master is a precious body that prevented me from marrying Jody.
If something happens to Master, we will be scolded by Colonel Bakuryuu.
Yes, I understand.
I see. If he sees me holding on to Saori,
I will be in trouble for marriage.
I'm really fine.
You guys clean the dojo.
Yes.
I decided to forget about Saori.
Goodbye, Saori!
That's not good, Ryo.
The plan has just begun.
This is...
This is a soap maker.
I sold it for kids to see what they misunderstood.
I will get it back in a week.
Saori!
Master, did something happen?
It's nothing.
It's really nothing.
Master is a precious body that prevented me from marrying.
I understand.
I understand, so let me take a shower.
Yes.
I'm sorry, Saori.
Forgive me.
But I'll break it.
Somehow, Saori is...
Is it really just me that did this?
It was only a normal thing.
Yes, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
If I had a boyfriend and amazing,
It's not true.
Well...
Though, it is true...
So, what's wrong?
If you say it's nothing, then it's nothing!
I can't believe it...
The display that was used to promote the 3x speed when the first Doki Memo was released!
There are more than 100,000 of these as a phantom item among the fans!
That's... That's...
What? Why are you here?
Oh, you're trying to interfere with my wedding!
Don't show me such an innocent smile!
I can't leave you here!
Saori...!
No! No...!
I have to have such a painful feeling...!
*Discorded*
I'll just watch TV...
Forget about Saori, Tatsunosuke Sakonji!
I'm taking a new step!
Forget about Saori!
*Discorded*
Hello?
You're so mean, Satchan!
You suddenly turned off the TV!
Saori!
It's okay. I'll make you feel better tomorrow!
No, that was...
This is Ryouzu's trap!
Don't you understand that?
I bought a new swimsuit for tomorrow's date.
I can see your belly button.
I can see your belly button?
*Discorded*
I can see your belly button!
That's not how it should be, Tatsunosuke!
Tatsunosuke!
I'm out.
Damn it!
You even hired a real voice actor!
I don't have any other choice.
*Discorded*
You still have a choice.
Be my guest tomorrow.
Hmm?
Is there something bothering you?
N-no, nothing.
From the start, nothing's happened.
I'm not sure about the future anymore.
The wedding dress is complete!
Tatsunosuke, Dad!
I'm doing the work now, Daddy.
To have gotten married to such a beautiful girl
I'm so happy to be able to do this!
This is good enough.
Saori...
Bobby...
There was such a game in the amusement park?
I haven't played games for a while.
It's a new one.
I see.
I did it!
What was that just now?
Why did you continue even though you won?
I'm curious.
I did it!
Alright, this time...
Oh, it's out.
Look this way.
Look, look this way.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
It's almost done!
I won't lose to a monster!
I did it!
Hurry up and take the girl from before...
If you win this time,
I'll...
I'll be with you...
I-I'm sure it's Saori!
What if I win? What's going to happen?
Wait, wait for me, Saori!
What's going to happen?
You got caught.
I've been a member of a program of a friend for a week.
It's a fighting game-style love simulation.
It's called "Docu-Memo Fight."
It's a horror game where you fall into the Docu-Memo while you don't know what's going on.
I'm going to win, Saori!
If you show this scene to Captain Bakuryuu and Jody,
you won't be able to get married.
Senpai, that's...
It's Bakuryuu.
I've saved my effort to call you.
Then let's go home together!
Saori!
So, I need to talk to you.
Wait! Wait, Saori!
What's this?
Papa! Tatsunosuke!
I can't forget about Bobby.
I can't marry him like this.
I need to talk to him again.
What?
I want to see the sea.
The sea?
Hey, Saori!
Wow, Saori!
If you go to the sea, you can see Saori's swimsuit.
Wow, swimsuit!
What should we do?
Go!
Someone's coming. Hurry!
Saori will disappear!
What's this?
Papa, what are you doing?
How about the wedding preparations?
Do whatever you want with that.
What?
Tatsunosuke!
Which is more important, me or her?
Saori, of course!
I see!
That's what I meant!
Everyone, go to hell!
Saori!
Where are you, Saori?
Do something, Bulba!
I can't stop you anymore!
Y-You're saying, Saori?
Yes.
There you are.
I-I-I-I-I-I-I...
You will pay for playing with your maidenly thoughts!
Ahh-!
So, after all, Jody and Saccongi's wedding is cancelled.
Yes, I knew Jody would be better with Bulba.
As already, Bobby年
is waiting to defeat me!
I'll wait for you to come back.
What about you, Sakonji-san?
I'm into Doki-Memo again.
My girl is already in love.
Doki-Doki...
*crying*
Dachi-chan, cheer up!
Eeeeeeeeh! Saori!
Doki-Chan, cheer up!
Even if I wake up at midnight,
If it's you, I'll be awake.
Even if I have boring talks,
I'll make the entire body hot.
Hey, friend,
I want to see you.
I want to be loved
Just a little
The more everyone says
I feel like we're melting
I want to shoot you
For some reason, love is just cowardly
Don't hide all the strong love
We visited the school that was about to be demolished
We met a girl who was like a dead classmate
The piano sound in the music room
It made our memories vivid
Next time, after a long break
Thank you!