"The End"
When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and try to look away
A place where it rains like someone is calling
I walked while looking back
I held my mother's hand
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk on the black side of the Ake-dogai Tile
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and see that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall there
There is a turtle there
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
"The Journey of the Rice and the Tenderloin"
P-please...
Someone help me...
Reiko, please...
Please, something to eat...
Something to eat...
No!
Reiko...
I'll eat it with you
This is for Ryo-chan
Reiko, you mean...
Something to eat...
No matter what you say, it's not good
Nakagawa-kun...
Stop it, senpai!
Don't come any further!
Nakagawa, 100 yen, 50 yen...
30 yen is enough...
I beg you...
Senpai, I'm sorry but...
I can't lend you money
You know, right?
This is a director's order
Shut up, I don't understand
What are you saying, Nakagawa?
Normally, if you see a painful sight, you'll be stubborn
But Ryo-chan, every month...
Even if you go to the front of the gashi, you still won't be stubborn
Since long ago, the edokko has been decided that it does not have the money to spend the night
Then, like edokko
You are proud of it and you are very angry
Director!
You don't think about the future
You buy more and more what you want with your salary
You don't have any food expenses
Who will agree to that?
The big hearted director will...
Who will?
If you want to eat white rice every day
You can use your salary as planned
How many times do I have to tell you?
Big hearted director...
You should put that feeling into your stomach
Got it?
If you understand, you will not waste it again
Say it out loud!
I won't waste it
You shouldn't forget those words
In order not to give money to Ryo-chan
There is nothing you can't understand even if you say it with your mouth
There is nothing to be learned by body
Yes
Ryo-chan
Wake up, Ryo-chan
Let's deliver the food
Ryo-chan
Please give me the signature of the receipt
Thank you
It's rice!
Yahoo!
It's rice! It's rice! I'm so happy!
You did a great job with everything
What is this rice?
I don't know, but it's for me
I made it myself
It's mine!
Look, senior
You've applied for the 10th anniversary quiz of the Ekimai supermarket
The 10th anniversary quiz of the Ekimai supermarket
Ah, the prize from that time!
Oh my god!
Heaven didn't let me go!
Now it's smooth without a mess
That's great, senior
What a lucky person
This rice is mine
It's not just a piece of cake if you touch it
That's right
Hey, master!
I've ordered it!
I've brought your rice cooker
Ok, here it comes
What's that?
No, it's from Niconico Ryo's kitchen
I just took it from there
Ryo-chan, I'll do it
Don't be a coward!
You seem to be feeling better.
You should stay away for a while.
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
It's like a beast.
If you eat so fast, your stomach will not accept it.
Here, look.
Shall we bring the washing machine?
Wow!
I ate all 15 of them.
Here we go.
You're going to eat again?
Let's eat!
I can't get enough of white rice.
I guess he's getting bored.
What?
What's that?
You're going to cook with that?
What a sad dish.
I feel thelling of life for you.
BREAK!
You bourgeoisies...
You shouldn't be aware of...
But I can't understand the taste of this seasoned rice
This is fried rice seasoned with only salt and pepper
Since it is seasoned with only salt and pepper, the taste of the rice itself is not killed
The outside is crispy and the inside is fluffy
This frying method is successful in bringing out the texture of the rice to the maximum
And the omurice-like rice seasoned with only ketchup
The moist ketchup is entwined with the rice
The ketchup wraps the taste of the rice well
And brings out the taste of the rice
And the rice sushi that is served with fresh white rice
The original taste of the rice and the rice are not quarreled
They are mixed well on the tongue
And bring out the exquisite harmony
Let's eat
Delicious
This is delicious, too
Too delicious
Very delicious
Super delicious
You guys have been observing me since a while ago
You guys want to eat this
You have been so cold a while ago
Who will share it with you?
Well, I am not a demon
I have two more people
Lord Ryochi
I am very sorry for what happened just now
I will eat it if you forgive me
Why do I have to apologize?
That's right, you have to apologize
Ah, is that so?
Well
Delicious
It's delicious!
Lord Gyoji, I'm terribly sorry for what happened earlier.
The world of rice is...
...unceasingly wide!
Thank you for waiting.
Here, inside there is fried rice.
Fried rice without any ingredients, with rice!
This is truly the ultimate dish.
And for Reiko, it's healthy, spicy rice!
Could this be...
...rice with spicy rice?
Yes, put it on rice.
This is truly the ultimate dish.
And for Honda, it's a special, Zargome.
Zargome?
It's smooth like Zaru-soba.
Smooth?
I'll eat it!
This is the ultimate dish!
How is it?
I can't say anything about it.
It's just not like rice.
It's hard to eat this, Seppai.
Eat without leaving any leftovers.
Don't forget to take good care of the rice.
Lord Gyoji!
What?
Lord Gyoji, I'd like to have your signature.
This is rice.
Rice again.
This is hard to eat.
What the hell is this?
The Rice Eating Association?
What's that?
Ryo-chan, when did you join such a group?
This is hard to eat.
I see.
I put out a post on a campaign to think of a new name for rice.
The name I thought of, "Rice-chan", has been selected and has been sent as a product.
"Rice-chan"?
Is that your name?
It's so hard to eat!
But, Seppai, what are you going to do with so much rice?
Hmm...
Damn it.
Oh, Ryo-chan, welcome.
Hey, old lady.
Nice to meet you.
This is my familiar place.
That's right.
Old lady, as I told you on the phone, I'm going to rent a place.
Oh, you can use it anywhere you want.
I'm free anyway.
Hehe.
Ryo-chan!
This is such a boring place.
I've been looking for a long time.
Oh, I've been waiting.
But, are you really going to start a business here?
You don't seem to be doing as you like.
Really?
No worries.
Here you go.
It's a lot of numbers.
What are those numbers?
This is the amount of time I needed to spend the whole time in Kameari-cho, which broke the patrol rule.
Really?
I thought that the next time would be useful, so I decided to find a better location instead.
That's what I decided.
Especially around here, it's far from the station,
and there are many factories, but there are very few restaurants.
There are no convenience stores, so if I were to say a business,
it's just a hamburger shop across the street.
Before, when it was noon,
the factory workers would come to buy bread.
A few years ago, I suddenly thought that construction had started across the street...
From now on, we will be rivals, but please take care of us.
-Kyosuke. -Huh?
I'm sorry, but this world is a world of weak meat and strong food.
Since then, I've been very relaxed.
If that's the case, we can also do business without any worries.
How about 30% of what you are getting?
Huh? Is that really okay?
It's a business deal, a business deal.
After all, it's free.
That's right. And I don't know if it will sell.
It will sell. It's obvious that it will sell.
Yes, it will sell. I'll sell it.
Are you selling this rice ball?
If you eat only hamburgers every day, you'll get bored, right?
And if you're Japanese, you'll miss the rice.
I see.
As expected of Ryo-sama.
It's time.
What's this siren?
It's a sign of a lunch break at the factory.
Why are there so many customers?
Okay, I can't lose either.
The battle begins.
Welcome. Welcome.
This is Ryo-tsu's real rice ball.
Today, we're going to sell a lot of things.
Each one is 50 yen.
Sake, tarako, plum, and kelp.
Welcome. Welcome.
50 yen is cheap.
I want plum and tarako.
I want tarako and kelp.
It's 350 yen.
Three kelp for two salmon.
Hey, Maidari.
You're so young.
Line up in a row.
What's wrong?
The shop across the street is selling rice balls.
The customers are all over there.
What?
What should we do?
Senpai, we sold 50 salmon rice balls.
We sold plum and tarako.
How much is the rice?
Let's eat more and more.
Okay.
Are we out of sales?
We'll be able to sell next time, so please wait a moment.
Hot and spicy Texas burger.
We will wait for you at any time.
Come here.
Let's go.
Maidari.
Nsome meat is here.
What have you seen?
Moist, right.
them on the other side,
Do you know?
He's calling the police.
Why is the police here?
You're going to be very worried to be released next time.
I prepared three rice cooker for you.
And this is the rice cooker that I developed.
It can make 20 rice balls at once.
It's a rice ball machine.
I see.
This is easy to make.
And whoever makes it can make it the same size.
Hey, Maria!
Don't put so much rice in it!
Why, Master Ryo?
If you make a lot of rice with the same amount of rice,
it will become so small.
To show the amount of rice,
you have to make it softly.
You're going to make it big.
Make more rice balls with one grain of rice.
That's what business is about.
You have to make 500 rice balls per grain.
How can I count 500 rice balls?
You can count them on the scale.
This is about 480 rice balls.
Add 20 more.
Okay.
Hey, you put too much in.
20 rice balls is too much.
I'm sorry, Master Ryo.
You're a good boy.
Ryo, I'm in trouble!
We started selling hamburgers and rice balls.
What?
Welcome! Welcome!
We started selling rice balls at Texas Burger.
And they are cheaper than both rice balls.
99 yen.
What a fool!
They are cheaper than those.
So we are going to go there.
I'm going to the other side.
Can we sell it cheap?
No, it's dangerous to ride the enemy's provocation and run into a sleep-down competition.
The price will remain the same, and the quality of the product will be improved.
Come on, come on.
Depending on your taste, you can choose the ingredients of the rice ball at the place.
Only Ryotsu rice ball store.
There are two thousand combinations.
Wow!
Welcome!
Thank you!
Please come in.
I'll also combine it.
Boss!
Cheap and delicious, the combination of three thousand kinds of Texas burger rice balls.
Saboten, piranha, toka-ge and sasori.
There are a lot of rice balls that you can only taste here.
You are imitating me again.
I've already thought of the next step.
Now, what is it?
It's a character.
How about a rice ball that has cute animals and nostalgic anime characters?
I can't lose to that child's spirit.
Boss!
Texas Burger Original Adult Rice Ball.
Boss?
This is a rice ball for adults.
Saboten!
This is a color rice ball.
It's all colored with natural colors such as coffee and brown rice.
It's safe.
But the blue rice ball is a little strange.
This is a colorful rice ball.
It looks terrible.
It's a rice ball covered with sushi.
It's a rice ball covered with tuna.
It's hard to eat.
This is the ultimate rice ball.
It's the world's top three rice balls.
It's full of high-quality ingredients, such as mitriff, foie gras, caviar, and matsutake.
It's wrapped in gold foil instead of seaweed.
It's a high-quality rice ball.
It's 5,000 yen each.
Can it be sold?
Well, this is a special type for parties and gatherings.
I see.
My idea is infinite.
How far can you go?
It's a lottery to win a gold and silver diamond for ten.
Please stop it, boss.
If you do that, I will be disbanded.
Ryotsu Rice Ball Headquarters.
It has been the first to sell rice balls in the city.
After that, the number of customers increased with my ideas.
It's a great hit to develop a vending machine that can rent the power of Nagagawa to make frozen rice balls into grilled rice balls in 10 seconds.
It's a catchphrase that you can hold on your own.
A handmade rice ball set sold at a station.
An airtight pack rice ball that can be stored for 60 days is also a big hit.
Ryotsu Rice Ball Headquarters has been taken over by the media and continues to sell steadily.
On the other hand,
The
I think I'm going to be a great salesman.
I'm looking forward to the next game.
The
Why aren't there any customers?
I think I should return it to the original hamburger shop.
Ryo! Do you think I'm waiting for you?
I don't like you.
You traitor!
And then...
Ryo! The hamburger shop across the street is...
Finally, it's broken down.
The hamburger shop across the street is...
It's becoming a more and more absurd store.
You've completely lost sight of the direction.
Thank you for the meal.
After that, the hamburger shop continued to change from a rental video store to a Famicom shop.
It seems that the parking lot has settled down.
Everything is the most difficult.
No, I can't say that it's all a waste.
The boom is a family thing.
I'm going to get bored of it.
So, the Ryo-tsu hamburger shop is...
I'm going to go out to the big cliff that has a view of the world.
I have a bad feeling.
You're doing it in a flashy way.
Senpai, don't be angry.
Call the overseas media and...
I'm going to shoot a big campaign of the Ryo-tsu hamburger shop.
I thought it would be accomplish a big deal but...
It was completed.
There's no mistake of getting a Guinness Book of Records.
This is Japanese traditional fast food.
It's a delivery disruptions.
Ryo-tsu's real comercial gusto has now completed the biggest delivery disruptions in the world.
President Ryo-tsu.
President, would you please sit on top of the rice ball?
Yes, sir!
Okay, then let's make a round like the one Mikoshi does in this rice ball.
Oh!
Hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim...
Hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim, hashim...
Waaah!
I don't know what's going on.
Because of that man, my life is ruined.
I'll start over again after this.
Thank you very much, Nikka!
Get in there!
No good! We're gonna burn on the other side of the warehouse too!
Help! Help! Help!
They did it again in a flashy way.
Thanks to that, the word "yaki o musubi" became famous all over the world.
But the name "Kome-chan" is going to be changed because it's going to be down in the image.
You were very helpful in that big fire, Senpai.
I feel sorry for Ryo-sama.
Hmph, you idiot.
I got punished for wasting the rice.
Here is my cute request for something that I broke.
Does that mean, maybe, that you will...
I will turn tailored as the staff of the U.S.A. back home.
Give it to me, Ryo-chan!
♪ Awaken the clock on the clock all day long, my little finger hurts.
♪ When you draw your eyebrows, you can still see the station.
Every day is no problem
When I take a hot shower
I get well with a sleeping pillow
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
I'm drinking on Monday
Monday Monday Go Go Go
I was kicked out of the dormitory
and I went to the manager's house
This is so boring
I'm going to use the bathroom
And I can't drink or gamble
Damn it
I'll somehow change my life
Next time
Ah! The life of hell
See you next time
Thank you for watching