Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ in a taiko park ♪
♪ and laughed that I was still fine ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ as a good boy ♪
♪ I only have a bad mood ♪
♪ and a bad mood ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes ♪
♪ is so kind ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ and the moose is groaning ♪
♪ Are there any roasted chickens? ♪
♪ I wonder if ♪
♪ you'll be able to see ♪
♪ at Taishakuten ♪
♪ My hat is hanging over my head ♪
♪ The sunset is falling ♪
♪ I'm going to wake up tomorrow ♪
♪ and end it ♪
♪ I'm going to lose my happiness ♪
♪ again in the year-end ♪
♪ I'm the stupid fool who noticed ♪
♪ because I lost it ♪
"Shiratori vs. Ryo"
Ryo vs. Shiratori
"A Big Vagabond"
Well, I'll go first.
Tomorrow is the day off.
I'm so happy!
What the heck is this?
I did it!
I got it!
Ryo has been captured!
I did it!
What the hell are you doing?
I don't have money.
I know that.
If you don't have money, I'll make it for you.
What?
Hey, where are you taking me?
I'll write your profile here.
Profile?
This is too expensive.
I'm in danger, but I'm in a good condition.
It's okay to be a little dangerous.
Hey, don't decide it yourself.
I told you, the victim is here.
That's right. Ryo has no right to speak.
If you have a special skill or a qualification, please register it.
If I have a qualification, I have enough to sell.
First, I'm a dangerous person.
I'm a boiler repairman.
And then...
Please introduce me to a job that I can earn quickly.
Even if you say that, I don't have a qualification, a passion, a physical strength, or a special skill.
But pride is one in a million.
That's a problem, Shiratori-san.
Shiratori?
Chichi-chi.
If you take pride from this Shiratori Reiji, nothing will remain after you.
You're weak.
Anyway, you're suitable for me.
It's easy, gorgeous, and lively.
Please introduce me to a job that I can earn quickly.
Shiratori Reiji!
What are you doing here?
Hey!
Your father's company was crushed again because of this.
So, you came here to look for a job.
You're sharp.
No, don't say something so rude.
This is a social tour of the Teyogaku.
It's just to spread the word as the next president of the Shiratori Iron Company.
Hahaha.
You're a poor man.
What?
A newspaper?
You finally ate up enough to not make a fake newspaper to spread the word?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Well, that's it.
Ryo-tsu-san.
Shiratori-san.
Ah?
Ryo-tsu-san.
If you're a friend, could you please take care of Shiratori-san?
What?
That's not a joke!
No, that's fine.
I don't think Ryo-san is alone.
He's always hanging out with other people.
It's not like he knows what he's doing.
Oh, you need a friend to see him off.
It's not a good idea to be with someone like him.
I can't stand being with this vulgar person.
Shiratori-san.
You can't do anything by yourself.
So don't say that.
What?
You're a loser.
To be honest.
You can't go anywhere by yourself.
I don't care.
I'm with you.
Hey!
You're too quick to say anything, Shiratori.
I'm the chief, so I'm going to help you.
Well, then.
It's decided.
Get!
Decided.
Hey!
I'm not done!
Please take care of Ryo-tsu-san's family here.
Understood.
Don't decide it on your own!
Well, then, let's go!
What?
What are you doing?
Well, this...
There's no one here.
Hey!
Let me do it!
I'm strong, but I'm not trying to win.
Why?
Oh, there.
His heart is in pain.
Try this!
You can do it, Shiratori-san!
I can't do it!
Masakopo is here!
Don't bother me!
It's me, Masakopo!
Welcome! I'm the best in Japan!
I'm the best in Japan!
You idiot! The passers-by are running away!
Take it, you poor thing!
Are you feeling better, Shiratori?
Yes.
Okay, now that you've calmed down, you can do whatever you want.
You're the one who's poor.
But what's wrong with this Kanmi Yomogi-jiru?
Ugh! It's bad!
What is this?
Shut up!
This is the new Kanmi Yomogi-jiru, the best-selling service.
Is this good? Isn't it a crime to give away something like this?
Hey! You can't do this without giving it to me!
Hey, did you drink this?
Of course!
It's really bad, right?
Yeah.
No, it's not!
Just give me the Yomogi-jiru!
It doesn't matter if it's good or bad!
I'll give it to you without leaking, Shiratori!
But this tastes like a puddle.
It's not canned juice, it's canned.
A puddle.
Let's say that's the president.
Excellent!
I'm not the one to give away something like this to the world...
Hey! You still say that?
Hey! Don't you dare hit the head of a Yomogi doll!
What's wrong? Is there a problem with my Kanmi Yomogi-jiru?
No, there's no problem, president.
No, I'll tell you, but something bad is bad.
I was born to drink such bad things.
I've never heard of it.
What? Yomogi-jiru is bad?
No, it's bad.
This Yomogi-jiru is bad.
In other words, it's good, president.
That's right. As expected of the ambassador of the Koukoku.
He knows the true nature of young people.
No, he said that this Kanmi Yomogi-jiru is bad.
Hey, Shiratori, you!
What are you doing to Yomogi?
If you like it so much, you can drink it yourself!
President!
I'm sorry.
I can't force you!
You two, stop!
I've been bringing all kinds of luggage into the house.
If this is the case, I don't know how long it will take to get a asset...
Please pack your luggage, which you have downloaded from the container, efficiently, from the far end of the warehouse.
Any questions?
All right, sir!
Hey, aren't there any vouchers in Armania or Valencia?
Huh? Shiratori.
You're only @shiratori0 people, huh?
It's a treasure chest to lock it in such a moldy warehouse.
Eh?
No, it's nothing. I'll do it perfectly.
Really?
Then, nice to meet you.
What are you doing?
Listen, Shiratori! If you mess up this time, I won't know anymore!
You're with me, so you're doing the job.
I want you to be a little grateful.
Gr-grateful?
Listen, if you ask someone who saw this situation now,
they would say "100 people are 100 people, and you're the one who's bothering them!"
I can't let you say that I'm bothering you.
You're a super rich me.
I'm a super poor person now.
This super cool Shiratori, Reiji-sama,
is a super poor person and a little troublesome to you,
so people don't call it a bother.
Huh?
Because!
Because I'm Shiratori Reiji!
I can't do this anymore!
You're a sunbathing moron!
Unfortunately, the weather is bad, so I'm not a sunbathing moron.
Hey, get out of the way!
That's dangerous! That's dangerous!
That's dangerous!
Come on, come on!
Hey, stop!
Get out of the way!
That's dangerous!
Hey, get out of the way!
There's no more space to assume!
If you don't line up, it'll collapse!
Stuff like that should stay under the roof and avoid any raincast!
If you stand up in a row, nobody notices!
Ahhh, I'm so delicate and so precious!
Because someone like this can't be helped!
My back is shaking and my trachea is aching.
Whether you're a whore or a spinster, stand up down,
why do I have to carry the burden of a Shiratori?
Well, if I'm aalarmy,
It's not fair for someone else to do it.
Look over there. The box is different.
This box is slanted and it's about to collapse.
This box and this box are different types.
How's that?
My sense of balance that I've trained in games for years.
There's a big hole in the middle.
Look over here and there.
It's about to collapse.
This is how you do it.
Now it won't collapse.
It's going to collapse!
You guys, get ready!
I'm the only one who has been doing the country debt and taking a bath and eating and playing games.
Thanks to this guy.
I've always been bad at places like this.
I hated Shiso and Blanco.
Shut up.
Get up and get out of here.
Get out of here.
It's shaking.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's dangerous.
Leave this kind of job to those who like expensive places.
We should have a job that's more like us.
Stop it.
You're mean.
You're not in a position to say you're luxurious.
Then I'll ask you.
What kind of job do you think you're good at?
That's...
Rich, high-class, celebrity, gorgeous.
What are you doing?
Enough.
You're not rich, high-class, celebrity, or maribu.
You can't get out of here until the window is blown.
Blow outside while you're dreaming, you idiot.
Idiot.
Idiot?
Don't blow like that.
Go straight.
You're in trouble twice.
I've never done anything like this before.
Hey, you.
Okay, fine.
Just sit there and move the gondola.
Should I push this?
I...
No!
It's high!
It's scary!
No!
You've already blown it up.
Push down.
It's high.
It's scary.
Then, do it slowly.
Idiot, you idiot.
This is not good.
Push.
Huh?
What?
It's strange.
Did it break?
Move.
What?
What is this?
Well?
I won't let you go.
I didn't know you were here.
Well, I'm not rich.
You're on one side.
You too?
The End
Hey, is this the job of a rich, high-class, celebrity and gorgeous?
Don't complain.
I got this job to meet your expectations.
If you don't want it, do you want to ride a gondola again?
Huh?
Do you want to ride a gondola and climb a high place?
You can also do a house tour, right?
That's...no.
Then work without complaining!
F-40, I was its owner until recently.
Huh?
It's the same as your car until it's modified into an automatic.
I miss those days.
Those days, the world belonged to me.
Unfortunately, the world belongs to everyone now and then.
trouver
Hey, there's a guest like you in here.
Yes, sir and ladies!
This is what I've been waiting for!
Mr. 삼企部 九尺エステグループ出身
Mr. 九尺パトリック 三千代
Master!
You're obviously a fraud.
It's real!
Hey, Hirohudo Shiratari!
Stop it!
You don't have any pride!
What are you talking about?
You were just imitating me until recently.
Listen.
We are here to earn money.
We will give you your pride.
Give it to those crows!
Money! Money!
What?
Where is my F40?
Yes.
It has been waiting for a long time.
I will give you the money.
Okay.
I will take your car here.
Ryo-tsu!
Yes!
What are you doing there?
Give me your F40.
Okay.
I am Ryo-tsu, who is in charge of F40 maintenance and inspection.
I'm Igo Omishiri.
I am Gyo-Kyo!
Ryo-tsu!
Take this.
Bring me my car quickly!
I'm back!
Earn money!
Shiratari!
My F40!
Hey, where are you going?
Bring it back quickly!
Yes!
Shiratari!
Wait!
Wait, hey!
Hey, if you get hurt by a car, it's a problem! Get off the car!
No!
No? You don't have that right!
I'm not giving it to you!
It's not your car!
I don't want to!
What?
You must be hungry from your old self.
That has nothing to do with him or this F40!
Stop hitting him, Shiratori!
No, no, no!
My F40!
S-Shiratori!
My legs are touching yours, so don't leave me!
Don't follow me, you sick man!
That's a terrible thing to say.
Terrible?
It's like this.
I've always been rich, like you, who's always been poor.
But I'm like you, who's always been delicate.
In other words...
I have a different resistance to the mass violence in the world.
If I do that, my sense of justice...
Sense of justice?
Yeah.
Better not show off your shirakashita!
Ow ow ow ow ow ow!
Enough!
Don't bother me anymore!
I understand!
But you should need me!
What?
You are the only one who needs me.
You can't do it alone.
Even if I borrow your hand, I can live alone.
I have a job.
Hey, you!
What?
Don't be silly!
I can't even do such a simple job.
You don't have to be depressed. Just watch.
Just as you told me, I did something to him.
Him?
It was like I was looking at myself from the past.
I couldn't stand it, and I was envious.
I was a foolish and immature duckling until now.
Shiratori.
You've become a good man when you're poor.
I'm a good man.
Actually, I'm just a plain, humble man.
Until now, I was just a descendant of Shiratori Tekko.
I was just trying to show my weakness to others.
Now I finally understand that.
That discovery has no effect on humanity.
But it's a big step for you.
That's right.
I did it.
Yes.
I guess I'll try to master this job.
It seems to be a job that can't be mastered or not.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble up to now.
But I've changed.
Shiratori Reiji has died.
Please keep an eye on me.
Look at me.
Shiratori.
Ryotsu.
You're good.
So, did you return the debt?
Not yet.
But I've made many mistakes, and the debt has increased by tenfold.
What?
From now on, I'm going to work hard to pay it off.
Is that a salary you can work hard to pay off?
You're very calm, Ryo-san.
I can't change the money. I got something important.
You can't change the money?
Did you have that kind of thing?
Hey, you're being rude, Nakagawa.
You're a man, and you're a man.
A man's friendship is a treasure that can be used for anything.
A man and a man's friendship?
I'm sure you worked with Shiratori Reiji-san, right?
Does that mean that Shiratori-san and a man's friendship has developed?
What?
He's changed.
Listen, Reiko.
Don't judge a man by his looks.
There are some men who have a pure and humble soul under the white skin.
There are men like that.
No way.
Shiratori, what happened?
My father's company has been restored.
So I'm going back to living a rich and famous life.
What?
Shiratori's company has invested a lot of money into the steel industry.
I see.
Is that possible?
Hey, Reiko.
Please accept my love.
Oh.
How about a cruise on my yacht for the next holiday?
He hasn't changed at all.
Shiratori.
Shiratori Reiji is a man of character.
лег аlike a man of character!
Like a hero....
like a hero....
Some one calls me.
After a long rainy day.
Walking, looking back.
I walked home
My mom was holding my hand
That time I felt
A strange feeling
So
I tried to walk
On the black tile of the arcade
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgot
The politician with a great face
And the blue lady above her eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Yeah!
Let's go!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What?
I'm in a commercial?
Okay, leave it to me!
I see, I knew you'd watch it!
Listen, headmaster
Please look only at the good points of me
It's impossible!
And next,
HonestyDavid!
I'm counting on you!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!