"The Unwanted Cat"
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and
try to look away.
"The Unwanted Cat"
Come to me,
if you're a poor man!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Come to me,
if you're a poor man!
"The Unwanted Cat"
Come to me!
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
It'll be alright eventually
You know, right?
You know, you know!
If you know, then just follow me!
Ryo-san, you're getting bigger!
You idiot!
I'll kill you right now!
Stop killing me!
I'll see you later, boss!
Ryo-san, what did you do this time?
He found the place where he was playing at the game center
That's part of the patrol!
That's amazing, Ryo-san!
I'm the one who got caught
I see. It's a pretty fun patrol
This time, take me with you!
Of course, boss! It'll be fun!
I'm a fool!
I see
I finally got him to forgive me
If I'm found by the chief,
He'll become really angry at me!
The chief hates me
He's always mad at me
He doesn't even look at me when I'm working seriously
Every time, every time, every time
When I'm on a work trip,
Only when I'm feeling a little better.
You big idiot!
That's why it's good.
If you're going to be scolded, you'd better do what you like.
It's like a rebellious child.
Then what?
Have you ever skipped a single second of your work?
That's...
One second is...
It's not like that, but...
Look! Even if you skip the same time, you won't be scolded and I will be scolded.
The manager hates me.
Excuse me.
How do I get to the Kameari Library?
The traffic light ahead is on the right.
It'll be noticeable, so you'll understand soon.
Thank you very much.
I'm the one who taught you.
You should thank me.
I'm the one who's being told that.
Always.
That's not true.
I've told my seniors about it.
Even if I do it seriously, in the end, I'll be scolded.
It seems like it's useless to say anything now.
Let's leave it for a while.
Go in, go in, go in, go in.
Professor Ezaki
This is the gorilla and his friends.
It's a coincidence, isn't it?
We're always here.
It's strange that we met here.
If you have time, will you go with me for a while?
Gorilla-kun.
I'm working right now.
I don't have that much time.
That's not true.
I'm trying to help Gorilla-kun so much.
It's not good to be involved with you.
Well, it can't be helped.
If only for a while.
『 Manju and Jumbo Manju 』
Do you want to eat manju first?
Here you are.
Just a manju?
...
No way.
I'm sorry.
That's a new generation supplement.
Jumbo Manju.
Jumbo Manju?
No way it's going to make my body bigger if I eat it.
Ping-pong table tennis!
All sportsmen think they have a good shape
That's right, mama! It's a revolutionary invention called "Sacrificing Victory"!
That's a good thing about doping!
Well, that's one way of saying it.
When you grow up, your life will change, Gorilla.
What?
You've been hiding in the shadows of people and lived a simple life!
I'm jealous...
You can eat only this jumbo manju!
Bak! Bak! Bak! Bak!
Ah! That's a great sportsman!
He's popular among girls!
What's wrong with him...
This great invention, the jumbo manju, is...
...now in my hands!
One is not enough, big guy. Two is not enough, big guy.
Three is...
It doesn't taste bad either.
What?
It's not like you're a gorilla.
Your body is so...
...much-much.
Not at all.
You're so...
...much-much.
Not at all?
As I thought, you shouldn't be a gorilla, you should be a human.
I'm a human!
You're late, Ryo-san.
Damn it!
Ryo-chan!
Senior!
What? It seems like you guys have become smaller.
It's not that! Senior has grown up!
What?!
It seems like my jumbo manju is working.
Jumbo manju?
I think it's probably a new invention by Professor Ezaki.
I see! But Ryo-san, you're doing good.
He's got long legs and looks like a NBA player!
R-really?
No, he's pretty cool!
But if you guys change your perspective like this,
you'll have to forgive all the rude things you've done to me before.
I wonder if I can forgive them.
You've grown so big, even your heart and body.
I wish I could, but...
I have a favor to ask.
- Me? - Yes.
When you grow up, your life will change, Goriya!
Here it comes.
What kind of voice is that?
- Here you go. - Thank you.
It's a cheap meal.
It's decided.
N-no way!
And what's that?
- Yosuke! - Senpai!
- It's bigger than before! - Oh no!
This is going to be a daily routine.
I'm sure you'll be late.
I guess so. I'm going.
Where are you going?
Hey, Bram. How's the cake?
Oh, just as good as before.
This is faster.
Move, move, move!
Bram, Bram.
Come on!
Come on, Bram.
Bram, Bram.
Hey, Goriya.
It sounds like you're having a good time with the jambo-manju.
How does it feel to have grown up?
You're not talking about that!
It's too big!
You have to change your body size.
Come on, Goriya.
What's that?
What's this?
This is a super ultra hyper jumbo manju made with a concentrated supplement.
Do you want to try it?
No! The manju will get smaller!
No, it's only getting bigger.
That's a problem. Do you want me to live with this size for a long time?
No, it's not that size for a long time!
Huh? Will it go back to normal naturally?
That's also wrong.
If you eat one jumbo manju, it's a little big.
If you eat two, it's a little big.
If you eat three, it's...
If you eat three, it's a little bigger!
What?
It's too big!
What's going on?
It's a monster!
Yes, this is the exit in front of the park.
What? A monster is swimming in the river?
What?
It's alive!
Nesiko!
It's a turtle!
I don't understand.
Where did it come from?
Anyway, let's evacuate the citizens to a safe place!
Hurry!
What are you doing?
You're not here, are you?
This is noisy.
I should look around.
It's there!!!
You're not here, are you?
Where are you?
No, no, no!
"Fought for a
My beloved, what do you think of my special uniform?
Please come, Bu-chan!
Senpai, what do you think of the special uniform?
It fits perfectly.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience, Nakagawa.
We have arranged the daily necessities for the time being.
If there is anything else you need, please let me know.
I have to stay here for a while.
Well, it's convenient because the room is close.
Even so, everyone is small.
It's like a well-made figure.
It's about the future, Ohara-kun.
Director, I will take charge of the director.
Please take care of Ryotsu so that he can work as a detective.
But even if it's a job, it's not that kind of thing.
Ryotsu should have something to do.
I'm sure something.
Director!
What's wrong?
Carrier accident!
What?
Ryotsu, it's work!
Hey, how about that?
The carrier is broken.
Don't worry. I'm a policeman.
It's dangerous, so everyone get down.
It's like the first gauge railway model.
This is really before I woke up.
When the steam train ran conditioning, he was having trouble getting to the correct track.
It's done.
Eh? Is it you? The cause of the traffic jam?
Right?
Can't be helped.
I can't help but feel sorry for you.
Look here!
Everyone, get off the way.
Go. Go!
What? The ?
Hey, come down.
What? Did you want to catch an octopus with the TV?
Did you get hurt?
Can't you get down?
Ryo-san, help me!
Ryo-san, I'm begging you!
Ryo-san, it's a big problem!
I was busy today as well.
Well, I guess I'll go to bed.
What's wrong, chief?
Sometimes it's good to sleep while looking at the stars outside.
I think that's a good thing.
You seem to be working hard every day.
Yeah, I can't skip work because it stands out.
The chief of the office is very happy with your work lately.
If he's happy, I want him to show his face a little more.
Like, "I want a feast of 1000 yakiniku."
You can't make it a special treat for yourself all of a sudden.
There are other staff at work, too.
You can make it a special treat for me.
It's a special treat.
He's here!
What's going on here?
"I want a feast of 1000 yakiniku."
I want a feast of 1000 yakiniku.
The chief of the office is going to give me a thank-you letter.
I'm so glad.
"Thank you?"
That's right.
"Thank you".
I would like to thank you on behalf of the Katsushika and the citizens for your new work.
Thank you.
Katsushika's President, Tonda Gomez.
Thank you? Is this all you have?
100 rice and 100 million yen in cash?
Good job!
You've got a lot of people, and you only have one of these?
You're eating a sign for the emergency every day!
Ohara-kun!
Hey, Ryotsu! Don't get carried away!
I'm grateful for the thanks you've received!
I understand.
If you don't reward me, I won't work anymore.
But I might get in the way of the citizens' lives.
Idiot! You're still a policeman!
It's better to be a policeman.
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going, Ryotsu?
Senpai, he left...
Ryo-chan...
If this goes on, I'll survive on my own!
Koji was late and got drunk!
I'll be saved!
Huh? Leave it to me!
Eizi!
Hurry up and fix it!
Cut!
Good! Perfect!
Thank you!
I'll leave the fish to you!
Okay!
I'm tired!
Good work!
Senpai, good work!
Yeah.
What's the schedule for tomorrow?
Tomorrow is the guest of the elementary school sports club and the cleaning of the department in front of the station.
The maintenance of the roof of the Tokyo Dome and the shooting of the Dogira vs. Mecha Dogira.
That's the continuation of our shooting.
That's a lot of work.
There's a rumor that we'll earn our annual salary in a day.
Senpai, you're amazing!
I'm doing hundreds of people's work alone.
It's a matter of course.
I'm tired, so I'll go to bed today.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah!
Good night, senpai!
I'll be better!
Well, then, introduce your friends.
On the way to the program, an emergency press conference will be held from the prime minister's office.
W, what is it?
Emergency communications have just come in from President America.
In ten hours, a large-duty meteorite is going to fall on Earth.
And the meteorite army will fall precisely on Earth.
A new location has been discovered.
That location is the Katsushikaku in Tokyo, Kameari!
Kameari?
I wonder if we can get it done by Ryochi, Ohara-kun.
Even if you say meteorites, each one of them look small.
There is no other way.
Ryochi will do something about it.
What? Meteorites?
The price will change depending on the size.
Idiot! Don't be so serious, Ryochi!
The residents of Kameari have already started to evacuate.
Why don't you get a part-time job?
It's better to protect the Kameari town than that!
We're also living here, chief.
We're starving, so we're going to have to pay a lot of money.
I understand.
I'll do what you say.
Let's hear what you have to say.
Chief, please don't make Ryochi feel bad.
It's fine. It's fine.
Well, I'll have a 1,000 serving of Otoro sushi,
1,000 servings of grilled meat from the Matsuzaka-class,
and a 1,000 serving of Chinese food as dessert.
If you'll let me eat it every day for a year, I'll take it.
Idiot!
You're still being polite because you're obsessed with the weakness of others!
There are other ways.
I don't need your help anymore!
Go!
Ohara-kun!
Ohara-kun, what are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
Ryochi is just about to...
Soon, a number of meteorites will fall in this area.
It's dangerous, so please evacuate immediately.
I repeat, a number of meteorites will fall in this area soon.
Are you still there?
Ryo-chan, do you remember the thank-you letter we received from the general manager?
Thank-you letter?
That is what President Ohara asked the general manager for.
What did he say?
I can't raise the salary immediately, but I want to at least make Ryo-chan's salary.
Hey!
The person who asked the chief and the police chief to keep Ryo-san in the Kazushika office was Chief Ohara.
Chief Ohara?
I think you hate Chief Ohara, but that's not true. Chief Ohara loves you.
Oh, they're already here. You guys, evacuate quickly! Hurry!
Roger that, Ryo-san.
There they are!
Get out of here!
Gah!
Look! Chief Ryotsu is shooting back the meteorite!
Ryotsu!
We just received some new information.
We found that the center of this meteorite army is a giant meteorite, not a gas.
The diameter of this giant meteorite is almost the same as the Kamiari district, and the damage caused by its fall is...
Tokyo's disappearance?
Ah!
Tokyo's disappearance!
We need to evacuate Ryotsu!
Damn it! They're still coming!
Ryotsu!
Ryotsu! It's over! The giant meteorite is coming! Run away now! Hurry!
How big is the giant meteorite?
It's about the same size as the Kamiari district. Tokyo will be destroyed!
What did you say?
Run away, Ryotsu! Run away with full power!
It's the Super Ultra Hyper Jumbo Manju!
That's right!
Over there!
Ezaki!
Oh, it's Gorilla-kun!
Do you have Hyper Manju?
If you have Hyper, there's a lot here!
I'll take all of it!
You should evacuate quickly too!
Gah!
Dyamu!
Good job.
Good!
Is that it?
Gyaaaaa!
Please watch over the head!
We did it! The meteorite's orbit has changed!
The Moon Dome since the center of the Earth is saved!
We're saved!
Ryozu, you did a great job!
We did it, Bujou!
Now, Ryozu the police chief, who saved humanity, is back on Earth...
Could it be...
Is this Bujou?
That's impossible!
You're fired!
At that time I felt some kind of strange feeling
That's why, I came along the street at daybreak
And walked only in the street light
Everyone was just a young child, but everybody had forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a silhouette in his eyes
Don't go up there, old lady!
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone there
There's a turtle over there
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
What?
You call coffee "South American bean soup"?
If you force me to say it in Japanese, it's hard to understand!
I'm really into Japanese, but why is Kami-san an American?
Next time, "Yamato Damashii Hozonkai"
Thank you!
There's a turtle over there
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!