Golden hair, fierce! Spring is fierce!
Here is Katsushikaku Toadjack Arhurator
Mass production power full-scale special
The most dangerous survival
Subtitles by Subdivers - Genki Bakuhatsu Ganbaruger
Detective Nakagawa, no
Now we can go overseas for training together.
What?
Now we will complete the boys' club.
Wait a minute!
Get out of my way!
Mr. Ryo!
What are you doing here?
Chief, you are so mean!
Why didn't you tell me that I have the shooting test?
It's useless to teach the guy who has been absent for 10 years.
What are you talking about?
The winner and the runner-up have the advantage to go overseas for training.
Do you think you can go overseas for training?
Of course.
What's so funny?
You don't have to train, but you can't win the top position.
You are just making an excuse.
Stop it.
I'm not kidding.
I always get the best score in the shooting test at the game center.
Idiot!
Don't do the same as the game.
Anyway,
I can't give you the lowest score.
Go home now.
I'll definitely go out.
No, you can't.
I will.
You can't.
Mr. Ohara, it's fine.
Let Ryo shoot.
But…
It's a good chance to know how important the shooting training is.
If I get the lowest score, I won't leave you alone.
Don't worry.
Chief Kan-kichi Ryo will go.
I will.
Good luck.
What?
What does he do?
You sure?
I am also a hearing man.
Good luck.
Excuse me who's shooting?
I'll shoot.
OK
Why do you shoot?
Well…
Hey,
Huh?
-Boo-stah! -Boo-stah!
You! You deliberately made a mistake at the end!
Ryo-tsu Shunsa, the first to make a mistake, gets 99 points!
Therefore, the winner of the men's division, Nakagawa Shunsa, is the second-place winner, Ryo-tsu Shunsa!
I can't believe it!
It's just like this.
Ryo-sama! It's wonderful!
Now we can go to overseas training together!
You made a mistake on purpose!
I'm very excited to go to training with my seniors!
It was on purpose, Ryo-tsu!
You're doing great, Ryo-chan! You've reviewed it!
It was on purpose, right? Say it was on purpose!
I did it. A vacation abroad with coffee!
Please say it was on purpose!
Right, Ryo-tsu?
Why is it so?
The only reason I'm happy with my senior is because I love my senior!
Why don't they have aТыO?
But they are the only ones who are happy with it.
If it was on purpose, it would be a pity.
It's this one.
Okay, okay, that's it!
But, I also couldn't wear it!
It seems that only my senior and I can find a title offer for the company.
It's just your knowledge, Shun!
Keiichi Shinpachi's knowledge is what's important!
Listen, everyone.
Really?
I'll take care of the training and take you to the dream full course of Patsukin Bakunyugyaru.
But I don't have Otohime-chan...
Oh, right. Then I'll have to take care of Patsukin Bakunyugyaru myself.
It's a shame. I'm a Patsukin Bakunyugyaru, but it's a waste.
Patsukin Bakunyugyaru, Patsukin Bakunyugyaru, Patsukin Bakunyugyaru...
Senpai, I'll follow you!
I see. I'm counting on you, Captain Kirikomi!
Okay...
Ryo-sama!
What's a Patsukin Bakunyugyaru?
That's...
No, no, no! Don't do that!
Get off! Get off!
Well then, shall we go?
Huh? Where are Senpai and Honda-san?
They were here just now.
It's about Ryo-chan, so maybe they're going to have a Patsukin Bakunyugyaru party at the beach.
Ryo-sama, wait!
Hey, Honda, I'm glad you came.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well then, let's go!
Yes!
We'll apply oil for free.
If you wish, we'll give you a massage.
How about a massage?
What are you doing?
Ryo-sama, I'm here to practice, aren't I?
Honda-san will go to Otohime-chan, too.
No, don't bother about that!
Oh, you brought a lot.
Of course.
You can even shoot guns that you can't shoot in Japan here.
Senpai and Honda-san, please take whatever you like.
Oh, is that so?
I'll be right back.
Good luck with your practice.
Good luck!
Ryo-chan, did you hear that?
A male instructor is going to become a great man at a young age.
A great man?
Even though he's Japanese, it can't be that he'd become a Greenberry of the American Army.
He's been fighting wars all over the world.
After that, he was also a sniper who did many things for the mafia in New York.
Hehehe...
Interesting!
We should have him do a lot of work, right Honda?
Huh?
I'm going home!
Don't be scared. I'm here!
Huh?
Why? No one's here.
You're late!
Huh?
I, Saigo Borubo, will teach you all for a week.
Don't be late from now on.
What?
I'm going to do it!
You scared me, bastard!
Listen to this.
Huh?
Next time you come any closer, I'll kill you.
Not yet!
Gcrr!
We won't let you pass!
Hehehe...
I expected that. I've had enough of thatك
As expected, this is the Special Training festival training. We've had enough of that.
I don't want to be beaten anymore.
I want to go home.
What are you going to do with that?
The morning training is just for the sake of it.
The afternoon training is even more difficult.
I want to go home.
Well...
Stop!
Idiot!
Why did you suddenly shoot?
He was just looking for his wallet!
In New York, they say that if you put your hand in a place, you will be shot.
Even if you shoot, it's still a fair defense.
This is not New York!
I see.
This is a failure.
Who is the guy who just made a gun hammer?
I'm asking for backup.
Idiot!
Where is the enemy?
That's what I'm talking about.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
The body reacts to any sound in the Green Beret era.
This is a failure again!
I want to go home.
However, this is not enough to eat or drink.
We will hold the gun.
Is this okay?
OK.
What is the bulge on your chest?
This is...
Show me what you got!
What's this?
I'm sure you didn't hide anything else.
Yes.
Really?
Absolutely.
Now, Nagagawa, take a look at your pants.
I have a bad PPK.
There is a chief here.
What do you mean?
No.
For the sake of the moment.
Stretch your right hand as much as you can.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't care.
I said stretch your right hand.
Yes.
You are a hidden beast.
The Beretta Minx is on my left arm, too.
In this case, take off your clothes and check thoroughly.
No way.
Six small automatic guns, four Derringers, 120 bullets, three main guns, one plastic bomb, and six knives.
What?
You are hiding the full sound of the motel behind your back.
No.
What?
What are you talking about?
You are a walking weapon.
I'm sorry.
What?
What is this bulge?
This is not a Desert Eagle.
Oh.
It's gone.
What is a Desert Eagle?
It's a Nyanbu squid.
Excuse me.
I just got a little bit of a problem.
We will take care of these.
No.
All right.
Now, let's go.
A Coke.
Thank you!
It's a
Cucumber.
Where is it?
It's here.
Cucumber!
He's more pathetic than me.
This is terrible.
If Ryo is here, he'll go eat lunch with me.
That's fine.
We'll eat lunch together.
But...
I saw him!
What are you doing?
Oh, did I do too much?
Are you all right?
Who is this weirdo?
He's our instructor, Mr. Saigo Borubo.
He's so pathetic.
This place used to be full of men.
But a beauty came closer and...
My nose...
Please use it if you like.
Thank you.
What?
What's this?
The shock that pierced through this body...
It's beautiful.
I need a handkerchief.
Sorry.
This is strange.
I can't tell the difference between this beauty and this nose.
Could it be...
Connected by this woman?
Actually...
Yes?
Well...
Please have a date with me.
I'll go back to my room and get changed.
Let's meet in front of the fountain in front of this park in 30 minutes.
B-But...
Well...
Bye.
Ryo-sama! I don't want to date that kind of guy!
Please do something!
Hmm...
No, you should date him, Maria!
What?
No way!
That's terrible...
That's too terrible!
Ryo-chan, what are you saying?
Don't get excited!
Listen to me carefully!
He's a strange man who shoots at anyone, anywhere, and to everyone.
He's a strange man.
I don't think he's a strange man. He's a strange man.
I think the reason why he's so strange is because he's been living in a male-only, military-only, New York-style, and male-only job.
That's understandable.
He probably never dated a woman.
If he's on a date, it's a good chance to change his personality.
That's true, but Maria is a man.
That's why he's a man.
He's just as strange as he is.
But still, I don't want to date any other men except for Ryo-sama.
Maria, should I kill you?
What?
We'll be in training with that walking weapon for a week.
We can shoot him with any gun, but it's not that strange!
So, Maria, we'll be saved if you beat him up here!
Do you understand, Maria?!
...
Understood!
I'm going on a date for Ryo-sama!
You don't need to worry about it, Maria.
We have to follow him quietly...
I'll go with you, Ryo.
Will you come with me, Ryo?
Well, I guess.
I knew it! You're Ryo!
I'm so happy!
I told you not to get in the way!
There she is.
She's coming at the right time.
She doesn't have a rifle, does she?
Look closely.
She's holding a gun with her right hand.
She has a gun on her left side.
She has a revolver on her left and right.
Her pockets are full of bullets.
She's right.
She still has a gun even though she took it just now.
She's so cowardly.
She always has a good position to fight.
She's always good to her eyes.
She's like a SP for the mercenary guard.
She's a very good date.
Maria, start the operation.
I'll follow you in the car.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry. I got close from behind.
My name is Asato Ai.
Everyone calls me Maria.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry.
I'm here for a little...
Well, let's go.
Okay.
Are you okay, Maria?
Don't you regret it a little bit, Senpai?
A little bit.
Why are you wearing a suit and jungle boots?
Well, it's easier to move when something happens.
It's iron-coated, so I can beat a cow in one shot.
I was on the battlefield as a mercenary for a long time.
After that, I became very diligent.
Maria, hide!
Are you having fun?
What's wrong?
The mafia once shot a car.
I was shot by a car, so it's hard to get close to a strange car.
Oh no, oh no, you're too close.
I'm sorry.
You're a great guy, Mr. Volvo.
There was a shotgun in that flower pot.
I can't get close without flying.
That is the M60 tank with the reactive armor.
Reactive armor is explosive reaction armor.
In other words, even if you're hit by a war missile,
it's the latest armor that reduces damage due to the reaction of the armor explosion.
Do you understand?
Yes.
If you think about where you're going on a date,
it's a gang movie and a war movie.
Maria, I feel sorry for you.
You've been looking for weapons for three hours.
Be with me.
No, be with me on the premise of marriage.
What?
No, I don't mean anything.
This time, I went to a sports gym.
What kind of dating course is it?
It's unique.
Poor Maria.
Alright, let's go!
15!
He comes to this gym every day.
He's training his body, isn't he?
Oh, my!
Is it a punching ball?
I'll try it.
It's dangerous, so please stay away from it.
Yes.
Amazing! He's really good at it!
I thought I'd lost my grip a little bit.
That bastard got carried away.
Hey, Maria!
Yes?
You try it, too.
Is that okay?
Yeah, do it!
Yes!
I'll try it, too!
Are you okay?
Yes!
I'm sorry.
It's amazing!
Amazing punching power!
I was practicing kickboxing a little bit.
Kickboxing?
I can't imagine it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That's right.
There is a pool in the back.
It's wide and the atmosphere is great.
But what about the swimsuit?
There's a rental.
Let's go.
One, two, three!
Two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four.
Let's get married...
to...
Well, it's true that...
I'm waiting.
Oh?
Beautiful!
When I was at a job full of men,
I didn't know that women are so beautiful!
Um...
What is that?
This is...
It's the Heckler & Koch P-11.
It's a pistol that can be fired underwater.
Unless you have this in the pool,
you will be targeted at places where you can't use your weapons, such as the pool or the pool.
I had this experience while I was in the mercenary service.
That's why I kept my holster on even when I took a bath.
This school is so cheap.
It's almost a pervert school.
The pool is really big!
Ah, uh, Maria...
Huh?
A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-a nice weather.
I'm going to make a "hito-oyaki!"
He's so powerful.
It's a big trouble surrounding us.
Ah, ugh.
Huh?
I-I-I'm screwed!
Get out of the pool!
Get out of here!
You're gonna make me the captain, huh?
How can you swim in that form?
Maria, it's the enemy! Hide!
Um, is that explosion yours, Mr. Boruto?
Huh?
Oh, it's true!
Oh, everyone, please be quiet! I accidentally shot the main gun in the middle of...
It's not accidentally, that idiot!
After all, he's a walking weapon.
Oh, Maria and the others!
Yeah?
You're going to climb into the diving platform, aren't you?
Oh, no. I can't keep up with you up there.
Maria!
Um, how far are we going to climb?
It's a great opportunity, so let's go to the top!
It's an amazing height...
M- Maria!
Y- Yes?
Actually, um, that...
Ge- ge- ge- ge- ge-
Nooo!
It looks like we're in a dangerous state.
What should I do?
There's no point! Just tell her that you're a man!
I- I understand.
Actually, I have something to tell her.
Huh?
A- a confession of love from Maria-san?
Actually, I'm a man!
What?
Ahaha!
Is this a joke?
I don't want to hear it at a time like this!
A- more importantly, Maria-san, me and...
Ryo-sama, you don't believe me at all.
What should I do?
It can't be helped. I'll show you the evidence that you're a man!
What? It can't be helped. I'll show you the evidence that you're a man!
That's right! You have to show that evidence to a man, Maria!
I- I can't do such a disgusting thing!
I don't care what happens, Maria!
I don't want to do it!
Do it, Maria!
I- I don't want to do it!
Look closely at me, please!
M- Maria-san, you're...
I- I don't want to do it!
No way...
If you're one meter from the pool, it's just a pool...
They're too hard to save.
I- I- that's impossible...
I- I was lying down... I was lying down...
It's a disaster!
I really did something bad to Mr. Bulbul yesterday.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks to you, I don't have to learn from that armory instructor.
If you had learned from him, you wouldn't have lost so many lives.
Fantasia!
Good morning!
Well, I was executed yesterday.
Why are you here?
I'm here!
Didn't you get hospitalized?
No, I didn't get hospitalized for a scratch like this.
You fell from such a high place.
I'm training.
You're not a human.
Well, I'm sorry about yesterday.
No, don't worry about it.
I thought it was strange.
I didn't get any nosebleeds even though I was such a beautiful woman.
Anyway, Maria.
Now that you know that I'm a man, you should train with Mr. Ryotsu and the others.
What?
I'm fine. I'll do it.
Don't bother.
If you can train that punch, you can do a Green Belly.
What? John?
I told you not to get so close to my back.
I'm sorry.
I got an airmail from America.
America?
This is...
What's wrong?
You suddenly look pale.
It's an unfortunate letter.
That's all.
What?
Captain Bakuryu is coming.
And today.
Captain Bakuryu?
Who is he?
He's the commander of the Green Belly.
He's a soldier who broke through many shurabas.
He's a good-looking man.
He's the commander of the Volvo.
He's a terrible pervert.
You're right.
It's not a joke.
He's a scary man who's called the evil army.
He's not an army.
He's a colonel.
The toxicity of the colonel is not kidding.
How many times have I tried to escape from here?
I'm afraid that the captain's squad is the strongest in the world.
Someone is enough!
This way, we won't be defeated.
Don't suddenly lower your hand.
The whole body shall gather in the waiting room.
It's only a bullet 방 agreed.
You should change your clothes too.
No matter how much I try, am I going overboard?
That can be said because you don't know the terror of the colonel.
It can be said because you don't know the terror of the colonel.
He's the one who's going to hit me instead of greeting me.
I don't care even if I hit a shooting ball.
Don't scare me.
Anyway, you should change as you were told.
Like Mr. Honda.
That was quick.
I want to go home!
Are you going to send rocket launchers to the Balkans
and start a war?
This is not enough.
I want a tank as well.
What?
This music is Wagner's Walcure.
Why can I hear it from outside?
The colonel asked me
if I could hear it.
It must be the sound of a helicopter.
I knew it.
Isn't it a helicopter from the mass media?
That is...
It's an Apache!
Why is the American military aircraft here?
They're coming this way.
Get them all!
All of you get on the wall!
I didn't expect the rocket launchers
to come all of a sudden.
I told you so.
Stop it!
My gosh! Did you miss it?
It's about the colonel.
I'll go back ten times, no, a hundred times!
Get out of here!
You've gone too far, Polvo!
This is what happened because I used a rocket launcher!
What are you talking about? You must have prepared that!
That's to protect myself.
It's not for attacking!
Um, I came down, but...
I'm sorry.
It's been a while, Bolgo Saigo.
Is this the colonel?
It's been a while, colonel!
You look good in military clothes.
As usual.
Thank you!
You're too naive, Saigo!
I really shot him!
He's a terrible man!
He's not that bad.
But he can't be a soldier who's one year older.
We're not soldiers!
You! You're not a soldier who's one year older.
You're not a soldier who's one year older.
I don't remember having you as my colonel!
Shut up!
I won't forgive you for your words.
You're too naive!
You destroyed the training ground!
You're way too naive!
Goodness, sir!
The child of sums that has to be taken down completely.
That's the key that 기억ed my life.
That's the intensive rank of survival.
Even so, it was a big scratch, wasn't it?
Yes.
Young lady Oji-ho!
You noticed this in good place.
Yes, sir!
Your face is just a small part.
This fight is my history.
Amazing!
This is my history.
This is after I was shot in Vietnam.
This is done after I was shot in Vietnam.
This is the wound at Falkland Line.
This is Wei Ruan Line.
However...
That.
thady
When he was arrested by his wife.
It seems like there is something wrong with him.
It's easy to get an accordion for such a long distance.
No, no, no. He is the kind of person who wants to talk.
Do you think he'll be fine, anyway?
What do you mean by "I think"?
I do not think so.
Excuse me? This is my director's room.
I thought so too.
Ouch!
You're injured because you're weak after all!
What?
What do you mean?
You're quite brave.
Well, not really.
What's the name of this lawless man?
I call him Ryotsu.
Mr. Ryotsu, you're not afraid of anything.
I can't believe you're giving me your opinion.
I'll give you something wonderful.
What's that?
It's the best gift.
It's a present.
Oh, it's on my back!
What did you put in it?
Tell me!
Did you see the power of the Shiryudan?
This is what happens when you make me angry.
Maybe I used too little medicine.
Maybe I should have used more.
You idiot!
You're not a kid!
Don't use things like a knee beater!
By the way, why are you here, Colonel?
I forgot.
Hey!
4th
Here! I'm Ryotsu. Nice to meet you!
I'm Honda.
I'm Volvo.
Nice to meet you, I'm Jody.
Jody is my daughter.
You're lying.
It's true. I'm a mother.
I see.
Actually, I chose you as my bride for Jody's wedding.
Nice to meet you.
You're talking too much.
Think about it, Porubo.
No matter how good a woman you are, your father is that guy.
If you say so.
Saigo, can I make this nice buddy yours?
If you marry her, you'll have 1000 times more land in Yankees Stadium.
1000 times more land in Yankees Stadium?
Captain, please give her to me.
Don't apologize.
There are many other candidates.
I will finally choose one among them.
I see.
I believe that a man must be strong.
I know a strong man.
I will choose one among those strong men.
But, Porubo hates women.
What the hell are you talking about?
Captain, I'm confident that you're strong.
Please choose me as your candidate.
You're dirty. How dare you sell yourself!
Ryo!
Nakagawa and Honda will choose you as their candidate.
I...
Run!
Captain!
Mr. Nakagawa!
It's a rubber club.
What?
You're wearing a bulletproof vest.
Yeah.
All right.
If Saigo wins, you pass the test.
Yay!
Me too?
What's up with your happiness, Ryo?
I'm so frustrated.
He's that kind of man.
Give up.
Well, I'm fine.
So, I'll quit this time.
What?
You!
You're a coward!
Bust 95.
West 58.
Hip 90.
Keep moving!
Do you hate this nice body?
Ah, but I have Otohime...
You're going to insult your daughter?
What?
No, I don't mean that!
Then, you can pass the test.
Yes, of course, I'll pass.
What?
Why did you have to say that from the beginning?
Good luck.
Oh.
Ah...
Yes! Honda Hayato will do his best!
Alright! Then, the three of us will go to Africa for the final test!
Yeah! Africa!
Africa!
Now, here in Africa, we will hold the competition of my daughter Jody's pick of flowers.
You are all chosen from many candidates, and you are all very tough.
The only man in this world who is the strongest man,
and you are all ready to marry Jody.
This is the final battle of Africa's great ultra course.
You will pass this course and win the one who reaches the goal as soon as possible.
The course is, from here, you will cut through the savanna and cross the river,
and then cross the savanna and the desert, and the summit of the mountain after that.
The course is 100 kilometers long.
Now, I hope you will consider it.
Wait a minute!
What?
It's too much if the enemy has a knife in Africa with a dog!
Yeah! It's too much if the enemy has a knife in Africa with a dog!
It's true. At least, a rifle is enough.
That's not the case!
A man who is really strong has a knife and a gun.
Whoever has a grudge should be disqualified here.
Yeah, I'm fine as long as I'm disqualified.
Everyone, be careful and do your best.
Chu.
You...
Okay, I'll do my best!
If you buy it and marry, you will get 1000 times the land of Yankees Stadium.
In other words, it's worth a million dollars.
How can you stop now?
I'll be a flower boy.
I'll become a true thief.
I can't lose this match.
Then, get ready for the position.
The course is full of mountains and valleys.
There may be a hole to fall.
What's that?
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Well...
But, I can't do anything.
Senior, if I really fall, you will pull me up, won't you?
Don't worry. I'll go with you.
Okay.
Ouch!
That was close. It wasn't just a hole to fall.
That's right.
I'll go with you.
Senior, the movie trap is over.
Hello.
I'm so sorry.
You have to be careful until the end.
Right?
Yes.
Is- is it really a trap?
Let's move outside.
Means the hadron has been removed.
We're coming!
Yes.
Geez.
It's a trap!
Yes.
I think it's a trap too.
It's a trap.
Oh.
I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
What should we do?
It's very dangerous!
Yes.
Poof!
So, Mr. Ryozu did it that way.
I-I...
Yeah!
I-I will definitely be in danger!
I will never allow danger!
Yes, look at that!
Kiryu ability:
Zzz! Zzz! Zzz!
Nooooo!
Hey! That hurts! Let go!
Lucky.
But what did I get this afternoon?
Zzz!
What are you doing here, Borugo?
Help me!
If you go out, you'll be in their way.
I-I-I'm going home.
Huh?
Senpai, that...
What?
Help me!
It's a ostrich's toy.
What is this?
Hey, look at that!
I see.
You can't tell by its appearance.
But I feel like I'll be exposed once I wake up.
But if you get eaten by it,
it'll be an embarrassment for you to the end.
You're right.
I don't think there's any animal like this.
Help me!
You've made a mistake.
Oh, no!
that would be awful.
What?
How about a'mari tout?
How about that?
That's a good idea.
We did it!
Brood of a monster.
But thanks to you, I was saved.
Mr. Ryotsu, I won't waste your sacrifice, so please make it up to me.
How many are there? How many are there?
Your luck is that you bit my stone head.
Let's go!
You know how to play.
It's a goal! I see the goal!
Who's going to climb that?
There's no way I can climb that!
It's impossible. It's impossible.
Alright, let's go!
It's impossible! We'll die if we fall down the middle of the road!
What about the others?
Don't you have the intention of marrying your daughter and becoming a rich man?
I want to go home!
Why are you doing that to me?
Ryotsu! You're not going to lose!
From now on, the real hell awaits you.
Begin attack!
Two target fighters!
What did you come up with, you fisherman?!
This is the kind of person the Colonel is!
Oh, no!
Lucky! You're gonna be my
I'm gonna be your
lucky
The last warning is left!
There's more?
Th- this is...
The last battle is against Jody!
Oh, are you alright?
Hang in there, Saigo!
Why are you fighting against Jody?
A man who loses to a woman has no right to do so.
There's no need to hold back.
Jody is a Jajauma girl who fought against ten men in the Marine Corps and sent them to the hospital.
That's right!
You can fight seriously!
Alright!
Try winning and making me your bride!
From now on, Jody will have the final match against Corvo Saigo!
Finally, Jajauma girl is...
It's time to get married, Saigo.
No, I'm not going to lose to you, Borubo.
You're alive, aren't you?
Borubo is strong against men because of the military accident, but he has no immunity against women.
The match is clear.
I see.
What's wrong? Why aren't you fighting?
After all, it's not right to fight against a woman as a man!
I don't need your help, Hatsuyo!
Then, I won't hold back!
You're the one who should be fighting!
What?!
Oh!
No!
Change!
My... my boobs...
Are you alright? I thought you'd be able to take a good look at yourself...
My boobs... I thought you'd be able to take a good look at yourself...
How could you be so weak?
It can't be helped. Now, Hanamu Koerobi is back to his original form.
Jody, let's go home!
Yes, Papa!
Well, farewell!
Goodbye!
After all, it's a waste of time to be a bone-dead.
Huh? But, senpai, how are we going to go home from here?
Huh?
Hey! You're going to leave us behind?!
Give it back to me!
In the meantime, we'll choose Hanamu Koerobi Part 2.
If you survive until then, we'll let you participate again!
I'll be waiting!
Then, I wish you all good luck.
Hey, hey, wait! Wait!
Huh?
Ready, set, go!
I must know something!
I have to do something to win!
A lot of people will like Hanamu Koerobi.
I'd appreciate it!
Thanks!
You'll be into my play.
Of course, I won't.
Can I do that?
No way.
Kid, you're really bad!
No way!
Your plan was so difficult!
Agree with me, please?
I'm starting my return!
That's a great success!
That's my favorite!
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
God"
"The
Great
♪ It's an embarrassing song, the energy ♩
♪ Forget about the past ♩
♪ And always hold on to your first feeling ♩
♪ The rainbow-colored star shines brightly ♩
♪ I don't know anymore ♩
♪ If everyone comes here ♩
♪ It's the final energy like a dream ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday ♩
♪ Draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ The rainbow-colored star will shine and draw a circle ♩
♪ This is good, right? ♩
♪ There's no excuse, right? ♩
♪ The rainbow-colored star will shine and draw a circle ♩