Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♩
♪ The brightest and the best harem ♩
♪ Passing through the new era ♩
♪ The hero is diving alone ♩
♪ It's not just a trend ♩
♪ The more you wear it, the more you'll be loved ♩
♪ Let it ring! ♩
♪ Everybody can do it! ♩
♪ Let's run and run ♩
♪ Dreams can't stop ♩
♪ Let's go to the sea tomorrow ♩
♪ Love you, love! ♩
♪ Everybody can do it! ♩
♪ It's a little dark, but it doesn't hurt to spit it out ♩
♪ Hold your excited curiosity ♩
♪ And throw it hard and high ♩
♪ A light that reaches the end of the road ♩
♪ Let's try to overcome this! ♩
Look at that!
That's the result of your previous medical exam.
Did you notice anything?
Your blood sugar is high.
You should be careful of your urine.
Where are you looking?
Here, here!
Your body is as big as 35 years old.
35 years old, 35 years old!
Wow.
You're young.
Is there a secret?
Actually,
I went to an athletic club about 3 months ago
and started building my body.
Athletic club?
That's right.
I went there because I was invited by my friends,
and it was very effective.
I'm not going to lose to young people.
No, I'm not going to lose to Ryotsu.
By the way,
you seem to have a nice face lately.
That's right.
I've also fixed my stiff shoulders.
What do you think, Terai?
Why don't you go there?
Oh,
but I'm not good at sports.
I'm tired.
Don't worry about that.
I'll start with the computer.
I'll test my strength with a computer
and start with the menu that suits the person.
I'm really good at it.
Good morning, Chief.
What do you mean, good morning?
You seem to be living a poor life as usual.
Do you think you can get a proper job with that?
Don't worry about that.
I have confidence in my strength.
I'm making a plastic model right now
and I've been working two nights.
The night before that,
I've completed two new games.
Before that,
I've had a drink with my friends.
You idiot!
I think his voice is more powerful than usual.
Is this the result of the athleticism?
Athleticism?
What's wrong, Chief?
Don't call me athletic.
I haven't eaten yet.
You should train your head
before you train your body.
It's not food.
Athletic club is a place
where you train your body
and exercise for your health.
It's where you can train your body
with the latest fitness machines
and computer-based physical examination.
It's a place where you can train your body
with the latest physical examination.
You know that.
You're going to get paid.
Why are you so stupid?
You're going to exercise
with your money?
You don't understand, do you?
It's common sense
to spend money on beauty and health.
In the West,
people who can't quit smoking
and those who are obese
are considered people
who can't even manage their own body.
They can't become elite businessmen.
You're right.
You should experience both
when you can't even manage your own body.
I'm telling you,
you don't have to go there.
You have the strength.
You idiot!
I'm telling you that
scientifically calculated exercise.
I'm telling you,
if you let me say it,
you're wasting your money.
What?
All right.
Then let's see
which one has more physical strength.
It's an athletic competition.
A competition?
Please stop it.
You're so mature.
Now,
are you scared?
Say whatever you want.
What's so funny
about wasting your physical strength?
You idiot.
What?
You always
talk a lot.
Well,
you don't have to compete.
I can see the result.
I understand.
Let's accept that challenge and stand up.
Oh,
you're motivated.
You don't have to regret it.
I have my own physical strength.
As proven,
I'm 35 years old.
But
let me decide the place.
Kamiari Athletic Square
from 2 o'clock tomorrow.
All right.
Be ready,
Ryotsu.
What's wrong with you,
Senpai?
I'm a little suspicious.
No,
I'm fine.
I don't care.
What the hell is going on?
Kamiari Athletic Square
open anniversary?
A hundred million yen
bargain.
There is nothing wrong with this.
We can do it.
What? Athletics?
I was just paying for it.
You don't have to join us.
I want 1 million yen.
I'll pay for the house.
Hey, I've been waiting.
Oh, you're all here?
Yeah, we're all here to join you.
I see.
You're all so generous.
Is there something you want?
I wonder.
Oh, that voice.
The great man of Kameari.
You're all here too?
I can't believe I'm meeting you here.
We're all here.
We should go somewhere else.
Don't say that.
Hey, Ryo.
I knew it.
There's a ramen shop, a model shop, and a bar.
Ryo, pay for the house right away.
What else can you say about money?
We don't want to say it.
If you don't want to, give it back.
Wait.
When I have the money, I'll give it back.
Money? What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Welcome, everyone.
From now on,
we will hold a survival race to earn one million yen.
What?
Ryo, what's going on?
Huh? What is it?
I didn't know.
You used me?
You used healthy sports to make money?
Well, well, Chief.
It doesn't change the game.
Or do you accept defeat without fighting?
No, I won't lose to you.
I won't lose to you.
Then please enter.
If you participate, please change into this.
What's this?
What?
It's a cockroach.
Then please move over here.
Why do I have to dress like this?
I don't want to.
Ooooo.
Wow, it's amazing.
A huge large facility.
What's going on here?
Are we going to be cockroaches?
Ice, this is Utsubi'saría.
Everyone, welcome.
I think there are more than 20 cesarias here.
He's been through a lot and has gone through a lot of obstacles.
That's a real "Gokiburi's secret experience".
I didn't expect him to make something like this.
If you're going to quit, it's a matter of time.
What? Who said I'm going to quit? Let's see who wins!
The goal is the bread on the rack in the fridge.
The person who reaches this bread within 30 minutes is the winner.
There are three courses on the floor.
You can choose which course you want to take.
Choose your favorite course.
It's the closest way to go from the front.
No, there's too much space.
There must be a trap.
I'll go through the top drain.
I hope you all have a good time.
Ready...
Start!
This is the best!
I'll do my best for my own money!
You've been imitating Ryo, haven't you?
Let's leave it to Ryo-chan's "Gokiburi-like" intuition.
Yes.
It's hard to climb, isn't it?
We'll break through the front!
One more chance!
The Gokiburi-like power is on the floor!
This is so real!
The electricity here is not strong.
I can't see it.
The floor is sticky.
Ouch!
What is this?
No way!
This is...
The Gokiburi-like power!
The floor is in a panic.
The drain is the correct answer.
The million yen is mine!
Ouch!
Help me...
Ryo-san, help me.
That's right.
If you can make the plastic and radio-con plug
work, I think I can help you.
That's terrible!
Yes, if you want.
Wait!
I understand, so help me!
I have to.
Come on, get caught here.
It's too late.
You're late.
You go first, Ryotsu.
Damn it.
It seems that it will disappear every minute.
We'll break through the next time it disappears.
One minute.
I can't wait one minute.
I can't believe this.
It's not human.
You're an adult, so you should not overdo it.
I can't believe it.
Chief, a criminal named Goto is waiting for you over there.
What? Where?
Where?
What?
You can't break through the world with your strength alone.
You have to use your head too.
Ryotsu.
You're tough. You go first.
You're dirty.
There's a criminal named Goto.
Chief, there's no idiot who gets caught with the same hand.
There are 10000 yen there.
What? 10000 yen?
He's so simple.
How about that, Ryotsu?
Try to do something with your proud head.
I'm still going to lose.
How far have you gone, Ryo?
What is this?
It's the rule.
Hey!
What? Ryo-chan is inside the Gokiburi Koi-koi?
Yeah, even if it's Ryo-tsu, it's impossible to escape from there.
If he's not there, there's no need to panic.
I was a little too focused on flying earlier.
I'm sorry.
A lot of things are coming together!
Wow! It made the impossible possible!
It's exactly the strength of a Gokiburi.
It's a wonderful strength.
Owner, the forecast is a high pace.
At this rate, a considerable number of people will be able to reach the goal in less than 30 minutes.
What?
That's why I told you.
What are you going to do with all the money you're going to spend?
I don't have the time to spend money right now!
I see.
I didn't know you'd use this.
I'm a little late.
I'm sorry.
What?
Go!
How is this a gas?
Did you see the power of the robot arm?
For the moment of truth...
I don't know if this is true, but I can still see the power of a gas.
I'm going to push on the gas.
I can't move it, so I'll push on the gas.
I can't move it.
I'm going to push on the gas.
But thanks to you, we got the stone.
It's here!
Ryo?
What? The Nakagawa are here?
Yes. They attacked us and we ran away.
But we couldn't get out of here.
Damn it. I can't stand here with a million yen.
Let's all get out of here at once.
What?
They are machines. They can't move fast.
While someone is being sacrificed, the others can move forward.
Interesting.
Good.
Listen, no one should be hurt.
Now! Go!
They are being attacked.
I knew it.
They are cheating!
Who is cheating?
Now!
Damn it! I'm the only one who got beaten!
Don't eat me!
I'm sorry, senpai.
Don't bother me. I'm not your opponent.
I'll teach you a lesson.
How is it?
It's hard to hit a vertical.
Ryo!
Chief, you are alive?
I won't forgive you.
Damn it.
Amazing! They are getting closer to the wall.
It's like a real cockroach.
I must get out of here at once.
It seems to be hard.
I'll be down in no time.
I can't.
Funny!
I'll make a good accident with this ball.
Don't touch this ball!
You too, you.
You're a calculative.
That's right!
dumbbell.
I heard it.
Don't follow me around! You're always imitating me!
You're the one who's imitating me!
You're a coward!
Senpai, you finally got beaten.
You've gone to such a good place.
He came out of there!
He's moving more than a real person!
The chief is pretty good too.
Hehehehe...
Chief! A present for you!
Now I've got a million yen!
Here you are!
There's nowhere to hide from me from now on.
As expected, the goalkeeper is tough.
He's not going to be able to keep up with me.
*slurp*
The goal is right in front of me.
The million yen belongs to me!
Here you are!
Here you are, chief!
I won't forgive you!
Please calm down!
A small voice...
Come here!
What's going on?
I found you!
*slurp*
Damn!
I was almost there!
You came all the way here and got beaten!
*slurp*
Okay!
Now that's my deal!
*slurp*
This feels bad.
I'm going to bring this over completely.
*slurp*
You don't think it's going to stop me?
All of you are done for.
Yeah, of all of us, all of you are done for!
Hey, chief!
You won't get away with this, not yet.
*slurp*
Wow!
Breaking!
One million yen!
Give me that!
What a mess!
How about this?
What's going on?
No! I'll be caught in the rain!
I'll be caught in the rain!
He flew away!
Damn it! My guts!
I did it!
I got one million yen!
One million yen!
Chief, I told you.
It's useless to pay for athletics.
Can't you change?
I liked it, so I got it as a souvenir.
Live as a cockroach for the rest of your life!
You did it, Ryo.
Congratulations!
I knew you'd do it.
And as promised...
There's a whole Komuro family over there!
Damn it!
If you can do it, then do it!
You're weak!
That's one million yen!
Damn it!
You're so strong.
It hurts!
Take this!
Hey!
Hey! Wait! I have a million yen!
Oh, this is...
What's wrong?
Look at this!
Recently, there was a witness saying that he saw a giant cockroach on the island of dreams.
And finally, we, the crew, succeeded in putting that figure on the camera.
Cockroach?
Then, please watch the shocking video.
A million yen.
My million yen.
Damn it! Where did it go?
My million yen!
What should I do?
I failed to create a picture of the precious photo asked by the director!
No good! No good! No good!
If you find it out, I will not forgive you.
I have to lie to you whatever it is.
Next time, we will reproduce the film "Kyoto Lyoko".
Please look forward to it.
Watch for the next time
Because time will pass
Don't look down
Let's laugh and live
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be clear
Bye bye
Let's wash our hands
Goodbye for the unpleasant things
Oh yeah
Let's live as we like
There are good things
Outside the door
Let's go
The sun is calling