"How to See the World Through a TV"
When you see a TV, make your room bright and stand out from the rest.
Come to me, you poor people!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
I'm sure it'll be all right.
Come to me, you jobless people!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the burning red clouds.
I'm sure it'll be all right.
You know what to do, right?
If you know what to do, come to me quietly.
He is a big man, but he knows only how to act.
"How to See the World Through a TV"
Why don't you teach me how to do it?
*Gasps*
*Buzzing*
Huh? The door is open?
I think I closed it before, but...
Uh... UwaaaaaaaaaAAAAAAAAAAA!!!
*Gasps*
He's completely ignoring us,
because he's aiming for a 5-minute-long
building from our station.
Oh, there it is.
Hello.
Ah, thank you for your hard work.
How's the fingerprint?
So far, there's no one other than the victim.
*Buzzing*
You're such a rude rascal.
How's the victim?
The cash is 50,000 yen,
and there are two bags from a famous luxury brand,
and a few accessories worth 500,000 yen.
And the victim?
He's been given a self-examination
during the inspection.
*Gasps*
There he is.
You locked the door properly, didn't you?
Yes, I locked it properly.
There was a safety lock on the window, too.
Yes, I put it on all the windows.
Even the key to the entrance
was installed with the latest technology.
But...
But the key to the entrance was open.
That means...
It was the pickings.
Didn't you open it from the inside?
Huh? From where?
Ah.
From the side of the street.
I entered from there.
No way.
It's the sixth floor.
Ryotsu! Don't say such a thing!
It's impossible!
I can do it. Please watch.
What are you doing?
Amazing.
How did you get so high up?
See? You can do it.
But it's easy to get to the sixth floor.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm going to climb up like this.
Amazing.
I really started climbing up.
That's amazing.
Captain! We have arrived at the sixth floor.
We will enter the room from here.
What a guy.
There is a key on the window of the balcony.
There is a safety shield.
I think it's from the bathroom.
There is a trace of opening it.
Ouch.
I'm removing the window of the bathroom.
What?
I'll remove it like this.
He went in.
What's wrong with him?
It's only been a minute since he climbed up.
It's very fast.
If you remove the glass, the window will remain closed.
That's why...
The safety shield does not work.
It's a professional's trick.
See?
That's pretty good, isn't it?
He just opened the door.
Why are you here?
He went out of the room
and get off the plane,
and talk to the coldness of the door.
What?
Are you the one who is the criminal?
Don't be silly.
Shut up!
Stop it!
Why do you always have a multi-purpose driver?
That's a keychain.
Nakagawa, check if there's anything else.
Yes.
What?
Stop it! Let go!
Senior.
Excuse me.
Multi-purpose driver, mini light, wire, knife...
Aren't they all theft tools?
No, they're for survival.
Wait a minute.
Stop it! Let go!
Let go!
Chief!
If I were a thief, I wouldn't be aiming for a student's room like this!
I'd aim for Nakagawa and Reiko's house!
That's true.
If you're a thief, why do you have to eat rice balls at convenience stores for a month?
You're a student, too.
You don't live alone in a house like this.
Even if you say that, your parents are safe because it's an auto-locked apartment.
That's a dangerous thing to say.
It's as dangerous as an auto-lock.
Is that so?
It's an auto-locked apartment, so it's hard to get in.
Once you get in, you'll think everyone is residents and will not doubt it.
Once you get in, you can go to any floor in the elevator.
It's a high floor, so there's no room for worry.
I tend to forget to close the lock.
I'm often targeted for a short time.
I steal it in just 2 minutes if I'm a professional.
You're too familiar.
You want me to come to the headquarters?
That's not it.
You're so familiar that you have practical skills.
It's natural to be suspected.
That's not it.
Anyway, the guy named Akishi is a friend of the residents.
He's right next to you.
You're familiar with that process.
His skill is great.
He can climb up here in a minute and enter.
It takes me 3 minutes.
You're aiming for an old man from the bank, aren't you?
That's easier.
I'm aiming for an old man from the bank.
Why?
I have a lot of money, and I can fool people easily.
It's a high success rate.
We have the same way of thinking.
I'm the one who's the human.
I don't make decisions like me.
What?
What is it?
You're a little unexpected.
You're not going to call the queen to this race.
This race is determined by three libre-based sharing machines.
É
Wearing a training suit.
OK.
If you get hit, bring something else for the next race.
See you.
Thanks.
What an officer.
It's so heartbreaking to be here.
I'm so sick of this.
Let's find another place.
The scene where the red Tenga 707 and the blue Tenga 745 were stolen.
It seems that the two gangs of criminals who were in the center of Adachi and Edogawa have come to the Katsushika district.
So, they started to increase patrol by increasing the number of patrol cars.
You can't do that kind of micro thing.
Ryo, Ryo-tsu.
There is a limit to patrol the Katsushika district without any problem if you increase the number of patrol cars.
That's true, but...
The criminals will be pressured and there is no other way to stop the damage.
There is. We have to be careful from the sky.
The sky? You mean using the helicopter?
The helicopter is too fast and the big Tenga is too small.
The sound of the propeller will make the criminals feel the opposite effect.
If the helicopter is not good, then it is the airplane.
Hmm...
There is a vehicle that can fly more slowly and have a sense of control over the criminals.
Anyway, leave it to me.
Okay, it's my chance.
Leave some cash.
Don't let the criminals know that it is empty.
Okay.
The residents will be back soon, so let's escape from the veranda.
Okay, there is no one.
Ahem.
Well, it's okay.
This doesn't have an audio sound from the ecologies and it can fly slowly, so we can monitor the ground.
I didn't expect this to be an airplane.
Indeed, the apartment seems to be seen one room at a time.
Hey, it's slow, so you can check it as much as possible.
What does it look for those two?
That's suspicious.
Get out of my way!
W-what the hell is that?!
Huh?! It's coming!
Those guys are so boring!
Nakagawa, tell Sean!
Yes, sir!
Captain Katsushika!
Oh no! Run!
If you wait for the bus, you'll get away!
I'll catch you in person!
Senpai!
Ryotsu!
Fly!
Huh?!
I-Idiot!
I did it!
All right!
W-what the?!
A-amazing!
Huh?!
You're the ones from before!
P-please forgive us!
All right! Pull them up!
W-what?
The 707th of the Shimei-tehai?
The 707th?
It's a big hit, sir!
I'm sending a picture of the culprit there.
This is the 707th's photo of the Shimei-tehai.
Yeah.
I'm sending it over my phone.
Oh, here it is!
Oh, it's true!
It's a treasure, Ohara-kun!
Thank you very much!
"The 707th of the Shimei-tehai"
That's great!
Thank you very much!
All right!
"The 707th of the Shimei-tehai"
Thanks.
A grand prize!
"The 707th of the Shimei-tehai"
I know, I've always been cheering on you, but...
Well, uh...
...I don't know what to say.
How about we play some Cross Maybelline?
Can we?
Hey, can you demonstrate?
You're so good at talking.
You brought my idea to a good place.
Excuse me.
I have this.
Oh, you're a photographer.
This is actually your idea, right?
Yeah.
It's terrible for a boss to take a subordinate's work.
Right? You're a good guy.
Thank you.
I can put you on my magazine.
Let me take a picture of you.
I like you more and more.
Thank you.
I'd like to take a picture of you from the inside and above the airport.
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure. I'll fly every day, so come anytime.
Thank you.
Mr. Ryotsu, isn't Odaiba a tourist destination?
It's a special service.
The location is better than Katsushikaku, so it's worth it.
Yeah.
Oh!
What's wrong?
The rock singer Joe Miyake and actress Matsushita Momoko are on board that ship.
What?
It's a scoop. Please lower the code a little more.
Oh!
It's a big scoop. Thank you.
This is a small amount, but it's an interview fee.
Oh, I see. Then I'll give it to you.
Then, excuse me.
Interview fee.
Oh, this much?
This is...
We're almost there.
Okay, here we are.
I see.
Oh...
This place is the biggest house for famous actors of film industry.
It's too big.
Huh?
The famous actor is already here...
in the afternoon.
All right.
Everyone, I'm ready to go.
Where are they?
What are they doing?
What?
Where?
Where is it?
It's the house next to the mansion.
What?
That's...
Bulbo!
Bring me number 745's handbook!
Here it is.
It's number 745's handbook.
Oh, no doubt about it.
Bulbo, get close to that house!
We'll catch you!
Roger!
Thanks!
"Liangziang"
Ryo,
I just got a call and an e-mail from the Jyo Miyake's office.
It seems they had a photographer on the flight and got this picture taken!
I have no idea what they're talking about.
Don't lie!
They say this was the only place they could take pictures from this angle!
If it keeps going like this, Director Fuyuki will be dead by now!
Well, that's true.
Don't make a fool out of yourself.
Thanks to you, we were able to arrest number 745.
What?
Bring me the picture!
It's definitely number 745!
It's true!
And that's how we got the director and two other officers arrested,
including the person who couldn't be arrested by the head office.
The head office is behind him.
The head office is behind him, and so might the secretary of the head office.
S-s-så...
...
Now I see.
Then even the head office can be the chief of our department.
Chief?
Where's the chief?
*Girly laugh*
But still, what's your problem?
Well, I'll deal with this one myself.
*Girly laugh*
Ryotsu, from now on, you'll be the captain of the Air Force.
Yes!
*Girly laugh*
I didn't think that just writing the logo would bring the laborious situation.
but it didn't just bring the laborious situation.
But won't it be bad if we could earn money in flight?
This is just a spin-off of patrol.
You can't complain about it because you could beat the criminals by flying and prevent a crime.
Well, it shouldn't be a thing.
Alright, Ryotsu.
Eh?
Kaneganaru Denguo?
Your rival company.
Oh, I see. The budget is 5 million yen. Is that okay?
Yes, I understand.
I'm happy! The advertising fee will be included again!
That's amazing.
Yes! Hey, old man car?
Oh, this is Toyoyama car.
I see. Is this Hikaru Hamasaki's new song campaign?
Senpai, isn't this a flying advertisement?
It's written on the paper.
It doesn't matter where it's written.
Besides, there are so many companies' names and advertisements.
It can be said that the Japanese economy is still doing well.
But the word "Katsushika" is nowhere to be seen.
Don't worry. It's still there.
Senpai, where are you?
To the left!
Where?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
Senpai, this is too small.
It's not good unless it's as big as this Heart Bus Tour, right?
It's okay if it's written.
Hmm? Heart Bus Tour? Bus Tour?
Yes! There's a way to make more money!
There are no customers.
What do you mean?
Well...
I didn't know I could see Tokyo from the sky.
Besides, I can watch soccer matches for free.
I'm glad we canceled the bus tour.
Yeah.
I didn't expect to attract a lot of bus tour customers.
Really, you're a genius in business.
I don't think there are any restaurants that sell bento or juice.
Unfortunately, there are not many services like that.
Bento?
Here it is.
I came up with a way to make more money!
There's only one customer today.
We're just the same.
We've all been canceled lately.
What the hell are you doing?
Great!
That's awesome!
Thanks, everyone.
See you!
Thank you for waiting!
How about some "Flying Line" goods for the Chosun Festival?
"Flying Line Gold Gold"
"Flying Line Senbu"
"Flying Line Juice"
"Flying Line Manji"
And other things like "Eha-Kan" and T-shirts!
Senpai!
Number 3!
Three extra Yakitori!
Yes!
This is Number 7!
Serve it up!
Yes!
You've made a lot of money!
I didn't think I'd get this much!
Two million for one flight!
Three flights a day!
Six million!
One month!
That's...
One hundred and eighty million yen!
Even if you cut the cost of materials and maintenance,
you'll still get a hundred million.
You can make this your main business,
or make the police your sub-business!
When I went to the headquarters today,
I found the names of the 707th and 737th
and 745th prisoners in the police station.
I got a compliment from the general manager.
That's good.
Ohara,
the way we're doing right now
may not be a dream.
I agree!
Chief,
I want to invite you to a drink tonight.
Sounds good.
It's about time to get back from patrol.
I'll call you back.
Ouch!
Oh, no!
Get on the fire extinguisher!
Hurry up!
Oh, no!
It won't work!
What?
No!
Oh, no!
It's okay!
It'll be all right!
I'll get rid of it!
Oh, no!
Please stop!
It is impossible!
The sunset is clearly red today.
Yes.
On the contrary,
the sunset is...
No, the CAS JOINS--
They're coming this way!
Is that...
A flying rocket?
What?
I'm back!
I...
This way!
-The money! -Ryo, run!
This is the last one. I can't see Ryo and the others.
-What? -Ryo!
-The money! -Run!
-Ryo! -The money!
-Let go of my money! -Ryo!
-The money! -S, S, Mr. President
The money and the money that I made made me rich!
S, Ryo!
You have to settle your expenses so you can get on the plane.
How can this be happening always?
"I'm a little kid, but I like historical dramas."
"Why?"
"Why? Why?"
"Good day, why?"
"Why?"
"Demon is a kindergarten boy, but he likes historical dramas."
"His little beard is slightly small."
"Why?"
"When he rides a motorcycle, his personality changes."
"He only sleeps once every four years."
"Why?"
"Nakagawa doesn't lend money to Ryosan."
"But he can easily borrow a tank and a fighter."
"Why?"
"I don't know."
"Why do you work at an exhaust's pump?"
"Why?"
Everyone, are you listening?
This radio program started today
Ryo-san's "2-3 hours tonight"
I am Ryo-chi Kankichi of personality
Life advice, requests, and the story of friends
I'm waiting for a postcard because I don't care
Next time, here is a Kameari broadcast song
Thank you
Kameari there
Kameari for sure
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you