Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new era lightly ♪
♪ The hero is diving alone to the city ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing only trendy things ♪
♪ I'll be a hundred times more handsome ♪
♪ Let it rain ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Running, running, running ♪
♪ The dream never stops ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♪
♪ Love you, love ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ It's a little dark ♪
♪ I don't want to say it even if I start to crawl ♪
♪ I hold the buzzing curiosity ♪
♪ And raise it up strongly ♪
♪ And burn it down with my singing ♪
♪ Love me, love me, love me, love me, love me ♪
♪ Love me, love me, love, love me ♪
♪ ♪
*Gasp*
Hm?
What's wrong, young lady?
I'm hungry.
You haven't eaten lunch yet?
No.
What about Mama?
I'm busy right now, so I'll leave you to it.
What are you doing?
Don't let me eat lunch with this cute young lady.
Aren't you her mother?
You're a big burden.
What right do you have to get in my way?
It has nothing to do with you, right?
No!
Let me go.
I'm really sorry.
I won't leave my daughter alone again.
Mariko, let's go eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm feeling a little now.
I feel like I'm having a little fun.
Got it.
Isn't that a good ones?
I don't want this kind of flower.
You're the perfect woman for my Porsche's passenger seat.
This kind of rose is only good for a newbie.
I-Is that so?
How about we drive to Yokohama from now on?
We can have dinner at a fancy restaurant and watch the sunset.
But we're still on duty.
Pearl White's Porsche is unusual.
Hm?
He's very careful.
I'm glad to meet a girl who knows the unique model of the first-class.
Mademoiselle...
Do you mean Mademoiselle?
That's right. You are my ideal Madom... Madom...
Madomazel.
In other words, this car's passenger seat is prepared for you.
Why don't you drive to Yokohama?
Sorry, but I prefer the driver's seat to the passenger seat.
Besides, I shouldn't use words that I'm not used to.
You shouldn't use words that you're not used to.
Miss, I'm super rich Shiratori Reiji.
I want to know where I come from.
Of course, I want to know where I come from.
I haven't heard of it.
Let's go.
Where is my home?
Of course, I'm a power tycoon.
I have 150 plots of land.
What? You're super rich?
It's not a big deal.
You always brag about yourself like that.
You should pay the fine.
I don't want to hear any bad words.
Miss, I have a Porsche.
You can't get away from me.
I'll catch up with him.
He'll catch up with you.
Don't worry.
He won't catch up with you.
Damn it!
Why can't you follow my fast shifting?
I heard that there are more women with Pachinko addiction.
I didn't know you had a mother like that.
It's a big social problem.
What?
What's wrong?
I heard you say it's a big social problem.
Ryotsu, it's good to be interested in social problems.
Really?
I can't get paid because there are more female customers.
I have to do something about it.
Idiot!
You're not a man.
Manager Kim!
What's this sound?
I knew it.
I'm in trouble.
Reiko, what's wrong?
The man in the Porsche is getting angry.
He's getting angry.
Finally, he's getting angry.
Porsche will cry if he hears that.
Damn it!
Why did you stop?
You're a bad driver.
Who are you?
The diamond Rollax with diamond shining on the soil!
A jacket and coat by Karyo Mani!
The ostentatious Fantix!
The Możuвиhan is a spectrums the konkretint!
The whole body, 1,000,000 yen!
My name is Sir. Super Money-Buy thì Sir.
You're a descendant of the super Saiyan?
No, I'm not!
It's just a moronic.
Let's come back!
Hey!
What?
You're so brave to ignore me.
I'll praise you.
Don't come in here without permission!
You're no use.
Get out of my way.
What I'm interested in is...
You.
I hate you for making me fall in love with this Shiratori Reiji.
I'm busy today. See you later.
No, no.
You can't run away from me anymore.
You're a lucky man who can ride my Porsche.
I don't want to ride your Enst Corp Porsche.
I stopped at that place.
I'm not Enst, no matter what.
I got it. Don't lie to me.
Miss, let's go for a drive with my Porsche.
I'm on a business trip, so I can't.
How about a meal after work?
There's a restaurant in Ginza.
I have something to do tonight.
What? Where's my house?
It's 150 pcs of lotus root soup.
I just came here.
I see.
Huh? My father?
He's talking to himself.
He's the president of Shiratori Railways.
I'm going to be the president in the future.
Isn't that great?
I told you not to run away, didn't I?
Shiratori Railways is a top-notch company.
That is a TV commercial.
Oh, you mean the person who talks with his parents out on the beach.
Do you know that, poor people?
He is stubborn and stubborn-headed.
That's because he deals with iron.
He's had a life of his life.
Ha! Ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
The Shiratoritekkojo
My father is in that commercial.
How is it?
I get the impression that he is feeling cold.
Shut up!
You've been complaining about it for a while.
I don't like super poor people because of this.
Reiko, you have to move to the right of him to escape.
Okay.
You don't know the difficulties of the family.
Stop being so grumpy.
Huh?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Hey, you!
Hey, you! What?
Damn!
Don't underestimate me!
I-I will never give up!
I will never give up!
I will forgive him!
He's still grueling.
Lilan, wait a minute!
And what about that Shiratori guy?
He might still be hospitalized.
But he's still like that.
He's got the same money, but he's not like Reiko or Nakagawa.
That Shiratori guy.
Maybe that's because of his father.
What? You know him?
Shiratori Steelworks is a sub-company of my father's company.
Oh, really?
What? You don't know the lady from the parent company?
You're so dumb.
If you say something, I'll do it.
I'm gonna rip you apart, you idiot!
Man, don't you have to be so poor in the station!
Can you pay me?
I've had to pay you every day.
We're not far.
Be quiet!
This is not Enst!
We're trying to stop you!
Why?
Do you swear?
How dare you!
You're a tough one.
Miss, I'm going to drive you today.
I'm going to be an enlist soon, so I don't want to.
Shut up!
You shouldn't push yourself to drive a Porsche.
I'm a loser!
You!
You're quite handsome.
Are you her lover?
Yes.
Even if you're a lover, you can't win.
Because I'm a man.
I'm a man.
And I have a white Porsche.
Stop it!
You're a loser!
Damn it!
I don't want to wait here.
I'm a loser!
Shut up!
You're a loser!
If you look at the camera, you'll get a backache.
You hit me with a bullet?
I don't know how to do it.
You're a loser!
How much is your salary?
About 220,000 yen.
You'll pay the same amount for one pair of shoes.
Only one shoe will be paid for my salary?
I feel so miserable.
How much do you want?
I don't care.
About 700 million yen.
You can't pay the same amount for Lorax's annointing gold modeling mirror.
Damn it!
I did it again.
Don't underestimate a super rich shiratorireiji.
Don't underestimate us!
Now you know the difference between super poor and super rich!
Hahaha, now I know.
Now, if you're with such poor people, you'll become poor.
Let's go to a rich meal together.
Stop it!
Oh no, Reiko is out!
I've been telling you!
Stop it, Reiko!
Let go of me, Ryo-chan!
Calm down, Reiko!
Aren't you frustrated that he said that?
Ryo-chan is always completely out of control!
That's true, but that kind of man doesn't know what to do if he's being too proud.
Go out with him right away.
Huh?
Of course, you're not alone.
Your work is almost done.
Nagagawa and I will go with you to the bodyguard.
What?
You're not alone.
Are you trying to get to the table?
I'm just a bodyguard.
I see.
Well, if you're with me.
Okay, deal.
Why do I have to treat them like that?
Did you say something?
Well, I said that I thought it would be nice to treat poor people and rich people together.
I said that it would be nice to treat them like that.
My Ferrari can carry four people.
If you follow him in a Ferrari, his pride will be hurt.
He'll be pampered and fed.
So, Reiko is a food.
As expected!
Super poor man's thinking is amazing!
But he can't do anything about that driving.
This will open up the world.
I've been running in the road all the time.
Reiko Akimoto.
What a nice name.
So, where do you live?
I live in Hiro.
Oh, it's a luxury residential area next to the garden.
Huh? With your parents?
No, I live alone.
Oh, that's a one-room apartment.
It's a 4LDK apartment.
Oh, really?
Then, the rent must be expensive.
My father bought it for me, so I don't pay rent.
You were quite rich.
So, what about your family?
I'm from Ashiya.
You're the head of the power plant in Kansai.
Then, how much is your land?
About 150 square meters?
A little more than that.
200 square meters?
A little more.
Then, 300 square meters?
Maybe 500 square meters.
500 square meters!
Idiot, he's acting again.
Don't worry, Reiji.
Even if it's 500 square meters, it's definitely a mountain without Ashiya.
By the way, I'm a royal family.
Where's your university from?
It's a luxury university.
I won!
It's a good university for young girls.
I heard you can enter it with an escalator from kindergarten.
I'm from a university.
Until then, it was a high school in St. Paul's University.
I don't know such a university.
It's a very strict school for all students.
Do you know it?
I know it.
I think it was in Chiba.
It's Switzerland.
Switzerland!
Siratori, shall we change the driver?
It's okay.
But there's a huge traffic jam behind us.
Idiot, you can't get out if you get stuck!
I know!
Hurry up!
Oh, Reiko's changed!
Reiko has her A-class license.
Driver, please follow them so you don't lose sight of them.
Okay.
That's too good!
Episode 1: The
I come to this shop often, but I can't help it.
Ah, this is Akimoto-sama.
Ah, so you're here with Nakagawa-sama.
Welcome.
Hello.
Come, this way.
Hey! Why didn't you greet me?
Excuse me, but who are you?
I'm Shiratori Reiji, the one who made an appointment.
I'll pay for the meal.
Excuse me.
I made an appointment with two people.
I'll show you the table of four people.
Come, this way.
But Reiko-san, anyway,
I didn't expect you to come to such a high-class restaurant.
No, I didn't.
I came here once or twice.
What? You've only come once or twice?
Don't surprise me.
Hahaha.
Every week, though.
Hey, super rich man.
Don't lose.
Hmph.
It's not the number of times.
It's how much money you spend at once.
You can order anything you want.
As expected, super rich people have different tickets.
Yes. As expected, super rich people have different tickets.
Really?
Hahaha.
Hmm...
I've been looking at the voting date map,
but it's so common.
I've been looking at the voting date map, but it's so common.
Sir, have you made your order?
Oh, I've made my order.
Well...
I'll write it all down in French.
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, all the dishes here are delicious.
I'm just wondering.
What's going on?
Well, I'm going to go top of the list when I get here.
Won't it be better to leave it to Chef No. 20?
Huh?
Well, that's too bad.
I meant to do the same as you did.
Well, all of us super rich people have a good taste.
Hahaha.
I'll do the same.
Yes, sir.
I'm free.
That seems quite internacional.
Lord Nakagawa?
This one is fine.
Welcome.
If you'd like, we have a VIP room available.
Oh, I see.
I wonder if I've been found out by the vice president of Shiratori Tekko.
I'll be in your care.
I'm fine here.
Good-bye.
Oh, wait!
I told you I was going!
Damn it!
Well, well, I'm a super rich guy.
Don't worry about it!
Ah, ah, ah!
I always wanted to try at the government office.
Can I order some steak?
Please, please!
Excuse me, I'd like an extra steak.
Oh, Ryo-chan...
If I'm in your care, I'd like an 82-year-old Bordeaux steak.
I think an 83-year-old steak is better than an 82-year-old steak.
You're really a well-versed man, Lord Nakagawa.
Hey!
The super rich guy is the one who pays for the money!
It's me! Why didn't you ask me!?
Huh?
You don't ask him about me, do you?
Why, why do you all ignore me?
Hey, Meiji!
Huh?
Father!
Oh, Mr. President's son?
Yeah. Wait a minute.
So you came too?
Father is as lively as ever.
It's a secret from your mother.
Huh?
Hey, you're a good boy.
Where did you get this?
I don't like it.
Unlike my father, I'm not as good as my sister.
But I'll show her right away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me introduce you.
Here.
Good evening, Mr. President.
No!
Huh? Do you know him?
You!
You're so annoying!
You're such a fool from the Akimoto organization!
You're such a dirty bastard!
I'm very sorry to make you mess with me!
M-Mr. President!
You don't have to do that!
Why the hell do you say that!?
I'm a friend of Akimoto's organization!
Th-th-that's enough!
I'm his father, you know.
Tell me what's wrong!
It's okay.
Super Kame Mochi has a good personality.
Huh?
Yeah.
What's Kaori doing here?
I did something bad to him.
You don't have any responsibility.
He's the one who called us.
But...
Hello, everyone.
Who are you?
Mr. Shiratori.
What's wrong with your outfit?
My father was impressed by me after that,
and I became a super poor person.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
I'll grow up soon
and become a super rich person.
Goodbye.
He's a tough guy.
Be a super rich person and
treat me to a feast.
I'm a super rich person!
Next time
Why am I digging a tunnel?
It's in the movie, isn't it?
I'm running away.
The chief locked me in a cage,
so I'm trying to dig a hole and escape.
Please wait for me, chief.
I'm going to revenge.
Next time
"Ryo's Great Escape"
See you!
"A Big Escape"
♪ Even if you try to stop me, time will pass by ♩
♪ Don't stare at me, laugh to death and live ♩
♪ Even if it rains today ♩
♪ Tomorrow will be sunny ♩
♪ Bye bye, let's wash our hands ♩
♪ Good bye to the unpleasant things ♩
♪ Oh yeah, let's live as we like ♩
♪ There are good things ♩
♪ The sun is calling outside the door ♩