♪T-t-when you watch TV ♪
♪Look at the room ♫
♫and leave the room! ♫
♪T-the two of us have a big dream of a world that will...♫
♪As one of us looks at a real beautiful day in the middle of the night sky...♫
I kicked a love stone and it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to go to the gym that I've been saving up for
I laughed at myself saying that I was crying
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can't help but cry
I can't change even one of my hiccups
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the waterfront of Tongari-boshi to Kaishakuten
The sun sets
Tomorrow will end like this
But I'm happy again
I noticed I lost my happiness
Because I'm a fool
Alright! It's done!
It's not a kotatsu
It's not just any kotatsu
It's not a Hori-Gotatsu.
Go inside without asking anything.
There must be some kind of strange trick.
I can get my feet down.
There's a hole in the floor.
How about this?
This is a Hori-Gotatsu.
I bought it at a sale at the electric shop.
But I can't open the hole on the second floor of the dorm.
Is this a Hori-Gotatsu?
I'm glad my feet are comfortable.
Really.
I used to hide a lot when I was a hidden child.
If you're a child, you can get in.
However,
In the past, Hori-Gotatsu was not electricity.
They used to use beans and lotus.
Because it burns charcoal.
The inside of the kotatsu is sealed.
If you keep it in there for a long time, it will become a carbon monoxide poisoning.
There was a time when everyone who was hiding turned their eyes and it was a big mess.
I thought I was going to die at that time.
Oh my god.
That's dangerous.
I'm not worried about that after I become an electric heater like now.
Well, I'm going to patrol.
I'm going to the library.
Ryo, please take care of the room.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
It's warm and I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
Hmm?
I can't go.
I forgot to screw it.
It's dangerous to move.
I'll screw it firmly.
Thank you very much.
Please put it on.
No, it's a passing road anyway.
That's right.
Why don't you go a little closer?
Ryo made Hori-Gotatsu.
It's warm.
Oh, really?
I'm a Hori-Gotatsu.
The country house is still a Hori-Gotatsu.
How about this guy?
He's a good and serious man working at a yakuba.
No, mom.
I don't want to marry in the long run.
You're really in trouble.
You're the only daughter who hasn't gone to marry in the village.
No, no, no.
The image of a clean city girl is broken.
What happened?
What's wrong, Komachi?
Oh, nothing. I've never done a Horigotatsu before.
I'm so excited!
This is good.
Really?
This is Horigotatsu!
Come on in. It's warm.
It's warm!
You don't need to be cold.
Really.
Oh, no. I can't go out.
I can't go out.
I can't help it.
I'll stay here until Reiko and the others go.
What? There's something like a tarp in the kotatsu.
What?
A tarp?
Oh, no.
Where?
Around here.
Oh, really?
But it's warm.
Then is it a cat like a tarp?
That's weird.
No way!
Stop it!
Ryo, Kanchi!
You were hiding in the slum, weren't you?
No!
If I were to screw you, you would be in trouble!
No need to be so rude!
You're a woman's enemy!
You're a pervert!
What's wrong with you, you little...
Komachi, have you been too indifferent to Ryo lately?
I can't keep up with him.
I wish this perverted gorilla would disappear.
Damn you, Komachi!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I found it!
Yes!
Oh, Mom!
How are you?
I was wondering how you were doing with Ryochi.
I'm not joking!
I'm not going to be with that perverted gorilla!
You don't have to be so embarrassed.
When I took you to my house the other day,
you seemed to be doing pretty well.
Yeah, I told you I was wrong!
I told you so many times!
I was talking to dad just now,
but he said he'd be good at living in the countryside,
so he'd better go back to your place and have a first-aid kit.
What?
I'm not talking to you!
I'm going to kill you!
Geez, you're completely misunderstanding me.
I'm really getting mad at Ryochi.
When he's embarrassed,
I wonder if he thought you were a pervert.
I'm sure Komachi likes Ryochi.
The problem is what Ryochi thinks.
I'm going to go to Tokyo and ask him how he feels.
That's a good idea.
If he comes to my place,
I won't have anything to say to him.
Leave it to me.
I'll go to Tokyo.
I'll go to Ryochi.
I'll go to my place.
I'll go to bride Komachi's.
This is K Francisco!
This is princess Komachi!
you're here to save us.
Come in my arms.
Yes, prince.
Prince!
Princess!
Sister!
It's so severe.
That was so scary.
What kind of dream is that? There's a limit to nightmares.
Ryo's dream of Kankichi being the prince is the worst in the world!
If this is the case, Ryo won't notice.
Well then, let's start investigating.
What? Ryo-san?
That person is healthy.
Even if he falls off an airplane or hits a bullet train, he's always in a good mood.
He's happy.
I see. He's healthy and doesn't worry about getting sick.
I guess he's a person who stays in the wild.
He's perfect for living in the countryside.
He's the type that won't stop when he's bored.
He doesn't sleep at night and makes plums.
He's a hardworking researcher.
He's perfect for getting married.
I had a weird dream, so I was in a bad mood today.
I had a bad dream.
Hey, I have a fortune-telling that works.
If you check it out, you'll find a future partner.
I guess so.
I can see it. You're wearing a wedding dress.
Really?
The person next to you is...
What kind of person?
He's tall, handsome, rich, and has a Ferrari.
That's Nakagawa-san.
Shut up.
What kind of person is it?
He has really thin eyebrows.
And his bangs are short.
He has a thick jaw that can laughed all kinds of questions
and oily hair...
There's no way that's true.
That's Ryo Tsukangichi.
That's the real thing.
N-No way!
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
But the first man I met here was exactly the same person.
That's a lie!
It's obvious that he's a fool.
But everyone says that this is a good spot to hit.
I'm just saying it out of the blue.
Ah, Komachi!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Ah, Komachi.
R-Ryotsu! Kaikichi!
The first man I met here was...
No! No! No!
You pervert gorilla! Why are you following me?
What? You're the one who hit me!
Oh, I see!
You're a real man!
What's with this grumpy woman?
What's wrong with you?
You bastard!
He's got a good eye.
Uh-huh, he himself has good eyes, and it's good.
Alright, all there is left is to make sure that Ryochi-san feels better.
Hey, stupid boy!
Drink up and come home already!
Ryo-san, are you going to make another one-point trip like that?
Yeah.
I can't wait till one thing gets me a date like that!
And do you just think about it?
Komachi's the real deal.
Oh!
Welcome.
What can I do for you?
That horseman...
The horseman!
Is she that good?
Well, she's a bit rough, but she's a good match for me.
Yeah, that's true.
What are you doing?
She's a horse that goes well with horses.
Yeah, that's true.
Her legs are great when she's running,
but her eyes are so beautiful.
You like Komachi too, don't you?
Of course.
I fell in love with her at first sight.
I said I'd bet on her.
Okay.
If you know that, you should hurry up.
Pizza is said to be eaten while it's still hot.
Okay.
I want to quit.
I can't handle the customer.
What's wrong with him?
Does he like her that much?
He's like Komachi Sakura.
What?
You're in that restaurant?
Really?
Yeah.
By the way,
you're going to be an 80-year-old woman, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I'm a woman, right?
I'm a woman.
I don't know.
I don't have the time to talk with you.
But the horse is good.
I can't believe you're saying that.
What?
I don't want any more couples.
Alright, if he's getting married, I'll give him anything.
It's like a dream, Maesa.
To think that Kankichi is getting married...
Well then, I'll proceed with the discussion.
No problem!
I'm good at this!
Let's just do it without any fuss!
What?!
J-Just stop joking around!
Marrying a gay man like that!
So that fortune-telling was true after all?
What do you mean, Naoko?
Isn't that Komachi's father?
You should be quick about things like this.
Your mother is also your...
Cut it out!
I hate that pervert gorilla!
You don't have to be shy.
I like what I like.
Well, why don't you ask him?
You like Komachi, too, don't you?
Of course!
You fell in love at first sight.
I'm going to bet on him!
What?
You're confessing your love!
You're kidding, right?
I'll let you know how many times I tell you.
There you go!
You fell in love at first sight.
Stop it!
The big news!
Ryo, Kankichi, and Komachi are confessing their love for marriage!
Ryo and Komachi are getting married?
No way!
I have a request for the president of the two.
If that's the case, we'll let you off the hook.
If Ryo leaves the office and goes to the countryside,
there's nothing more I can do.
Ryo is finally getting married!
He might have a big mountain in the countryside
or he might have to repay the debt.
He might have to repay the debt.
That psycho Ryo...
He's going to have to throw a big party.
Komachi!
What happened?
People around the world are saying you and I are getting married!
It's your fault, right?
I'm young, cute, and sexy,
but I confess that I love you in front of my dad.
What?
I don't remember saying that!
But the tape recorded it.
I fell in love at first sight.
You're stupid!
You like Komachi, too, don't you?
I see.
The guest who was in the bar at that time
misunderstood that I said I like Komachi Sakura.
Komachi Sakura?
It's a horse.
I like horse-riding more than you, the horse-riding horse.
What the hell!
I don't want to be called a grumpy monster!
Grumpy monster?
Where am I grumpy?
You have grumpy eyebrows, so you're a grumpy monster, got it?
It's not polite to say bad things about people's physical condition, Komachi.
Hey, you two.
It's hot.
What?
You two came to pick a wedding ring.
I'm jealous.
What?
I won't bother you.
See you later, you two.
Hey, you two.
No, you're not, Sakonji.
Ah, ah.
What are you doing?
You misunderstood again.
Shut up!
He misunderstood without permission.
If you don't come here, this won't happen.
It's always your fault.
Don't say anything of your own, Komachi.
It's not my own.
It's not your fault that you were here
or that you know Sakonji.
It's all your fault.
Hey, are you listening?
That's not the point, Komachi.
What?
What about me?
If you're listening, then go!
Show me some of the gems in that box.
What do you own in this jewelery store?
Or do you...
Quiet!
I'll ask the owner to come with you.
You two will hold a wedding ring?
In that case, Rita will have lost her hand.
Hahahahaha.
Senpai, you're taking your time on your long solo life?
If it's true, I'll have to congratulate you.
What did you say?
They're the diamond robbers.
There's no doubt about it.
I see.
If you think you've seen them somewhere, it's a robbery.
If that's the case, we'll definitely be killed for the sake of the mouth seal.
We have to get out of here quickly.
Oh, no, no.
Ryotsu Shinrou is a police officer who is loved by everyone.
The number of death sentences is the first in the country.
Even the men's department, who don't want to get married,
No, no, no.
This is not a compliment.
I can't believe it's so difficult to praise him.
Brother.
It went well.
It was a dangerous place.
What are the two people behind you going to do?
What?
I'll have you fall down the valley with this car.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to untie the rope.
Liar.
I touched it because I was confused.
Who will touch your butt?
I touched it.
I won't touch it.
This is not the time to do that.
Untie this rope quickly.
No.
This is my trouble.
My worry.
No, my pride.
I am shaken by Akane's lies.
It looks like we're in the mountain.
We have to do something.
What should we do?
I am not loops.
For now, get up.
I am not good.
I can't really help it.
I wonder if I can do it.
Ready, set, go!
I did it!
This is nothing!
Nice try!
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
You idiot! Who would do such a thing at a time like this?
Did you hear something just now?
There are many raccoons and foxes around here.
Komachi, don't let go of my leg!
I-I can't do this!
I-I can't do this anymore!
Hang in there!
Listen, rub the rope on the road surface and cut it.
I did it!
Thank you!
Now, let's start the counterattack!
Damn it!
Komachi, stay here!
No, I have to pay them back for what they did to me!
I don't know what to do.
Ready, set, go!
It's a tunnel!
Get in!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're quite reliable.
Now let's start.
Ready!
No wait!
One, two, three.
Jump down from the right and left.
How's that?
Leave it to me!
When I was a kid, I used to play with you all the time!
Okay, I'll go.
One, two, three!
Yes!
Whoa!
Hey!
motion
Don't move!
Good thing you came along.
I didn't mean to let you live, but I'll have you die here.
I'm saved, Komachi!
It's a cliff!
Break!
Komachi, are you okay?
I'm fine.
No, I don't want to.
What's wrong with me?
You're doing great.
I've watched you again.
I feel nervous.
Let's go and pick up the thugs.
This is a great reward.
Congratulations!
You finally did it!
Congratulations, Komachi!
Thank you!
Put the curtain down!
The curtain?
What's that?
What?
I thought it was a good idea to do this early.
I'm glad you all helped me.
Come on, Komachi!
This way!
Now, we will hold a wedding ceremony
for Ryotsu, Ono, and Ryouke.
Great job, Kankichi!
Don't do that.
Congratulations, Komachi!
Why do I have to marry such a thug?
I'm a thug!
If you're a thug, you're a thug.
You've been good at it since you were a child.
Thug?
What's wrong with you?
I've been waiting for you!
I'm not in a good mood!
I'll hold you!
You're a thug!
That's more like it!
I hate you too much!
You're a thug!
♪ I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go ♪
♪ Like a dream, the final energy ♪
♪ Looking at tomorrow, believing in yesterday ♪
♪ Drawing the universe, standing on the ground ♪
♪ The stardust star draws a circle ♪
♪ Isn't this good? ♪
♪ There's no reason to say it's good ♪
♪ I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go ♪