Translated by 方 Hou.
I look at the sunset that floats in the middle of the river.
When I kick the stone, it flies to my shoes.
I wonder if I'm going to save money.
I was laughed at as it was.
Even if I try to cheer up, I can only win.
There is a camel and a badger.
The cityscape that doesn't change is strangely gentle.
I wonder if I'm going to save money. I wonder if I'm going to save money.
I wonder if I'm going to save money.
From the main waterway of Tongari-boshi to Kaishakuten,
the sunset falls.
Tomorrow will end like this.
I lost my happiness because I was happy.
I noticed.
I'm an idiot.
Grandpa and the Bomberman
Well, sir.
When the Abashin villa was here,
I was called Okuyama, the eight-man killer.
I was probably threatened.
Now, I live a life of revenge.
I have done everything right.
For a day, it became so much bigger.
There's nothing I've ever seen.
You don't think so?
It will be hard to see you go up and go down?
I think it's a little too much.
Take a shot of and replace it.
Well, if you don't play hard, it's not a big deal.
Now come on, that's the beaker you want
You can't show off the spoilers.
Get away from that woman.
Stop it! I'm busy and can't take care of you!
Damn it!
You too!
I wonder if he can tell from this photo.
No, no.
You're a total mess.
I can't use a gun.
If I were to use it, I'd have to use my head more.
What do you think?
Huh?
Hey, can you give me a cup of tea?
I'm not sure if you can.
I'm so used to hearing about new people.
Ah, I see.
You're still as friendly as ever.
That's not how it used to be in the past.
Really?
Huh?
That's not how it used to be in the past!
Back in the day, you'd be nice to a local like me.
You'd be nice to me and be nice to me.
Sometimes, you'd come to me for advice.
Sometimes, you'd be nice to me and be nice to me.
At least, I'd give you advice.
Once I got to see you, you won't even be nice to me.
Same thing here.
- Hey! - You, too.
I've seen enough of you, learn from those people.
I know!
Yeah, I'll be like that.
And I'll go and support the men.
I'mma have time, wait for me.
Everyone was scared.
I had to tell them about our date.
Okuyama.
Oh, this is Gome.
And Dai.
Actually, there's a thing between these two.
There's a thing between these two.
Here you are.
Why do I have to pay for it?
Chief, here's the deadline for last month.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
I'll write it down this month.
Don't do that.
I'll give you a special mission.
What?
Hey, Mr. Ochi.
I want to eat matcha ice cream for dessert.
What?
I've decided to eat matcha ice cream after dinner.
I can't eat it except for Morikame Seikai.
That place is the best.
Okuyama.
Since we're here,
I'll send you to Ryotsu's house.
It's about time.
I'll send you there.
It's you!
You're the one who took the luggage of the Kazushika office,
the police officer and Ryotsu of Shiba.
Huh?
What's with this old man?
He's too arrogant.
Well, well, we're looking forward to working with you.
Fine, I know.
I'll send you to home, no matter what.
Don't be careless.
I got it.
Damn it. Why do I have to send such an old man for the Shimasu office?
What? Is there something you want to say?
I thought you were a good husband.
What?
There's no doubt. I've seen you for many years.
You're a good man now, but you'll be the best in Japan soon.
I see. How about a drink at my house?
Sounds good.
When did you get that sake?
From there.
From there?
Don't take it from me.
You're so mean.
This one. I think this one is better.
Hey!
Welcome.
My grandson will pay for the money.
Wait!
That's right.
You're so mean.
Where did you go?
How is it?
It's a bit expensive, but I recommend it.
It's a good deal.
My grandson will pay for the money.
Wait!
You're so mean!
I'll kill you!
Get out of here!
What are you doing?
He's a good man.
How can I kill him?
No, this is...
I'll take it.
He's under all the pressure.
What is that?
Wait, wait, why are you doing this?
Take your daughter to the hospital.
You won't die from nothing.
That's where I live.
We were living together and we had nothing.
Debut.
I'll be back in two days.
I'm sorry.
Is your son born in Niijima?
They have a brother.
I'll get him from the hospital.
Sorry for making you worry, Ryo.
Don't be so mean!
You're older than me, so you don't deserve it.
Where's the house?
Here.
What?
Is this your house?
It's my son's.
Your son's?
He's always putting out the laundry.
Get in the car.
Yeah.
Wow!
Napoleon and Hennessy.
All expensive drinks.
Do whatever you want.
Is that alright?
Yeah.
My son's wife buys him drinks for his overseas trips.
But he's living such a good life.
Why would he do something like that?
Good life?
He's a top-notch fighter.
He's a hero.
His wife is Miss Universe.
His grandchild is the president of the school.
His cat is a fighter, too.
Ha ha.
You're laughing at me, Ryo.
I used to be a man of my word, but I can't win against my age.
Now I'm taking care of my son.
But...
Yeah.
I'm a man of my word.
My son's like a poisonous bug in a new house.
Yeah.
His wife doesn't want to eat with me.
His grandchild...
His grandchild still calls me "grandpa."
That's a tough story.
I've had enough of this.
I'll make you some snacks.
It's easy.
Yeah.
Mikaki is a poor old man.
You bastard!
Don't touch!
He's yelling again and again!
You bastard.
You bastard!
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
Stay down!
You bastard!
I don't have an old man!
What? He's your father!
Father?
You tricked me, old man!
Damn it! Where did that old man go?
If you find him, I'll poke him in the ear and make him talk!
What's wrong? Did you fall?
Stop!
What a boring play!
Why don't you call your granddad?
Mr. Ryo, I want to take a look at it.
This is the real house.
Here? It's like a tanke gym.
Grandpa, is there no family?
Oh, I'm all alone.
I've been living in the city for a long time, but that's a lie.
There are umbrellas and umbrellas in the rain.
It's so cold in winter.
Well, this is also a rust from the body.
I cut the leaves of the tea.
Yeah, I'm fine with water.
Oh, no. I'll go buy it, so wait a minute.
Grandpa is having a hard time, too.
What?
What is this?
Hey, it's huge!
I'm too tired.
Hey, stop! There's someone in here!
Chris...
Dragon King Jr.
Dragon King Junior
Monogatari
Jun
Fuck you!
Go away!
We should just chase him now.
I was thinking he might have some more bones.
What?
Maybe before he uses me?
That old man...
Huh? What's that?
Everyone!
I'm in the Departure Sky where there's been a series of riots!
The culprit was chased by the police around 6:00 PM,
and ran into this department!
He ran up to the roof,
and then he ran into an old man who happened to be with him!
A man suddenly came in because he had a gun.
He's running away.
I don't know what's going on!
Don't shoot!
The police chief is on duty!
Hey! Save me!
Hey!
No!
The host is asking for help!
Hey!
I'm the police!
Damn it!
It's that old man!
What?
Isn't that Ryotsu?
Yes, sir.
What's wrong with that face?
You look like a man.
That doesn't matter!
Let me in!
You can't!
The chief has been ordered not to let anyone in until he comes!
Chief?
So, what's the culprit's request?
Oh, a car for a runaway with a fine of 5 million yen.
Get a car for a runaway with 5 million yen.
Okay, I'll convince him.
You think he'll believe it?
What?
It's nothing compared to the old man in Okoyama.
Damn it!
I'm sorry.
Damn.
I must bring that old man back before he finds out.
Or else my position will be...
I'm telling the truth!
I'm the chief of Katoshika camp, Tom ISUKI.
Stop pretending, and come out quietly!
Shut up!
I'm counting on you, Oharu.
Come on, come on.
Gome and Dai are too much for us.
We have no choice but to protect ourselves.
Come on!
Get the car and the 5 million yen!
Poor you.
What?
The special forces are coming.
You're a bad guy.
No way.
We have a hostage.
You can't run away if you use your head.
Don't underestimate the police.
What?
What are they doing?
I'm telling you.
The old women are the hardest to kill.
I know.
I've known it for a long time.
Who are you?
Me?
You know, don't you?
The case of the 3 million yen robbery in 1943.
I know that much.
Don't tell me you...
It's okay, Yasue.
Leave this to me.
What should we do?
You idiot, get on the car.
First, go to the control room for the emergency.
Don't let them in.
Go, go, go!
What?
What's going on?
Chief.
The way you enter the department's building has been set.
What?
I'm testing it.
I'm sorry.
President Gomez!
300 million yen in an hour!
500 million yen!
Bring 500 million yen!
Prepare a helicopter to escape!
A jumbo jet to escape abroad!
Prepare a jumbo jet to escape abroad!
That old man...
Are you alright, old man?
You can't be so nice.
And bring three specials for Sushi Masa!
Bring three specials for Sushi Masa!
Damn it.
He's asking for it.
I've never eaten a special.
I'll tell the culprit.
I can't accept your request.
Release the sheep and come down.
What should we do, old man?
Just do as I say.
That's what the former president, Tonda Gomez, said when he was a judge.
What?
A man who fell in love with a woman...
Mr. Gomez said he'd die if he didn't marry her.
And he left his job.
He sat in front of her house for a week.
He was about to be fired.
Shut up! What are you talking about?
He's an old man.
And he has three lovers.
It's a very touching story.
President, are you serious?
You're such a fool!
But why does the culprit know such a truth?
It's not true.
President, is the old man...
Damn it!
He's talking so much that he's advertising his presence!
Next, Tonda Gomez, Ohara, Taijiro, and Ryo...
They're fighting for money in Yoshiwara.
They're the police.
President, that's not...
Bad news.
I'll tell the culprit.
Don't be hasty.
Prepare 500 million yen immediately.
President!
Grandpa...
Huh?
Cheers!
Ah, um...
It's Shimada.
I brought you a special order.
President, what should we do next?
Hmm...
Should we shoot a rocket at a hostage?
President!
Grandpa, you're amazing.
500 million yen is a lot, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah.
Hey, teach me when you get 300 million yen, okay?
Yeah, right.
At that time, I was really nervous.
But it's not an opportunity to let it slip.
Dear dearest...
I decided to put it out of my mind-
Everywhere, everyone trusts me!
Hey, old man!
You're not old!
I thought you were drunk, but you're eating sushi.
Where did you come from?
Don't get close!
Shut up! I have a complaint with this old man!
Idiot!
I have a complaint here!
What?
I don't want to follow my plan because of you!
It's a bad plan anyway!
Shut up, you!
What do you say?
Shut up!
You don't have any business!
Wait, I'll talk to you!
Shut up!
I'll split the money between you and my grandpa!
I won't let anyone get in my way!
Split the money?
What the hell are you talking about?
If you're in my way, I'll get rid of you!
Damn it!
I should have knocked you down!
I'll get you out of here!
What are you going to do if you get hit?
I'm fine!
Don't you have a problem with me?
Shut up you bastard, your head is on fire!
Just what are you going to do with your head?!
You! You betrayed me!
Watch this!
What?
That's a cow's eye!
That's it!
That's an explosion, remember!
Go on and die along the wrong path!
Wait!
Oh no...
It's a dimensional device, so it won't explode.
You're fooling me, you bastard!
What the hell?
Hey, grandpa, retreat!
Ryo, stay there!
Okay, tie me up!
Leave it to me.
My tie is a military hell!
Okay, I'll do it.
Good job, grandpa.
See you.
Hey, where are you going?
I'll be out in a minute.
What?
Ryo, you're the one who did it.
You were a good friend to me when I was treated as a troublemaker.
You came to save me without looking at the danger of your life.
I was so happy.
Grandpa, I'll be out in a minute.
Grandpa, come to the bridge if you're lonely.
Everyone is a nice guy.
Come on!
What?
Hey, grandpa, you did it!
There are still many more, Ryo.
Hey, come back here!
No!
Oh, it seems that Ryo arrested the culprit.
What? Ryo?
Somebody, please help me!
Hey!
It's a departmental prison case where a long prison sentence was expected.
But the culprit was arrested by a brave policeman.
Do the truth before the DevOps case.
What is up with you this time?
That's right.
You have gloves on.
The police?
I'll give an example.
The police have requested the police to report the second他们.
Aunt, something is happening.
Yes, I think it's dangerous to go to the police station.
Well.
I will go now.
Goods are here.
Can you go?
Yes.
Hahaha!
Huh?
Hey, Reiko.
I'm back.
Oh, you're back already?
Oh, Ryo!
Oh, Senpai!
Are you alright?
Grandpa.
What are you doing here?
I came to play with you.
Ryo.
You got the president's award, right?
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Grandpa, you're funny.
I heard you're friends with the president and the chief.
I heard a lot of funny stories about you.
Ryo, sit down.
This tofu is delicious.
It's handmade.
Ryo, next.
Chief.
What's wrong with the pressure gauge?
Just a little bit more.
Come here.
Ouch!
You're going to be hospitalized again?
You're the one who's going to be in trouble.
Why is the old man from Okuyama here?
I don't know.
Chief.
You said you'd come.
I'm the boss.
Ouch!
Please forgive me.
I'm a victim too.
Ryo!
I'm sorry.
I'm a victim too.
Ryo.
Ryo, I'm sorry.
You're the one who's going to be in trouble.
Ryo!
I'm sorry.
Rumor has it that I'm a little too young
But there are so many things I want to do
I'm a little too young
I want to ride in a bike
In the vast desert
I want to be free
More than a bird
The speed of the full moon
Changes into a lady's dream
My love, I'm sorry
Wait for me
The future of the panorama
The dazzling light that dives in
You understand, right?
I'm sorry
Wait for me