Let's Go Home
When watching the TV, make the room bright and look away from the TV.
Come to me, people without money!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, you jobless man
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red moon is burning
The red moon is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, shut up and follow me
Go, Sosamo!
Did you understand?
If you understand, don't ever be late again!
Eeeh?
Ah, you're so noisy in the morning, aren't you?
Oh no!
I forgot to come to Yamanaka today!
Eeeh?
Well, there's a park called Toyo in that area, isn't there?
Oh, Toyo Elementary School?
It's close to Toyo Elementary School, isn't it?
By the way, Ryo-chan
Ah!
Huh?
When did you come?
Ryo-chan, you're going to get out again!
But he's not noticed at all
Ryo-chan is really a genius of escape
Damn it, the No. 2 is crazy there
This is also a debt life this month
Maruhi
Passing through point A
Passing through point B
I've been feeling something for a while
Maruhi has noticed
Okay, ready!
Ah!
What is this?
Damn it!
Ah!
Damn it!!
Damnit!!
C You are kidding me
Uh ...
Welcome back, Ryo-chan
Oh, jeez!
C Presents
K
R
U
I'm going to punish him.
80%?
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I can't eat if he punishes me 80%.
Please, chief.
Then, Ryotsu, I'll give you a special task.
Special task?
Yes.
We're going to use a new system to find the culprit.
We'll do a big investigation training with 101 police officers and the police station.
The suspect is set to escape, and the suspect will be in the area where the PHS signal reaches Tokyo 23 district.
And you will be the one to do that escape.
Me?
The fact that you escaped early was proven in the preliminary test.
So that's what happened just now.
What do you think, Ryotsu?
If the case is closed and you escape,
then you'll be the one to be the culprit.
It's like a gold rush.
Gold rush?
What do you think, Ryotsu?
Will you accept this task?
Yes!
I'll gladly accept it, chief Ryotsu!
Is it okay to say that to your senior?
If he really escapes, he'll be the one to escape.
I'll do my best, Ryotsu.
Now, we're going to do a big investigation training as planned.
Everyone, please be a part of this task.
The police officer who played the culprit
will be given a real police officer.
I know that, but we'll have to get the police officer in the know.
I'll see if you can get him to feel safe.
I'm going to investigate juice and take care of it.
I know who's in charge of the case,
Everyone, wait a moment.
Please wait, I'll go.
Question 3, you two are scapegoats.
And 3 of you, I'll protect the crime.
Name, situation, topic, number, stage.
Name, situation, topic, stage.
I'll be the JR for now.
Let's begin!
Everyone, turn on the PHS.
I've got it.
Right now, the three of us are in front of Tokyo Street Hotel, in the center of Tokyo Station.
I'll capture them all in an hour!
Then, let's go to Yamate Line.
What?
It's already here!
It hasn't even been an hour yet!
Ryotsu, you...
Take them all! Get them!
Is that okay!?
Hey! We're the culprits!
That's true, but...
You stand out when they're all stuck together!
I'm the JR!
I'm the inside!
I'm the outside!
Ryotsu won't make it in time.
Ouch!
Don't be reckless.
The culprit is right there.
The culprit has been separated into three directions.
It seems that a police officer has entered Tokyo Station.
He escaped from the touch screen.
However, this light is the only thing that's on and off.
Why?
Probably not inside the car.
Probably outside the car, close to the pantograph.
What!?
Damn it! It's a new car!
I wonder if it's...
The window is open!
It's open!
Yes!
The next station is already full of people!
I'm pretty good at this!
Okay, let's switch trains!
He's running from train to train, and then switching trains!
I guess Senpai is the one who does that.
It's amazing how you can tell just by looking at him.
One of the culprits returns to Tokyo Station.
The police at Tokyo Station have already left.
The police at Yurakucho Station just informed us that the culprit is not on the train.
Send them to Tokyo Station immediately!
Roger that.
Hey, it's Tokyo Station!
That's it!
Help me with the investigation training!
I got it!
Well, it's about time everyone headed for Tokyo Station.
I'll be right there!
It's the police!
Sorry to have you worried!
I'll be counting on you for your investigation training!
The culprit has switched trains again.
What?
He's a tough guy.
What's wrong, Captain?
Are you going to take a U-turn again?
Ah, let's see what's going on for a while.
The culprit is in the middle of the train.
Please ensure that the police are not noticed by the culprit from the front and rear.
Roger that, Captain.
Roger that.
-Captain! -Roger that!
He's fast on the sea speed.
What?!
Oh no! I can't stop him, so there's no escape route!
We've found the culprit!
He's driving in the car!
He wasn't on the sea speed!
From the front!
Tatsunosuke Sakonji
I won't let you catch me for free!
I'll teach you how hard it is to arrest me!
-Gah! -Gah!
-How many? -How many?
It looks like the culprit was caught in the center of the ship.
We just got a message that he's fighting with the culprit!
Alright, well done!
I won't let you get away!
The other one got off the train and is running through the Akehabara electricity district.
It's easier to escape when you're surrounded by people!
-I'm going! -I'm going!
-That way! -Come on!
-Stop! -Wait!
-You! -You!
-Come on! -Come on!
He's gone!
- There! -There!
He's not here!
Go after him!
-Wait! -Wait!
Don't let him get away!
Damn it!
Alright!
Goodbye, Akechi-kun!
Damn it...
That was close.
Next is Shinbashi.
A-Heey! I'm very sleepy too!
Mmm...
"I don't have any money, but I can afford to buy a car."
"I'm sure that he is on this train."
"Why can't I find my number while driving like a madman!"
"I was message from a helicopter because I can't find my number."
"The man is driving straight."
"The helicopter found the man."
It seems that it's going to attack us.
What!?
The culprit has been transferred to the rock.
This is the end!
Special forces are coming!
This is it!
Kakuo!
The light has gone out.
The culprit has been transferred to the Shiba Island.
Special forces are heading to Odaiba.
Damn it!
This is good.
It's like a ride in the sky on an Advalon.
It's already here.
What!?
No, I can't anger them!!
I can't!
I'm got food!
"What's wrong?"
Now this is "Awaiting the At Mess"!!!
Some told me the still-wrestling team justters found the girl being arrested in Advaleon, and apparently disappeared!
What?
The killer was on the highway, probably running away in his car.
Ugh! What kind of people are they!?
............
We can't reach the edge of the river.
So...
Looks like we're off to a good start.
You can do it.
Eeeh?
It's repeating again!
Hello?
Hey, Tsuka.
What? Where's Volvo?
Where are you now?
I fell into the truck's bed.
If I run away from the highway, I won't use it.
Are you an idiot?
Why?
The highway has L systems that are higher than PHS.
And the exit is surrounded.
The police are good at that.
What should I do?
Jump down and get off the emergency stairs.
The
Hey, Volvo!
Volvo was caught.
What did Sakonji do?
I'm in the car.
They're in trouble.
The ones I've met are all very stubborn.
Tch.
It's no use talking to me.
Come on, Kirigiri.
Hey!
Huh?
The culprit of the robbery...
-Ah! -A-Ah!
-A-Ah! -A-Ah!
That's right.
If you pull this guy out, I'll be caught too!
-A-Ah! -A-Ah!
What the hell is this?!
-What? -A-Ah!
-A-Ah! -A-Ah!
-A-Ah!
You're a cop, aren't you?
Why are you running away?
There are many reasons!
Hey!
You can't go anywhere!
Huh?
We've caught the culprit.
He's probably in the sewer.
Don't let him escape!
Arrest him!
Take him!
Or we'll kill him, too!
Arrest him!
If he was a cop, why would he have him?
-What? -What?
-Why would he do that? - Prioritize him!
I'm not a knight!
I'm a soldier!
Get out of here!
Finally we caught up.
But someone is with us.
Ryotsu, give up!
Damn it!
It's the police!
Ryotsu!
I'm gonna get caught!
You're the one who's gonna get caught!
Shut up!
Stop!
It's dangerous!
Ryotsu!
He's gonna fall!
Who's there?
This is...
The punishment for the fear of the command!
Please!
Arrest him!
We're all gonna talk!
WHAT!
This is a big prize!
Contact the head Princely Head dept.
Let's settle it in a tight car!
Search the place!
Yes sir!
Reiko, look at this.
Right.
Um...
Oh, I found it.
Huh?
Hmm?
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Senior!
Ryo-chan the real one?
Yes. Why aren't you looking for me?
The investigation training is already over.
If it's over, tell me right away.
I was running around Tokyo, being chased by my dream every day.
Idiot! Where is the idiot who keeps running for three months?
I don't have a salary because I'm not working!
Well, that's...
I'm done.
No, I'm just an idiot.
Please, go home right now!
I love you so much!
Wait, what is he doing?
It's a big picture, isn't it?
Look at me now!
Kameari
Ah, Kitto Kameari
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!