The End
Eh? Ryo-san is on the radio?
Yeah. The director asked me to do it.
He said I should be on a local radio show.
So Ryo-san said "OK" to it?
Yeah. He said I could talk to him as much as I want since I'm an amateur.
He said I could get a good appearance and even get a good price.
What a good story!
But the director didn't say anything.
If he finds out, it'll be bad.
Don't worry. He won't find out.
The show starts at 10:00 tonight.
Listen carefully.
When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away.
Then you'll dream of a nice time like a dream.
Make the time to look - Look
at the blue sky, look at the white clouds. I
'm sure they'll come eventually. Make
I know it!
I know, I know!
If you do, then just hide and follow me!
This is Kameyari Broadcasting Station.
Wow!
Meow!
Hey there! It's 10 o'clock in the night.
"Wai Wai Paradise" starts tonight!
Today, I invited a special guest of Katsushika's specialty, Mr. Omawari.
Introducing, Mr. Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
*bark*
Sorry, sorry!
I ate eight dumplings and lebanese for dinner.
*bark*
Yes! I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi!
Call me "Ryo-san"!
Y-Yes...
B-By the way, I heard that you work at the station before Kameari Park.
Yeah, that area is like my garden.
From the maniac plastic shop to the popular pachinko shop, I know everything.
Pa-pachinko shop?
Yeah, it's called "Pachinko Plaza Kamedasu".
It's a really good shop.
The nails are sweet, and the wheels spin.
The furniture is all organized, and there are lots of unbreakable stalls.
I line up at 3 a.m. every morning.
Every morning!?
Ah, no.
Now it's just here.
If I get in trouble, I'll get scolded again.
B-But this is a live broadcast.
No, I'm not!
Hey! Just a little while ago! Cut! Cut!
No, it's a live broadcast, so I'll edit.
You're talking as if you like me.
I told you just a minute ago... I told you just a minute ago... I told you just a minute ago... I told you just a minute ago... I told you just a minute ago...
I'm sorry.
Yes.
It's the "Telephone Life Consultation" corner!
Ryo-san, I'm looking forward to your advice.
Leave it to me.
Ask me anything.
This is very reliable.
Well then, let's start with the first person.
Let's call him Mr. A.
Mr. A?
Yes.
What would you like to talk about?
Ah, yes.
Uh, well...
Don't be shy.
I'm actually...
Are you nervous?
Relax, relax.
Ah, yes.
Um, well...
What's wrong?
Please give me some advice.
I understand.
Um...
What should I say?
You idiot!
I'm here for advice!
I'm not here to talk about that nonsense!
If you're a man, just say it!
You idiot!
Uh, yes.
All right, I'll listen to it.
Go on now.
Actually, um, um...
I have someone I love, so...
And?
Someone I love...
And so, um...
I'm wondering what I should do.
Do you talk about that anything?
That...
It's something that's important to me,
and if I say it...
You idiot!!
No need to worry over that.
If you have time to call here,
just tell me about it.
Confess, now!
Confess?
Yes, if you like him, you like him.
You can't be too sure of your partner.
But...
It's hard to say if you like him or not, A-san.
Yes...
Then, send him a love letter, or send him an e-mail.
No! That's not it!
I won't allow you to do that!
If you get lost, hit him!
Got it?
Yes...
Okay, next!
But, if it doesn't work...
I don't care!
That's it!
Next!
Let's go to the next person.
Hello?
What's your problem?
Well, my boyfriend is really cold these days.
He doesn't call me at all.
He's always busy, and he doesn't go on dates.
You're cheating, huh?
That's it!
Hey, wait!
Don't decide that on your own!
Confession is the most important thing!
Okay...
I can't do this anymore!
What's wrong?
My company is being taken over, my god is running away, my wallet is being stolen, my car is being stolen...
What should I do now?
I don't know either.
See you later.
Wait, wait!
That's not the answer, is it?
But, I don't know what's going on with you.
No, no!
I'm irresponsible!
What?
Why do you have to be responsible for something that I've never done?
Don't say that!
You can't do anything about your own life!
That's why you're being taken over and run away from God!
Do you understand?
Um, thank you for your simple advice.
Shall we go to the next one?
Do it.
Ah!
Now, it's time for Radio Shopping!
Hi!
Hello, hello!
Listen and understand!
Buy and understand!
This is the time for Japanese Takeda's Radio Shopping!
I've been waiting for you!
Thank you for your good reaction.
Today's product is this!
The highest quality beef fat bag, 4 points set!
Oh!
What a wonderful bag!
This product is an original product only for Japanese Takeda.
Is that so?
But, if it's a product like this, the price is...
But, this time, this product is...
It's sold for 30,000 yen!
Oh!
This is 30,000 yen!
Yes!
Well, it's 5,000 yen.
Ugh!
I'm telling you it's the highest quality, but no matter how you look at it, it's cheap!
Oh!
What are you saying, you!
This is the most luxurious beef fat!
Huh!
Is it really beef fat?
Is it a rat's skin or something?
What are you saying?
You don't even have a chance to see the product, so don't say anything.
What?
Are you trying to sell something good?
What kind of attitude is that?
What's wrong?
I'm going to give this to everyone now!
This is for everyone who calls the theater now.
I will give you this bag.
Come on, bring it on!
No way!
It's the best beef fat I've ever seen.
Yes, yes.
The phone inside the theater is in full swing.
That's right.
What's going on?
I can't wait anymore!
I'm going to chase him out!
What?
Well, the listeners' opinions are that it's funny so do more is overwhelming.
It's been a great response since the show started, such as "it's fun and irresponsible" or "I like crazy stuff" or "tomorrow too".
Awesome! Awesome!
And this time, at the place of Sugi Heisuke, the chief of the red light, Takashi Beed came to greet us, and the members of the red light noticed that our chief is a great person.
So they said, "What's up?"
What? Regular appearance?
Yeah, I heard that you really liked yesterday's show. I'm starting as the main personality from tonight.
Huh?
No matter what happens to my broadcast, it's attractive enough to be broadcast live.
That's true.
So I'll leave everything to me from this program to the composition.
What? That's amazing!
Everyone who's listening to the radio is watching.
I'll make it an overwhelming show.
Don't forget to listen to it.
It's around 5 o'clock today.
No, I'll wait.
Nakagawa, are you listening?
What?
Ouch!
Why is my senior's voice...
This program started from today.
What?
Ryo-san's "2 to 3 hours tonight".
I'm the personality, Ryo Tsukankichi.
I'm the main personality, Ryo Tsukankichi.
Nice to meet you.
Is he your senior?
By the way, Nakagawa is my subordinate.
By the way, he has a big money with the ability to come up with three or four
bells.
He's a rich man.
He's probably driving around Roppongi in his Ferrari.
He'll pay you for everything.
Call him if you see him.
The number is Mr. Shinagawa's.
Wait!
What?
What's going on?
Wait!
I had a very embarrassing experience.
So he's your senior?
He's been aggressive for four or eight years.
I didn't expect him to be a radio personality.
That's all right.
I've had a very embarrassing experience.
My colleague has a woman.
But I've been embarrassed.
So no one is the right one.
Anyway, he's a man like me.
I'm calm now.
But before, he always talked with girls.
He hung out with girls at night.
But he has high goals.
He said he would marry a woman like Kyo Koyama and Miho Nakayama.
He said.
I'm not saying that I'm going to get married.
It's a story that everyone understands.
Are you listening, Honda?
Ryo is really talking.
It's still a mess.
He's making fun of us.
Next fax.
Pink penguin female high school student.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Ryo.
I have a question.
What should I do to make my chest bigger?
I don't think men know this.
There's a woman named Reiko Akimoto at the Kameari Park.
Ask her.
That's all.
Next fax.
Don't give me his name.
Come on.
Reiko?
That's amazing.
Ryo, you idiot.
Next fax.
You're right.
I don't know.
Ryo.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
I'm counting on you.
The five of you, please.
Okay, next message.
"My name is Yamadome Tatsuhiko.
The police seems to have a strict relationship with me.
Do you have a bad boss?"
Yes, I do.
"I can't use my computer or my cell phone,
but I'm always angry.
I've been in the metal industry for 40 years.
I still haven't been able to get a good job.
I'm a pitiful boss who just got promoted in the year-end school.
But I'm talking about you, Chief Ohara."
Well, there are no bad bosses like that anywhere.
"By the way, Chief Ohara is like a big city when he gets angry.
He's a little bit arrogant and a little bit mischievous.
So if you see him in the city,
please smile and smile at him."
Damn it, Ryotsu!
I'm the one who wants to say it with public radio.
I will never forgive you!
Driver, change the destination.
Immediately!
Please go to this radio station.
Yes, sir!
Both of them are not bad.
It's like a manga.
Then, commercial.
What's the next corner?
What was it, Fujiyama-chan?
Hey, Ryotsu!
Ryotsu!
Senpai!
It's you!
You!
You're a bad guy!
You're terrible, senpai!
What are you doing?
What are you going to say?
Huh?
Maybe everyone's listening to the radio.
Why are you all...
Oh, I see.
They're trying to make fun of everyone.
What are you doing?
Let's get rid of them right away.
As expected of Mr. Wario.
I didn't expect you to prepare such a performance.
A performance?
Oh!
Mr. Ryo made a joke of his colleague on purpose.
He got angry and came into the studio.
It's amazing that he came with such a hand.
This is going to be a great show.
Who do you usually refuse and go on the radio?
Do you think it's okay for me, your boss, to do this without permission?
But, Mr. Ryo.
Listeners are looking for personalities like me.
Shut up!
This program is a sudden stop.
No way!
It's not possible to continue a program that makes people talk without refusing.
That's right, senpai!
Please reflect on yourself.
Let's go home, Ryo.
Huh?
No way!
I can't throw out the program on the way during the live broadcast.
I can't do such irresponsible things.
I've been through so much trouble at times like this.
If this happens, I'll bring it back with me.
Come on!
I don't want to!
Hey!
Ryo is a jerk!
I don't want to!
Huh?
Ryo is a jerk!
You better not...
D-Dynamite!?
I said Ryo is a jerk!
Is it you?
So disgusting!
What do you want?
Don't you remember me?
What?
I talked to you in the live broadcast yesterday.
I talked to you first.
Well...
I was telling you I was a good guy!
Was there such a guy?
There was someone I liked, but I asked him what to do!
Hmm?
Ah, I think there was someone like that.
I confessed to him as you said.
Then, then...
It seems that he was dumped.
He was taken by his senior's irresponsible advice.
Poor thing...
Ryo-tsu! You are not only us, but also a nuisance to the general public!
No way!
It's not good to blame me for being dumped!
Shut up!
You played with my order!
If this happens, I'll blow them all away!
Hey!
Wait! Calm down!
Let's talk calmly!
There's nothing to talk about! I can't do it either!
I have dreams and hopes.
I've lost everything.
Ryo-tsu! It's all because of your heartless words!
I told you not to listen to what I say!
Shut up!
Yes, yes.
It's amazing!
The phone and fax are all punk!
The question "Is the bomb real?" is coming like a mountain!
It's definitely fake!
It's a fake!
It's amazing, Ryo-san!
You can't even do this!
But I have a friend I can talk to!
Hello?
I have a friend I can talk to!
President!
What's that radio you're on right now?
It's not just Ryo-tsu!
It's a bomb!
I'm in touch with the book!
Is that real?
What's wrong with you?
I don't like it, President!
It's definitely fake!
It's Ryo-san's performance!
Performance?
Yes!
I told you that I'd make a great show that everyone will be surprised!
So please don't worry!
I'm in touch with the commercial!
Ryo-san, close the door!
Huh?
Then I'll be doing the commercial here!
Ryo-tsu Kakuchi's "2 to 3 hours tonight!"
Did you hear that?
If it's a real bomb, there's no way we're going to do a commercial!
That's true, but...
But I'm jealous of everyone.
I wanted to be on the radio, too.
You guys, don't sleep!
Ryo-san's "2 to 3 hours tonight!"
We're on the way to the program, but I'll tell you the news here.
Around 6:30 this afternoon, dynamite was stolen from a construction site in Katsushika.
According to the witness, the culprit is a man in his 20s and is currently searching for his whereabouts.
I repeat, around 6:30 this afternoon, dynamite was stolen from a construction site in Katsushika.
Is this Ryo-san's performance, too?
No!
Then, over there is...
A real bomb killer?
Yes, Mr. Katsushika.
There's a bomb killer in the radio station?
That's all a play.
There's no way there's such a messy story.
But, Genny, right now...
Don't worry. Ryo-tsu is doing it anyway, so it's a lie.
Yes, yes.
Ryo-tsu, Katsushika.
I can't believe you.
What should we do?
Wait a minute.
There's a real bomb killer and the police!
A real bomb killer and the police!
What should we do?
There's no way they can do something like this!
We'll continue broadcasting!
What?
This is going to be a great show!
Listen to me for now!
Shut up!
Your story is useless!
But, you know, you can't be a loser just because you were dumped once.
That's right. I've been dumped over and over again.
If you live, you'll find someone wonderful someday.
Someday?
Today?
Or later?
When?
Well, that's...
That's right!
That's just right!
Reiko, you go out with him.
What are you doing, Ryo-tsu?
This is also a story of some kind.
Reiko, if you fall in love with him, this case will be solved at any time.
Don't say anything.
Don't do anything.
You can decide at this time.
What is this time?
Don't make a joke at this time.
Shut up!
Hey!
What?
You keep talking nonsense.
How can you understand how I feel?
Stop!
You can understand it if you talk to me.
You say it again.
It's all your fault that I became like this.
If you let me say it, you'll get in trouble.
Don't blame others for everything.
If you didn't talk about such a stupid thing, this wouldn't have happened.
Stupid?
Ryo-tsu is terrible.
He is talking seriously with people who are listening.
That's right.
You are too insincere.
Radio has to speak with responsibility for every word.
But you are...
I'm going to be on his side, too.
I won't forgive you.
I can't let you live like you.
It's all your fault.
That's right, Ryo-tsu.
Everyone is right.
It's all your fault.
Chief!
You're unresponsive.
You go on the radio, don't think.
You talk back, you bother others.
This is the result you've been connected with.
But you say you're bad at everybody's business?
You can't be a fool and you'll get a good assignment.
Sorry, chief.
Well.
You're very responsible.
I'll let you have your decision.
You're not able to decide.
Do you think women will be
a man you can't decide for yourself?
Okay, now! Play the music!
Yes!
Don't blame others for your mistakes!
Even if there are other causes, you're the one who made the final decision!
You're not always being spoiled because you're old!
Life isn't all good.
There are many painful and painful things too.
So what if you get jealous of other people and get old?
Even in the most painful times, you must endure it and do something about it!
That's what being an adult is!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Damn it. I'm sorry.
As long as you understand.
Life is long.
You still have a long way to go.
What?
One, two, three...
You've been a great leader.
It's well done.
I'm glad you didn't have to take it seriously.
Really really.
All I thought about was what would happen one day.
You brought everything to a leader.
Yes!
What a good story!
Ryo-san's play is as good as expected!
Let's go.
Yes.
I sent it by document touch.
But the chief's line was a little smelly.
The music was a little smelly, Fujiyama-chan.
Ryotsu, what are you doing?
What? The continuation of the program.
Katsu, are you still coming? This big idiot.
See, I'm going home.
No.
Come on.
You.
I'm not going.
I said the broadcast is canceled.
I'll continue.
I said I won't forgive you.
It's on air.
I'm on the radio.
Yes.
The power that even Ryotsu can't understand.
That warmth that made the bomb victims cry.
Please appear in our new program.
The title of the program is "You win over the chief Ohara".
This is decided.
No, I don't want to.
I'm begging you.
The era needs a personality like Ohara-san.
Please.
But...
There.
Please somehow.
After all, my program is canceled once.
It can't be helped.
I caused such a problem.
It's up to you.
But the chief's persuasion was really powerful.
Please appear.
It's over.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh, no.
Please appear.
Yes, dear.
Ah...
Oh...
To be a different person,
I need to know.
I'm a sap.
I went buy a ball...
No.
I don't believe it.
My speech wasалы.
I think if I had become a boy I would have become a man.
To be the father of the most important baby.
Why?
Why does it happen only once every four years?
Nakagawa-san doesn't lend money to Ryo-san
But he can easily borrow a tank or a fighter
Why?
Rei-ko-san is very rich
But he works at the gas station
Why?
Over
I used up the money I collected from the first trip
I'll be in trouble if I don't take everyone to the trip
Who thought of the octopus in Atami?
Next time, "Atami Octopus Trip"
Don't forget it!
Come to our town!
Thank you!