Back to the Future
Whenever you're watching the television,
brighten up your room and try looking far away!
sostilely And those who have no money, come to my place
Come on!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
It will be alright
If you don't have a job, come to me
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the burning red clouds
It will be alright
I know, I know, I know
If you know, then come to me silently!
Ryo's Love Proclamation
Huh?
You have even written in one screw
Yeah
It's my radio
I'm trying to make a radio
Ah, good morning, chief
Good morning
Ryo!
Ah, ah, ah!
Chief!
Please don't shout suddenly
What are you doing, Sensha?
I've been making it since yesterday
It's worse to make something like that while you're working!
More importantly, this
What is this?
This is a photo of our meeting
Eh?
I'm not interested in marriage at all
Shut up!
A man like you should have a wife!
Thank you very much
I've collected it from my relatives and neighbors
Just look at it!
You're so persistent
Did you forget the time when I met you at the chief's recommendation a few years ago?
Huh?
You took me to the meeting forcefully without showing me the photo of our meeting
Do you want to take one with me?
Thank you for waiting
Let's go
Nice to meet you
This is Ryo. I'm important chief
Th..Thank you
Then I'll introduce you to my mother
It's Yasuyo Takahashi
Nice to meet you
I'm Yoshie, your daughter
I'm Yuka, your grandson
Hello
Hello. You're a cute young lady.
Boss, you're not a child.
Don't be so courteous.
I'm just grateful that you like me.
More importantly, you're a pretty girl.
That's right.
You don't seem to be a good girl.
Well, we'll leave it at that.
Now it's time for the other two to leave.
That's right.
Well, take care, Mother.
Yes.
Yuka, let's go.
Well, you're the one who's going to be the bride's husband.
No, I don't want to.
I have a husband.
Then the one who's going to be the bride's husband is...
Jozo!
Boss!
You're laughing, aren't you?
Don't look into the other person's affairs,
and try to be the one who's going to be the bride's husband.
I'm sorry.
That's the boss's fault, after all.
I'm really sorry about that time.
I heard that there was only one daughter who was separated from her husband at the age of three,
so I thought that the daughter was young.
My pure heart is fluttering.
I don't want to think about that again.
I'll return this.
After that meeting, I remembered that I was paid 30,000 yen for a sushi restaurant that was so poisonous to me.
And I remembered that my husband was the one who was going to be the bride's husband.
Did something like that happen?
Shut up!
Anyway, choose one of us and see each other.
This is an order.
Got it?
Boss!
Don't be a joke.
Who's going to see each other?
Ryo-chan!
The boss is also worried about Ryo-chan, so he's going to see you.
What happened?
Look at this!
What?
She's so beautiful.
Ryo-chan, take a look.
I didn't expect the boss to bring such a beautiful girl to me.
Ryo-chan, you should definitely meet her.
Really?
Ryo-chan accepted the meeting.
That's good.
But...
Did something happen?
This girl...
Oh, I knew it.
What do you mean, "I knew it"?
Ryo-chan must have thought that she would choose Yoshinaga-san's daughter.
Was she your acquaintance?
Yes.
She often shows up at the flower fair.
She's a very nice girl with a low level of wealth.
That's true, but...
I think it's too much for Ryo-chan.
Is that so?
I think it suits her.
Hmm...
Ryo-chan's name is on your name card.
She's been dreaming about you for years.
I'm sure you'll be able to get her.
Hmm...
Ah, but I don't think I can.
I'm the head of the Ryo-tsu Kan-kichi Police Station.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Makoto-san.
I'm Yoshinaga Makoto.
I'm from Futsutsuka, but I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you, too.
Makoto-san, let's stop the formalities here and let's just get to work.
Yes, madam.
I didn't know that Japanese clothes would look so good on you.
Huh?
Uh, um, I don't think that old lady over there is the one you're looking for, right?
Ryo-tsu, that's not true.
But the head of the police station has a good wife who's the right one for you.
Hehehe.
When I was a baby, I was a nanny.
She helped me with the housework.
Ah, thank you.
Ryo-tsu-san, the police station is a wonderful job that protects the peace of the city and our safe lives.
Ah, yes.
M-Makoto-san.
Yes?
What's your hobby?
I'm a music director.
So you're a classical musician?
Yes, I love Mozart.
Oh, is that so?
M-M-Mozart, huh?
Ryo-tsu-san, are you interested in Mozart, too?
No, I just like Mozart's "Katsusandu" at the coffee shop.
Ah, I see.
Ah, no, thank you.
What's your hobby, Ryo-tsu-san?
Uh, well, I like horses.
Horses?
I love horses, too, and I often go on them.
Are you British? Or Western?
I'm from the middle of the country.
I go to the head of the army, but I'm usually a British.
Is that a track and field?
Oh, no, I'm not.
Ryo-tsu-san, you're a humorous person, aren't you?
No, thank you.
You look like you're having a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Okay, come here.
Wow, so many people are gathering.
Ryo-tsu-san, you're amazing.
Yeah, my relatives often feed me at the pond in the sushi restaurant.
Unfortunately, I don't have any food.
Ouch!
Hey, your kimono is going to get wet.
Ryo-tsu-san!
That idiot!
Oh, no, he's a fun person.
Ryo-tsu-san, are you okay?
Ryo-tsu-san!
Oh, my kimono is getting wet.
I don't care about your kimono.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm sorry.
This is no good.
It's your turn.
Oof, idiot.
Ryo-tsu-san, how was it?
Huh?
We have a marriage proposal.
Oh, I see, you had a nice girl.
Oh, Ryo-tsu-san, you're so cute!
You said that you were having a marriage proposal!
I was.
I feel like your face never fits?
You can't have a girl who likes a gorilla man doing like this.
Shut up, leave it to me.
Ryo-tsu-san!
What?
It's terrible!
What's wrong, Chief? You're in such a hurry.
Did you get a million yen?
More than that happened.
No way! 100,000, no, a million yen?
You idiot! No, I can't believe it.
I got a message that Makoto likes you and wants to go out with you.
What?
This is a dream, isn't it?
Honda, pinch my cheek as hard as you can.
What?
Then...
Ouch!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Senior, you're terrible.
You're the one who always said that.
What?
Then, is it possible that...
It's not a dream. It seems that Makoto really likes you.
No way!
All right!
The End
As expected, those who understand my value can understand it.
Someone who likes Ryochi and Kankichi is definitely a volunteer or a person who likes them.
Well, maybe a gorilla girl more than Ryochi and Kankichi.
What's that?
You don't have to say bad things about me, but don't tell Makoto's bad words.
I'll do it.
Don't be violent.
Let go of me, Chief.
Calm down!
You see, compared to you, Makoto-san is just like Tsuki and Spon, no, Bob Sapp and Benjono Mop!
B-Benjono?
Mop?
I said it again!
I don't want you, the number one man who doesn't want to marry for 20 years in a row, to say that!
What did you say?
Makoto-san is a gentle, wonderful woman who's as kind as Yamato Nadeshiko!
Hey, stop it!
Excuse me while we're in the middle of recording.
Ah, Makoto-san!
Hello!
You surprised me.
L-Lies!
T-This is definitely a nightmare!
Ouch!
Why isn't it a dream?
That's why I said you guys are both Sapp and Mop!
You're the same age as us!
You have such a great style!
Hey, Jiro!
Don't look at me like that!
How rude!
Makoto-san, what's up today?
I thought I'd be a little bit rude, but I brought a lunch box for you.
Really?
Would you like to eat it?
I'm so happy!
I'll eat it!
Wow, that looks delicious!
Right, Senpai?
Y-Yeah.
Here you go, please eat.
Y-Yes.
Thank you.
Itadakimasu!
It's delicious!
This saltiness of the tapioca is the best, Makoto-san!
I'm so glad you're happy!
You guys should try it!
Itadakimasu!
Yum, it's delicious!
It really is.
It's like a restaurant dish!
You don't cook, you just eat lunch boxes at the convenience store.
You're different from some girls.
What?
It's really like a restaurant dish.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just that you just put it in a box.
That's absolutely not true!
The young lady has been working hard for the master since early in the morning.
She's been working hard for the master since early in the morning.
This bar shop is swear by the gods that it's true.
Yes, ma'am.
Ryo-sama!
Maria!
I heard from Meiko-san!
She can't believe that she can have a date while she knows I'm such a jerk!
It hurts!
Please turn into a girl!
Ryo-san?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Who is this?
This woman is so used to my Ryo-sama!
Maria-chan!
This is the date for Ryo-tsu Kan Kishi.
...is my match.
What did you say?!
Wait a minute!
Ryo and I spent the night together in Ryo-sama's room!
What?!
Is there such a woman?!
Ms. Makoto, you're misunderstanding!
Maria is...
...a woman.
Is that so?
What's with that laugh?!
I won't forgive you!
M-Maria-chan...
I-I'm sorry! I'm a 5th grade Aikido student!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I-I lost...
Maria-chan, what's with that Yamato-nadeshiko?!
She's better than us!
I'll give you back your words, but...
...I just became a teacher for you.
I'm so sorry, Ms. Makoto.
You're a master of the Ikebana, Sado, Nichibu, and Okoto.
R-Really?
Yes.
From my point of view, you're a lady who can't stand the heat.
Excuse me.
I'll show you.
I don't have any feelings for Sado, so I'll drink to my heart's content.
Please enjoy without being offended.
Oh? I thought it was something more sour.
It's surprisingly good.
Reiko, would you like to try it?
Y-Yes.
Please enjoy.
I'll take it.
Komachi, Naoko.
I'm still hungry.
Are you going to say something bad about Ms. Makoto?
It seems that you've noticed your mistake.
Reiko, listen to me.
What's wrong?
You were taking a break from your work earlier.
Naoko!
Ryo Tsukankichi!
Good job.
I'm sorry for the other day.
Thank you.
You should do your best to protect the peace of the city and the safety of the citizens.
Well, let's go, Ms. Makoto.
Yes, Mr. Ryo.
And when you come with the chief...
From Mr. Ryo.
You're showing off as if you're lovers.
I can't forgive you.
Why is that gorilla man so popular?
You think he's strange?
Mr. Reiko?
What's up?
Mr. Reiko, what's wrong?
Huh?
Oh, the girl who can understand Ryo's lies has finally appeared.
I should make her happy.
I, I see...
You're all right.
But...
Oh...
It's very fast.
It's been modified a lot.
If it's not a large place like this, we can't play.
Yo yo.
You're showing off from the front.
Heh, can you lend me a little bit of your pocket money?
The kids are in the way.
Ryoichi-san.
Makoto-san, no need to worry.
Don't be so cool.
Hey, let's get the money out quietly.
I don't think you guys are talking to me.
What?
Do you want to see me?
Huh?
Ryoichi-san!
I'm sorry!
I like Ryoichi-san more and more because he can get rid of those scary people with one word.
It can't be this good.
It's too good.
I'm sorry.
Makoto-san.
Huh?
You're just a girl with no talent like Makoto-san.
Why do you want to date a man like me?
Don't men around you usually leave you?
Can you tell me honestly?
You're an adult.
I'll tell you properly.
I...
I had a dream to be a fashion designer since I was a child.
What a wonderful dream.
So I told my parents that I was going to study abroad in Paris.
They were very against it.
They told me to get married without following my childhood dream.
So you don't have any relationship with your parents anymore.
That's right.
That's true.
But I realized it after dating you.
I...
Wait.
Don't say that just because we've met a few times.
I'm sorry.
I'm not seeing you today.
Ryotsu.
I hate people who give up their dreams because they are against their parents.
I'm sorry, but I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
Ryotsu.
What?
Ryotsu Kankichi was dumped?
She seems to be very depressed.
Right, Reiko?
Yes.
I thought it was strange.
I finally understood the true nature of Ryotsu Kankichi.
He can get rid of the ghostly face of a gorilla man.
Komachi.
Yes?
What'd he say?
What?
He looked at you like the protagonist of a comedy.
He told you that she was dumped anyway, so he told you to look away.
Ryotsu.
Don't you touch me even if you've been mistreated.
You should know that she has never accepted any kind of man.
Ser...
Don't say that.
That girl doesn't like me.
I just like her.
I like a woman who's in her thirties, who's fat and has a lot of fat.
Aren't you overreacting?
I'm not overreacting!
Anyway, Honda.
You're done with work, right?
Yeah.
Come with me tonight.
Okay.
That's why I'm here!
Okay, let's go!
Don't drink too much.
Okay, I'll wait.
Here.
Dad, get me two or three more of these.
Ryo-san, shouldn't you stop drinking?
You idiot!
You'll get arrested if you don't!
I can't help it.
Hey, Honda!
Didn't you say you were going to drink with me until morning?
Get up!
I can't drink anymore.
Please forgive me.
You're so annoying.
I'll go with you.
Boss?
Dad, I'll take care of him.
Sure, see you later.
I'm glad you're going with me.
Give me a drink, please.
You're so cute, you're making me look like an idiot.
I'm good.
I'll try some, then.
Here you go, Ryo-san.
Here, drink!
Thanks, thanks.
Oh my...
You're such an idiot.
What?
Makoto-san, the address contestant told me what happened.
He was very grateful to you.
He said you were a slut,
then he convinced your parents
and made you study in Paris.
Really?
Oh, is that so?
Well...
You're not even a model, but you're so cool.
Is that so?
Good, good.
Chief, please, please.
Even though you followed me, you're really a big idiot.
Don't call me an idiot.
Oh, she was a good woman.
She was a good woman.
I said, "Well, do you have California money?"
Oh, I don't have California money.
I'm not in America.
I'm sorry.
Um, I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Well then, kushi-age, kaki-age, katsu-age, whatever, age-age?
What is it?
What do you recommend?
Just be careful with "katsu-age."
Huh?
That's a father joke.
Yes.
Yes, sorry.
There's no reason.
That's strange.
Really?
I didn't find the scar at the peak of the Sumida River
The scar found in the wall of the river was the scar when I rode a motorcycle and fell into the river when I was a junior high school student.
The memory of that junior high school time that opened up to fights and pranks is now vividly revived.
Next time, "Asakusa Shonen Guren Tai"
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!