Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming seasons ♪
♪ The best harem shines ♪
♪ Overcoming the new era ♪
♪ Diving to the city in a yellow-gold car ♪
♪ I wanna dive into paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing the trendy clothes ♪
♪ The more handsome you are, the better you look ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Running, running, running ♪
♪ Dreams never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Just a little bit ♪
♪ It doesn't hurt to stick out ♪
♪ Holding the buzzing curiosity ♪
♪ I've grown stronger and higher ♪
♪ It's not a joke, really ♪
♪ It can't be true ♪
♪ The one small difference between us ♪
♪ You and I together ♪
It's so fun seeing you do your job now.
I got a big order.
I'll be there in a minute.
Mr. SOpen!
♪ Diving to the city in a yellow-gold car ♪
♪ The yellow-gold car ♪
♪ The only thing I wanna do ♪
♪ It's driving me crazy ♪
It locks automatically.
Huh?
The key is this electronic lock key.
That's amazing. It's so quick.
Now we don't need to arrest the culprit.
Finally the high school students are here.
Today's night shift was tough.
You look pretty sleepy, Ryo.
I'm not sleepy at all.
I went to the beach five days ago.
Every night I went to the night club to sing and drink.
Then I played the iron man for 70 hours.
And I went to the night club right away.
I haven't slept for 120 hours.
You're so silly.
I'll sleep for 100 hours when I get home.
My body's tired.
You have to change your lifestyle.
I can't order.
I can't.
What's that?
This is a new stroller.
It locks in 0.2 seconds.
That's interesting.
I can touch it.
This is useful.
I'll open it with this key.
Cool!
This is interesting.
It's so quick.
You were so sleepy.
He has no eyes for play.
Well, I'm done with the training. Let's go home.
I want this.
If you're tired, go home and sleep.
You're with your child.
What?
I said go home!
You're under arrest!
What?
The key!
He ate it!
Hey!
Damn it! He ran away!
What are we going to do?
I don't care!
Hey, do something, Nakagawa!
It's not me. It's a guy Terai borrowed from the headquarters.
I'll try to get in touch with him.
He should have the spare key.
We'll get you all out of trouble.
Yes, that's right.
You talked so loudly, you little fool.
He ran away, you know?
You should have taken him away!
I don't want to know why you caught him.
That can't be it.
He went, you know...
He's on vacation.
Huh?
When's he coming back?
He's staying here until the next day.
What?
What?! You've been with Reiko for 48 hours?!
That's my line!
Wait!
Is it Saturday today?
I don't know...
I'm not kidding!
It's the day of the festival!
We don't have time for this!
We have to do something about it!
That's the latest style!
I can't get a scratch!
I've had a bad feeling since we were playing on the table.
Then, I'm sorry, but I'm busy, so I'll go home.
What?! Hey!
Wait, hey!
Ryo-chan will work with me!
What?!
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a minute!
I haven't slept for 120 hours!
Are you going to make me work for another 8 hours?!
But I can't help it!
Today is the day of the festival!
Why are you working?!
It's okay.
Then, you can sleep freely.
Yeah.
Of course, of course.
I'm going to sleep.
Wow!
It didn't take even a second!
He can sleep anywhere.
He's just like an animal.
Yes, this is the Kamianari Park branch.
Yes, I'm here.
Reiko-san, the headquarters is calling.
Me?
Ouch!
My eyes are cold!
Come here!
Hey, hey!
Yes, I'm here.
Yes.
Huh?
Are you going to the library?
Right away?
Yes, I understand.
My head is burning!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
I'm going to the library.
No!
I'm not going!
What are you going to do?
Huh?
You!
Maybe you're in a hurry!
Hey, hey!
I'm going!
Stop!
Hey, see? Reiko!
Why do I have to run?
It can't be helped.
Two people can't ride when the chain is attached.
Well, let's do it!
Do your best!
Stop!
NoOO!
I won't be so rude anymore.
What? That was definitely a world record!
Get your hands together.
If you find it, you'll be embarrassed.
Boss, what a brave couple.
They're a perfect match.
Hey, stop!
What?
Over here. I want to pee.
I can't go with you.
I can't? What are you going to do? I'll take it!
I'm in trouble.
That's right.
What if I pee in the back yard?
You want to pee in the back of the book?
I can't stand it.
Hurry up.
Oh, no.
What's wrong with you?
Reiko!
What are you doing in such a place?
I'm going to the sun.
No, Reiko.
Let's play volleyball.
No!
Oh, no!
It's still too early!
What?
I can't!
It's too early!
Oh, no!
You said it's early!
I must have been treated like a pervert!
No way.
So, excuse me!
Yeah.
Good job.
Ryo.
Huh?
I guess you have work to do.
Let's get going.
Well,well...
You're going to the bathroom?
Well, if I come along,
I'll have to be a real pervert.
I'll be in trouble!
Just do it outside like me.
I'll close my eyes and do it.
You can't do that, can you?
Then, wait until I get back to the station.
There's only one way.
How?
Like this...
And this!
I don't like this kind of life anymore.
They treated me like a pervert, too.
I'm tired.
My left hand hurts.
I'm tired, too.
I'm lack of sleep, so I'm dragging you around.
I'm sweating.
Should I take a bath?
What? A bath?
Hm?
No, no, it's okay.
I'm sure you can't see.
What's with your eyes?
Are you trying to make me look like a swine?
Ryo...
But just in case.
Damn it.
You're making me faint again.
Don't hit me every time I change my clothes or go to the bathroom.
You're getting more and more resistant.
You're getting more and more aware of it.
You're talking like a cockroach.
Are you going to take a bath?
Let me in, too.
Wait, I'll be right out.
No, I'll be right out.
Don't get naked in here.
If you want to go in, go ahead.
Don't be so reckless.
But how did you change your clothes when your hands were tied?
Hm?
I have a little tip for you.
That was refreshing.
I'm not refreshing at all.
I'll take a bath while I'm wearing my clothes.
I told you to go in!
Oh, who could it be?
Mr. Akimoto.
It's the manager's aunt.
That aunt is famous for her talk.
I don't know what kind of rumors will spread if I find her in a place like this.
It doesn't matter what you say.
I'm not going to go.
Mr. Akimoto.
Santalum.
Hello.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Oh, were you in the bathroom?
The luggage is here.
Thank you.
Then...
Oh yes.
Do you know the girl in room 8?
I don't like rumors very much.
If I were that girl, I'd take you to different places every day,
and then take you to your room every day,
and I wouldn't give you a bath.
I have a little thing for you.
Uwaaaah!
What was that just now?
You're quite unusual compared to that.
You're not fluttering like a weirdo.
Ugh, this guy's tough...
Let's go to bed.
Let's change into your pajamas...
Huh?
You didn't do anything and you fell asleep.
If you sleep in a place like that, you'll catch a cold.
It's not impossible.
You've been up for 135 hours.
Yes?
It's me, Papa.
I'm Pum Pum.
What are you doing at this hour, Papa?
I'm heading over there.
Oh, you're going to Tokyo?
What's that?
What?
I'm not going to the wedding!
That's strange.
Anyway, tomorrow at 1:00 p.m.,
the other party will be Tenkamaru Shoji, the boss of our business.
But even if you say that so suddenly...
Besides, I'm not going to get married yet.
Huh?
Are you going to have a lover?
It's not like that, but...
Chief, I didn't do it.
Reiko!
What was that man's voice?
Oh, no, Papa.
It's the sound of the TV.
Oh, no.
It's Ryo.
No, Reiko.
Stop it.
I asked you to stop it.
Just now, you said Reiko.
Ah, the TV...
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Phew...
I'm in trouble.
If I take Ryo with me like this, it'll be a big commotion.
Papa might be shocked and fall asleep.
I think it's about time, but I'm sorry.
No, I don't mind being a little late.
I can wait for you for hours.
Right, Papa?
Yes, Tomo.
Excuse me.
Oh, Reiko-san?
Hello, sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh?
I'm sorry. I got caught up in traffic.
I'll leave you here for a moment.
Here we go.
Isn't she cute? I love her.
She's always with me wherever I go.
Ryo-chan has been sleeping since yesterday.
If she stays asleep, everything will be over.
Reiko-san, you're so cute.
I like it when you say that.
Well, thank you.
I'm Tenkamaru Daisuke, the daughter of Tenkamaru Shoji.
I'm happy to have you with me on this trip.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Hi.
What's your hobby?
I like money.
I have too much money, so I have a hard time using it.
That's a good hobby.
What's your hobby, Reiko-san?
It's just my imagination.
What?
This is mine.
If you still don't tell me, I'll just call you a fool.
I'll tell you my imagination.
I'm glad I brought you here.
Ryo-chan, good night.
Please go home now.
It's my first time seeing you in a magic operation.
So am I to be dressed like a raccoon?
Ryo-chan, please.
Don't tell anyone until the wedding is over.
You...
Do you like such a stupid guy?
No, I don't.
He's my dad's important business partner.
If things go well, I'll buy you the Radicon helicopter Ryo-chan wanted.
What? Radicon?
Okay, I'll take it.
Leave it to me.
It seems that the girl is doing miscalculation.
Even though it is a Radicon, it's pretty hard to stay still.
Huh?
It looks delicious. There's alcohol, too.
Come to think of it, I haven't eaten anything since last night.
Okay, watch me.
Anyway, my family is...
The first-rate investor is Himiko's mother.
Ryo-chan's...
This is how you should treat her.
Reiko.
Yes.
If you're getting married, where would you like to live?
Ashiya? Den-en-chofu?
Anywhere.
Really? I don't mind anywhere but the city of the town.
What?
No, wait.
You can't do that with a Radicon.
The town is old-fashioned and ugly.
Damn it.
I don't like it.
I don't like the town I've been in for a long time.
It's so ugly.
I really don't like it.
What do you think, Reiko?
It's delicious.
Water!
Give me water!
I need water.
Water!
Right, Tenkamaru-san?
That's right.
Reiko-san.
Yes?
Finally, we're together.
Y-Yes.
Reiko-san...
Ever since I saw you...
U-Um...
Reiko-san...
We're doing a Dragon King show over there!
What? Dragon King?
Dragon King!
It seems the raccoon was running out of breath.
Dragon Queen!
Dragon Jack!
Dragon King!
Ah, I like things like this sometimes.
Y-Yes.
I just took the chance.
Good, Dragon King.
There! Dragon King!
Ah!
Oh, what's wrong?
Ah...
No, it's nothing.
That's strange.
Calm down. Calm down.
Dragon Jack!
Ah!
Dragon King!
This is the Kachikachiyama raccoon!
Ryo, let's go!
Kachikachiyama!
Eh?
That was really close.
But, it's all right.
Even with only half of your face, you're safe.
Damn it.
But, there's a problem.
At this rate...
Reiko-san!
What should we do?
We'll be caught!
Oh?
Reiko-san!
Ahhhhh!
Why are you so quiet?
What?
You're here?
It's your turn!
Hurry up!
What?
Here, take this!
Ah!
Ahhhhh!
Dragon King!
You're here, Dragon King!
Ah!
What?
But, who is this girl?
Oh, Dragon King!
I'm a big fan!
Ah!
Look!
Pink Devil!
Hey!
Ah!
Devil Shogun Pink Devil is here!
What are you doing?
Reiko, you do it too!
What?
He's serious!
If he's really into it, let's do it too!
Yeah!
Oh, no!
I can't do it!
Ah!
I won!
No!
Where is he?
Ah!
Ha?!
Reiko!
Ah!
Ha!
Reiko!
What?
You're not getting away!
It seems that Tenkamaru's temper is not suitable for you.
The rest was a mess.
But I'm relieved that I finally got the handbook.
I was really impressed by the handbook.
But you may still be lucky.
The person in charge said that he's been absent for a month.
A month? That's a dangerous place!
By the way, where's Reiko's engagement ceremony?
Of course, she refused from the other side.
This?
Yes, the promised Radicon Heli.
I did it!
So, did the engagement ceremony go well?
No, no.
I don't have the right to get married anyway.
I got my father's face up and had an engagement ceremony,
but I didn't like it that much.
I was worried about how to refuse.
It's all thanks to Ryo.
I thought so, too.
This handbook is useful, too.
Ryo.
Chief!
Good morning.
You're playing with that again while you're on duty?
No, I'm not.
I always have a job.
Look, this is not a toy.
It's the latest handbook.
Hmm.
Right?
It's amazing, isn't it?
I see.
I got it, so take it off.
Yes, sir.
This key is...
Huh?
Ah!
Take it off now!
Chief!
What's wrong?
Can't you take it off for a month?
You!
What are you going to do?
I'll die, if I'm with Chief.
Don't forget that.
He's really ropey.
Hikari
Whisucker
This is Kameyari, from Hikari.
I was busy...
What?
There's a turnout in the shopping street!
I can't take responsibility for it, so get this!
Wait, why do I have to go?
Next time, I'll go with Zou!
Even if I try to stop the clock
Time will pass
Don't look at me
Let's laugh and live
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be clear
Bye bye
Let's wash our hands
I don't want to
Oh Yeah
Let's live the way we like
There is something good
The sunset calls me outside the door