'Animals are raising their sleigh'
Ah, the summer is coming again this year
It's come, it's come!
The wave is coming, the wave is this way, this way
"Noyajukuri"
"Kachidoki Bridge"
Open the Kachidoki Bridge!
What a wonderful wedding!
Cheers!
Hey, we've come all the way to Ginza.
Let's go back to Kachidoki Bridge.
But the direction is the other way around.
What? You're not saying anything.
I understand.
It's Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan, we're going to Kachidoki Bridge.
Ryo-chan, we've arrived. Wake up.
You should have told us to go by ourselves.
Kei-chan, stop the car!
What's wrong?
There's a man on the bridge.
He's not a ghost, is he?
Where are you, Reiko?
I think I saw him on the bridge.
"Kachidoki Bridge"
It seems there were no accidents near the bridge.
Kachigukiboshi?
But why is there a person in such a place?
Good morning.
Senpai, you're lucky.
The chief is in a good mood this morning.
Lucky.
Good morning.
I think I drank a little too much.
Idiot!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't yell at me.
My head is so hot.
Come here.
I'll squeeze you.
I'm not a stray cat.
Hey, where are you in such a good mood?
Hurry up and come here.
What's wrong?
He was in such a good mood.
Idiot!
It's a illegal parking lot.
Good morning.
Oh, it's a police car.
That's Sapporo No.
Yes.
I've been driving next to Kachigukiboshi since last night.
Kachigukiboshi?
Since last night?
Yes.
A man in white clothes was driving by.
White clothes?
Could it be last night's car?
Hello, can you tell me who owns this car?
The No. is Sapporo.
So it wasn't an illegal parking lot.
Is this an incident?
No, it's still a car.
It's not like it's a man's car.
Yes. Sapporo City, Toyohiakku, yes.
Shiratori, white bird, pure water, Shiratori Jun.
Thank you very much.
Did something happen to Shiratori Jun?
Yes.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Do you know him, Pyo-chan?
Yes.
He's my friend from middle school.
But it was only for a short time.
He left his car near Kachidoki Bridge and disappeared somewhere.
Kachidoki Bridge?
Oh, right. He came to see the bridge.
The bridge?
What do you mean, Senpai?
Yes. That was when I was a cute junior high school student.
Hello, Kankichi.
Yes.
Wow.
That's awesome.
Yes.
Big spin, medium speed.
My eyes are spinning.
Kankichi!
Who told you to do the big spin?
It's a service.
Kankichi, you're awesome.
Jun, did you have fun?
Next time, I'll show you something even more flashy.
Kankichi, you're awesome. The next time, I'll show you something even more flashy.
Kankichi!
Yes!
Next time, I'll show you something even more silly.
Next time, I'll show you something even more trickier.
Hey, Jun, you went on a night trip, didn't you?
That's amazing!
But I couldn't see well because I'm so busy.
I went by bullet train.
Have you ride "Tonkichi"?
Soldiers have never been on it before.
Would you like some tea?
Yes.
Food for everyone please.
Oh, it's cake again!
Sorry for always having to do this, auntie.
It's okay.
From now on, be good friends with Jun.
Okay.
Then, take your time.
When I'm watching the gym,
I don't feel bored at all when I'm watching Kan-chan and the others.
Kan-Kishi's torii is only about energy.
Damn you!
Next time, I'll show you my back.
Instead, show me again during the test.
My vision is 2.5 and it's for the tanning.
Hahaha!
That's a really good book.
Did you read all of these?
Most of them.
I'll lend you one anytime.
We're not good at these kind of thick books.
Right, Tonkichi?
Yeah, just the textbook is enough.
That's right.
I think this is interesting.
Japanese...
That's the bridge over the Sumida River.
Wow.
You made me remember it in elementary school.
What I like the most is the Kachidoki Bridge.
It moves like a gaga.
I want to see it.
You've never seen it?
I want to see it, but it's far away.
It's close. It's just over Ginza.
You stop the car and the bridge opens slowly.
When you look at the bridge, the road is like a wall.
It's very powerful.
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Let's go to Kachidoki Bridge.
It takes about 20 minutes by bicycle.
OK.
Let's go!
"Kachidoki Bridge"
A large army of soldiers appears here.
Ta-da!
The bridge of Kachidoki Bridge
"Kachidoki Bridge"
We're almost there.
The End
Look, over there!
That bridge opens!
It's perfect to look at from here!
I always buy bread and watch while eating.
Oh, the boat is here!
We did it! It opens!
There we go!
Gugugutta!
Huh?
It won't open.
That's strange. It should always open at noon.
What's wrong?
What? It won't open anymore?
It opened yesterday.
The Kado-kyo is no longer popular.
From now on, it's the era of land transport.
It's easier to carry water.
I didn't know that at all.
What?
The Kachidoki Bridge won't open anymore?
Once the station is decided, it won't open again.
The ones who are made to suffer by the flow of time are always the weak ones like us.
The Kachidoki Bridge
Tch. I came to see it. I'm disappointed.
I understand.
Jun, you were looking forward to it.
Don't lose your temper, Jun.
Kondo.
Yes!
Shibayama.
Shiratori is a dead man.
Sensei, what's wrong with Jun?
He's sleeping with a fever.
I heard he was shocked when he heard about Kachidoki Bridge.
Shibayama.
Let's go back.
Yes.
What?
The weather is getting better.
I'm moving to Hokkaido where the air is nice.
I got along with everyone.
We're friends even if we go far away.
Yes.
That's right.
But...
There's only one thing left in my mind.
I couldn't see the Kachidoki Bridge.
I wanted to see it with everyone.
Jun, when are you going to Hokkaido?
The day after tomorrow.
That soon?
I see.
Jun moved.
That's too bad.
I can't eat such delicious cake for the rest of my life.
I'll come back to the zero point test again.
Jun, you were disappointed about the Kachidoki Bridge.
I wanted to show you the place where the bridge opens.
That's right.
I'll show you the place where the bridge opens.
What?
It's impossible.
We'll open it.
We'll open the bridge.
We'll open the bridge and show it to Jun.
What?
Kanchan.
What are you doing here?
Come with me.
I'll show you how to open a Kachidoki Bridge.
What?
How to open a Kachidoki Bridge?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Wait.
I'm going to change.
Over here.
John, I'll be right back.
This is the best view.
Wait here, Jun.
Can we really open it?
Don't worry.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
There are four towers in Kachidoki Bridge.
The only one with stairs is that tower.
That must be the driver's room.
I'll give you the bridge.
You two stop the car.
Okay.
It's as I thought it would be.
Here it is.
As I thought, it is locked.
However...
It's useless.
I'm good at opening.
Stop.
I'll open it.
I can't.
I can't stop it at all.
This one too can't stop.
It's open.
I got it.
It's so crispy.
There are so many switches.
I guess I have to turn on the power.
How do I do it?
Stop!
Please stop!
What are you doing?
Why did you stop the car?
Go!
Mr. Hakushu, Mr. Omawari found us.
Sola, wait!
Mr. Hakushu, close the door!
Sola, open the door!
What are you going to do?
No! The car won't stop, and Mr. Omawari will find us.
The plan was too reckless. Let's stop it.
Idiot! Jun is waiting for you!
Will it really open?
Sola!
How will you do it if you can open the door?
I give up!
Open it!
Please, get out of there.
What are you going to do, KhangKi?
I'm going to open the door.
Only this chance!
Good!
You are so nice.
Shut down the power!
Sola, don't touch it!
Sola!
Yankee!
The power is on!
Okay, put in all the switches!
Yes!
Gun, stop the car immediately!
Stop it!
Open it!
Oh, the signal of the Kachidoki Bridge has arrived!
Impossible! That bridge should have been closed!
Move! The bridge will rise!
Oh, no!
Please, move! The Kachidoki Bridge!
Stop it!
The Kachidoki Bridge is here!
The Kachidoki Bridge!
Open it!
The bridge is...
The Kachidoki Bridge is here!
Open it! Open it!
Open it more!
The bridge is...
I knew it was real!
The Kachidoki Bridge is...
What is going on?
Idiot!
Please, return the signal!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
Yes!
It's fully open!
We did it!
Yes!
The Kachidoki Bridge is open!
It's like they are celebrating!
The bridge is open again?
The Kachidoki Bridge is not supposed to be like this, after all!
It's because of Sumida's face!
It's really amazing!
It's more than I could imagine, Kan-chan!
I did it!
Did you see Jun?
Yes!
It's amazing, 3-B.
Enough, cut the bullshit!
Let's break!
He just 경찰ied the bridge!
Feeling the pressure...
I see the bridge!
Now, the bridge!
You can run!
I'm going!
Run!
Bye bye!
Hey! Hold your horses up and let's escape!
Gee, look at them!
Boss!
Help! Help!
Get him!
And then they swam to Hamarikyu, and then they ran away and came back.
Takami was watching the chaos of the Kachidoki Bridge.
It's been a mess for a long time.
I'm sure Jun was happy.
Of course. I can't forget the excited smile of that time.
But if Jun had left the car and climbed the Kachidoki Bridge...
Maybe...
That's impossible.
He was weak, but he was strong.
Excuse me.
The car in front...
Jun!
Kan-chan?
Why are you here?
He looks like a policeman.
Kan-chan is the police.
Are you serious?
Don't laugh. You're a criminal.
No, I was just thinking that the repairman would take me.
Oh, yeah.
This...
A professor?
You're here, Jun!
It's all thanks to Kan-chan.
I can't forget the day when he raised the bridge with his life.
Now he's designing the bridge.
He's designing the bridge.
Then, what made you climb the Kachidoki Bridge?
There was something I really wanted to find out.
Hm?
The Kachidoki Bridge is very good.
Oh, Chief!
That's my friend, Dr. Kouhaku.
Everyone told me about you, Ryo-tsu.
What? You heard about me?
Chief, you're acting strange.
Yeah.
I heard that you were hung up together when the bridge was raised.
You were hung up together when the bridge was raised.
That's right.
I remember that I was so nervous and worked so hard on my legs.
But at the end, I fell down and fell on the river.
Do you remember the policeman's face?
Of course.
He had such a strange look.
He had such thick eyebrows.
His nose was so long.
And he had such a big mouth.
I'd forget about that if I ever saw him again.
Ryo-chan.
What?
He had such a strange look.
What did he have?
He had such a thin, thick eyebrows.
I-I can't believe it.
He had such a strange look.
I'm that policeman!
I finally met the culprit of that riot.
Calm down, chief!
Hey, wait!
It's already an accident!
I did it!
Osmo's final blow hit!
Four final blows will be taken.
I'll invite Reiko and take Nakagawa with me.
Who should I choose as the last one?
Chief!
I'm kidding!
I'll invite you, chief!
Next time on Tokoton Osmo!
Thank you!
Let's smile anytime
Even when something ridiculous happens
Let's smile cutely
You can leave with a face that's nothing
Hey, smile for me
You're not in any bad shape
You're in the same mood as before
Let's smile cutely
You aren't young
Smile as you usually do
If you aren't a child
Smiling is not beautiful
Smiling is he question
Smiling is OK
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry."