The End
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and look away
Like someone calling you
After the rain
You walk while looking back
At the end of the rain
Give your hand to your mother
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried to walk
On the black tile of the Akihito Gai
Who is it?
I was a child once
But everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You can see everyone
There is a wall
Come on everyone
To our town
Thank you!
Akihito Gai
Video Cameraman
Money, money, money.
Hmm, that's a lot.
Are you looking for a part-time job?
I just got paid last week.
That's not true. I used it on that day.
What?
You can't live a joyful life with just a salary.
Some people earn 300,000 yen with a freighter.
I can't stand people who don't get a job.
I'm going to work as a freighter from today.
But you're a civil servant.
So I'm going to work as a freighter while being a civil servant.
The pay will double.
Oh?
8,000 yen for a full-time job.
That's it!
No!
I'm disqualified.
If I come with a young man, everyone will be flustered.
Next, next.
Move, move, move.
8,000 yen for a full-time job.
There's no doubt about it.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, good.
First inspection passed.
Second inspection as it is.
Hey, Kiroko.
Happy 30th anniversary.
Happy 90th anniversary.
30th inspection begins the modern revolution.
Yes, yes.
There are only four remaining.
Good.
In this journey,
I have passed the 30th anniversary of overseas experience television
of Taitokyo TV
in my own company.
This is really honorable.
With great luck,
I would like to make this project a success.
So what should we do?
Yes.
Tomorrow,
with all of us,
I, the director,
I'm the director, the cameraman, the sound man, the assistant director, so AD.
This is the basic of the staff.
And you guys will be the assistant of AD.
So it's AAD.
It's like DDT.
Super Idol, the shining star, Alps.
It's a project that makes idols popular.
We're going to walk from here.
All four of us will carry this equipment to the top of the mountain.
You have to be strong.
Ouch!
We're not carrying it.
We're carrying it.
We're not going to waste a minute or a second.
The president of the old Katagi's hot TV man's survival is famous in the industry.
Don't talk nonsense!
I'm a super idol.
You have to be prepared because you can work three times as much as you can.
I don't complain if I get a part-time job.
This is this.
Then the CD campaign is like that.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Thank you.
The air is fresh.
Hikaru-chan.
It's Hikaru, the shooting star.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Yes.
Hikaru, the shooting star, is motivated.
I'm motivated.
A little more.
Let's make a good show.
Yes.
President!
If you are so violent, Hikaru will be broken.
Oh, this is rude.
What are you talking about?
Get ready quickly.
Then, first of all, I will take the first shot of the departure here.
Next, the camera will follow Hikaru-san walking along the river.
Yes.
What?
Did you just say to Hikaru, the shooting star, to walk on the mountain road?
Did you hear that?
You said to walk on the super idol.
It's a climbing program, so you have to walk.
Hikaru, the shooting star, won't walk more than five times.
Why?
Because I'm an idol.
Two.
I'm a salesman with three or four super idols.
Do you understand?
But unfortunately, we can't get a car from here.
If Hikaru-san doesn't walk, we won't be able to shoot, but...
Is that so?
Then it can't be helped.
Let's go home, Hikaru-chan.
Hey, wait a minute.
Are you going to come all the way here and get off the show?
It's ridiculous.
I just want to return it to other production companies.
What did you say?
If that's the case,
You're not going to be able to cross this industry, are you?
Of course I can.
That's the privilege of a popular idol.
Change the production company?
What about our part-time job?
It's not a joke!
I won't return it.
Please move.
Hey, boss.
It's a joke to walk Hikaru-chan.
It's tough.
Super idol shooting star Hikaru is standing there.
It's the same as climbing.
In other words,
Even if I'm not there,
It's the same as the top of Everest.
It's the same as climbing.
Thank you.
Boss, do you have a helicopter?
What?
It's a helicopter that carries Hikaru-san to the top of the mountain.
If the show goes on like this,
All that's left is the red paper.
Is that okay?
That's...
Then it's a loss, isn't it?
What?
But now the helicopter is coming.
You don't have to call me that now.
Selfish idol shooting star Hikaru.
Escape from the scene on the day of the recording.
A good story that has a wide show.
A climbing idol is a small scandal.
There are so many stories that it can't be restored.
It's scary.
Is that so?
Is that a helicopter?
Then, Soton,
The president should have said it earlier.
I'll bring you negotiation.
Ahaha...
Then I will give you a voice of starting with Title Bag.
Take 1.
Nihon Alps will be conquered.
It's come to an end.
Well then, I'll wait for you up there.
Hey hey.
Carry heavy equipment with you.
Hey, hey.
Damn it!
Let's go! Don't be lazy!
Hurry up! Get on the helicopter first!
It's impossible to get on the helicopter first!
If you have time to talk, then hurry up and walk!
The hourly wage for that is 8,000 yen!
There are 2 km left! Do your best!
I'm out of breath! I can't take it anymore!
Hey, don't be so stubborn!
You're going to work part-time?
I'll take care of the luggage!
Oh, I see! I'm counting on you!
However, I'll take your part-time wage!
That's fine!
But there are too many spare batteries!
One battery weighs 1.5 kg, so 100 batteries will weigh 150 kg!
Without batteries, the camera won't work.
I didn't overdo it.
I'm sorry!
Next!
He's also out of money!
Leave it to me!
It's heavy!
However, the part-time wage for 3 people is 24,000 yen!
I'm out of money, too!
In the end, the director, the cameraman, the sound man, and I were 4 people!
It's like I'm going to give birth to a baby!
I'm going to give birth to a baby!
Damn, I'm late.
I couldn't wait for super idols.
Well, it was quite late.
I thought I'd go home because it was too late.
Hahaha!
Mr. Hikaru
Mr. Hikaro
This is great!
Excuse me.
Thank you for your hard work.
If this is a shooting, I don't have to go up the mountain, but I can shoot in the studio.
I want to walk on my own.
I want to walk.
What? If you want to walk, you have to walk.
If you want to walk, you have to walk.
How is it?
It's okay if you walk.
We're going to the next park!
Can you let us ride it?
Yasuzawa, your face is pale. Are you okay?
It's been a while since Tetsuya.
Hold on tight!
I'm sorry.
Why would you do these things to me?
Give me a break!
*Sigh*
Okay, that's enough.
Good work.
Finally, the staff is just me and the president.
Hmm, no matter what you do, Hikaru-chan is still cute.
However, climbing up the mountain is not fun.
Hmm...
Oh, there it is!
The fire is falling from that tree.
Hikaru, the shooting star, will save it and put it back into the tree.
It will be a great scene where Hikaru-chan's kindness will be expressed.
Ugh...
Don't let me climb up or walk. How can I get it?
First of all, let me do this!
Oh, you say you can't get it?
Of course!
Then, there's no choice.
Now, let's go home.
Wait a minute!
This is a part-time job for five people!
How can you give up so easily?
Why don't you tell me when you die?
Oh...
When you die...
Let's go!
Ah, Hinaga!
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Hmm...
Well, you can use it if you're angry.
I'll borrow it for a while.
Okay.
I'll return it soon.
Yes.
Hmm?
Ouch!
Stop it!
Ahhhh!
The price is 40,000 yen!
Now, go back to the country.
Yes. Okay.
I'll get it back.
Wonderful!
You're the best, Hikaru!
You're kind and the fans are already tears.
Now, not only young people but also middle-aged hearts can come here!
Ahhhh!
Ah, it's beautiful.
Yes. Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, what kind of fruit is this?
Well...
It's pretty, isn't it?
It's a potato.
Oh, I see.
Can you eat it?
Yes.
It's good!
But you know it well.
Before my debut, my father took me to the mountains.
That's unusual.
I was quite good at it.
Hahaha.
Oh!
It's a good face!
Alright, let's shoot a scene where I eat a potato.
Yes, sir!
Oh, my, my, my!
Hikaru-chan, you shouldn't eat this.
But everyone is eating it.
No, you can't.
If you break your stomach, you can use it for tomorrow's work, right?
It's a little fine.
Hikaru, the shooting star,
If you take a break from one show,
you'll get tens of thousands of red beans.
Will you take responsibility for me?
Tens of thousands!
Then, I'll take a different shot.
Yes, that's it.
Oh, it's not good.
After all, Hikaru-chan doesn't like wild vegetables.
Let's stop.
Hikaru-chan, let's go next.
Yes, sir.
We'll take a shot of Hikaru-chan swimming.
I see, sir.
Will you take a shot of Hikaru-chan swimming?
Yes, sir.
I don't know.
Will you take a shot of her swimming?
No, sir.
Hey! Hey! The water's...
What? The screen is...
Ah! The cameraman's sinking!
You idiot!
You're gonna fill up the water? Be careful!
It's rocks! I'm gonna crash!
I'm so thirsty...
Ouch!
It's not the temple's money! You idiot!
I'm sorry.
But it's not fun to just swim.
How about...
Oh! That's it!
How about jumping into a waterfall from that rock?
This will be a thrilling video.
The fans will be sweating.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't make him jump again.
Of course.
This program is a documentary.
There are so many lies and frauds.
Where is the documentary?
I don't like it.
Whether it's a lie or a drama,
we just want to impress the viewers.
No!
The real video is the most touching.
The viewers are waiting for the idol, Hikaru Nagareboshi.
No one wants the real Hikaru Nagareboshi.
The giant statue we're making...
Hikaru Nagareboshi is the real Hikaru Nagareboshi.
She's just an idol.
She's just a fake.
Okay, enough.
If you want to walk, you can walk.
Hikaru Nagareboshi
Can you say a phrase like "No" when you die?
I can do it, too.
It's awful.
That's all half of it.
Isn't it, Hikaru-chan?
I'm going to swim.
What? Did you say something?
Hikaru-chan?
I'm going to swim.
What's wrong, Hikaru-chan?
I can do it too! I'm not a doll!
Hey, hey, Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru!
Th-this is...
Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru-chan...
Hikaru!
How nice it feels!
I've been forgetting this feeling for a long time.
What did you say? You're retiring from the entertainment world?
From now on, I'll be a child.
I'll walk the path I believe in with my own feet.
Why are you doing that all of a sudden?
This Ryotsu-san taught me.
What?
Thank you for waking me up.
No, I...
Is it your fault? What did you do to Hikaru? What did you do to Hikaru?
I don't know anything!
And then, I have a request.
Please stop broadcasting this video.
That's not who I really am.
You're just lying.
I'm not joking!
If you really retire, this is your last job, isn't it?
You can't just send me such a precious video, can you?
A precious video?
Oh, President. Please keep that tape tightly.
Don't worry about it. I won't let anyone touch it.
I won't let anyone touch it.
I'm sorry, President. For my sake...
No, I'm the one who should thank you.
Thanks to you, I woke up. Thank you.
Wait a minute! What about my pay?
I'm retiring from the entertainment world. I'm sorry, but I won't give you my pay.
What?
I worked so hard, but I only get 40,000 yen for my pay?
It's all your fault!
I'll make you pay! I'll sue you!
No, I'm not a victim!
Senpai, you did it again.
You're a star now.
What's next?
Everest? Matterhorn?
Did you climb the Amazon River?
You're the only king in the South Pole.
That's amazing!
I'm retiring from the entertainment world and going to the adventure world.
I'm surprised.
Thanks to you, I made fans all over Japan my enemy.
I was a great man.
I told them to walk on their own feet, but I didn't tell them to walk to the South Pole.
I finally arrived at the South Pole.
The wind was like a lie until yesterday.
Hikaru, get a little closer to the penguin.
Idiot!
It's a documentary to capture the moment of love.
Thank you for your support.
And what I have now is the money of a staff who taught me to walk on my own feet.
Thank you, Mr. Kan-kichi Ryotsu.
The End
To Be Continued
Every day is no problem
When I take a hot shower
I recover my health with a sleeping pillow
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
I'm flying on Monday
Monday, Monday, Monday
In the rice naming contest,
the rice I made won
and I got a lot of rice
But I can't finish it by myself
Let's start a business with this
Next time, "Traveling between rice and rice balls"
See you next time
Thank you for watching