Tencent Video"
When you're watching the TV, bright your room and leave it.
Those who have no money, come to me.
I don't have any, but I worry.
I'm worried about you
Look at the blue sky
The white clouds
I'm sure that one day
We'll be able to do something
Come to me
I'm not here
But don't worry
Look at the burning
Red light
Blue clouds
We'll be able to do something
You know it, don't you?
You know it, you know it.
If you do, then shut up and follow me!
The Robot
What a great robot!
Is this the latest type of humanoid robot?
It moves smoothly.
In the old days, when you imitated robots...
Gashin!
Gashin! Gashin!
That's right.
The real robot was that one.
That's why.
It's a great progress.
The study of practicality is also in progress, isn't it?
Yes.
There are also fire stations that actually work on fire sites.
In the meantime, it may be time to leave all dangerous work to robots.
The robot officer may have appeared.
There was a robot officer!
Development 001!
It was a useless robot.
The robot officer is already in trouble.
That's right.
Certainly.
Everyone, be happy!
The latest robot officer will be deployed at this launch site.
Boss! What did you say now?
The latest robot officer will come.
Development 004.
Why? Aren't you happy?
I'm not happy!
Anyway, it is like 001.
The crap of the modern age will come.
You are naive, Ryotsu.
What?
Based on the experience so far,
we have joined 2,000 researchers.
We have invented 3,000 cutting-edge technologies.
Then,
something like this?
This time, a car will transform!
Yeah.
"I think it's not a humanoid robot."
"It looks like a great robot is coming this time, Ryo-san."
"No, I can't be relieved until I see the real thing."
"Don't look down on the real thing, Ryo-tsu."
"This is the latest robot model developed by 2000 researchers and 3000 cutting-edge technology, the development 0045 Otsugata."
"Hello, this is the development 0045 Otsugata."
"How is it? You look surprised and you can't even speak."
"This is..."
"The latest model?"
"It's got a very human-like atmosphere."
"What are you doing?"
"Hey, Ryo-tsu!"
"It's definitely a robot."
"Of course!"
"It's the latest model developed by 2000 researchers and 3000 cutting-edge technology."
"But the design sense is old."
"What?"
"This design was designed by a thousand famous designers and their maximum number of contracts was put together."
"So to speak, it's the most advanced design in the 21st century."
"It's not something you can put together."
"The contents must be amazing."
"That's right."
"I'm counting on you, 0045."
"Yes, I'll do my best."
"Senpai, what are you going to do, 0045?"
"If you make me do something wrong, I'll just complain to the director."
"Let's get out of here."
"No way!"
"I came here to do my job. Please let me do something."
"I got it, I got it."
"It's really human-like."
"It's the latest model after all."
"So, what can you do?"
"Yes, I've memorized all the laws."
"What about the work of the station?"
"No, I've been told that I can learn it on the spot."
"You're really a new officer."
"Hmm."
"Maybe you should think of it as the same as a normal new officer."
"I guess so."
"Alright, I got it."
"I don't know if it's the latest model, but I'll treat it as a new officer here."
"What?"
"Do you have a problem?"
"No, not really."
"I'm not a new officer."
"I'm a senior in this office."
"I'm supposed to be told to obey seniors."
"Yes, I got it, senior."
"You're not a senior. Call me God."
"God?"
"Yes, it's up to me to educate you to be a good detective."
"So, I'm God to you."
"I see."
"I got it, God."
"What?"
"I don't need that!"
"Yes, God."
"Alright, that's enough. I'll go patrol. Follow me, 0045!"
"A police officer who is in the police station writes documents such as address, address, and escape, and patrols to protect his or her safety."
"I see."
"It's important to be careful to be loved by the residents."
"What do you mean?"
"For example."
"I'll take your hand and give it to the old woman who's waiting for the signal."
"Okay, I got it."
"Hey!"
"Let's go together."
"Don't hesitate."
"Help!"
"Are you alright, old woman?"
"Ow, ow, ow."
"You idiot! You're going to kill me, aren't you?"
"I'm going to do as God says."
"Look closely! The signal is red."
"Oh, you're right."
"Come on, be strong."
"I'm sorry."
"You bastard!"
"No, it's a fight."
"Oh, I'm scared."
"Hey, you can't be scared."
"I'm not good at fighting."
"It's the police officer's job to stop the fight."
"Ah, the police officer's job?"
"A robot can't lose to a human."
"Go, 0045!"
"Y-Yes, God."
"You bastard!"
"Please stop!"
"Go, 0045!"
"God, help me!"
"He's really weak."
"Hey, stop it!"
"Aah!"
"I'm really sorry, God."
"Show me something useful."
"I'll do my best."
"Ah, Yuji!"
"Ah!"
"Get out of my way!"
"Ah, the kid!"
"I'll help you!"
"Huh?"
"Aah!"
"Wait, 0045!"
"I'll help you!"
"Aah!"
"I'm hurt!"
"God, please help me!"
"If you can't swim, don't jump!"
"Aah!"
"Ah!"
"I'm so relieved, Yuji."
"Geez, how did humans have to help robots?"
"It's the opposite of normal."
I'm sorry, God.
Wake up! We're going to continue patrolling!
It looks like the water got in and it's not working anymore.
What?
Just do some waterproofing.
I mean, which one of these is the latest model?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
All right.
This should be fine.
Oh, really?
Thank you, God.
I'm sorry. The truck's broken down.
This kind of hard work is the job of a robot, 0045.
Yes, I understand, God.
Do your best, 0045!
Be strong!
Just a little more.
I'm sorry. Let me rest for a while.
Are you really a robot?
All right. Here's your second try.
Just one more breath.
Yes!
Stop it!
Help me, God!
Don't increase my work!
I'm sorry!
Good job, Ryo.
I'm not strong. I have zero athletic ability.
And I always fail no matter what I do.
I'm really a bad robot.
I'm sorry.
Everyone fails at first.
Don't be afraid. Just do your best.
Thank you very much. I'll do my best.
Oh, no! I drank tea.
I have no energy.
What do I do? My body is so rusty!
Calm down and spit it out.
He's got a name.
Huh?
All right.
I'm Dametaro.
Dametaro?
I think it's a good name.
Dametaro.
Robot Officer Dametaro
Hey, Dametaro! Let's go on a patrol!
Yes, God!
Well, I'm going to go for a bit.
Have a good trip!
Be careful!
You two are a good pair.
Dametaro-kun has gotten used to this dressing room.
Hmm... I'll take a break for a bit.
It looks delicious.
If you drink it, it'll rust, right?
Yes.
Don't look so pathetic.
I thought something like this would happen.
This is a high-end pure katsu for a radio station.
Wow! Thank you, God!
Drink it carefully.
Yes, sir.
Ryo-chan is quite kind.
Reiko? Are you back from shopping?
Yes.
Good work.
Ryo-chan,
are you on a patrol?
Yes.
I'm taking a break.
Sir,
kick it!
Oh!
God,
please let me do this.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Yes, sir.
Here we go!
Ouch!
Dametaro-kun!
What are you doing, Dametaro?
Hahaha, I feel like I have a bad brother.
Ohara-kun.
I'm talking about 004 development of Robot Police.
Have you heard of them?
Huh?
What?
It seems that they are calling you Dametaro
in front of the police force in the field.
004 is a robot made by 2000 researchers
and 3000 cutting-edge technologies.
It's a robot made of a piece of paper.
Why is that nickname?
I saw the report, but there seems to be a lot of failures.
That's probably because Ryotsu made his failure 004.
No, I can't just say that.
Some people have actually seen 004 fail.
At this rate, we will be held responsible.
I'll have to do something about it.
Yes, sir.
I'm back.
Ryotsu, Chief Ohara is waiting for you.
At times like this, it's not a good idea to talk about it.
What is it, Chief?
Ryotsu.
What did you do to 004?
What?
What did you say?
004 was made by collecting the essence of the latest technology.
That's useless.
What did you do to make it like that?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Don't lie.
Then why did 004 become like that?
It was like that from the beginning.
Don't be stupid.
You must have done something.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The chief will be here in three days.
At that time, 004 will have the power.
If you don't have the power, you won't get any bonus.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you don't want that, you have to put it back in three days.
That's ridiculous.
If I can't give you the power in three days, what will happen to 004?
If it's useless, you have to collect it.
I guess we have to scrap it.
What?
Dametaro scrapped it?
Ryo, what you just said...
You guys heard that?
Dametaro didn't...
It's okay.
I'll go to the library with Terai.
I see.
Is that true, senpai?
Dametaro will be scrapped.
He'll be scrapped.
If the investigation comes from the capital three days later, and it's still not good,
that's what's going to happen.
What?
I'll scrap that guy.
Is this the god's room?
Here's the god's room.
You're going to sleep here for a while.
What are you doing, god?
Oh, my God!
This is the design of 004 that I got at a very low price.
If it is made as it is, it should be able to exert more power than humans.
Let's look into it.
There is no abnormality.
Let's try and increase the output a little.
All right. How is this?
How do you feel, Damedaro?
No! Something's wrong!
What? The transmission? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Stop it, Damedaro!
Damn it!
Emergency!
The transmission is here.
I knew it.
That was dangerous.
The voltage may have been too high.
How about this time?
How do you feel, Damedaro?
Oh, it's been a long time, God.
You didn't come to see me at all.
I was lonely.
You're right.
I'll make you a snack sometime.
Yeah.
That's great.
You've become more girlish.
Why does my body start to flutter?
It seems to be more useful than before.
Damedaro is a genius.
What about Miyako?
I got it.
You got something?
No?
My head!
What should we do, senpai?
We should do some special training!
Look, your chin's up!
Three more laps!
Okay!
It's no use doing such a thing to a robot.
Yeah, it's not like it's going to give you muscle.
No, it's actually quite meaningful.
What?
Dametaro has the latest learning features.
So by accumulating experiences,
he learns how to move efficiently.
As a result, he should be able to show off his skills more and more.
Huh?
I see.
The problem is that he only has two days left.
Hey, your hips aren't in!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Like this!
Shoooo!
Come on, 100 more laps!
Ouch... I wanna get out of here...
You don't!
Swim faster!
Oh...
What's with your motivation?
200 more...
Oh-! It's me!
What's the problem!?
I'm the leader!
Okay! I'll be right back!
*Sigh*
I'm going back to the toilet.
200 more laps.
Let's do it one more time!
Okay.
Alright.
Oh, the battery's dead.
Huh? Nobody's here.
Let me charge it up.
What? Is it today?
Really?
Oh, it's God's voice.
You were supposed to come two days later, right?
I was in a hurry for the general meeting.
No way!
It won't change much when it's today.
Or are you planning something bad?
No, I'm not!
Please, wait a little longer!
I don't want to scrap the useless ones!
I'm going to scrap them!
Ryo-tsu.
Yes, it's Ohara.
Ah, I understand.
I heard that we'll be able to see the general office soon.
What?
Damn it!
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Who's there?
What kind of place have you placed your clothes in?
Ah, these are Tametaro's clothes!
I didn't know you listened to what I just said.
Tametaro!
Even though you were born as a robot police officer,
it was such a waste of time that you didn't use them at all.
Ah!
- The
tank is exploding! - We can't fight it! - There
are people left! - We'll be caught up in the explosion! - What?
- You can't run. I'm a police officer! - - - You
're...!
-
- - - - - - - - - - -
- - - - - - - - - -
I'm sorry!
Thanks to you, we didn't get into a mess.
We saved the officer officer.
Of course.
As expected of a new robot officer.
He has 2,000 researchers and 3,000 advanced technology.
If he can't move due to a battery out, he should have said so from the beginning.
If he can't move, he can't talk.
Ryo is happy.
I've never seen such a senior before.
What did you do, God?
Nothing!
As a policeman, you're still a criminal.
I'll train you more and more.
Wait!
Ouch!
Idiot! Don't jump out of the road suddenly!
But, God...
What'd you up to?
To be continued.
♪ La La La La ♪
♪ You don't want to be ♪
♪ one to trade delusions by wearing luxe clothes ♩
♪ When you get stuck on the corner ♪
If you're going down this road, the moon will escape
Now isn't everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat a little
You're sometimes helping someone
Baby do you know me?
Head to tomorrow with a nice breath
Don't feel wrecked
I'll do what I do
A cute heart breath
What's hard to understand
That's right I want to show you
Than to look back
It's alright
Next time
You appeared again, Professor To-no-mo!
What? The medicine to become a transparent person?
Who would cooperate with such a human experiment?
Wait, my legs are transparent before I knew it!
Damn it! You're not good at measuring!
Next time, "The Transparent Deca-Arawaru"
Thank you for watching!
♪ Over there is a turtle-ah-ah, a turtle-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Over there is a turtle-ah-ah-ah, a turtle-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Over there is a turtle-ah-ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!