Excuse me.
Yes.
Excuse me, where is Kameari station?
Ah, go straight on this road to the left and you will get to the station.
Is that so? Thank you very much.
Excuse me, I have a question. Could it be Tendou Yoshimi?
No, it's not. I've heard that we look a lot alike.
Ah, is that so?
When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away.
Come to me, you poor thing.
I don't have money, but I'll buy you a drink.
I'm worried about you.
Look at the blue sky.
White clouds.
I'm sure things will be alright.
Ahahahaha!
Translation by Lyrical Nonsense
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
So, we begin!
The
What the?
Why did they come to my house?
The judge of the Ryotsukanchichi Police Department has decided to take the seat of the ginseng office!
Oh my god! Oh my god! Ohara-kun!
It's like a dream, Chief!
Me too, Ohara-kun!
C-Chief!
Ohara-kun!
Chief!
Huh? Ryo-chan is the one who's transferred?
That's right.
He's the best police officer in the country.
The number of death sentences is astronomical, and the Katsushika office has always been left to us.
The decision was made this time because it was decided that only the Katsushika office would be held responsible for that.
Even so, the president of the ginseng office has accepted the senior's acceptance.
He's got the courage.
Well, that's...
How should I put it?
Well, I don't mind the small things.
Anyway, I'm happy.
If I think about it, I'll become his superior and go soon.
Blood pressure rises, my heart weakens, and I become an evil demon.
I've been through all the hardships of life.
I won't be exhausted today.
The long winter for me is over, and spring is coming at last.
The president is also very happy.
He's going to give all the employees a special bonus to celebrate the release of Ryo-chan.
Ryo-chan is so pitiful.
If you talk about it, Ryo-chan will come.
What's with Ryo-chan's outfit?
It's terrible.
Ryo-chan was kicked out, too.
Where does he live?
It seems that he will stay in the guesthouse of the post office for the time being.
Oh?
Oh, isn't that Mr. Ryo-chan?
Mr. Ryo-chan?
From today on, you are neither my secretary nor my subordinate.
Of course, it's polite to call me by my last name.
Oh, and Mr. Ryo-chan.
Don't call me even if you happen to be in town.
I understand.
You look happy.
I will not be scolded by you anymore.
What?
I don't want to be scolded.
It's not that.
It's because you are the one who is bad.
What will happen again?
Generally, the leader is like this.
That's why I'm not a superior anymore.
I'm no longer with you.
I have a guest.
If you need anything, consult a new superior.
Goodbye.
Senpai.
Ryo-chan.
Nakagawa.
Reiko.
Live in a taxi.
No.
Senpai.
How are you?
Show me your face sometimes, Ryo-chan.
Damn it.
If I don't leave the station before the park,
this show will have to change the title.
Do you understand?
He left without a word.
Senpai.
Did you come here to say something?
By the way, Ryo-chan.
Where will you be assigned to the station in Ginza?
I think it's the station in front of Kabukiza in East Ginza.
There is Ginza.
Ginza is surely there.
A new place is approaching.
Bus stop.
Welcome to our city.
You're doing well.
You rushed from a down town to downtown Tokyo.
Geez, they look different.
Besides, enemy at Kabukiza is your grandma.
Ouch!
Sorry.
Who are you?
What is it?
The Tachibana family has been lost somewhere.
The Tachibana family?
Oh, you came to see the Kabukiza.
You said you lost everyone.
You must have been lost.
It doesn't matter.
Look for them.
Okay.
I got it.
No matter how close you are to the Kabukiza,
you always see the same old woman on the right or left.
Don't you remember what kind of old woman you were with?
I don't remember at all.
The Tachibana family, the Tachibana family, the Tachibana family...
Oh, my.
What?
The old woman is gone.
Hey, where is the old woman now?
Damn it.
Everyone looks the same.
Hey, where are you?
Oh, there she is.
Hey, don't get lost again.
There are too many people.
I'm dizzy.
This is faster.
Hey, everyone.
I don't know this old woman.
Tachibana Kaido.
I'm the old woman.
Oh, there she is.
It's Kante.
This way.
Thank you, Mr. Monster.
You saved me.
It's okay.
Don't get lost anymore.
Oh, no.
I was swallowed by the old woman's waves.
The old woman's power is tremendous.
I'm going to live a long life.
Excuse me.
Oh.
What?
I got the old woman.
This time she's a foreigner.
Would you tell me where the department store is?
No way.
You don't understand English at all.
If you come to Japan, you'll be able to speak Japanese.
What's wrong?
I'm sick of it.
I'm getting sick of it.
You're just talking about things you don't understand.
May I help you?
I want to go to the department store.
Yes.
Keep going straight.
You can find the right side.
Thank you.
Yamashita, you're so good at English.
I'm learning it after work every day.
This is the plan of the class president.
What?
You're here at an unexpected place.
Ryotsu!
Yes, class president!
The Showa Street traffic light in the 7th street of Ginza has broken.
Please go and organize the traffic immediately.
Yes, sir.
I've never done this before.
Well, this is how...
This is how it was.
No, no, no.
Well, this is how...
Idiot! What are you doing?
What?
You're the one who did it.
Then my life is in danger.
Wait a minute.
I'll call for backup.
It's finally noon.
I feel three times longer than usual.
I'm hungry.
Welcome.
Ten-don.
Yes, sir.
Ten-don!
I can eat whenever I want.
I'll call for backup.
Yes, I will.
I'll start the meeting.
Please come back to the exit immediately.
But I can't finish it yet.
I don't have time.
Come here!
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
I was right.
Benz and six-point didn't get off board.
I can't get off the bus with a car.
Oh, yeah, anyway, we're in the same boat.
I'll start after work.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
I was asked the way by a lot of people on the way.
You must have lost your way.
I just asked if you were really my officer.
Oh, I didn't know.
In other words, this hub is a past-competition type.
No matter how much you say it,
Chief Ohara is still better.
It seems that Ryotsu hasn't caused any problems since then.
Even if he is a Ryō,
it hasn't been a week since he was transferred.
I don't know. It's about him.
Every morning, every time I read the newspaper,
I'm worried that he might be causing some problems.
What? Is there no Ryō-san?
It's no good without Ryō-san.
But Senpai is...
What?
Even if it's not Ryōtsu, you can talk to us about anything.
That's why it's no good without Ryō-san.
This...
I have to move.
I thought you would fix it.
A radio controller?
Hmm...
We can't get this.
Is there any Ryō-san?
Oh, there's no Ryōtsu.
But please tell us anything that can be of help.
It's no good without Ryō-san.
Can you fix a pot with a hole?
Oh, that's a little...
Without Ryō-chan, this is a disaster.
Oh...
Thank you very much.
I see, the escape port to Kabukizama.
That's why there are so many people.
Is he able to go to work with us from here?
I see.
That's the escape port.
All right.
Um...
This is the first street.
The road doesn't have any...
Oh, I'm tired.
You still can't remember the map?
Idiot!
I'm good at memorizing, but I'm not good at studying after school.
I'm not good at memorizing, but I'm not good at studying after school.
You're not good at it, but you'll get it in your head.
You're calling me an idiot!
No, I'm not!
Wait!
I'm not!
But you used to guide the way to the station where you lived before, right?
I used to live in the city of Shita.
I was born in Shita, so I could remember the map right away.
I've only been to Ginza about three times since I was born.
You're extreme.
Why did you quit the station where you lived before?
If I were to tell you, it's because I don't have the same personality as the chief.
You don't have the same personality.
I'd like to ask you about the way.
What?
Where is the Enbu Shrine in Shinbashi?
The Enbu Shrine in Shinbashi...
Hey, Yamashita! Where is it?
It's a good opportunity. Let's look it up ourselves.
Damn it. You're talking like a teacher at school.
Please wait a moment.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
I remember!
I think I broke it.
It was a long time ago with the Japanese Army.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, old man.
Ryozu, stop it.
It must be there.
I got it.
Here you go.
Thank you.
He's a thoughtful clerk.
But Ryozu...
What's wrong with your personality?
Oh, that's it.
The chief is called Ohara.
He's a stubborn, stubborn, and stubborn guy.
He's always angry all year round.
But he's a bad guy.
You know what he's like?
Hey, Ryozu.
You're a fool.
He's like an idiot.
Every day, every day.
He's really annoying.
He's like a fool.
Isn't that why you're angry?
What?
Why is the old man angry?
No, it's just...
My opinion as a third party.
Your opinion as a third party.
I'm sure your boss has a bad subordinate.
It's not a joke.
I'm a serious guy.
I'm not serious.
The boss is hysterical.
nitpicking
That's why I only look forward to scolding the subordinate.
These guys are so little.
It's me.
It's not.
I'm not a letter writer.
It's someone else.
I told you I'm not your boss
or your subordinate.
I'm not crying!
You're not!
I'm going to add to your life as a human being!
That's cheating!
Shut up, Ryozu!
Wait!
Hey, don't cry!
No, you were crying from the beginning.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Kago-san.
I can't do this anymore.
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
Anyway, let's take her to the emergency room.
Where do you come from?
I'm having a bad sleep right now.
No, you can't.
You can't speak English, Chinese, or Mongolian.
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
Don't cry!
Ryozu, do something!
You're good at fighting children.
Yes, I know.
Hey!
It's Godzilla!
A Japanese famous monster!
What? You don't know?
Then what is it?
It's Gamera!
A Mothra's larva.
I don't know Girala, but it's a small town.
Hey, Ryozu, get away from the monster!
Kids like monsters.
I'll make something foreign children can understand.
What about this?
It's a horse!
Wow!
You finally understand.
Suho! Suho!
What? A horse is called Suho?
Suho!
No way! No way!
What?
Suho!
Yes, I'm Ryozu.
Ryo-tsu.
That's right, Ryo-tsu.
What about you?
Pao!
Ryo-tsu.
Pao.
Apparently, it's called Pao.
Pao?
Ryo-tsu, try to guess where it came from.
Wait a minute.
Ryo-tsu. Japan.
Japanese.
What about Pao?
Pao came to Japan by plane, didn't he?
Yes, he did!
Where did he come from?
Pao!
U-ke!
Ryo-tsu!
U-ja-ra-ge?
U-ja-ra-ge!
M-e-a-s-ri-n-p-u-a-u-n-ja-ra-ge!
What?
Gra-fu-bu-a-u-n-ja-ra-ge!
I got it.
He came from a country called U-n-ja-ra-ge.
Chief, I understand.
You're a big boy, Ryo-tsu.
I've never heard of a country called U-n-ja-ra-ge, but...
The world is bigger than you think.
So you came to see Kabuki and got separated from your parents.
Kabuki is boring for kids.
An accident?
What's this?
It's a horse!
I'll handle the accident!
Ryo-tsu will take care of the traffic!
Okay!
Hey, watch out!
Hey!
Ryo-tsu!
Catch him!
I know!
Don't!
Don't come any closer!
This is terrible.
The call!
Hey, wait!
Are you crazy?
Suho! Suho! I've noticed you, Suho!
Why'd you come all the way to Gintagundari and have to get on a horse?!
Hey, calm down, you!
Stop!
Ryotsu!
What was that?!
Pao?!
Ryotsu, stop!
I don't need to hear it!
Pao, watch out!
This isn't just about you and me!
Pao!
Raaaah!
De puh recid?
Vuohh!
Whoa!
Roar!
It hurt me!
A horse is rampaging near Ginza's 4th:"chomeする"
Please give me support!
Uwaaah!
Aaaahhh!
Raah!
Gyaahhh, he came flying!
Ryo-tsu!
Where is Ryo-tsu?
Over there!
Ryo-tsu?
Ryo-tsu!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
Even if you say I'm responsible, I'm...
An excuse is an excuse!
You're putting mud on my face!
I'll ask the president to kill you!
Wait a minute.
Ryo-tsu is here to help this kid.
You are?
Ryo-tsu's former boss, Ohara.
Chief!
Ohara!
You're the former boss?
So it's your responsibility that this kid isn't educated.
It's your responsibility that this kid isn't educated.
He's a fool who can't do anything.
He can't speak foreign languages like you.
But this kid and I understand each other.
I think it's more useful than just a tip of the tongue.
Pao!
Maro!
Good, good.
Chief!
This is Prince Pao of the Unjara Kingdom.
Prince Pao?
He came to Kabuki Kenbutsu with Kokou-gu with the Shinobi.
If anything happened to the prince, there would be a big trouble.
Is that so?
So you're saying that's good.
Well, yeah.
Ryo-tsu!
Yes?
Yes.
After hearing about Prince Pao,
you're a wonderful police officer.
I hope you come to my country.
What?
Could that be...
I'm going! I'm going!
Ryo-tsu! You!
Well then, Chief!
Everyone, I'm going to the Unjara Kingdom,
not the Ha-nem-ae, but the Unjara Kingdom.
In case there's something wrong,
I'm just going to say,
"Ah, that's the Unjara Kingdom."
"Come on, everyone, come to our land."
Hey, hey! Did you call me a policeman?!
Our story is different!
♪ Unjara Kingdom ♪
誰かが呼んでるような 雨上がりのとこ 振り返りながら歩いた ガージャに手を引かれ
あの時感じた 不思議な気持ち だから あけどがりのタイルを 黒いとこだけ歩いてみたよ
誰でも一度は子供だったけど みんな忘れてる
偉そうな顔したセリフ
何時かや 目の上ブルーなおばさんを 曲がってごらんよ あの角を みんなにみんなに会えるよ
あそこはカメアリー あーきっとカメアリー みんなおいでよ俺たちの街へ
ありがとう!
あーきっとカメアリー あーきっとカメアリー みんなおいでよ俺たちの街へ
また出やがったな とんでも教授
なんだと わしの頭の中の 左脳が眠ってる?
それを働かせれば わしは秀才になれるってのか?
そうかそうか わしには秘められた力があったってことだな
次回 目覚めよ まじめ人間 リョウツ
よろしくな
あそこはカメアリー あーきっとカメアリー みんなおいでよ俺たちの街へ
Let's go to our town!
Thank you!