"The
"When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away!"
"Come to me, you poor people!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried."
"Look at the blue sky!"
"White clouds!"
"I'm sure it'll be all right!"
"You know that, right?"
"If you know that, then shut up and follow me!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried."
"Geez, this summer was so strange..."
"Aah, it's all..."
"Aah, it's all..." "Aah, it's all..."
"Aah, it's all..." "You're so bad, Big Brother!"
"Here, take this off! Here, take this off!"
"Sorry, please take off this!"
"Aah!"
"Alright, so you're up,"
"but I can't get off anymore, right?"
"Not going to be helped. I'm gonna go."
"Are you all right, little one?"
Huh?
You know what? I'll get off slowly one step at a time.
Ryosuke!
Get him!
Don't let him go!
What?
No!
I thought I was going to die.
That's my line!
It seems you climbed the roof of Kannon-do and Goju-no-to in Asakusa.
It seems so.
There are 14 in Taito-ku, Sumida-ku, and Katsushika-ku.
Plus the chimney of this Kame-no-yu.
And the Jyoshu-han.
Here you are.
Thank you.
If you like high places, there are many places where you can climb more safely and comfortably.
Safety?
There are many high-rise buildings all over Tokyo, including the tower and the department store.
I've never climbed the chimney of a bathhouse at that age.
What about the new place?
It doesn't matter whether it's new or old.
I'm telling you not to bother others.
Did you bother me?
I did.
I did it to the bathhouse, me, and the neighbors.
I see.
You did a bad thing.
That's all?
That's all.
I'll forgive you for today, Ryo-chan.
Listen, don't ever climb again.
I'll help you next time.
Thank you for everything.
That old man doesn't have a family or a family.
At that time, a warm wind blew.
I'm happy.
олж
Stop, Ryo-san.
What?
Mr.miş
Why are you being so angry?
I'm in trouble.
I'm afraid of ghosts.
I wasn't worried about you.
así
I'm an old man, isn't yourת
I'm an old man, isn't your 분
"Nyaaah!"
The police have finally arrived.
If only I could spread the rumor of the ghosts to the temple,
I thought it would be safe to stay away from people.
What are you doing there?!
Stop!
"Nyaaah!"
Be quiet!
Ryo-san!
Hm?
Terai!
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
Terai, please take care of this guy.
I'm sure there are some of his items in the temple.
There are still some in the temple.
I understand.
So, where's Ryo-san?
I'm going to clean up after him.
"Nyaaah!"
Is that all?
It's a bad omen.
Don't take it the wrong way.
How many are there?
Okay.
Here's the address.
Please take a seat.
Ryo-san.
Do you want to listen to anything more?
What?
I want to talk to you.
Ryo-san.
Ryo-san!
I'm so surprised!
Nothing's changed.
Well, first, if you turn left along the shopping street, there's Kameari Station.
From there, go to Kitasenju on the upper line and then switch to Tobu-Isezaki Line, and then the end point is Asakusa.
Understood?
From Kameari Station to the upper line in Kitasenju...
From there, to the end point of Tobu-Isezaki Line...
Yes! Thank you very much!
Thank you.
What's that?
Mr. Shoukichi, it's dangerous to climb up there again!
Come down quickly!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
You can't! If you don't come down, we'll go this way!
What's wrong?
I don't know where the station is.
It'll take an hour from there. It's not a path you'll get lost on.
I understand. I understand. I'll send you to the station after you finish eating, so wait a bit.
Yes! I'll be waiting!
It's hard to eat when you look at me like that. Are you hungry?
What's your name?
Hanayo.
Hanayo, huh? How old are you?
17 years old.
Where did you come from?
Umm...
Over there.
Over there?
Don't tease the police!
Good morning, Ryo.
Ah, Reiko. I'm glad you're here.
I'll send this girl to the station, so please take care of her.
Huh? This girl?
I'll be right back. Let's go.
Okay.
It's been a while, Asakusa.
It's rare to see a young girl like you in Asakusa.
I'm not alone. I'm meeting a friend.
What? Then why don't you ask your friend to pick you up?
Does your friend have a cell phone?
Cell phone? I don't think so.
That's rare.
Well, I don't think all the students have one.
I think you're right.
Huh?
You're not a housewife, are you?
No, I'm not.
Really? Then where's your house?
You can't go over there or over here.
You need to go to your address.
Your address.
Huh? Here?
That means you're not a temple girl.
There's no temple headman here.
That means you're lying.
What?
There's no temple headman.
Temple headman! I'll go home if you're joking!
Okay?
Ryo.
Yeah! When did you come?
Ryo, will you take me to Asakusa?
No, I can't help you lie.
Huh?
Huh? I thought I returned everything yesterday.
Ryo, you left one thing behind.
Huh? Why?
If you tell me the truth, will you take me to Asakusa?
Susamu! Tell me the truth!
Where did I come from?
Huh? Huh?
What the hell are you talking about?
Huh?
What is that?
It's like you appeared from under the grave I killed?
That look is too much to be realistic.
Huh?
Oh, you're right.
I have one, two, three, four, five of those.
Ah, ugh!
Don't run away, Ryo.
Roger.
I'll wake him up right away.
Okay.
I woke him up.
Why won't it disappear?
I'm sorry for killing the grave. Please go back and rest in peace.
What are you going to do to me anymore?
I really want to go to Asakusa. Ryo-san, please take me there.
I want to go to Asakusa.
I can see the bear below my eyes.
I can see it.
I can not see it.
In other words, all I can see is you.
Ryo-san!
She seems to be in a bad mood, so I want to follow her.
We're here, Hana. This is Asakusa.
This is... Asakusa?
And this is the Asakusa Rock.
There's a lot of cinemas and theater here, so it used to be a bit more lively.
This is...?
I have a place I want to go, too.
Give me your amulets and your cards.
I have a lot of things, but...
I'll give you all of them!
No good?
Thanks to you, I'm so cool and I'm saved.
Oh, by the way, you said you were meeting someone earlier.
I promised to climb to the 12th floor with you.
12th floor? Which building is the 12th floor?
Asakusa's...
Even if you just look at it, there are more than 50,000 buildings in the 12th floor.
Are you going to make me climb from the edge?
Hmm...
Seriously?
I'm home!
Ryo!
What's wrong with your face?
What a mean face.
What happened?
Ryo said he was feeling strange.
Reiko was very worried about him.
Oh, I see.
I see, so let me rest a little.
I'm tired, too.
Ryo!
Who are you talking to, Ryo?
Can you see something?
Huh?
Oh, it's the night of the flowers.
Night of the flowers?
When I caught Akisu last night, I defeated the destruction stone of the temple.
It seems that it followed me at that time.
What?
You're joking, right?
That's a ghost?
Now, in front of you guys...
What?
Is it terrible to avoid it?
It can't be helped.
I can only see the flowers.
If you say you have something you can't see, everyone will be scared.
It seems that the girl's heart is hurt.
Is Hanayo a maiden?
She is 17 years old.
I see.
Oh, I'm sorry to run away.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Just...
I'm not used to such a guest.
Hm?
Well, I understand.
Haa...
Ryo, are you okay?
Your face is pale.
Yeah.
As long as you don't let Hanayo's heart be hurt,
please stay away from me.
I see.
When I couldn't, Ryo was my soul mate.
I can't believe you feel the same.
Senpai, what was Hanayo's camellia?
When I realized you really want to climb to floor 12 at the ASAKUSA building,
I climbed to floor 12 as far as I could,
but it was the different fill...
Floor 12...
I promised to my boyfriend and his best friend,
and he was unable to do it.
That's the only thing that remains in his mind.
Hm?
Shoukichi?
Ryo-san, that old man who likes high places is also Shoukichi-san.
That Shoukichi-san also wants to climb to a high place like Hanayo-chan.
Oi oi, he's Hanayo's boyfriend.
There's probably too much age gap.
But he's too good for a coincidence.
Yes.
Hanayo, how old is Shoukichi?
Shoukichi's age is...
...two years older?
That means he's at least 19 or 20 years old.
Unfortunately, no matter how you think about it, it's not...
This is it!
Hm?
The 12th floor that Hanayo-san was talking about must be this!
Ryo-unkaku?
It's commonly known as Asakusa 12th floor.
At the beginning of the 23rd year, Ryo-unkaku, a brick-making tower 12th floor in Asakusa, opened.
The view from the observatory was amazing.
It's special and it's a place where you can see Fuji and Tsukuba in the clouds.
On sunny days, you can even see Hakone and Nikko on a telescope.
It's said that when it opened, the visitors who paid entrance fees and tried to climb there were very excited.
The Great Kanto Earthquake of September 1st, 12th year of Taisho, collapsed from the 8th floor.
It was destroyed on the same month, and the 12th floor disappeared from Asakusa.
That's right.
When I was born, there was no shadow or shape.
If we go back to Hanayo-san's age, it's around the time of Taisho's death.
Maybe Hanayo-san died during the earthquake.
Hanayo, give up on the 12th floor.
You can't climb on something that doesn't exist.
What is it? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Head.
What are you doing, Hanayo?
Do you want to kill me?
I understand.
Genki, where is Shokichi-san?
That's right.
Shokichi-san is nowhere to be found.
What?
Please look for Shokichi-jisan.
Understood.
I'll ask Mr. Honda for help.
I'm going to look for a place that's high.
I've been careful this morning, so I don't think I can climb to a high place for a while.
Why is that?
I'm always the one who is kind to the elderly.
Because Ryo-san is going out.
Don't be so arrogant, Terai.
If you don't say it, that old man will repeat it over and over again.
I'm sorry.
I don't have the time.
If it's difficult to look for him, I have no choice but to lure him out.
What do you mean by lure him out?
Nagagawa.
Yes.
Use your power to build another Ryoukaku in Asakusa.
What?
What's going on?
It's no good. I can't find him anywhere.
I can't either.
But what does it mean that if you don't find Grandpa, Ryo-tsu's life will be in danger?
I don't know.
We're here, Ryo-san.
Yeah.
Boss!
What did you say?
Are you really Ryo-tsu?
We're now at Azumabachi Sanchomeijoku.
We're about to cross the Sumida River.
What is that?
Amazing! It's just like the real thing.
It's a model of a real object that was made by the Nakagawa Group's movie set company.
From now on, we're not going anywhere.
We're counting on your help!
Don't be ridiculous, you bastard!
If you don't want to be crushed, you should just wait.
What?
We have to block the road for 20 minutes.
20 minutes?
20 minutes, 20 minutes?
This is what you wanted to see, showing from the 12th floor.
The scene must be very different now that it's been 80 years, but I can do this!
Where are you, Grandpa?
I'll be waiting for you, Hanayo.
Huh?
This is nostalgic!
Grandpa!
Huh? Who are you?
Don't worry about me. You know Hanayo, right?
Yeah, I think I know her.
Hanayo is here. Can't you see her?
What? Hanayo?
She's the Shokichi you wanted to see, Hanayo!
Why didn't you show yourself to me?
You don't know what it's like to be an old man, do you?
Mr. Shokichi.
Hanayo, where have you been all this time?
I'm glad you found me, Mr. Shokichi.
I've been waiting for you, Hanayo, since you left me.
I thought about what you did when you left me and died 12 times.
What did you do?
The 50 towers of Kannon-do were burned to ashes.
I thought maybe if I climbed them, I'd see you, Hanayo.
You climbed them?
Yeah. The shrine's torii, the cedar tree, the bathhouse chimney...
I climbed a lot of things.
I was waiting for you down there.
I was waiting for you down there, Mr. Shokichi.
I'm sorry, Hanayo.
No, it's fine.
We were able to go up to the 12th floor together, so there's nothing left for me to think about.
I'm going with you.
Huh?
I'll be waiting for you.
What?
Oh, my.
I wonder what happened after all those people gathered here...
The spirits have been restored.
*Coffee*
Good.
Where did you meet Hanayo?
Hanayo was a assistant of Rock's Cafe.
It's rare for him to have never climbed the 12th floor of Asakusa.
Good. I'll take you there next time.
Hmph.
Hanayo was the cutest in Rock.
He was so cute.
Nanpaka, you're good, old man.
It took me a year to get rid of Hanayo.
Hmph.
I've kept you waiting for a long time for your first love.
Yono, Yono.
Yona, Yono, Yono.
Yono, Yono, Yono.
I will never forget.
I will always remain with you.
Please come back, Hanayo.
Thank you very much, Hanayo.
Well, time to go home, everyone.
Yono, Yono, Yono, Yono.
Have a good night.
I walked only the black part
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and see that corner
I can see everyone
Let's go!
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Come to our town
Thank you!
Huge! Too big!
The huge athletic competition with a prize of one hundred million yen
It's huge!
It was an athletic competition in the world
But to pay back the money
I will win no matter what
Next time, a huge athletic competition with a prize of one hundred million yen
Thank you!
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Come to our town
Thank you!