When you watch TV, lit up your room and try to get away from them.
When I don't have any money, come to my place.
I don't have any, but I worry
I'm worried about you
Look at the blue sky
And the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be fine
Come to me if you don't have a job
I don't have one either but don't worry
Look, it's burning
The red cloud
I'm sure it'll be fine
I know, I know, I know
If you do, just shut up and follow me
I'll teach you the ninja's way
This show has been popular lately
What they do is like ninja training
Then if you get the real one, you win
What's wrong, senpai?
I heard it's the real ninja
So I remembered someone
If it's a ninja, it's here
The dog spoke
Do you understand human language?
It's me, it's me
Even if it's me
It's the old man of Bulbo
Oh, Bulbo's old man is the real ninja
He's using ninja skills
Teenagerplank
This is ninja's way of speaking
He's hiding somewhere and talking
Where is he?
Huh?!
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't believe I'm ruined
I'm afraid I'll make them destroy me
What are you saying?
So, why did you come out of Kyushu?
Actually, I wanted to open a ninja school in Tokyo.
You said that before.
You didn't want to open it in Kyushu?
Because it seems like it would be more profitable in Tokyo.
That's a pretty easy to understand idea.
Do you know about it, Borubo-san?
I was on my way to his house and got lost on the way.
I came here to follow the map.
When did you find the map?
I think it's from the annual...
That's Borubo's room.
He's staying at home today.
Let's contact him.
No, that's not possible.
But...
It's dangerous to enter Borubo's house without permission.
The gang of thugs who tried to get into Borubo's room the other day...
They got caught in Borubo's trap.
They got caught in the trap that they set up.
I can see that they're not good.
So, I'll show you how to do it.
Hey, hey!
First, the smoke bomb!
He's in a panic state.
That's enough.
Isn't that too much?
That's fine.
I'm in a panic.
These guys are even worse at the game than I thought!
Let's start with the fire can.
I need a good strategy.
The old man from Kyushu is...
No!
The Volvo is completely in combat mode!
Can't we stop him somehow?
I don't know.
It's my turn!
Hey, what the hell did you do?
It's a Nude Trump's Nympho.
What's a Nympho?
What?
Are you opening a ninja school in Tokyo?
Yeah.
I was thinking of renting your room.
What's with this mess?
I might as well clean it up.
Grandpa did it earlier.
But it's impossible to open a ninja school in this room.
It can't be helped.
I'll buy land and build a classroom.
Do that from the beginning!
How much is your budget?
Don't get me wrong.
What?
It's 3 million yen.
You're so surprised.
Nakagawa, tell me the truth.
No matter how much the land price has dropped...
What?
I can't believe the land price is so high.
Grandpa, don't be discouraged.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't be careless.
Yes, sir.
But...
I can't believe the land price is so high.
I'm in trouble.
I'm so depressed.
Why don't you comfort me a little?
I'll throw you a shuriken or something.
I'll look for a classroom.
Really?
It might be a bed.
I may have to prepare myself.
Thank you very much!
It was good, grandpa.
Huh.
How could youλλ
Where?
I bought a building before it was demolished at a low price.
You're good at training Ninjya.
He..
I have something to tell you.
What?
What was that?
So there was a trap after all.
You're a pretty ugly old man!
Grandpa! I've brought Reiko and the others!
What?!
Thank you for coming!
Congratulations on your opening!
Thank you! Thank you!
You're as lively as a cockroach.
Stop that!
Let's take a look inside.
This is the Ninja Museum.
It's a store, isn't it?
It's the same as the Kyushu house we visited before.
They sell books, too.
It's not exactly the same.
This time, they're selling new shurikens.
What new shuriken is this?
It's an ordinary shuriken.
It's painted with fluorescent paint.
It shines at night and you can tell when it's the right time.
It's like a light-bulb.
You don't have to worry about fighting in the night.
You can see the enemy, though.
This is the latest in self-defense.
First, you cut it with a knife.
You can also use a pencil.
You can also use a saw.
And a hammer.
A saw.
If you combine two pieces, you can use scissors.
And a round-shaped magnet.
How is it?
It's good, right?
A ten-point knife is still better.
I'm sorry.
I slipped.
You did it on purpose.
How about some herbal tea?
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
This pattern.
No way.
It contains only one herb that can remove poison.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
It's a training to distinguish poison.
It's like a Russian roulette.
Then I'll...
Wait, wait.
I'll choose first.
If I get in the last one, I'll be in trouble.
Okay, this one.
It's good.
Grandpa, that's it, right?
Yeah.
A big hit.
What are you going to do?
I drank it all.
Don't worry.
I have a medicine to stop the kick.
It's a holy water from the sword.
It's perfect for you.
It's 1,500 yen.
It's too expensive.
Then I'll enjoy the low price.
I understand.
I'll buy it.
Grandpa, isn't this a poisonous bird's head?
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
Don't be surprised.
No, it might be garlic.
Actually, I don't know either.
I don't know.
Don't make me drink herbal tea.
Let's check it out.
It's poison after all.
If you look closely, the first one I put in wasn't a poisonous bird's head.
Look it up.
I'm not thirsty right now.
I'll hold it back, too.
That means you've been poisoned at an early age.
I'm in a bad mood.
I've been okay until now.
It's okay.
What?
What? You're still not a student?
Yeah, sometimes when the students come, they stop without even spending an hour.
Of course.
But it's a bit sad.
They came all the way to Tokyo.
I want to help them somehow.
That's right.
Actually, there's not a single student left.
Please, be the first student!
Why me?
If there's no student, we won't be able to go to school.
Please! Please! Please!
Stop it! Don't get close to Gao!
I'm sorry, Ryo-chan.
You're so pitiful.
I'll pay for the transfer.
You don't have to say that.
Let's do a 10% transfer fee for the students who are going to school.
Really?
Okay, I got it.
I'll go in.
See? This is the technique of convincing a student.
Okay.
Please, you two.
Please go to school.
Th-that's...
No, wait!
Let's get all the staff to go to school.
What?
Is that possible?
I see.
I'll have you apply it as a formal martial art technique like kendo or judo.
Yeah.
I see.
So that's the plan.
This guy might be able to make a lot of money.
Hmm...
Yes, I think it'd be interesting for police officers to learn the formal martial arts.
I think it'd be useful depending on how you use it.
What about you, Ryo-chan?
You wouldn't go out in front of the school, would you?
But...
What?
Ah...
*evil laugh*
Ryotsu, where are you?
I am here.
This is the Mokuton Jutsu.
It can be used when you are in a beautiful state or when you are in a tough situation.
Oh.
I am not sure if it can really be used.
Well, we will see the secret of the combat style ninjutsu from now on.
Hmm.
By the way, which is that Kogaremaru-san?
Ah...
Hahahaha!
I am here!
Where?
Where are you looking? Up there!
Huh? Up there?
Hahahaha!
I am the chief of the combat style ninjutsu school, Saigo Kogaremaru!
Ah! That's dangerous!
It's okay. I was riding it every day in Kyushu.
We are going there now.
Go!
Oh!
The secret of the Mokuton Jutsu!
Ah! That's dangerous!
Hahaha! Don't worry!
Gyaaah!
Ah! Ouch!
Are you okay? Hurry up and get an ambulance!
Ah, don't worry. It's just a scratch.
Then, I will give you an ambulance box.
I don't need that.
The ninja is walking with the medicine on him.
Hey!
It says it's a drug for constipation.
Ah!
Then, this one?
Or, maybe this one?
Hmm... Is it this one?
It's like a drug store in Toyama.
But, the essential medicine is not coming out.
Hey! It's troublesome!
If you eat spinach, you will be healthy.
Gyaaah!
Hmm?
It's like a Popeye.
What kind of person is he?
Why is he carrying the medicine?
Hmm...
Then, please enter the dojo.
Then, I will show you the ninja's technique.
Reiko is not here yet.
He might be in a hurry to change.
No, no.
I can't believe it.
Ah, I'm glad.
You are done changing, Reiko-san.
Ah!
Barbar!
Re-Reiko-san, what's the matter with your outfit?
Is this the family of the Kunoichi?
Yeah.
It's a great Kunoichi.
What is this Kunoichi?
It's a huge ear to search for enemies.
It's a smelly ear to protect himself.
Gyaaah!
And the enemy is Kunoichi.
I see.
Oh, my.
Ahem.
It's true that it's a charming family.
But some of the female members are not at all happy about it.
I see.
It's a shame.
Hmm?
No.
Ah...
The next day.
That is, where the popular place is, the weapon of the parasol.
Hmm.
We must hide under the ground and search for enemies.
For intrusion operations it is very convenient, isn't it?
It's said to be "under the ground",
but there are almost no ground in Tokyo.
Hmm.
Let's see how to use the rain clouds.
They cross the river without wetting the clothes.
Isn't the conversation fast?
It's faster, isn't it?
If the waves stand a little, it will turn around.
If you say so, I'll show you a special ninja technique.
Are you doing that?
Yeah. Ninja technique, Katon no Jutsu.
It's a technique that blows fire from the mouth and makes the opponent sway.
It should be applied to arresting criminals.
Oh, I can expect a little.
Let's go. First, put a special liquid in your mouth.
It's like a human pump.
I can't rely on you, ninja.
rows
this story
Let's let it go.
Ryotsu, you're not just playing.
I'm doing my job seriously.
What are you doing?
It's a great deal to make it ' Ingredients.
Because . . .
Sometimes I fail.
if this
But this is the least we can expect from the police.
We could just show them what a ninja can do to help the police.
Yeah!
Then we can arrest the criminal with our ninja skills!
Oh, that's a good idea!
Let's do it!
Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready anytime!
Start!
Oh! This is a good view!
Hello?
I'm Manegaru.
Be sure to keep an eye on the suspicious people.
I know!
You should take a little more action.
Hey, isn't that a little too much?
Tokyo has a lot of tall views.
It's not over yet.
Huh?
Grandpa!
Hey, do something!
Don't worry.
I'll do something about it.
Minpo!
Come back my taco-kun!
Daaah!
Let's chase them!
Now, how far are you going to be carried?
Huh?
What's going on?
It's me!
Senpai, this is terrible!
Huh?
We have caught a drug dealer at the main court...
The culprit ran away in the car! He ran into our ship! Please return immediately!
But even if you tell me to return immediately...
Huh? Wait a minute! This is a great machine that will show our power!
Nakagawa! What is the characteristic of the culprit's car?
Black sedan! It looks like a foreigner!
What is that?
What did you say?
They are trying to escape by helicopter!
They will be caught by us no matter what!
Oh!
Damn it! I can't make it in time!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
I can't help you at all!
I did it! This is the wind of God!
I won't let you get away!
Take this!
Oh! Japanese Ninja!
No! It's not working at all!
Aaaaaaah!
Ninja!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Hey, old man.
Ninnins won't be working in this era after all!
What? Not yet?
I never expected that there were still ninjas in Japan.
But they weren't our enemy.
I didn't mean to!
What's that sound?
I didn't know you had something like this!
This is the giant shuriken magic!
Finish him!
To drop a helicopter with a shuriken...
What a terrifying magic!
Hey, hey! That cannon...
Maybe it's a bad omen!
Ta-da!
My school!
Again?
I was so lucky to get a chance to make money!
Isn't something clicking?
Come to think of it...
Ah! No!
The self-destruct device switched on in that shock!
Why did you put that on?
It's the ninja's basic!
Get rid of it right away!
It's too late!
It'll explode in 5 seconds!
I do appreciate the fact that you arrested the culprit.
But...
There's a lot of protest from the people around here!
I know!
That's why I'm writing this paper!
Where did your grandpa go?
He just went back to Kyushu.
As expected of a ninja.
He's fast at running away.
Farewell!
See you again!
You're going with Mom!
Awright!
We just got back from Kyushu.
I'm on my way to Kyushu!
You're coming with me, too!
Okay!
I'm going with you!
I walked through the dark side of the arcade
Everyone was a kid once, but they all forgot
A politician with a big face and a blue aunt on top of his eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll meet everyone
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
What? You bought a cruiser?
Yes, I wanted to take the time to naturally interact with the children
So you suddenly bought a cruiser
You're a life-saving band, but you're a home steal from Manrei
Next time on Papa is a Young Master
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!