The Day of the Sandwich
Ryo-san, I think we'll be...
What? You're going to say "White Day" again on March 14th, right?
That's not what we're talking about!
No, it's not like that.
March 13th is the day of the sandwich.
The day of the sandwich?
You see, the letter "1" is sandwiched between the letters "3", right?
And then there's "3" and "1", "3" and "1", "3" and "1", and so on.
How stupid! Stop saying "What day is it today?"
When you're watching TV, make the room bright and look away!
If you're broke, come to my place!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
You'll be fine eventually.
If you don't have a job, come with me.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look, even the red clouds are burning.
You'll be fine eventually.
You got it, huh?
You got it, you got it!
If you know, you're quiet!
You're full of thought.
Come with me!
To my beloved big brother!
Ryo-san!
Oh, Fujita-san!
Hello.
Ryo-san, are you there?
I'm eating in the back.
Good.
It's getting warmer.
Ryo-san, open it for me.
What?
What do you mean, "people are eating"?
You're such a noisy guy.
Ryo-san, it's not the time to eat ramen.
I finally got it from America.
The picture of that beautiful woman with a gold medal.
Is that true?
It's true.
And it's a real one.
Shut up!
It's huge.
I'm sorry.
All right. Show it to me.
What's this?
It's a jigsaw puzzle.
And it's 2000 pieces.
If you import it properly, it will be stopped by tax.
It's a jigsaw puzzle to break the law.
Anyway, let's assemble it quickly.
I bought a panel.
You bought a table, didn't you?
I bought a table.
And a sitting desk.
Really?
Don't go there.
We don't want to be damaged when we're typing.
Hey, Ryo-san!
What are you doing?
Stop it.
We are busy, isn't it?
We are discussing the problem of the United States.
What are you talking about?
I need to make a phone call from my brother.
Your brother?
Yes.
Older brother.
Dad, Keiko's labor pain has started.
I'm trying to get her to come to the hospital, but she's not coming.
What is she doing at such an important time?
All right. I'll take her to the hospital. Don't worry.
See you.
What's wrong?
A baby is about to be born at Kinjirou's place.
Oh, is that so?
Then Ryo-chan will be an old man.
Well, I can finally have a baby or a baby.
My relatives were all old men and women.
It's good to be fresh.
A new life has been born.
Ryo-san, Ryo-san, hurry up.
What's wrong?
People are so impressed.
Hurry up.
Look, Ryo-san.
The rest is almost done.
It's amazing, isn't it?
That's right.
It's empty to see this kind of figure objectively.
I feel like a human being.
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
No, no. I'll do it by myself.
As an old man, I don't want to show this kind of figure.
Oops. That's not the time to say that.
Loose?
But I can do the first edition.
What's that stupid woman doing?
Hey, I'm going to my parents' house.
I'll be back soon.
Wow, amazing.
It's done in one step.
What?
Which one?
This is...
Bang, bang, bang.
I'll help you.
I feel like I'm used to it.
What are you talking about?
Hurry up.
I see.
Then, the last two pieces.
It's done.
What?
Hey, you.
I knew it.
It's New Hampshire.
We're going to bring something special on this holy day.
It's like Loose.
Who's following him?
What are you doing, Kankichi?
What?
I came here to steal money.
Don't be stupid.
Where were you?
I was in the city.
You are a good husband.
What?
Why are you here?
I was wondering.
I heard that
a baby is about to be born in Kinjiro.
I want you to come.
What?
It's hard.
I asked for your luggage.
Are you going to the hospital?
I will send you to the hospital by car.
Oh!
You're so mean.
I'm not.
I'll be an old lady soon.
You don't want to be told, do you?
What?
I just said the truth.
Well, let's go.
Please get on the car.
I'll take you with me.
Do you have a labor pain already?
Yes.
You'll have labor pains a few more times.
The time period will be shorter and shorter.
Ah.
If you have labor pain again,
please call me.
Thank you.
Did you get a call from mom?
Yes, my brother called me
and told me she was coming.
That's good.
This.
Huh? An amulet?
It's an amulet that brought me happiness.
If you have it, you'll be able to give birth to a healthy baby.
Hey, what kind of happiness did you bring me?
It'll take you a long time to tell me.
Please, let me hear it.
Yeah, that was when I was in elementary school.
It's a tiger!
Go, go!
Did you get bullied?
Yes...
I'll help you, so stop crying.
You have to be stronger.
I'm weak at fighting, so I can't be bullied.
I can't be bullied.
I want to be stronger, but I'm weak.
You're against violence, aren't you?
Huh? But I'm telling you to be strong now.
Strength isn't just about power. It's about being strong enough to not be discouraged.
Animals win over strong creatures, but humans are different.
Humans can talk to each other, right?
Talking to each other is the most important thing.
What is your brother doing?
He's a lawyer.
A lawyer?
Yeah.
By talking to each other, he can help and protect people.
I see.
The person who appeared in the sunset had a very kind smile.
And that encounter decided my life.
Here it comes!
Take this, you villains!
It's moving!
It's all over me!
I'm going to die!
It's a shootout!
You've turned into a stray dog with your 가장 rich personality!
That's enough!
Mom!
Can you come out and let me play some gunfire?
What?
The drug label has stepped into the enemy's hideout.
So it's an internal fight!
Mom!
Be careful!
Kinjiro hasn't been studying either, so we can't play together.
If you have been studying all this time, you're going to get a little sick.
That's right.
Idiot!
Then I'll go outside.
Hey, wait a minute.
Yes.
Put this orange box on the desk.
I have something to say.
It's a great environment.
I didn't know you were really studying outside.
Let's play together.
Play?
Eh? It's not a baby's thing.
Oh, I got it. I got it.
I'm almost ready to eat.
Daddy, it's time for dinner.
Yes.
I feel a little uncomfortable.
Perfect.
Finally, you're a junior high school student.
You look shy.
You look a little like your brother.
Brother, when you become a junior high school student,
don't bully me anymore.
Of course. I'm already an adult.
That's good.
I'm glad.
I want to be a good brother.
So, your brother entered junior high school,
and what do you think happened to me?
As usual, Brother bullied me.
Ping pong!
What kindness of your brother.
Aah!
Are you sick?
Idiots are not sick.
What?
Not only that,
I wonder if this traffic jam will be solved.
Keiko-san, you must be feeling down.
I have no choice.
Nakagawa, let's do this.
Get in the alley there.
I can't do it in such a narrow place.
Leave it to me.
Senpai, it's dangerous.
Okay, I'll fly.
Senpai, please stop.
It's dangerous.
Nakagawa, let's go back.
What are you doing?
It's a shortcut.
You don't have to be so busy.
Stop it.
Wait.
My daughter is waiting for you.
I'm coming.
They are here.
What?
You want to attend the national junior high school?
I decided to attend the national junior high school.
I have a lot of knowledge about nationality.
I will become a lawyer in the future.
Are you stupid?
What will you do in the future?
You can't play only with the kids.
You can only think about playing.
It's fine. Anyone can work when they grow up.
I feel like you're playing even when you grow up.
What?
I can say that.
Thank you very much!
You're welcome, Kankichi.
But it'll cost transportation in the Bunkyoku area.
I'll be working part-time.
Hey!
Why don't you go to the same junior high school, Kinjirou?
Because...
You'll be in the same school as your brother!
That's the spirit of the brothers!
N-No way!
I can't!
Dad! Mom! Please!
Let me take the exam!
Please!
She's serious.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I think it's hard to get a national license.
But if you just take it...
Yay!
Thank you, Dad! Mom!
Well, compared to the stupid Kankichi,
Kinjirou is 100 times smarter.
Dad!
Try as hard as you can.
Sure!
You're so stubborn, Kinjirou.
I really wanted to be a lawyer.
Hey, do you know the Kappa's Tomin badge?
Yes.
I think if I show it,
on Tomin Day,
the public facilities and buses in Tokyo
will be able to use it for free.
Right.
Here it comes!
Here you go.
The Kappa's badge.
It's free.
I'm sorry, my country.
The Kappa's badge!
It's not fake like last year.
Do you remember?
Oh, no.
He's the same driver as last year.
It's so small in Tokyo.
But this year, it's real.
All right.
The Kappa's badge.
Now, let's get off at the 3rd station of Hongo
and switch to the 16th line.
We can play with this for a day.
The Kappa's badge.
Oh, what is it, Kankichi?
Is that the school of nationality?
Yes, it is.
So what about that?
Kinjiro will take the industrial school.
Oh!
Kinjiro take the school?
That's great!
He's really smart.
He can also do well in school.
But he's only taking the test
from 23 사람들 nicht becast eest Tokyo, right?
He'll fail, no doubt.
It's impossible.
Yeah, I don't think it works.
My brother keeps on getting in the way of my studies.
Finally, the day before the exam...
Kinjiro, are you still awake?
I'm not in a state to sleep.
Stop it. You'll break my body.
Let go of me!
Ouch!
Tonight is the day before the exam!
You're worrying about your health!
Then leave me alone.
I'm in the way of my brother.
I understand.
Do as you please.
Where's my brother?
He went somewhere early in the morning.
He's hardly sleeping. Is he okay?
He's fine.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
You can do it.
Be careful.
Okay.
I've been studying hard, but I don't think I can do it.
You'll get a hangover with this.
Now, I'll sleep a little longer.
I'm nervous now.
An accident in the road.
What?
It won't move.
It's a big deal.
It took a long time to get to the Ushima engine.
I hope I can catch up to the road.
What?
Kinjiro!
Brother!
The road was hit by an accident.
Get on the back!
What?
I don't know the way to school.
Okay, get on it.
Yeah.
I know the road to school.
What?
Why?
Hold on tight.
Go, get in!
What?
All right.
I'll be able to make it in time.
Good.
That's right.
"I have to check the exam report."
Did I get it?
The exam ticket!
Stop it, brother!
What?
The exam ticket flew away!
It's in that place!
I can't take the exam without that.
I guess I have to wait until the end...
Brother!
Wait there, Kinjiro!
He jumped in!
It's so cold, but he's a crazy junior high school student!
Where is he?
He's not here!
Brother...
It's you, Matsu.
Brother!
Brother...
Brother...!
Are you okay?
It was quite a kind of you!
Here, the exam ticket.
Don't lose it this time.
Okay...
Ca-thank you...
Ah...!
Brother!
Um...
Awicoped up the unpleasant plaques of yours?
Get on them now!
Yeah.
Oh, right.
Huh?
You're a little wet, aren't you?
The rites of the passing-method...
Kinjiro, be confident!
Nii-chan...
You'll get it for sure. I believe in you!
Idiot! You'll cry after you pass the test!
Okay!
Now, we're really going to be late. Get on!
Thanks to you, I was able to pass the middle school test.
You're a good brother.
Yeah.
He was my brother who was always fighting, but he was the one who worried about me the most.
If you protect me with such a wonderful charm, I'm sure you'll be able to give birth to a healthy baby.
I'm coming in!
Hey!
Oh, you're still here.
Nii-san.
I was just talking about Nii-san.
You were talking about my bad words again, weren't you?
Keiko-san, are you okay?
I'm sorry to have called you, Mother.
I was going on a trip, so I was late.
Well, I'm fine now that Mother is here.
Father, thank you very much.
Hmm?
What's that? Isn't that a charm for passing the exam?
A charm for passing the exam.
This is it.
Isn't this a charm for passing the exam?
You're like a
I'm fine, brother.
I'm going to give birth with both of them.
Is that so?
Thank you, brother.
I'm sorry.
I think it started again.
Kenjiro!
Yeah.
I'll call the teacher.
Keiko-san.
Be good, okay?
Yes.
Why are you late?
It is because they are lessons.
Mr. Kenjiro!
Oh, dear mother and father.
Sorry to bother you.
Mr. Kenjiro.
Is Keiko?
Yes.
I think it's about to be.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I've beenstocking for you.
I'm here.
Oh, you're born!
I'm finally born.
That's good.
Gangop, are you a boy or a girl?
I'm a girl.
What? A girl?
What's wrong, Dad? You're fine, so it doesn't matter if you're a boy or a girl.
Well, you see, girls are like their fathers.
They're like their fathers.
Like their fathers.
What's wrong, Brother?
You're a cute baby to your mother.
Is that so?
I'm so glad, Kinjiro.
Hooray!
Kinjiro, I'm glad you're growing up well.
Kan-chan!
Hey, everyone in the town hall!
I heard from Gin that you're a girl!
Yeah!
You must be happy, too, right?
I brought you some alcohol, so you should come and celebrate here!
Oh, that's great!
Hooray!
Go for it!
She's happy!
He's still excited at the garden.
Oh, I can't believe there are so many blessings here.
This girl is really happy.
You're such a good character, aren't you, O-Mamori?
I am.
Yeah, that's right.
Yay! Yay! Yay!
I want to be happy! I want to be happy!
I want to be happy!
Yay! Yay!
Look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle
It must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!