The
Time of the memory sketch
Please prepare paper and drawing tools
It's a problem
Please draw a picture of Ryo's name, Ryo Tsukankichi, without seeing anything
It seems that I always see it, but people's memories are uncertain
What kind of hairstyle and what kind of eyebrows did Ryo have?
Can you draw properly?
Are you ready?
Ready, start!
When you watch TV, please make your room bright and leave
Come to me, who has no money
I'm not, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
It'll be fine in a while
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
I'm not working
Come to me, you who have no way!
I don't have it, but don't worry
Look! The red spider is burning
It will be somehow in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you understand, then quietly follow me!
Tsurupika Ryo
It's fall already
On such a sunny day, patrolling outside is the best, isn't it, senpai?
Senpai!
Oh, if you look away a little, it's like this
I can't work on such a sunny day
On such a day, I can only take a nap
Sigh, why don't you understand?
My hormones are a wonderful reward
If I use a little bit, I will know its value
But, isn't it made for Queer Salesman?
That's...
What a phantom!
Very very massive», I've never seen it!
I've never been defeated!
I might lose my product to that!
No!
What should I do if the salesman doesn't trust my product?!
This is a match!
Will his arrogance win or will my deodorant win?
Let's see!
I did it! My deodorant won!
After all, my product is excellent!
He seems to be 5 times stronger than my arm.
I might lose my product.
No! My product is the best in the world!
I can't lose to that arrogant guy!
It's a match!
How about this?
I did it! I won twice!
This is...
I won't accept any deodorant!
I can feel the strong will of the world!
This is a strong enemy!
The biggest enemy for my deodorant is right in front of me!
No, I can't back out here!
If I don't win this match, my product won't be able to reach the top of the world!
How is it?
I'm going to make a fortune!
As expected, it seems that I can't reach the top of the world.
But I'm not done yet!
I did it! I won 10 times!
My product is a real victory!
After all, my deodorant is the best in the world!
But as expected, he was a tough opponent.
I used up a whole bottle.
...Huh?
Hm? I was so absorbed in this until now that I didn't notice it, but...
Could this person be a police officer?
Could it be that I did something ridiculous?
You don't have anything to write anymore, do you?
Is there anywhere else where you can draw?
Huh?
The one with the head is sleeping.
Isn't that Ryo-san?
No, Ryo-san isn't this slimy.
I feel like he's similar, but...
His head is a bit lonely, isn't it?
I'll draw his head.
How is it?
Nice. I'll draw his beard, too.
It's interesting, but the beard...
This one's hair style suits you better.
How is it?
It's true!
It's a great beard.
It looks like a bear.
That's right.
Then, let's make him a bear.
It's a pain to paint everything.
Then, let's make him a panda.
That's cuter, isn't it?
Done!
It's not that cute.
Yeah. He looks like a man in a panda suit.
Ugh!
I slept well.
I feel like it was noisy around here.
I'll go home soon.
I feel like I can feel everyone's gaze.
I'm in trouble!
What?
You're in trouble!
I'm in trouble!
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
Stop it!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Sorry, but who is it?
I'm asking you what caused the fight!
You?
We didn't fight!
What did you say?
What?
Is it true?
It's true.
We were just having a little fun.
It's true, isn't it?
It's true!
Don't ever fight again!
Yes!
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
But I feel like it would be a terrible thing if he opposed us.
I feel like it would be a terrible thing if he opposed us.
I don't know if this will be good enough.
Yes, I do.
What are you doing?
What did you do to my child?!
You write in the cartoons about something.
Tell me.
What should I do?
It's autumn already.
It's a cool season.
It's good for a cool guy like Ryotsu.
And it's even more crowded than before.
Bro, it's been raining a lot lately.
I'll give you a ride on the G1 this time.
Don't be so rude.
What?
I'm sorry!
It's cool.
How was it, Headquarters Chief?
How's my Kazushika office?
The management is doing well.
As expected.
Thank you.
There's an exit over there.
Oh, I didn't want to show it.
Please stop the car.
Yes, sir.
Headquarters Chief, we're preparing for dinner at the library.
It'll be over soon.
I hope Ryotsu isn't here.
Is there anyone here?
I'm glad.
It looks like Ryotsu isn't here.
Yes, yes, I'm coming.
It's Ryotsu.
It looks like a toilet.
Oh, it's the Headquarters Chief.
This is Headquarters Chief and Headquarters Chief.
Thank you for your work.
R-Ryotsu, huh?
Yes, I'm Kan Kichi Ryotsu,
the head of the Kazushikaku Kamenari Park Exit.
I-I wonder when you're always like that.
I'm always like that.
Of course.
The exit is the face of the police.
As long as I'm here,
10 million people are at ease, Headquarters Chief.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I can't get over how excited Tonada is.
I better get him here today.
I think that's better.
Be careful!
I think Headquarters Chief was scared of my power.
I guess so.
I'm home!
Hey, you're late.
You're Senpai, right?
Who else but me?
You guys seem to have noticed.
How about it? My face is getting a little more powerful, right?
Yeah, yeah.
When a man is over thirty, he can't win with his face.
You can't do anything about it.
How about it? My face looks like Takakura Ken, right?
I-I guess so.
Hey, Ryo-chan, are you really doing that make-up?
I don't know.
Sometimes, Senpai comes up with something really bad.
That's right.
Then, to celebrate Ryo-chan's beauty, let's take a picture together.
Oh, sounds good.
Kei-chan, please.
Ah, okay.
Then, let's go.
Okay.
Look, it's coming out.
It's probably a little bit too much, isn't it?
Huh? Which one?
Hmm?
What's with this man with a funny face?
Huh?
Is that me?
Yes.
Huh?
W-What is this?
I knew you wouldn't notice.
You're really acting weird.
Did you think I was?
Y-You don't look so super!
Logitech
Starcast
Click here for the full episode!
Did you notice how it started?
It's just a magic trick.
When did it become like this?
I don't know. I don't remember anything.
When I lost my makeup, I looked like an alien.
You don't have eyebrows, so it's unnatural.
I see.
Do you want me to draw your eyebrows with your eyebrows?
Do that. It's creepy if you keep it like this.
By the way, what kind of eyebrows did Ryo-chan have?
I don't know. I don't usually look at my own face.
Well, was it like this?
I think the atmosphere is a little different.
Please lend me that.
Yes.
I think it was a thicker eyebrow.
Like this.
It looks like a snowman's eyebrows.
It's kind of weird.
I see. It was connected.
That's right.
You can connect it and draw it.
How is it?
Like this.
It's too neat.
Then,
how about drawing a tulip here?
It looks good on you.
If you can do it, draw the sun on it.
Then I'll draw a cute house.
Then I'll add flowers around the house.
It's cute.
Don't play with people's foreheads.
I'm sorry.
I'll draw it myself.
I'm scared to get angry with that face.
Leave it to you guys.
Are you okay?
I've been dating for more than 30 years.
I can do it.
How about this?
It's a little different.
Then it's the hero of the hero manga.
I see.
Both eyebrows were connected.
Like this.
That's right.
Then draw an eyeliner.
Draw an eyeliner.
How is it?
I'm a Kabuki actor.
I'm lonely, so I'll draw a flower.
I'll draw a flower garden here.
It's not an illustration board.
Don't draw it freely.
You drew it with a color pen.
It's not easy.
I'll draw a name on the back.
It's cute pink.
Then I have to write the address.
That's right.
It's Katsushika...
Don't be ridiculous.
Where is the guy who wrote the address and mission on the back?
I'm back from the library.
Hey, Goburo.
I'm not surprised by that.
I'm sorry, but I was really surprised.
Oh, are you going to put out the stove?
Yes, I'll get it out from Chief Ohara.
I was told to get it out from Chief Ohara.
But I'm weak.
That face won't work for me.
The police chief has a face picture on it, right?
Oh, I see.
I should have seen the police chief.
Ryo, where is the police chief?
I think I left it in my pocket.
You don't have it?
I don't remember putting it out, so it should be in somewhere.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Watch out!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Okay, I think it's all right now.
Dang it!
Hey, why is it only here?
Jealousy!
It's not my fault!
You left the stove here.
Put it there!
Okay.
Isn't that a little strange?
If you think about it, if it's a photo, it doesn't have to be a police photo, right?
Oh, I see.
There should be a photo that everyone took in the summer somewhere.
Where?
It's on the locker.
What?
That one!
Okay.
No way!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
The places where Senpai is reflected are all burned cleanly.
This one, too.
Gourmet!
Ryo-san is the one who told me to move the stove.
It's not a big deal.
It's not cold, so don't even think about putting the stove out.
Just put it outside.
I understand.
It's meaningless to put it in such a place.
Did you say something?
It's nothing!
But he's weak.
The only person who seems to have Senpai's photo is...
Maria-san!
Ryo-sama!
Poor Ryo-sama.
She's become like this.
Really?
If you're going to ask for help, do something.
Maria-chan, I asked you over the phone.
Here.
If it's Ryo-sama's photo, I'll have it with all my heart.
Huh?
Endori?
What's this?
Isn't this the photo from the virtual competition?
You can't tell if it's her face or not, right?
It's very cute.
Is there any other photo?
I can tell your face.
Don't worry.
Ryo-sama's photo is organized properly.
And it's in one album.
It's called "Ryo-sama, Maria, Love Album".
I don't care about the name.
Where is that album?
I brought it properly.
On this desk.
Ryo-sama and my love album...
It's full of heat.
Maria-chan, poor you.
Why are you putting the stove in such a place?
What's wrong?
Ryo-san left it outside.
Shut up!
When it comes to this, I can't remember people's faces.
You should be watching it almost every day.
I feel that Ryo-sama's eyebrows are very characteristic.
I think they are thick and connected.
I feel like I want flowers around here.
And I drew a house here.
Stop it!
I'm sorry, Ryo-sama.
Ryo-san's head looks like he wants to draw a house.
Anyway, this won't work.
Let's prepare a wig and a fake eyebrow.
Something is not right.
It doesn't look like Ryo-sama.
It looks like Mr. Honda.
Then, let's make it like Mr. Terai.
This is strange.
I feel like I'm a small citizen.
I made it like Mr. Sakonji.
No, it's not.
Make it like Mr. Reiko.
Stop it!
Make it like Komachi.
Make it like Nakagawa.
All of them are not good.
How about this?
It looks like Mr. Ohara.
It's the best I've ever seen.
That's right.
I don't like it.
I guess he's not here anymore.
What have I done?
I'm in a bad mood.
I should tell the police.
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
I think I've met you somewhere.
Me?
Yes.
I don't remember you.
No, I've seen you somewhere recently.
What?
I wonder if your hairstyle is different.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I knew it.
Yes, goodbye.
Hey, wait.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
I wanted to apologize.
Really.
What are you talking about?
I'll apologize honestly.
Please forgive me.
I don't mean to.
I'm sorry.
Really.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say it.
I don't want to apologize to you.
We also sell strong medicine for your health.
I see.
If you apply this medicine to the original shape, it will become the original shape.
Original shape?
But you don't know the original shape and you are struggling.
Is that so?
Hey! What are you doing, Ryo-tsu?
Chief!
Chief, do you know my face?
Of course! How many years have you been dating me?
Well, well...
Rather than that, you have to do something about your face.
I want to do something about it, but I can't remember the original face.
What?
I accidentally got rid of my hair with hair loss.
So you're trying to do as you normally do, but you don't know the original face.
What? Is that so?
If it's Ryo-tsu's face...
Hmm...
The eyebrows are like this.
See?
The hair is like this.
And...
Oh, it's a head.
How is it?
Wow!
It's Ryo-sama!
Yes, yes, it's this face.
I feel relieved.
Yes.
It's my face.
Geez, what are you doing with this?
Then, just like this...
It's your head.
This is the head.
And you chose Ryo's hair.
I know!
She said it's my head.
Your head shape looks great, though.
Oh, really?
After all, I'm a man like Ryo.
Sakuya's reputational girl.
Yeah!
So, by the way, your hair is growing fast!
Isn't it too fast?
Yeah, it's too fast.
What are you talking about? You should go back to normal.
What, what, what, what?
It's too strong!
I'm sorry!
After all, our product is...
the best in the world!
Hey, Ryouta!
It's not my fault!
My eyebrows are gone!
Like someone calling me
After the rain
I look back and walk
I'm holding my mom's hand
I felt
a strange feeling
So
I tried walking
with the dial
Everyone was a child once
But everyone has forgotten
The politics that looked so great
The blue-faced aunt
in front of me
Turn around and look
That corner
Everyone, everyone
I can see you
There's a turtle over there
Oh, there's definitely a turtle
Everyone, come here
To our town!
Thank you!
Hey, hey, Itaike!
Why are there so many things in your room?
Eh?
You're going to buy it without refusing sales?
Are you stupid?
You should just say you don't need it!
Next time,
"Get rid of the bad sales!"
Good luck!
Next time, "Get rid of the bad sales!"
Thank you!