"Cute and
When you watch TV,
brighten the room
and look away.
Come to me,
you poor guy!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky
and white clouds.
I wonder
how they'll end up.
I wonder how they'll end up.
I know, I know, I know!
If you know,
then shut up and
follow me!
If you know, then shut up and follow me!
I'm an actress,
Ryouko Kameari.
Senpai,
what are we going to do now?
In the end,
we won't get any votes
in the final race.
I'm hungry.
The race is a man's romance.
I'm a man. I'm a man who doesn't eat samurai.
What's that? I'm not a samurai.
Men are idiots.
Really, they're idiots.
Shut up!
You're a man who can't win a match, but you're a man who can't win a match, so you're a man who can't win a match, right?
Man...
Shut up! Don't write on the ground!
What do you girls know?
Then what is this?
Oh, the main race manpa sword?
What? Hey, why are you talking about that?
I won 100 yen for a car ride yesterday.
Is it your bread?
Wait!
I'm getting sick of it. I'm a man, and I'm a man.
Buffet Viking?
One person.
500 yen including tax?
Wow!
But that's money we can't afford.
Oh, that's right.
When I was in trouble, my grandmother gave me a 1,000 yen coin to protect me.
Really?
Yes. With this, this Viking...
Oh, this is a woman's limited edition.
What?
What? Only women can eat it for 500 yen.
Only women can eat it for 500 yen.
Why? Why can't men eat it?
Well, men can't get a foothold, right?
That's not true.
There are men who can eat a lot, and there are women who can eat a lot.
That's the theory, but...
I'm a woman. I'm a man.
I fight for true equality between men and women.
A man who can eat a lot, but can't get a foothold.
A woman's ability!
Wow, looks delicious.
Let's eat, Hayako.
Is this a way of fighting?
Yes. This is the true equality between men and women.
This is the true equality between men and women.
Thank you for the meal~
Hey Mr. Hayako.
You should eat a little more carefully!
Hey! Why does everyone eat so focussedly.
I can't eat effortlessly alone.
Shigo, shigo.
Really, I'll have some too.
Our battle has just begun.
That's right.
Huh? Huh?
This is bad, senpai.
What's that?
A wonderful meal of manly food.
No, I don't want to.
Would you like to come with me?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm like this.
The TV station's producer?
I'd like you to appear in our drama.
Here, it's done.
Senpai, it's beautiful.
Really?
Hanayama Tour, just like the TV.
Just like the TV.
Who is the main character of my drama?
The main character is Shiori Momoyama.
The number one actress you want to marry?
I'll go see the real thing.
Wow, it's Shiori Momoyama.
Wow, she's so serious.
I can't eat this much.
If I get fat, I'll die of hunger.
Yes, okay.
Okay.
What's my role?
You'll play Takako, the main character of Shiori and the same school.
Please.
Well, good luck.
Huh?
Well, um...
I'm Momoyama. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryouko Kameari. Nice to meet you.
As expected of a popular number one actress.
She's so beautiful that I don't think she's from this world.
Is it okay if I eat this?
You're already saying it so much.
Well, let's start the real thing without rehearsal.
Ready!
Start!
Ah!
Okay!
Hmm...
Y-Yes, okay!
Weird drama...
I'm sorry, I can't drink alcohol.
In other words, I want Ryoko to play another Takako in the main character's fantasy.
One sandwich will be 235 yen.
Hmm...
One more mochikin!
You ate that much, but you're eating a lot of lunch, aren't you?
If you don't eat, I'll take it.
This is for dinner tonight!
Oh, right. This is from the producer.
I ordered the price at the same time.
Which one? He-Hoo or Meat?
Hmm...
It's like a dream to eat and get a gift for lunch, Hayako-chan.
Then, as soon as you got out of the car, you were lucky, weren't you, Ryoko-senpai?
Here you go.
Um, I have more work to do, so please don't go home yet.
And next time, I have a line, so please read the script.
Line?
Isn't that amazing, senpai?
I'll be waiting for you.
Oh, it's starting!
What? What?
The drama of Shiori Momoyama, starting today.
It's amazing how she's overshadowed the common sense of the past.
Huh?
Takako-san, it's my treat today, so please eat a lot.
Oh, it looks delicious!
But I can't eat this much.
Takako-san, you're eating a little.
Ah...
Here you go.
It's just not enough to eat this much!
This, this!
This drama is really interesting!
Was it not enough to eat?
My wife's watching, too.
It's not enough to eat!
Right?
Right, right.
The actress who appeared in the fantasy scene of Shiori Momoyama
It's a masterpiece. It's just like Ryo-chan.
Eh? Is she an actress like Senpai?
I see. She was talking about her face somewhere.
It was even rumored in the book this morning.
Is that drama that interesting?
It's a drama about a woman who eats a lot.
It's a drama about her eating a lot.
It's a strange drama, isn't it, Senpai?
It's not a strange drama!
What?
It's a humorous and fantastic story about a woman who is being abused by a man named Momoyama.
It's not a strange drama like you say.
What?
Huh? Senpai, did you shave your beard?
By the way, you don't have a beard.
No, I don't. Men nowadays have to shave their beards.
You're late, Ryojiro-dono!
What?
You're late, Honda!
I'll let you go for about four hours.
Senpai, you're weird.
Yeah, you're pretty weird.
I've never been so popular with girls before.
You're not going to apologize all of a sudden, are you, Ryouko-senpai?
Good morning!
Huh?
Shiori-chan, open this up a little.
I can't finish all of it by today, Producer.
That's not good.
What's wrong?
Oh, Ryouko-chan!
I'm so sorry to hear that you're in a bad mood.
Senpai, it's a night shift today, right?
I have to go back to school as planned, so it's not good.
But...
It's the moon, and you're still being so selfish.
Why are you doing this?
Open this up!
How dare you!
Don't!
Shiori's more delicate than you are!
Yeah, and I don't want to open them up.
Ryouko-san, are you okay?
It's okay!
So, quickly, why did you bend your navel?
If I, the side character, got hit by a spot and got mad,
I wouldn't be worried about such a stupid thing.
I don't have any character with you,
and I think it will work well in the entertainment world.
Well, the queen of Lendora is not guaranteed, but...
I'm not worried about that.
Oh, right.
I fell in love with you...
I was dumped!
No way!
That's unbelievable!
What a surprise!
And who's the other one?
Ah, perhaps, the famous rock band's vocalist Perry?
Yes, I heard about him.
He's busy, and he doesn't have much time to meet up.
Then he said he had a crush on someone else.
Give it back! You're a lucky guy!
He played in the commercial before.
He's a six-year-old talent.
Ah, perhaps, the Queen of Gravia, Monaco.
That's the reason.
You're familiar with it, aren't you, Ryoko?
What? I'm not a girl!
The sports newspaper's entertainment industry is...
...checking everything about you.
Ever since he started dating me,
he's been dating her at the same time.
What?
That means he's been cheating on you?
Ugh, I'm so jealous!
No, I mean, he's such a jerk!
What do you want to do?
Do you want to start over with Perry?
No...
But...
I'm still frustrated.
Of course!
I got it.
Leave this to me!
Huh? What are you going to do?
I'm going to make you a fool!
You're a funny guy, aren't you, Ryoko?
Instead, you're just going to keep on working on this show.
30 million people are waiting for you.
Okay?
I got it.
Thank you.
What?
I'm going to make you a fool!
You're not getting away with this!
I'm going to make you pay for this!
They're getting more and more excited.
It's okay!
Thanks for your hard work!
I don't want to do this anymore.
Let's hurry, Ryoko-senpai.
I'll be right out!
Before we go back to the station,
I need to go somewhere.
Ugh!
My dog's soba is about to turn upside down.
By the way, Perry-san, there's a rumor that you're playing with Shiori Momoyama.
What's the truth about it?
Love is a fleeting mirage.
The new song is "Kanojo ni Kurakura".
But is there a model for the woman who appears here?
The answer is yes.
And no.
Because I'm an artist.
There's a rumor of a new love soon.
I'm waiting for the goddess to appear to heal my wounded heart.
Oh, is that so?
Then how about me?
You're Shiori's...
Don't put your hands on me, you punk!
Ouch!
Hey, what are you doing to my Perry?
You're the manager.
Yes.
I don't know if you're a rocker or a shocker.
But if you're the manager, you should teach this young man what justice is.
Yes.
If you call me again, I'll be back.
Thank you for looking for me.
I'm sure you'll get more and more popular.
I'll do my best.
This is an email from Shiori.
Ryoko, can I have a little time after the shoot tomorrow?
Of course.
I'll date you at midnight, Ryoko.
Yaaaa!
I knew the first-class entertainers would be different.
The night view is beautiful.
There's no shooting tomorrow, so if you'd like, you can stay tonight.
What?
Of course.
This time, you troubled me, so I want to apologize and thank you.
Thank you, Ryoko.
It's okay, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm your man.
I'm not saying that the man of the day has a lot of grudges, but...
This is the latest model, right?
Huh? Why isn't it working?
I've been in a bad mood for the past few days...
I wonder if it's broken.
Would you lend me a screwdriver?
What? Can you fix it?
Oh, wow! You can do anything, Ryoko!
Well, sure.
Oh, it smells good!
It's delicious! Shiori-chan, you're a good cook, aren't you?
How about a little more wine?
Not a little, but plenty.
Ryoko-san, there's a bath in the Juggsy.
Let's go in together later.
Because I want to.
Take off your towel and pode yourself.
I'm not! I'm strong and I'm muscular, and embarrass myself!
I have a lot of complexes, too.
Huh? You have some really badored feelings.
I'm glad I met you, Ryoko-san.
Huh?
In the arts, it's difficult to make friends that trust one another.
Right.
But, Ryoko-san is my friend, right?
You can always be my friend.
Of course.
Ryoko-san, your nose is bleeding.
No! I think I got it up.
Kourin, bring it here.
It's okay, Ryoko-san.
I'll go up first.
Ryoko-san?
It's okay. I'll go first.
I drank so much, but I'm still not sleepy.
I'm tired of doing this.
Ryoko-san, the president of the Katsushika office is coming today.
That Kameyari Ryoko is coming.
Really?
I'm going to get a line.
I'm sorry, Ryoko-san.
What do you mean?
I should have refused when I got an offer.
The producer of the drama said that it would be a promotion.
So I talked to him.
What are you doing?
I have to do it.
I'm sure you'll be found out.
I have a saying that I live in Todaimoto.
I may be okay.
This is a good outfit.
Where is she going?
To the hospital.
Is this a
A hospital?
That's it.
You're not good enough to be the assistant president.
Keep it up.
Excuse me.
Oh, there you are.
I heard that you are a little late.
I need to go to the toilet.
Hurry up.
I'll use this ceremony to make the trouble I've been in into a bubble of water.
The ladies' toilet is in a mess.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Ryouko Kameari.
I appoint you as the head of the Katsushika-shou.
I'm counting on you.
I'll do my best.
By the way, where did Ryouko go?
I'm sorry.
If I can get through here...
As soon as I turned back into a man, I was in trouble.
What's wrong, Komachi?
Hey, Ryouko.
The chief is looking for you.
What are you going to do to me?
Ryouko?
What's wrong, Shiori?
I was called as a special guest to surprise you.
But I was found first.
I'm so surprised that I'm about to die.
That villain.
If you find him, I won't leave him alone.
Oh, look.
Shiori Momoyama and Ryouko Kameari.
I'm a fan.
Please shake my hand.
I was a little confused earlier.
Yes.
I'm ready.
Ohara.
I haven't found Ryouko yet.
I haven't found him.
I'm sorry.
Please wait a little longer.
Ryouko is a good man to ignore the chief's orders.
I'll go fix my makeup.
Ryouko, where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
Ouch.
Your face is white.
Are you okay?
I think I should go to the doctor.
Before that, I want to take a picture.
Oh, it's Ryouko.
I think Ryouko's not here.
Is he still in the dressing room?
It hurts there.
Ouch.
Ryouko.
Wait.
Ryouko, you went to fix your makeup.
Let's go on the parade.
I feel like I'm in Nakashimari.
Watch out!
Jyotsu!
Ryoko...san?
Chief!
What the hell is going on here?
Y-y-y-you're wrong, Chief!
Chief!
What's so wrong with you, you idiot?!
Ryoko-san?
S-Shiori!
Ryoko-san...is he...a man?
Our friendship is eternal, right, Shiori?
Usagi!
Wait! There's more to this!
Do something you can't even imagine!
What?
A true man and a true woman!
For the equally-
Uwaaaah!
A true man and a true woman for the equally-
And just like everyone else, at the end of the show...
We walked around this place with the rain falling...
...and of course it was raining...
I'll hold my mom's hand
I felt that strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the Ake-do-gai's tile
Just a black spot
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a turtle over there
I'm sure there's a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Come to our town
Thank you!
Where are we?
Why are we trapped in such a dark space?
Could we be caught in a crime?
By the way, who are you?
Next time, "The Worst Escape in the World"
There's a turtle there