Hina-kun is Winnie the Pooh!
Do you have any tricks?
If you're watching TV,
light up the room first and stay away from it.
Hina-kun is Winnie the Pooh!
This is the end of the rain that someone is calling,
I walked while looking back at the rain that seemed to stop
"Mom, please help me!"
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I tried to walk only in the dark part of the Ake-do-gai
I tried to walk only in the dark part of the Ake-do-gai
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
Everyone is a political scientist
You can meet everyone
There's a wall over there
There must be a ordeal
Everyone, come to our town
"Thank you!"
"Chis!"
"One!"
"Stop!"
Japan!
We did it!
The team that will leave the Kameari Park
will be appointed as the representative of the Katsushika City!
We did it!
Let's go!
The Kameari Park's Exhibition Room.
Yaaah!
Shoo!
My "Suzume Gaishi" has no enemies.
Ouch!
Damn it!
I won't let this grudge go to waste!
"Miteore Kameari Park's Exhibition Room"!
Kendo in one shot!
Ouch!
That's cheating, Yama-san!
My sword is for practice!
Prepare yourself!
You idiot!
Ouch!
Chief, what are you doing?
It's a cowardly attack.
Which one is cowardly?
There is no such thing as a crazy Kendo
aiming for the shin!
Because if you fight seriously,
it's a great deal.
But if you just want to win,
you can't do anything about it.
Come on, Ryotsu.
I'll beat you up.
Look!
Chief Ohara and Ryotsu are going to fight!
As expected of Ryotsu,
he can't beat Chief Ohara.
Come at me, no matter where you're from.
Okay!
I'll do it!
Oho?
Damn it!
I don't have a chance!
Oh!
Chiyoko Shimakura!
Now!
You fool!
I'll beat you!
Listen, Ryotsu.
It's a battle against yourself and Kendo.
If you have a sense of balance.
There's no way you're going to lose to a wicked sword like you!
As expected of Chief Ohara!
He's amazing!
He's so convincing!
He's got a lot of power
Chief Ohara's sword is the best in Katsushika
Ohara-kun, you're doing great
Please do well in the main event
I'll do my best
If I can get V2 last year
I'll be a great leader among the chiefs
Ha ha ha ha
Damn, Chief
Chief
If I wear this and do this
Oh, I did it! I found my weakness!
What are you doing, senpai?
Another new game?
You're not getting tired of it, are you?
No, this is a simulation of Kendo
Oh, this is...
I got it! It's to beat the rival Shibamata Shou
Good
What?
To beat the chief!
To beat the chief?
That's right
I've input all the moves of the chief in the previous match
Now I know all of the chief's movements
Got it?
This is the chief
And this is me
For example, if I go in from the front
Then, in the case of the chief
I'll avoid the left with 80% probability
I'll aim for the right side without a break
Senpai's face is a mess
But, at this time, the chief's counterattack is only a two-way pattern of Kote or Do
There's no face at all
Oh
So, if I step in like this and do Do
One!
Oh
Here you go, I win
That's right
You studied it well, Ryo-san
But, if I beat the same team's chief, it can't be helped
You don't understand it at all!
It's true
You're being arrogant
Look at this, chief
It's me!
I'm sorry
Then, I'll go now, chief
I won't lose to a sword that has a distorted heart like you!
You're looking at me.
Watch me.
It's just like the simulation!
It's a fish!
One!
Yes!
The chief lost.
No way!
It's Ryo-san's one-on-one victory.
I lost.
I'm sorry for the sword that has a distorted heart.
My sword is in Ryo's hands.
You're still not trained enough, chief.
There's more to it.
What was your training like?
Um, chief...
Senpai used a computer to see the chief's position.
He analyzed it.
What did he say?
The chief is so stubborn that he can only make certain moves.
This is also a great strategy.
Eh?
I lost anyway.
I wasn't trained enough.
I'll start over.
Excuse me.
Oh, Ohara-kun.
Ohara-kun.
Will you come to the next sword competition?
Without you...
What?
I'll be fine if I'm here.
I'll be sure to win the V2 next year.
However, Shibamata-sho, who lost last year, prepared a secret weapon this year.
A secret weapon?
Rumor has it that Kojiro Sasaki will participate in it.
Eh? Kojiro Sasaki?
Do you know him, Kei-chan?
Yes, he's famous.
Nakagawa-an.
Is he that strong?
Speaking of Kojiro Sasaki,
he's a genius who won the national tournament and high school university,
and he's also a professional swordsman.
He's also a swordsman who uses a skill called hiken suzumegaeshi.
Suzumegaeshi?
Not Tsubamegaeshi?
Yes, it's a terrible skill.
By the way, look at his face.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'm Kojiro Sasaki.
What?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, hamburger.
I'm not surprised. He's a good man.
So this is Kojiro Sasaki.
He's a strange man.
Don't stand behind me!
Chief Shimamata.
You've been behind me since a while ago.
Hello, Chief Tonda.
Did you see that? This man is Chief Shimamata's secret soldier.
A hedgehog.
He's strange.
But why does he have to be with Chief Shimamata?
I mean, he was scouted by me.
What? How dirty!
This year, Chief Shimamata will be the champion.
And Gan is...
He's definitely strange.
Don't stand behind me!
Chief Shimamata
What was that?
Nobody was there.
You!
You tried to shoot me from behind, didn't you?
No, it's not...
No, you didn't!
Right?
Yes.
You're lucky.
If you had been 3.5 mm away, you wouldn't have been alive.
Hey!
You're too strong!
What did you just say?
I'm forcing you to do it.
Ryo.
I see.
You really want to see my hedgehog.
I didn't say that!
But if you saw it, you'd die.
Is that okay?
I can't help it.
Just once.
Don't talk to me without permission!
Yes!
Jack! Hedgehog!
Hedgehog!
Go to hell!
Hurry!
I had another reckless fight.
Hey!
You were aiming for that fly, weren't you?
You!
You really made me angry.
But you didn't scratch the fly.
And you said you were a bad dog.
I was born in Hiroshima.
Bad dog!
Don't be phony!
Calm down!
I had a grandfather's death.
He was afraid of killed.
It's you.
절대
You're so tough.
Of course.
What?
Who are you digits?
Mark!
I'm Mark, the black cat.
And I'm the black cat.
I'm the black cat.
Hello Max!
Hi Abs!
There's nothing to see here.
Nobody there?
Listen, the place of the duel is Ganryu Island.
Ganryu Island?
That place where Miyamoto Musashi and Sasaki Kojirou had a duel.
It's far away, so it's 30 minutes by train from here.
Ganryu Mountain.
It's 9:00 a.m.
Alright, goodbye.
Hey, don't decide on your own.
Well, I'll think about it when it comes to the winning greeting.
It's Nishinotatsu!
I told you it's me!
A half-boiled egg.
I don't get it.
I can see that you're stupid.
If this happens, we'll win against the Shibabata Shogunate.
If we win, we'll get a special bonus.
Really, Shoujo?
I'm counting on you, Ryo-tsu.
Everyone, leave it to me.
I'll definitely beat the Shibabata Shogunate and win.
But what are we going to do about the duel?
That's right, Ryo-chan.
What?
I don't care.
I have a plan.
Hmm.
Chapter 5: The Shibabata Shogunate
The Shibabata Shogunate
I've been to Ganryu Mountain so early in the day.
I'm not a stranger.
I can't be your leader.
I'm sure I'll win the first major sword competition.
In order to win the first major sword competition,
I'll use this tree and keep it here.
This is my plan.
Look, Sasaki Kojiro.
Hehehe.
Chapter 5: The Shibabata Shogunate
The Shibabata Shogunate
Chapter 6: The Shibabata Shogunate
Too late! Too late!
Hey!
Sorry, sorry. I overslept.
Musashi! No, Ryotsu! I was waiting for you!
I'm...
Wait!
Don't do that!
Kojiro, you're gonna lose.
What?
What's this?
It's the trap I set up yesterday.
I got into it.
How cowardly!
You're so cowardly today.
It's over!
What?
Why did you drop it here?
Tomugi, I set it up too.
You're so cowardly!
There are no rules in the martial arts.
You have to be prepared.
Let's go!
What?
What should we do?
What the heck?
You're the one!
You bastard!
This is...
Damn it!
Char Siu...
Melon!
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Point!
Goal!
One point!
How about that?
Huh?
You were playing Legas, so it's okay.
Are you a professional baseball catcher?
This is also a game of the law!
Kannonmen!
Handa Goten!
Doremi Asora!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Tanma!
Tanma is the first!
Oborozuki!
Tsuki!
Gomoku!
Soba!
Gomoku and Soba are different!
I'm not particular about the game.
I'm not particular about the game either.
Hehe!
Oni-san, this way!
Damn! Wait!
You've come with me.
You're a heavy pot.
Idiot!
There are a lot of bombs in this forest!
I'll settle this at once!
Tㅋㅋㅋ
Aaaaaaaaaaah!
Kill me-soba!
Senpai, are you really okay?
What?
But I thought he was going to do the same thing.
Well, he couldn't make it here with a much heavier shot.
Now, we'll have a competition against the police station.
Yes!
Everyone did a great job. It's finally the final round.
Leave it to me.
But the final round is that Shibamata-sho, isn't it?
Last year, I won because Chief Ohara was there.
I won because of that chief.
It's okay.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir. Don't forget the bonus.
I know.
Chief Ohara didn't come after all.
Yes.
We'll have the final round now.
The team to compete is the Shibamata-sho team, who won last time, and the Katsushika-sho team, who won last time.
Please come forward.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Why? Everyone has the same face.
Kojiro has five people?
This is the trump card of the Shibamata-sho.
The Sasakki Six Brothers.
The eldest son, Koichiro Sasakki.
The third son, Kosaburo Sasakki.
The fourth son, Koshiro Sasakki.
The fifth son, Kogoro Sasakki.
The sixth son, Korokoro Sasakki.
The fifth son, Harumageddon.
And the second son, Kojiro Sasakki.
That's all for the Sasakki Six Brothers.
Is he a Muttsugo?
Are you guys a bunch of morons?
What are we going to do, Ryo?
I can't believe we have six fools like him.
But we have no choice but to do it.
That's right. We have to do it no matter what.
One.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Leave it to me.
If I win, I'll get double the bonus.
Double?
Because I have to do my best as the head of the O-Hara club.
Okay, I got it. I'll do it.
You have to do it.
Okay, double, double.
Hajime!
One.
Ryo-tsu is the captain.
Amazing! Ryo-chan!
My power is amazing when the wind blows.
I'm so happy!
Hey, don't copy my jokes!
Hey, Kokoro, do it quickly!
Good job, Ryo-san!
Ryo-chan!
Senior!
Amazing, Ryo-chan!
Four of us are out!
There's only one left, Senior!
Even so, I'm a little tired.
But there's only one left.
One more and I'll get a special bonus.
Damn it!
Please, big brother!
Leave it to me.
Oh, it's a double-dealer.
This guy...
He seems to be pretty tired.
Fuse Akira, the brother's revenge!
Hajime!
Prepare yourself!
Double-dealer!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Ah!
My arm...
There!
My arm...!
Ah!
Ryo-san!
Senior!
Ah!
Hahahaha!
Hush beef!
You did it, big brother!
Damn it!
The bonus is...
Next, the general, Maie!
Huh?
Ah...
I'm sure Chief Ohara went somewhere.
That means...
The prize is ours.
Hahahaha!
Wait!
I'm the general of the Katsushika team!
Ah!
Chief!
Ohara-kun!
Chief Ohara!
Chief, you're on the same side as me!
We're now on a different side!
I'm so happy!
Ohara-kun, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
We're done for!
Chief!
He's the best in both defense and attack.
Looks like there's no room for a needle to pull.
He must have been practicing.
The reports say that he improved.
What's up?
Gyo, finish him off!
Double Suzu-me Daishi!
A chest!
Digan! Same pattern!
He'll be done for!
- стал! - Construction!
I got you!
One!
I did it!
The winner is the team that won before the Kamihari Park,
Our winner!
Chakashi!
Everyone, you did well for me.
What are you saying?
The chief has successfully overcome his weakness.
Yeah, you did well by getting injured.
No, it's all thanks to the chief that we won.
Ohara-kun, you did well.
You are the pride of the Katoshika-shou.
Now, it's a special bonus.
Bonus?
No, Chief.
I didn't do it for that.
I did it for you.
Chief,
I'll give you the bonus.
You can't do it.
You lost.
And you said that it's all thanks to the chief.
No way!
Chief, that's wrong.
It's all thanks to me that the chief has overcome his weakness.
I did my best until I got injured.
The chief said he doesn't need it,
so give me the bonus.
Chief, you did well!
Let's carry on.
You are the chief!
Ohara-kun, the chief is still hungry.
You must have eaten a lot of the food that I had taken 0:01:44.000,0:02:40.000 You must have eaten a lot of the food that I had taken 0:02:41.000,0:02:42.000 So you will still eat!
0:02:42.000,0:02:45.500 I will keep this..
♪ and more and more ♪
♪ I'm holding a bucket in one hand ♪
♪ but I'm so hot and cold ♪
♪ that I'm still irritated ♪
♪ I'm irritated, so I'll get it over with ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ When the hot shower comes in ♪
♪ I get better with a warm pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ on Monday ♪
♪ Monday Monday Groove Over ♪
Dad!
What? Who are you?
I don't like you, Dad!
You're my son, Kankichiro!
Son? Don't be silly!
But look! Your eyebrows are the same!
You're lying!
Next time on Kankichiro's Summer
"Nice to meet you!"
Don't say that!
Next time on Kankichiro's Summer "Nice to meet you!"