Takahashi Shounen
In 괸島おーるくん
There was a day when I learned from a study.
Ah, I see.
Senpai, what have you been talking about?
I'm surprised by your voice. I have a special spirit of the master of craft.
Really?
There is really something.
It's easy to get caught.
I'm taking a big car!
Wait!
Senpai, please wait for that hand!
I won't wait for you, but I'll change the menu.
I'll change the menu.
Can I change it?
If you want to wait, I'll do it.
Then I'll change from Katsu-don to Una-don.
Okay.
I'll return the gold and block the way to write.
Then I'll do the brush.
You are kind.
I'm defeated by Hankichi.
What is it? Lemon?
Don't scare me.
What is it? Lemon? Don't scare me.
Why am I defeated?
It's Nifu.
It's true!
I can't believe that I'm Nifu.
It's forbidden to hit two Nifu at the same time.
I did it! It's an eel gun!
It's Una-don, not an eel gun.
I treated Honda for lunch, and this is all I have left.
It's the only one left.
Hey, you.
Why did you bring lemon?
I brought it because you told me that you wanted to ask me to do it.
You wanted to ask me to do it?
My father is in a bad state of mind,
so I haven't had enough time to go to the restaurant.
Oh?
Do you want me to work part-time?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
I can't help it.
It's the lemon's job.
I want to do it.
Let me go!
When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away!
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be okay
I have no job
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds and the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be okay
You know what to do, don't you?
If you do, come to me!
If you do, come to me, don't you?
You know what to do, don't you?
Lemon's Salt Shop
I'm home!
Welcome back, young lady!
It's been a while, Mr. Ejiro!
I'll make you trouble again!
*Sigh*
Sorry, Ichiro.
I was having trouble on the day before work, so I'm going to go by boat.
You'll get paid for your part-time job, so you can work until tomorrow.
Yeah.
And you can eat sushi.
What?
You haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
Ahaha, it hurts.
It's okay.
Alright, the contract is a success!
It's a success!
It's a big deal that you only trained for a month last year.
Your hands are not good for your face.
It's not good for my face.
Alright, that's enough for now.
I don't know why you'd go to this restaurant again.
It's not too bad.
I can't even thank you enough.
Eat!
Wait over here!
W-W-What do you want me to do?
Can't you go to work?
Get off of me.
Ah!
Oh, my...
Compensation served to make me eat sushi.
Ugh...
Ow...
Hey, what are you doing?
Everyone, Kanchi is a man of Ryotsuke.
Don't be a nuisance.
If you eat a lot, you'll run away.
Grandma, Kanchi is useless.
I don't think so.
You're too much.
If you're a Ryotsuke man, you can eat my sushi and get a salary.
I'm a bear before the winter vacation.
Let's go together.
I'm sorry.
You're a bear before the winter vacation.
I'm so upset.
Grandma, you're talking too much.
Lemon asked Kanchi to come.
I can't help it if Lemon brought me here.
Then I can eat sushi, right?
Let's eat.
Sushi is human after work.
Let's clean the front of the store.
Why don't you answer me properly?
Yes, yes.
Say yes.
Yes.
I want to be a human soon.
Listen, you guys.
I'll say it again and again.
You can't trust a Ryotsuke man.
Okay?
I hate you.
You've been
doing this.
But that's a brother's problem.
I don't think it has anything to do with the grandchild's Kankichi.
I've talked about it before, but I tried to steal the treasure in the basement of my village.
That's because you couldn't talk to Matoi and made him angry.
I don't think Kankichi is a bad guy, as you say.
Yeah, half of what you say is right.
But there's a good part about that.
No, if I don't do it, my grandchildren will be spoiled by that good-for-nothing guy.
If I don't do something about it...
Two servings of Chirashi, please.
Yes, yes, wait a minute.
Yes, hello, I'm Chief Kanda.
Oh, you're here.
I understand.
I'll ask you right away.
This is the second serving of Okami Heights, Mr. Yoshikawa.
Five servings of Jouzushi, please.
Two servings of Uchi, please.
Yes, sir.
Five servings of Zashiki, please.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm off to work!
Grandma, why do you have to disguise yourself like this?
I'll tell you the reason later.
Now, let's follow Kankichi.
Well, Okami Heights, Okami Heights, Okami Heights...
Oh, that's it.
I'm hungry.
There's no one here.
Huh?
Hmm...
Hmm, one serving and four Tekka-maki, huh.
I can't tell even if I eat one by one.
The man in front of you!
I don't care about the trust of the restaurant, I'm trying to fulfill my hunger.
That man is such a man, Emon.
Hmm, the rust is working well.
Huh?
Hahahaha!
What's going on?
Huh?
I don't know what's going on, but I'll tell you.
Okay.
What's wrong, Ishiro?
Didn't you deliver a delivery?
Hmm, Jouzushi is five servings, and Uchi, Wasabi-nuki, is two servings.
All of them have wasabi in them.
Oh, no!
I mistook it for the one in the upper room.
You'd better be more careful, or the trust of the restaurant will be lost if I don't check.
I, I'm sorry.
I'm going to take it back right away.
As expected of Kankichi.
N-No, you mustn't be fooled.
I just noticed it when you were eating the snack.
As usual, please take the oki out to the entrance.
Here we go.
Huh?
Huh? Why aren't you going back to the store?
It's about that guy.
I'm going to be late. I'll be back.
Look at that ugly face.
That's the real form of a man from the Ryotsuke family.
He's just a kid. What are you looking at?
You don't need to know that.
Welcome.
You bastard! Give me the whole Ryotsuke family!
Hurry up!
Rope and gum tape!
Yes, sir!
What are you doing?
You bastard!
Did you forget? I'm the police!
I'll teach you a lesson!
I won't do it anymore!
Thank you very much.
I can't thank you enough.
It's okay.
This is also work.
Gum tape, 285 yen.
Rope, 288 yen.
Magazine, 580 yen.
Each item, including the consumption tax, is 1210 yen.
Oh, are you taking money?
Yes, it's my job.
Oh.
Put it on the head of the department of the Katsushika branch.
Okay, then sign here.
I'll do it, Kankichi.
Oh, no.
Why are you so rude today?
Kankichi, bring 10 more pressure cans while you're at it.
Okay.
Here you go.
Wait 10 more pressure cans.
You're really rude.
Miss, I'll have another one.
I...
Miss, this is still 20 years old, so you can't drink it.
I'm sorry.
That's too bad.
Miss, how about I drink it?
Okay, that's good.
Here you go.
I'm gonna drink it to death.
You're really quick to drink, Miss Lenny.
You'd better drink the cup.
Oh, sorry.
Wow!
It's so good!
Here you go.
Here's one more.
I feel good.
Kankichi, you're overdoing it.
What?
You're the next best customer in front of this man.
Right, boss?
I like it.
I said, drink up!
Please call me Ichiro.
Marina Azuka!
Ichiro-kun!
Next!
That idiot.
Is there no such thing as a penalty?
This is Ryo's man.
If it's just for the sake of it, you'll be a scum and drink it up.
Ichiro Ichiro!
I'll go in with a butter pot!
If you hit the ball with that, you'll break!
Break?
I see.
If you're playing baseball,
you shouldn't act like this.
Out!
You see, humans are born with a purpose.
You understand, right?
This mean, mean, mean man
is the true form of a scum.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
I'll come again.
Wow, I had so much fun tonight.
Ichiro-kun, you're the best.
I'll use this room for the next party.
Thank you.
Be careful on your way home.
I can't believe I can feel the customer's heart in one night.
As expected of Kankichi.
Huh? Why is this happening?
This is going to be very strange.
That's why the van will be closed some day.
I have a plan.
And Te oma.
And Ririka.
Two of them?
I'll change it and call them.
How much longer are you going to sleep?!
Wake up, Kankichi.
Oh no, I'll just get a little sleep.
Ouch! I... It hurts.
That's a normal thing to do.
I'll borrow it. Get up now!
I know, so don't shout.
I'm so mad.
I'm the best at drinking at times like this.
Don't talk nonsense!
You want to crush the restaurant?
I'm so mad!
You're a rough woman.
Who's a rough woman?
Get up!
Gevalt, you really got me.
You're lying, Dad!
What happened to Lemon?
Kankichi, do you know Lemon?
He's my father's assistant.
Dad's back in shape,
so he's out of the house.
He said he'd come back,
but he's been working overtime this morning.
I see.
Okay, I'll go out on my own.
Kankichi will come on his own?
You don't want me to come on my own?
No.
Then go home and prepare for kindergarten.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Lemon, 10 points.
10 points.
Kankichi, you're going out on your father's house?
Yes.
That's great.
Lemon's happy.
Yes.
There's no way.
Listen, Kankichi.
Don't be so rude to Lemon.
What do you mean?
Hey, Lemon.
What is this?
Yes.
It's a lion.
Yes, it's a lion.
You did a good job.
Yes.
Next picture.
What is this?
Yes, Mako.
Yes, it's an elephant.
Yes, you did a good job.
Yay.
Next is this.
It's a hippopotamus.
Hippo, hippo, hippo?
Yes, correct.
"Kaba" is an English word for hippopotamus, isn't it, Joji?
Yay.
It's a cat.
"Buta, buta, buta."
Yes, correct.
You all did a good job.
Next is...
Well...
It's Ichiro, the father of Lemon, the daughter of Lemon.
Yes, Ichiro.
What is it?
The first one to raise his hand is Lemon.
Why don't you let Lemon answer?
Kankichi...
I'm sorry.
So, next is this.
Who can answer?
What's wrong, Lemon?
Raise your hand.
I can't help it.
Does anyone know?
Hiroshi?
Yes, it's Kurao.
This is good.
That kid's father likes to fight.
I want to see his father's face.
It's me, but what is it?
What?
He he.
Quiet.
Hiroshi, the name of the horse is not your name, but the "horse".
This is the last one.
Anyone who knows?
Ehh...
Well then...
Lemon, do you know?
That's the boy called Alexander collector dog, a unique dog association.
Is that?
That's right.
That's correct.
Ehhh...
How is Lemon?
That's not a butterfly!
It's a fried chicken with Katsu-sand!
I can't say that!
That's the answer!
I see.
That old man is funny!
He's a weird old man!
Oh, it's a real-time video!
Oh, Ryo-san!
Is your kid in this kindergarten?
Yes.
Why is Ryo-san here?
He's my father's agent.
Agent?
That's so flashy!
That old man is Akira-kun's father, right?
Akira's dad?
Great!
Kankichi!
Don't mess with people's clothes and outfits!
I'm sorry!
Okay, I got it.
Jukkoku-do is doing a show in Asakusa.
That's called "Seifuku" .
Oh, I see.
What's he doing?
Well, it's a folk song.
Akira, your father is doing a great job!
You should be proud of him!
Your father is so cool!
He's so cool!
Ryo-san, I'm sorry.
I came here after the stage was over.
I didn't expect to see you in this outfit.
See? He's a good father.
Yeah!
I'm sorry for interrupting your class.
No, it's okay.
It was a good lesson.
Hey, everyone!
Yes!
I see.
Akira-kun's father is doing a stage show.
It's a good time to show him the Fukua Jutsu.
But I didn't bring a doll.
Okay.
Then I'll do the doll.
What?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Ryo-san, let's start.
Okay.
Ryo-san, you can't do Fukua Jutsu if you talk to yourself.
Oh, I see.
I'll do it again.
Okay, Ryo-san. Let's start.
By the way, do you know what my job is?
Yes, I know.
You're a Fukua Jutsu master, right?
Liar!
No, I'm not.
Then do you know what my job is?
Yes, I know. You're a
What kind of job is a playboy?
Then I'll just tell you.
Thank you.
First, I go to the station in the morning.
Then I go to sleep until noon.
And when the president comes,
When the president comes?
I'll run away!
Run away?
I'll play with a swing in the park.
Swing?
Sometimes I'll hit the ball!
I'll go back in the evening, eat dinner and sleep.
When do you work?
When I'm playing.
Wait a minute.
It's about me.
Did you find out?
Stop it.
The End
I'm home!
Welcome back, Lemon.
How was it, Father?
You didn't have to be ashamed of Kankichi, did you?
Not at all.
Kankichi was cooler than that.
Not really.
What? Kankichi is cooler?
Well then, Kankichi, see you later.
Yeah.
Go tell your father.
I'll go tell your father.
By the way, Matoi.
If you don't want Kankichi,
you can have Lemon as your wife.
What?
What do you mean "what"?
Kankichi!
You're still going on about having a lemon in kindergarten?
What the hell are you talking about?
It's a lemon joke, of course!
What?
Oh, so you're his wife.
Yeah.
Lemon is a joke!
Lemon!
Tell me it's a joke!
Kankichi!
I hate this!
All this crap!
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na.
People who make stupid looks don't want to be the type to fight back.
When I was walking on the street in the corner of the street, the moon went away.
♪ I'm not ready for this now ♪
♪ Don't be so indifferent ♪
♪ Even if you lie and cheat a little ♪
♪ I'm saving someone sometimes ♪
♪ Baby do you know me? ♪
♪ I'm heading to tomorrow ♪
♪ I'm breathing with a nice heart ♪
♪ Don't be rotten ♪
♪ I'll do what I have to do ♪
♪ I'm breathing with a nice heart ♪
♪ What's hard to understand ♪
♪ is the battle I want to show you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ It's better than seeing it again, right? ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
We meet again, Hanayama's old man!
What are you doing?
What?
Are you testing a magic carpet?
Is that the flying carpet that appears in Arabian Nights?
Wait a minute.
I think I can make a profit with this.
Next time, "Fly! Magic Carpet!"
Thank you for watching!
♪ There is a wall over there ♪
♪ There must be a wall ♪
♪ Come everyone to our town ♪
Thank you!