Captioning provided by the KittyKat Team at JishimeYuka.
If you're watching on TV, light up the room and try to look away.
There's a cat cat
there's a cat arey
there's a cat cat
If there's a cat with no tail, come to my place!
even though I don't have one I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
You'll be able to do something somehow
Come to me if you don't have a job
I don't have one either, but don't worry
Look, it's burning
Ah, it's burning
You'll be able to do something somehow
You know it, right?
You know it, you know it!
If you know it, then be quiet and follow me!
Ohara-kun, what is the exact time to attack the base?
...E.
...Ah, yes, I'm right here.
It's 9:56:48.
Apolo, 12 seconds ahead.
I heard that the general has been made to be a very strict festae,
I heard that you will be sent to the capital.
I have a direct call from the commander.
No need to rush, Ohara.
Let's go.
Yes sir.
I'm Ohara Tonda, the head of the Kazushika office.
Come in.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry that you two had to come here.
It's not a big deal.
My idiot, Ryotsu, must have done something terrible again.
Ryotsu?
Yes, the famous person of the Kazushika office.
I came here today because I have something to ask you.
Something to ask?
Before that, let me introduce this person.
Tsukuda-san.
Long time no see, Tonda-kun.
I'm here to help you.
Ohara-kun, what are you doing?
This is the famous officer Tsukuda.
The famous officer?
He's the head of Sakurada-mune.
I'm sorry.
If you lower your head like that, it'll be hard to ask.
Raise your head.
In fact, Tsukuda-san will retire tomorrow.
I see.
He has a career, but he's working hard on a lot of things.
He's a man.
The famous officer Tsukuda has been solved.
If it's true, he could be a police officer before me.
No, I'm not the top officer.
So, what do you want from the famous officer Tsukuda?
He said he'd like to work at the police station for a day before he retires.
The famous officer?
I wanted to work at the police station once since I joined the police.
I'll ask you.
Can you make Tsukuda-san's long-term dream come true?
I understand.
We'll take responsibility and let the famous officer do his best.
Thank you.
And don't let the people in the station get in the way.
Don't tell them that I'm the famous officer.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
Then, I'll leave the title to you.
Yes, sir.
The famous officer Tsukuda
Tsukuda's Wonderful Day
You're late.
It's already past 7:00.
I wonder if the road is crowded.
Ohara-kun, did you go directly to the police station?
What did you say?
It's bad, Ohara-kun.
If I go directly to the police station and see his state of work,
My neck will surely be blown away.
You are the most important, Mr. Chief!
Please get out of my way, Ohara-kun.
Ohara-kun
Are you going to retire today?
I'm only on a day off, but I'm looking forward to your help.
We're looking forward to your help.
Get out of my way, get out of my way, get out of my way!
Ohara-kun
What's wrong, the chief is still here?
I've been so in a hurry.
Oh, Reiko.
My newspaper didn't fly over.
I threw it in the trash.
Did you throw it?
Why?
I was granted a job.
So it's better to not be behind 8 minutes.
What a man.
I'll be here for a day.
Tsukuda, who was supposed to work at the police station.
I'm an officer.
Officer?
You're still an officer at that age?
Oh...
I don't know if it's Tsukuda or Tsukudani,
but you're a very useless policeman.
Senpai, that's rude.
That's right.
Ryo-chan, apologize.
I've been hiring such useless old people for a long time,
so my salary hasn't been rising much.
You can say that so well.
You're always bothering everyone.
Shut up!
Oh, it's Tsukudani.
Um, I'm Tsukuda.
Whatever your name is,
take off that red pencil.
Senpai, Tsukuda-san is an officer,
but he's a superior.
He's a superior, but an officer is an officer.
I'm the chief of the police.
It's unusual for you to be the chief of the police at that age.
Don't call yourself a full-time officer.
What are you doing to Tsukuda-san?
Ouch!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
What are you doing, Chief Ohara?
Who do you think this person is?
What are you talking about, chief?
This person is...
I promised not to reveal my identity.
What's the matter, chief?
N-nothing.
But on the way to the meeting...
Don't make me look like that person is a superior because he's an officer.
I understand.
It's quite interesting.
Well, I'm going to go out for a walk today.
I'm going to be an assistant to the chief of the police.
That's a very reckless way of thinking.
Interesting.
I'm going to go to the battle hall with the full-time officer, Tsukuda.
Ryotsu, be careful with your language.
Well, I'm going.
Chief Ohara...
You're right.
Chief, chief, what's wrong?
He's a superior?
A superior?
Was he that great?
Ohara, you can't help but cry.
That's right.
Let's watch Ryotsu not to do anything rude to Mr. Tsukuda.
The investigation team has been here for a long time.
Despite the full-time officer.
Yeah.
So, who are you?
Chief.
Don't lie!
That idiot.
I was so careful.
But it's too bad for my heart.
It's a big joke.
It's not a police family.
It's a cleaning family.
Good job.
Yamada, a sheet of the sheet.
I'm old, but I'm young.
I'm younger than the chief and the police.
I think so.
Lucky, a new store.
We'll take care of you when it opens.
When it opens, we'll serve you.
Let's go.
What?
Ohara, he's always like that.
Well, sometimes.
Welcome.
The most relaxing pachinko.
It's a big hit.
It's heavy.
Mr. Ryotsu.
What?
Pachinko is bad during patrol.
This is also part of the patrol.
It's my treat.
You do it, too.
Well, one.
You're a bad guy.
Let me hold you a little.
Mr. Ryotsu.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
This is my treat.
I put a cigarette in the toilet.
Look.
I'm here because of this.
You keep shooting.
It's a lie.
I was sitting in this seat at the same time as the store opened.
I just put this here.
You're old.
It's old to put such a dirty thing now.
Shut up.
You remember?
I'll forget it.
It's a big hit.
Come on.
What's going on, Mr. Tsukudano?
Mr. Tsukudano.
What?
You're a big hit.
Try to let me borrow it.
I'll do it later.
Really?
You did it.
You're a big hit.
It's a big hit.
I did it for the first time.
I didn't think it would be so fun.
You.
That's why you're a 10,000-year-old patrol.
I don't understand the people's feelings, so I thought the police officer would be in charge.
I see.
Ryozu is preaching.
It's a good thing that you don't know much about it.
By the way, what's going on with your family structure?
What's wrong?
No, I thought a father like you would be strict with his daughter.
Finally, the honor guard has been cut off.
What's wrong, old man Tsukudana?
Nothing.
I slipped my hand a little.
Now, let's continue the patrol.
I think you should write down your address.
I'm going to go.
This photo book series is on sale today.
Pichi Pichi Onee-san.
Steamed egg?
I'm going to wear a uniform.
Isn't it bad to buy a steamed egg?
That idiot!
Well, the photo book section is...
Wait, high school student.
If you go out of this bookstore as it is, it is a crime.
I'm sorry.
Old man Tsukudana.
Please return this to the sales area.
Huh?
Yes.
Oh, no, that...
Ohara-kun, I'm going.
No, that...
Please take the bill.
That...
You're not taking it to the workshop, are you?
It's like the first half.
He's reflecting on it, so there's no need for it.
Then where are you going?
My room of Nico Nico Ryo.
Huh?
It's a dump.
Start cleaning!
Put the field.
Yes, the vacuum cleaner.
Yes, good.
Yes, it's neat up to the sink.
Come on, come on.
More spirit.
Do it.
Yes, good.
That's it.
Yes, that's it.
Well done.
So, can I go home now?
Wait a minute.
All right.
That's it.
What?
Wow, nice.
Wow, wow, perfect!
I'll do it all.
And it's not like it's going to be polite again.
You're going to need to stuff the hair shop in order.
Don't stack your bags again.
You guys need to go home.
Okay.
Well, I'll go.
What a fine work.
They remodeled it.
Well, they remodeled it.
No issue of room cleaning
Or the failure of the photographed room.
*BLING*
*COMPLETE SPINE*
*BOOM*
*BING BONG*
*COUGH*
*ZAM*
*K não*
*orts*
*BLING*
*MOUNTAIN*
*STAND NINJA FICE*
*1315*
*астиO*
*THE NUMBER OF KILLERS, REMEMBERS *
* NEEME*
*境 lessen: 6*
*EPIDEOUS*
*OF DANGER*
*TRAB2ST denominate: Bal tu mae fights*
Old man Tsukuda, shoot!
You've never arrested a criminal before, so you're a year-round criminal.
I'll make you a good old man.
Hey, shoot!
Ah, then I'll be on your side.
Take this!
I hit you!
Get out of the way! I'll get you!
Mr. Tsukuda, you're pretty good, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I've only been playing judo for a long time, so I'm a bit of a black belt.
Old man, you're pretty good, aren't you?
I'll leave the rest to you!
Yes, when you're done, I'll be right back at the station.
Ah, I'll be waiting!
I'm a little hungry.
I'll write some ramen and go home.
Hm? What is it? A letter?
Oh, it's from Tsukuda.
I wonder if he dropped it.
Oh, I knew it.
Oh, you have a daughter?
What, what?
"How are you, Dad, Mom?"
Five years have passed since I left home after pushing the other side of the fence.
But please allow me to write this letter now.
At the time, Mr. Akira was as old as a burnt-out, as my father said.
But now he's fully recovered.
Last month, he was a member of the Katsushika Family, and he was a member of the Katsushika Family.
It is true that the Katsushika Family has opened a ramen specialty store.
Please come visit and eat the ramen my father and my mother made once.
Uh, is this address the station?
Ryouto!
What's the matter, both of you?
You're all dressed up like former police officers!
That doesn't matter.
What about the Honorary Inspector?
Honorary Inspector? Who is that?
Oh, Mr. Tsukuda.
That person is as great as the Inspector General.
Eh? Was that man such a great man?
But why is such a great person working at the station?
Hey, I don't have time to explain to you! Where did you hide it?
I arrested the gangsters, so I made them work together.
If you're that great of an old man...
I'm not an old man! Call me the honorary officer Tsukuda!
I see, you're back in the office.
Anyway, Director, please look at this.
Huh? What is it?
What's that?
I didn't know the honorary officer's daughter was being arrested.
Now the mystery has been solved, right, Director?
Oh, it's solved.
The mystery?
There are a lot of police stations and police stations in the city,
but why did you choose Kameari Park?
I guess I wanted to see how your daughter was doing.
Oh, I want to do something about it.
Yeah, I want to do something about it.
Well, if you say so, I'll do it.
You're not honest, you bastard.
You idiot!
Do you know how it feels to have a daughter like you?
Mr. Oharu, let's go to that ramen shop for now.
That's right, I'll rely on the address on the postcard.
Hey, I'll show you around.
There it is.
Oh, it's pretty popular.
A Tokyo ramen specialty store...
Well, I'll take my clothes off.
Do you have any good suggestions?
I do!
Leave it to me!
3 days later
Thanks for sending me this.
Hey, Mr. Ohara!
I don't know what your taste is,
but just keep your word!
Shut up!
Both of you, keep your mouth shut!
What did you say, Mr. Ohara?
You're the one who's talkative the most!
What's wrong with all three of you?
What do you think, Mr. Tsukuda?
Has it gotten any better here?
I'm here. Listen, I'm going to eat ramen.
I said I want Tokyo ramen with a refreshing taste, but they came.
Ramen is Sapporo ramen with miso flavor.
It's Hakata ramen with a rich tonkotsu soup.
What? Did you argue over that?
What ramen do you like?
I'm from the Edo, so I like Tokyo ramen.
That's right. I'll choose Tokyo ramen.
I know a good restaurant, so I'll treat you four.
Nice. I'll treat you.
Let's eat.
Four people, please come to the counter.
Yes.
Mr. Koshito, please sit here.
Thank you for coming.
There are only two menus.
You have a lot of confidence in taste.
Four ramen and beer.
Beer is not good.
It's wonderful.
I've been practicing for ten years.
I still have to run for five years.
Thank you for waiting.
It's delicious.
It's a good soup.
The noodles are delicious with the soup.
Thank you.
The restaurant is good.
The children will be happy.
Of course.
Of course you are right.
Maybe.
I'm back.
You're alright?
Minori!
Dad?
What?
Thank you.
Please come to see me.
No, it's not like that. They just followed me because they wanted to eat ramen.
Don't be so stubborn, old man Tsukuda.
No matter how moved you are, where are the parents who don't want to see their daughter alone?
Is that so?
The fight at the end was a play to bring me here, wasn't it?
That's...
I was put on the mouth of Ryotsu without running.
I picked this up.
When the old man threw the robber away, he fell.
Then I thought it was bad, but I read it.
Wait, father!
Listen to Minori.
It's true that Akira-san was bad.
But for the last five years, I've been trying hard to sleep.
Finally...
I managed to make ramen that makes you accept the two of us.
So I tried my best.
I wrote a letter to my father and mother.
I wanted them to see us now.
I wanted them to eat ramen.
I wanted them to forgive the two of us.
Minori...
Father, Minori never says a word about her father and mother for a day.
Please accept the two of us again.
You!
Do you know how much I was worried about my wife to take care of my daughter?
I'm sorry.
Father, I'm sorry.
One more thing.
Don't call my daughter's name anymore.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
My daughter?
Then Kando said...
That's what I said.
I said I'd accept the two of you.
Thank you, father.
Ryotsu, let's go home.
Yes, yes.
Director Kanji, please.
I'll come by every night, so I'll give you a service.
Thank you very much.
You did a good job.
See you later.
He's a tough guy.
But I understand how your father feels, Minori.
Son...
Don't be like this, Akira.
You can be Minori as you have always been.
But be careful in front of your father for a while.
That's right.
I'll use you separately.
Huh?
My father left it behind?
When did he...
It's a check for the savings.
Huh?
I've been eating it since my mother gave birth to you.
Use it well.
Next time, I'll come to eat with you.
You're so...
Dad!
Mom!
Thank you!
Thanks to everyone, it was a wonderful day.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad you met the young lady.
Well then, let's go to the Tsukuda Honor Guard.
Yeah.
Ohara-kun.
You're happy to have a wonderful subordinate like Ryotsu-kun, aren't you?
No, no, I'm going to say it again.
The Honor Guard is only here for a day, so I don't know if you're misunderstanding his essence.
Why?
You're being praised by your subordinate.
You have to be honestly happy.
I have to be happy, sir.
Please, take care.
Please come to play sometimes.
Old man Tsukuda, I'm going to be bored from tomorrow.
Let's play pachinko again.
I'll be with you anytime.
If you want, I can teach you anything.
Idiot!
What are you saying to the Honor Guard?
Hey!
Please stop, sir.
I'm a great subordinate of Ohara-buchou.
Ohara-buchou
Someone's calling me, on a rainy day.
Looking back, I walked.
Mom, put your hands on me.
I felt strange feelings at that time
That's why I walked only in black
on the Ake-do-gai's tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgets
I was a child once, but everyone forgets
Turn that corner
And see everyone
There's a wall there
There definitely is a wall
Let's go to our town
Thank you!
Next time
I can't believe that my eyebrows and hair are so smooth!
Oh well, I'll draw them with magic.
Huh? What kind of eyebrows do I have?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Next time on Tsurupika Ryo-san
Not good!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you!