Translated from Japanese by 八霜
♪When you watch TV, look from afar to light your room♪
"A Little
Little
♪ A girl with blue eyes and a big smile ♪
♪ Turn around and look at that corner ♪
♪ You'll see it all ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There must be a turtle ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!
"Tabimakase Onsen Tour"!
Oh, the competition was great the other day.
Oh, I didn't know you could play there.
Oh, it's no big deal.
Oh, luck is always good.
Ohara-kun, again.
Congratulations!
Thank you, sir!
Congratulations to everyone for 25 years!
Please stand up.
Thank you.
Please.
Huh?
"Tourist invitation"?
What's this?
It's the feeling of all the members.
The first-class hot spring hotel with a high-end design.
A luxurious invitation trip for two and three days.
And,
a guest is invited as a pair.
So, please come with us, Ohara-kun.
What? Ohara-kun?
Ohara-kun is the chief who will be taking care of Ryo-tsu Kan-kichi.
So, please enjoy it.
And,
I also thought that,
you could have a good time here.
Oh, thanks, everyone.
Ohara-kun, I'll be grateful if you go.
Yes, I will accompany you.
Thank you.
Wow, I'm glad you're so happy.
Really, really.
Oh, by the way, where is Ryo-chan?
Ryo-san paid the ticket fee for the trip.
Huh?
Mr. Terai!
What did you just say?
So, the trip fee for the trip was 300,000 yen.
By the way, the fee should be Mr. Terai's duty.
The payment for the trip is...
Why are you saying that, senpai?
No, because Ryo-san told me to go.
So, 300,000 yen?
Did you give it to him?
Yes.
I'm sorry, but...
Let me have 300,000 yen.
I don't think you can live in peace.
Attention, the train is about to depart.
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
It was the money you paid to the travel agency, wasn't it?
I'm okay.
I just borrowed 300,000 yen.
You borrowed it?
You're going to put it all in this one race?
It's a three times more expensive race.
If you return 900,000 yen, you can return 300,000 yen.
The gate has opened!
The 11th train has a beautiful start.
The most popular Yamano Hope continues to mark the 2nd most popular Harahorohirehale.
Alright!
Good!
It's going as expected!
The goal is 10 meters away!
I got 600,000 yen!
Good job!
What a surprising development.
The most popular Yamano Hope goes straight to the finish line.
What are you going to do, Ryo-san?
300,000 yen is too much!
What are you going to do?
Ouch!
I couldn't read the finish line.
Darn it!
I'm going to use this to my advantage.
Ryo-san!
I'm sorry.
You can read what's going to be the result.
What will be the punishment if you give up that?
Well, everyone told me that.
I see.
But it is's really hard for the director to say you can't travel anymore.
In that case, I'll give you money to travel for your poor family.
I'm not even having to spend money on the light of a house.
Really?
You must be starving to death from all this.
Poor president and president.
They stopped traveling because of someone.
Poor thing.
A coupon for a hot spring trip.
Yes. Two for 2,000 yen each.
That's too much.
2,000 yen for a place near you is too much.
It doesn't matter if it's cheap.
It doesn't matter if you don't have food.
You can sleep outside.
What about a return ticket for the ski bus?
That sounds good! Let's have it!
President, president.
Enjoy the hot spring trip.
I'll relax for the first time in a while.
I'm counting on you, everybody.
Isn't Haya late?
I think so.
President, president.
This way, please.
I've been waiting behind the book since just now.
That's true.
We have to open the front door in a hurry.
I'll be back.
Have a good trip!
Ryo seems to have paid for it.
It seems that it was our labor.
That's right. It's okay.
What's this?
What happened to Haya?
If it's Haya, he might get involved in a serious matter.
But now she's weak, so...
The function can be improved by repeating a little.
And now we will move to the bus.
To the bus?
Yes.
The bus is waiting just ahead.
You'll take part in a sports event.
It's at the last minute.
We'll be traveling by bicycle.
We'll all do the same.
We're both working for your health.
That's fine.
Okay.
Ryo will give us directions.
Yes, I'm Ryo-tsu Kankichi. I'll be your tour conductor for this trip.
Ryo-tsu, are you still on the bus?
No, just a little bit more. Just a little bit.
What do you mean, a little bit?
You haven't been running for over 30 minutes, have you, Ohara?
Ohara...
That was close. We were just about to leave the bus.
Well, what's the seat number?
That's strange. There's no H-Q-10.
Oh, I see. It's the seat that fits the budget.
Chief! Chief! This is the seat!
A support seat?
It's like a school trip.
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
The red light means it's windy.
Ryo-tsu, Ryo-tsu.
Yes, what is it?
How far are we going to the destination?
Well, it's supposed to be at 6 am tomorrow morning.
6 am!?
That means we'll be sleeping here.
I'm afraid I'll have a backache.
Isn't that a great chance?
Midori, do you want some snacks?
Thank you.
I have beer.
Oh, and some shikamono, too.
Yes.
Hey, you two.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Oh, you want to go to the bathroom?
Yes, yes.
Here you go.
I can't calm down, Chief.
This is a strange invitation trip.
Hey, everybody!
Thank you for taking the ski bus!
Enjoy this trip to the fullest!
Yay!
Oh, there's an adult snowboarder among the young ones!
There's an adult snowboarder among the young ones!
It's very rare!
This reminds me of something I've wanted to ask you.
Could you introduce yourselves?
Could you turn on your microphone?
Well, I'm just a bit confused by what just happened.
I'm Kazushika....
Oh, I'm Kazushika....
I think it will be a bad idea to call out the name of the police when we're here.
Yeah, I guess.
How do you say your name?
Well, I'm Tonda Gomez, President of an ice snorkeling company.
I'm Tonda Gomez, President of an ice snorkeling company.
I'll give him aomania if he makes me lead the way.
Mr. Tokuto, please call him Mr. Tsunawatari!
Yes, Mr. Tsunawatari!
And this is Mr. Daijirou Ohara, who has just been restored and is standing in the steam.
Please call him Osaki Makkura.
And this is a useless human called Ryo Tsukanki, who has been fired from the company due to his use of money.
Please call him Mr. Human Disqualified.
Mr. Human Disqualified!
Mr. Tsunawatari!
Mr. Osaki Makkura!
Isn't this great?
This is where the boss will do a gag on his father.
Oh, he's going to do it?
This will make him even more popular.
Friday is the Friday for Friday.
This is bad, boss!
Everyone is being fired!
It's a mess!
This is where the new president will be.
I'm going to make a great gag!
You're going to do what?
I'm going to make a great gag that will calm everyone down!
The bed is a bed!
The cat is sleeping!
I'm going to make a gag that will make the back door look better.
A story about fire.
A story about Heaven.
The story about that world.
And the story about that world.
But this is not the end.
I'm sorry.
In these ways,
people are awesome.
I'm sorry.
I'll be happy to help them.
Oh, that's a good.
What am I supposed to do?
Where is he?
He can't sleep anywhere.
I found the silver world!
I slept well this morning.
My head hurts from lack of sleep.
I was woken up after 10 minutes.
I will show you the first place.
This is the room.
I heard there is a hot spring hotel.
It's not bad, isn't it?
I can't say it's luxurious.
Actually, there is a problem.
He and the other 8 are in the same room.
What?
Ryo!
Can we rent another room?
It's difficult because there are many people skiing in this season.
But, they are very nice people.
Right, chief?
I understand.
I'll negotiate with them.
You don't have any money, but you want me to stop you?
Actually, I lost my money on the way.
I'm very sorry.
I can survive only the rain and wind.
I don't care if it's a horse house or anything.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a night's rest.
Is it really okay to stay here?
Yes, if you can stop me.
Chief!
I'm fine!
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm really okay.
I think this warehouse is good.
It's cold in here.
But, I think it's better to stay here.
Well, that's true.
Ryo, what about the meal?
Yes, I'll ask him.
What?
You want me to eat?
That's right.
I can't eat without drinking on the third day.
I'm dying.
Please.
I'll pay the rent and do whatever I want.
I'll work.
That's right.
If you can, you can put me in the main line.
Ryo.
Chief, what's going on?
Why are we doing this?
Well, it seems that the rumor that we are the people who were taken away from the restaurant has spread.
Then, the person in the inn kindly said, "It's a problem, right?
If you don't mind, you can work at my house."
He said that, and he said, "No, it's okay."
I refuse, Chief.
That's right.
Hey, don't talk nonsense and hurry up!
Yes, sir!
Go and ask him!
Next is Umenoba!
We can eat rice, too.
I'll eat it!
Well, the food after physical labor is delicious.
No, it's true.
Well, that's good.
After that, there will be plenty of physical labor.
I'm going to take a bath!
Bath?
Uh…
I guess we can join you once the cleaning is over.
But this isn't a safe trip.
Well, Chief.
But...
Let's finish it quickly.
Ouch!
You're a bunch of old-timers in the bus!
We're here to...
clean up.
We're here to... clean up.
You're in trouble.
I'm sorry.
We don't allow anyone to enter our baths.
No way.
We can't go into the hot springs.
We're in trouble.
We can't do anything.
I'm sorry.
We're in trouble.
Chief!
Let's go to the hot springs.
But you're not allowed to enter the baths.
No, the locals told me.
There's a famous bath that you can enter for free in this mountain.
Let's go.
Is there really a bath like this?
I mean, the hot springs are far away.
That's why I can enter the baths for free.
I'm sorry.
There's a hot spring around here.
Go away! Go away!
Wait!
Chief Kataoka!
Hey!
You're in trouble!
Oh, that's the Sukibe family!
Huh?
Ah, this is a snowboard restricted area!
You have to slide with your hands!
Let's go!
What?
I'm not going to look!
Let's aim.
You have to slide with your hands!
Yes, yes!
Okay, we're almost there. Let's go.
You're so mean.
Oh, here it is.
Someone's in here.
Oh, it's a snowboard.
It's bad if it's a girl.
This is a love bath.
Excuse me.
A love bath with a monkey!
Well, one of them.
Here, chief.
Yeah.
Well, I'll...
This is a key!
I'm in!
You bastard!
It's a fight between a monkey and a gorilla.
You're right.
It's a flow.
The voices of the children earlier...
What?
Hey!
Are you okay?
Where's Midori?
What?
Are you involved?
Where was that girl when she was involved?
Remember it now.
Hurry up!
Well, she was slipping behind me.
Where?
I think she was there.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Answer me.
Hey! Can you hear me?
We should contact the local police.
We won't make it in time.
If we get caught, we'll be at the limit of 15 minutes.
15 minutes?
If we get caught in 15 minutes, will Midori die?
No way!
Don't worry about it.
We'll find her.
You guys should also believe in us and find her.
Yes!
She's not here.
Did she run down there?
Or is she on the other side?
It's already been 10 minutes.
Do you know her phone number?
What?
Over there!
Midori!
She's okay. She's breathing.
Hey, get a grip!
Hey!
Okay, she's fine now.
That's good, that's good.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Hey!
Hey, wait!
It's been a long day, hasn't it?
Oh my, I don't remember days like this one, Director.
No, I was thinking the same thing.
We took care of the case in the limelight, without giving up.
You two had a strong sense of justice, huh?
Police!
Huh?
Crazy!
It was a pretty tough job.
Yeah, the case was a big one after all.
If we had done it wrong, we would have been fired.
We were both so young.
Being young was our only weapon.
Yes?
Good evening!
Thank you for your help earlier.
And thank you for saying all the rude things.
No, it's okay, Ohara-kun.
I don't care anymore.
They are very reliable, aren't they?
Yes, I respect them for being so polite on the spot.
Um, are they really police?
Hmm? No...
I'm sure they are.
They kept the office secret, didn't they?
Well, let's go there.
What should we do?
♪ We are doing well ♪
♪ in the near future. ♪
♪ I'm sorry. ♪
♪ Thank you. ♪
♪ Let's keep in touch. ♪
♪ The good part of the fruit ♪
♪ that we just picked up. ♪
Ohhh!
Welcome back!
Hello.
I brought you some treats.
And?
What did you think about our trip?
I enjoyed that with you.
I hope it was a lot of fun.
What does he mean by "a lot of fun"?
You know, we had a great trip, didn't we?
By the way, what about you, Ryo?
Vedder!
At the Gryffindor Museum
What's up, Gryffindor?
♪Wake up, 간다♫
♪Stick out your watch, put it on.♪
Oh, it hurts!
♪Just brush your eyebrows for now,♪
♪and we'll dash 삼성 might get you to the station, dash together.♪
I will sleep again on my dad's back
I have to eat this and ice cream and six more
I have a bucket in my hand
But, I still want to eat rice noodles
I think I need some cperture
and it's annoying but I will manage
Every day is no problem
If you take a hot shower
You can recover from a bad night's sleep
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
My heart is beating
Monday
I love myself like this