Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking up at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a stone ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ on the beach ♪
♪ and they laughed at me ♪
♪ for being a bad boy ♪
♪ Even though I'm fine ♪
♪ I can't help but get mad ♪
♪ I'm just a bad boy ♪
♪ The city is so kind ♪
♪ to me ♪
♪ I'm crying because of the crows ♪
♪ I'm so tired ♪
♪ I'm just a bad boy ♪
♪ I'm crying because of the crows ♪
♪ Clones,
Laugh and forgive!
Thank you for watching.
There's a strong market for the oil market.
Buy related stocks of 2 billion dollars each.
That's it.
President.
I want to ask you any questions.
Sidonie in 10 minutes?
OK, I'll finish my lunch in 5 minutes.
Get ready.
Yes sir!
It hurts!
Boss! What's wrong?
Boss!
Boss! Boss!
What?
Nakagawa is under emergency?
Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
I was eating lunch earlier...
The latest news has just arrived.
The world's most famous concert singer,
Nakagawa Group's music director,
Mr. Nakagawa Keiichi,
suffered from a serious injury
during his flight to Japan today,
and is currently under emergency surgery.
What?
Nakagawa?
That's what I'm saying.
He's on the Internet too.
He's been around the world for a long time.
He's been on the Internet for a long time.
That's bad.
Let's go to the hospital now.
Is this the hospital?
It looks like it's Nakagawa Group's hospital.
Yahoo!
What?
Hello…
Excuse me,
is this the Nakagawa International Hospital?
That's right.
It seems like Keiichi Nakagawa
is admitted here.
Yes,
it's Mr. Keiichi
who's been admitted to an emergency hospital.
Emergency hospital?
It's a hospital with a medical staff.
What? A hospital with a medical staff?
It's not like
everyone came to visit,
was it?
But since we've come here,
let's have a look at Keiichi's face.
Let's take a look.
So, where's the hospital?
It's on the top floor of that building.
So this was the hospital after all.
Doctor Mahi Mahi.
It's time for the surgery.
Oh, right.
I'll take the longboard.
This one?
See you later.
Aloha.
Looks like that person was a doctor.
What kind of hospital is this?
Anyway, let's go in.
Thank you for waiting.
I have the permission to meet Mr. Nakagawa Keiichi.
Well, this is the entrance.
What is this place?
This floor is a waterway.
Please proceed by boat.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm not here to play.
I just want to meet Mr. Nakagawa.
I understand.
The back of the jungle is the elevator to the special hospital.
All right, get in.
It's like a prince going to save his wife.
Yes.
Hi, everyone.
Did you all get in?
Yes.
Welcome to the jungle boat.
I'm the captain, Donald Cook.
Applause.
Don't be a coward.
Go on.
You're a bad customer.
Let's go.
We're finally here.
Yes.
Well, let's go in that door.
Let's go inside the door.
Yes.
Ah, I made a mistake.
It was a elephant apartment.
This time, Mr. --
This time, it was a elephant apartment.
This time, I'm coming.
Why are there snakes in the jungle?
This time, it's a backdraft.
What kind of attraction is this?
Just hurry up and take me to the inn!
Understood!
But there are still a lot of bad customers.
The back of this temple is the special room.
It's like a movie temple I saw somewhere.
Where is this place?
It's a hospital.
Are we really going to arrive?
There it is!
Please come in.
Oh, you're finally here!
Ah, hello.
You look much better than I thought.
How are you doing, sensei?
I'm doing well, and I'll be able to leave in a week.
That's good. I was really worried about you.
I'm sorry. I couldn't get in touch with you.
It's nothing.
It's nothing. I couldn't get in touch with you.
Are you okay, Kei?
I just had surgery.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Where should I put your nose?
Let's get the TV out of the way.
Are you okay?
When I smile, my wounds hurt.
Please be careful.
I'm sorry.
You're so...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I've polished this floor too much!
Nakagawa, does laughing hurt that much?
Say it, Ryōtsu.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
By the way, Nakagawa,
why is this hospital
like an amusement park?
I don't know.
I wanted to make the image of the hospital
like a bright place.
I see.
I wanted to make the image of the hospital
But when I become a patient,
I don't know because I'm in the hospital.
You found out after you were hospitalized?
You're an idiot, Kaichou!
Ah, I can't do it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're so...
If you keep it up,
I don't know what Ryōtsu will do.
He looks fine.
I'll pull him up soon.
That sounds better.
Well then, Nakagawa-kun, take care of him.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
You idiot!
Oh, Ryō-chan.
I came to see you.
Nakagawa-shi, who was hospitalized
at the emergency hospital,
was discharged yesterday safely.
He's still basking in blood.
You're write that off the news, aren't you?
It was in the CMM news all over the world.
In that case,
Nakagawa will fall into a grave disaster.
It will be a huge disaster for Nakagawa.
Even if he falls down,
the whole world will panic.
As you thought,
because of your fart earlier,
the global economy
was in aっていう.
You think so?
This time,
when Kei-chan was hospitalized,
the Japanese stock prices
dropped tremendously.
Are you serious?
I'm sure it's true.
"Nakagawa-san, congratulations on becoming a doctor!"
"Thank you."
"Congratulations!"
"You're very popular."
"You have a huge influence in the society."
"If I got hospitalized, it would have a huge influence on the society."
"I think your case is probably..."
"Did you decide on lunch?"
"I think it's udon."
"Yeah, udon is fine."
"Oh no!"
"My senior has been hospitalized!"
"What?"
"Then, I'll order lunch."
"I think soba is better."
"Me too."
"No..."
"It has a 2 second effect."
"That's terrible!"
"Hey, Nakagawa, don't laugh!"
"What?"
"I'm sorry."
"Captain, please don't make me laugh."
"If I laugh, my wound will still hurt."
"I'm sorry."
"You're the only one who cries."
"You're my best friend."
"You're too nice, Captain, and Kei-chan is too funny."
"No, no."
"We're the same person, so why are we so different?"
"I'm really frustrated."
"Senpai."
"Human beings live simply."
"Rather than being number 1 like me."
"We envy people like senpai and senpai only likeisa."
"The only one we respect!"
"Honest."
"Hey, listen"
"Don't smile so it doesn't hurt you!"
"What?"
"You said you're from a high position!"
"It doesn't mean there's other high positions!"
"What?"
"High position?"
It's a very high position!
Poor Senpai!
It's a very low position! Poor Senpai!
Let's fix it!
You said a lot.
Ryo-chan, you're pretty twisted.
Because I'm a small man.
Oh no...
It's true that fixing Senpai's mood like this is more difficult than fixing Japan's economy.
Senpai is the only one among the only ones.
Senpai has a unique face.
And his actions are beyond the police.
Nakagawa's face is drawn to his face.
If you make him laugh, he'll be the best in the world.
Ah!
Senpai was also the number one in that sense.
Kei-chan, you haven't become a follow.
You're getting worse, Ryo-chan.
I know.
What are you talking about?
I'm just kidding, Nakagawa.
Were you surprised?
Stop it already, Senpai.
You're not the only one who is unhappy about this.
I thought it was strange.
It's just a little bit of a prank.
Then don't hit me that hard.
Sorry.
If you're the best in the world,
I'll make you laugh like this.
I'll make it hurt.
Here I go!
Ryujin...
P-Yanjun...
You're so similar!
Oh, yeah!
Speaking of P...
This is...
A little...
A little too old?
Okay, next.
This...
This is...
Oh, this is a little similar.
What's with that face?
Oh, really?
Do you know who this is?
You know, right?
No, not me.
Why...
Senpai, do you think I don't have to go to work?
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to work.
You're working for me, too.
I'm just not on time.
The lottery is already on its way.
What?
Oh, no!
Who is the loser?
Aya...
*Refreshing sound*
*Clearing throat*
*Sneeze*
*Clears throat*
What?! Nobody's here.
I was in a hurry.
Oh! Lucky!
This is a sports drink.
I don't know who this is, but it's my treat!
*Clears throat*
So, what was this about?
Well, well, well.
I'll make you laugh.
Well, that's not what I meant.
Oh!
It's a medicine!
Senpai, did you drink it?
Huh? A medicine?
It's a medicine that took months to develop.
Why would you do this?
Shut up, you guys!
If it's such an important medicine,
don't put it in a plastic bottle!
It's disgusting!
It's the same as putting soba soup in a coke bottle
and making a mistake.
*Clearing throat*
*Clears throat*
Why would you put soba soup in a coke bottle?
I've never put it in a bottle.
Oh, well.
This is why it's so expensive.
Well, that's fine.
I was going to ask Gorilla-kun to drink it anyway.
Huh?
You're trying to experiment with me again?
What kind of medicine did I take?
Well, soon you'll have a high effect.
What?
The principal...
The principal!
*Clears throat*
You're so annoying.
Why are you so weird?
You're like a big dog.
Next.
*Clears throat*
Stay there.
My stomach hurts!
I can imagine the effect of medicine.
You can't help but laugh.
Hey, professor!
What kind of medicine is it?
He's laughing as he gets angry.
Shut up!
I'm angry, but I'll laugh at you.
I'll teach you.
Hurry up!
*Leaves*
*Bark bark*
He's laughing numerous times.
It's very painful.
Look.
The dog is laughing.
It's like an appropriate scene.
What are you laughing for?
Ryo-chan drank the relaxation pills that Professor Ezaki invented.
Relaxation pills?
It's a kind of laughing medicine.
That's right!
On the laughing side, it's...
It's here!
That's right! That's right! That's right!
By laughing, humans can release beta-endorphin from the brain and relax.
It's too much! Stop it already!
You drank too much.
It's not. It's actually 3 milliliters.
What did you say?
When are you going to stop?
You're going to stop soon.
It's about the scooter.
Scooter?
The guy who told me about the trouble.
Ryo-chan, I'll do it.
It's okay. I can do it.
I heard that the scooter was found.
I heard that it was broken...
I wonder if there's a scar.
Wait.
Like being captured by the bandit, the parts are missing and...
It's almost a waste of eunuchs.
You don't have to say that.
Geus, you'll return to Rei-kyon.
Sure.
It's your fault, so you were replaced.
No.
No, it's not!
What?
What are you talking about?
Don't eat me, you bastard!
I got you!
My abs are cramped! Help me!
The culprit will definitely be caught.
What kind of escape room is this?
The medicine is good enough.
It's not the time to take a note.
You'll really die.
You'll die.
I'll pay for it!
Give it to me!
Ryo!
What are you doing?
Could it be...
It's a relaxation medicine.
It works so fast.
I'm sure it'll work faster if we go to the hospital.
Stop taking notes!
Professor, you're not related to science.
I'm sad that I'm a little late.
Senpai...
What?
The futon flew away.
The futon flew away?
It hurts!
I'll be punished for this!
Not only does he laugh, but he also does simple jokes.
It's a side effect.
I can't take it anymore, Kid!
That's enough, Reiko.
If we start laughing, we're done with sadness.
Let's break up, for example!
Well, I'll give it a try.
Are we done?
What is it, Reiko?
What do you dislike about me?
What do you mean?
My chin, my mouth, my nose, my eyes, my eyebrows, my hairstyle...
Oh, really?
I knew it!
Well, see you later!
Hello, this is the park exit.
A gold mine!
Sorry, but it's not that weird.
I understand.
Hey, everyone!
The gold mine is filled with robbers and they're hiding in there!
I'm going to go right now!
The next day
You're late for the support.
I wonder what everyone's doing.
Wait, come here!
Leave the rest to us.
And the culprit is...
I'm inside.
Why are you all laughing?
I don't care about that.
Then, should I bow to the culprit's face?
What the hell are you doing?
He's like a picture of the culprit.
He's just as I imagined.
I'm not going to laugh.
I'll laugh and shoot!
That's a toy pistol.
What?
You're a real culprit, aren't you?
Now I know.
Now, go outside!
A real one is a moped!
Oh, my God!
You can't say that!
Moped!
A trumpet!
Oh, my God!
Mr. Nakagawa!
He's a bit shy.
He brought his own little tool and said a joke.
What the hell is wrong with you guys!
Come on!
I'm not stupid!
I'm a good guy!
What the hell is wrong with you guys!
Oh no!
I'm an idiot killer!
Help me!
Oh no!
Ohara-kun, you're really something.
You're definitely a police officer.
A police officer?
Is that a good thing?
Don't say such a thing in front of the chief.
I don't have to write much anyway.
I'm sorry for being cheap.
I'm just kidding.
What's wrong with you guys?
The chief just flew away.
You idiot!
What's wrong with Ohara-kun?
I'm going to make you all the worst!
I won't let you do that.
Why do I have to be kicked out like this?
I don't want to be kicked out.
If we're all together, it won't be lonely.
The effect of the medicine will last for more than a week.
Don't always take the data.
Stop it!
Thank you for your hard work.
You two.
It's my fault.
Don't be like this doubtful.
Watch your own business.
Without thinking about it,
we didn't have any other way out.
You also didn't know about the poison.
You also weren't Estonia.
We'll be off tomorrow.
Bye.
I haven't done it for a long time.
What?
I haven't done it for a long time, either.
♪ ♫ ♫ ♪
Isn't it!?
Wow!
♪ ♫ ♫ ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
"I'm Kankichi!"
How cute am I?
If so, tell me that I'm cool and reliable!
Well, if this happens, I'll raise this cuteness!
Next time, "Hananoko Ryo-chan"!
See you!
♪ That's Kameari ♪
♪ Oh, it must be Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!