Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I took off my love stone and flew to the end ♪
♪ I laughed at the captain of the taiko who was jogging ♪
♪ He said that he was fine as a joke ♪
♪ Even if I try to cheer up in the place, I can only get angry ♪
♪ The cityscape that never changes is more kind than a bad habit ♪
♪ The fire is already burning because the glass is crying ♪
♪ The yakitori is overflowing ♪
♪ The beer is overflowing ♪
♪ The hot water bottle is coming out of my cap ♪
♪ The sun is falling down at Taishakuten ♪
♪ I'll wake up tomorrow and end it ♪
♪ But I lost my happiness again ♪
♪ I'm the stupid one who noticed it ♪
Transform Before-After
Check it out.
Delegation Ohtari!
It's the photo of her grand-tudor's kid!
It's Rei's...
Daishkey and Sakura!
They are so cute!
You guys are like angels.
Oh my, I had only the sweetest time to find one.
Give me one back.
That's so cute.
You two should be together every day, right?
I think I'm going to get a heart attack.
Well, that's true.
Is there something good going on today?
No, nothing.
I think the chief is happy today.
I wonder.
It's because of Reiko-kun's feeling.
Help making noodles?
You who are thinking of repairing a fake house,
free of charge.
Give it back.
Are you going to make it a fake house?
Ah, shut up.
If I talk to you, I'm going to be in a bad mood.
Let's work hard today.
Okay?
I'm counting on you.
Yes.
The chief is weird.
Really?
The chief made it a fake house and went with his granddaughter.
I see.
That's why he seemed so happy.
That's what it was.
What? What do you mean?
Ryo-san.
Ryo-san, help me.
What's wrong, Kiyama's father?
I have no work.
I'm going to be destroyed this time.
The job of a carpenter is to build a house, right?
What's the point of destroying it?
That's why I said I don't have any orders even if I want to build one.
Then, it can't be helped even if you're destroyed.
No way.
Ryo-chan,
you don't have that attitude, do you?
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
Because there are no good shops in the shopping street.
Look at the street.
There's no good shop.
If you're destroyed, it's not scary.
Stop it.
Ryo-chan.
It's a joke.
Oh my.
Ryo-san has had many businesses so far.
How can you get back?
Tell me.
Please.
Stop it.
I understand.
I'll do something.
Ryo-san.
First of all, I'll reform this store.
Reform?
It's an unprecedented reform boom.
Yes.
I'll make it a fancy design office.
I'll feed new customers who are easy to eat.
And,
you'll reform yourself from a craftsman to a creator.
Reform?
You look a little uncomfortable.
With this outfit.
Ryo-san, I want to laugh at you.
That was a polite laugh.
It's okay.
You're pretty cool.
Really?
Listen closely.
Even in Fukuoka,
designer's houses and fancy houses
are sold well.
Even the people in the forefront of business are good.
So, this outfit?
Considering the balance as a duo,
I'll go with a good business style.
I understand.
Yes.
Then, come closer.
Here. Here. Here.
I'm coming.
Yes, I'm waiting.
What?
I'll rely on your style
and get my wife to take over the TV.
Even if you're good at it
and you look good,
you'll get no customers.
It's my first time on TV.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
You're pushing your mother's opposition
and trying to make a living.
I'll do my best.
I'll rely on you, Ryo-san.
But, I'm not good at it.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Ryo-tsu,
the sales and marketing director of Reform Kiyama.
I'm Ryo-tsu, the sales and marketing director of Reform Kiyama.
I've seen the ribbon many times
with Sanji's wife's reform.
I'm looking forward to something interesting.
Are you the president?
Yes, I'm the owner and designer.
I'm Kiyama Mokuzo.
The customers are already standing
at the site, so let's go.
Let's go.
Hello. I'm Yamanaka.
Mr. Yamanaka.
You've been homeless and
blackmailed for 30 years
and you have no money to despise.
How would this help?
If there's no situation
or recognition,
it won't be easy.
Ryo-san, what are you gonna do?
Don't worry.
I have some solution.
Do you know
I was in deep trouble there.
Thank you for applying for the renewal campaign of the reform Kiyama.
Thank you.
Lord Yamanaka is the number one customer to commemorate.
We will accept your request for a special reform.
Like?
Like!
I can't believe you can reform with this like.
It would be great if you could raise it to about 100,000 yen.
Wait a minute.
I've never heard of a whole apartment being reformed to 100,000 yen.
Please wait a minute.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
So do it.
I told you to do your best.
This is advertising.
Show your motivation in front of the camera.
Now, 30 people who arrived first are receiving the reform with a like.
What?
No way.
I want my own room soon.
Make it a really cool room, Ryo.
Yes, sir.
Junpei, Cappei, Bo-chan.
Two rooms for 6 people.
And what about the budget?
Brother.
Yes.
Please.
Here it is.
500 yen.
I lost it.
I can't afford a 500-yen reform.
If you think about the advertising effect, I want to make it a success.
Let's go.
But 500 yen is not a cheap work.
I see.
Let's take a big service of the amount of blood.
Really?
President, that's great.
Yes.
I did it.
Ryo.
Yes?
I want to ask for a house in Gonta.
Gonta?
This.
The reform of the doghouse?
I'll do my best to get rid of it.
I understand.
I'll do it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it, llamond.
Yes, Ganya...
Wow, who's the owner of Ganya…
It's Mr. Takfromatsu.
I'm really glad to hear that.
So I do the same thing.
Let's go, I'm coming.
After the reform, we'll meet with the Yamanaka-Sou!
T-this is...
From today, the Yamanaka-Sou will be renewed!
Method Versailles Urban Yamanaka!
So, Silbpre?
Versailles!
It's been changed so much with only 100,000 yen!
That's the miracle technique of the reform Kiyama!
It's got a purse!
Ouch, it looks real!
Because of the budget, we've asked the students to help with the construction.
There's a parking lot behind it.
It's here.
Amazing! It's so luxurious!
I thought so, but it's all gone.
Well, it's enough to fulfill the role of a luxury car.
Amazing!
We've eliminated all the poverty of the Yasu Apartment!
This is the door to the room.
This is the Yasu Apartment!
This is the entrance.
It's a public place.
There are also various rooms for each theme.
For example, the theme of this room is "Narikin".
I can't tell what's real from the sound of it!
For those who are lonely, this room...
It's a great crowd!
We've incorporated the shoddy city of Shinjuku into the interior.
This room is already being watched by someone.
I think I'll be attracted to the car.
I think so.
It takes some time until you get used to it.
Wow! Amazing!
Wow! It's so fun!
It's made of cardboard!
This might be a hot topic.
It's a Ryo-chan-like idea, isn't it?
That's just the beginning!
Ryo-chan!
Huh? I just saw it on TV.
It's obviously for recording.
Yes, this is Reform Kiyama.
Oh, the owner of Versailles.
What?
The whole apartment has a tenant!
But the company of the important Kiyama-san is...
That's the problem.
Thanks for the nice dog house!
As soon as the Reform Kiyama campaign ended,
the customers were full.
This is not only profitable,
but also a good way to return the money that was inflated in the campaign.
And the best thing is the basics of business.
The name of Reform Kiyama has been known around the world.
The game starts now.
Ryo-san, you can trust me, can't you?
Hello.
Welcome.
What? The campaign is over?
Unfortunately.
Too bad.
Then let's go home.
Please wait.
Oh, I saw it on TV.
Consultation is free.
By the way, what kind of reforms do you think?
The room is small, so even a little...
I want to make it bigger.
Yes.
Let's make it bigger.
Ryo-san!
Huh? Will it be bigger?
Of course.
Ryo-san.
Hey, excuse me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh.
Ryo-san.
It starts with a thief.
If you know that I deceived a customer and did business,
this time you'll be rewarded by mom.
I'm not telling you to deceive customers.
I'm telling you to show me your wisdom.
My art skills.
I can't.
How can you make a small room bigger.
If it's impossible, the reason will be drawn in.
I'll do it.
I don't want to let go of this shop and land anymore.
I can do anything even if I just crush it against the window.
What was that?
Demolition?
Why all of a sudden?
Can't you hear it?
The sound of success approaching!
Last time was very popular.
The unique transformation of Reform Kiyama.
Do you remember it?
This time, as the second part,
along with Reform, who surprised us even more,
they have reappeared.
Reform! Reform!
The original Reform!
Please leave it to Reform Kiyama!
Yes!
The client is a couple who just got married this spring,
and they are newly married.
How did it turn out?
I'm really looking forward to it!
Then, let's take a look at the house.
The appearance doesn't show any noticeable changes,
but the interior hasn't changed much.
I see.
This way, please.
What's with this handle?
First, turn the handle at the top.
The top?
What the hell?
What's with this sound?
Nobifu!
I'm surprised!
It's a great idea, President!
It's a Debea that was sent from the window.
Reform Kiyama special guest is coming out!
Thank you!
And if you turn this handle...
The ceiling is stretched!
No way!
Reform Kiyama
Here we go!
Another ceiling has been slided from the wall!
Reform Kiyama
Here is the floor of the second floor.
Here we go!
Now we have three rooms.
There's another handle.
Reform Kiyama
Here we go!
Second floor.
If you pull this handle,
there is no gap between the neighbors,
and if you press this button,
the floor will come out.
So cool.
Right?
Morning, gardening.
Night, in the planetarium,
depending on how you use it.
Well thought out idea!
Is the problem a construction standard?
It'll be all right.
If anything happens,
quickly return to Earth,
is
just like this,
amazing
.
There are many problems that should be cleared, but
this may be hit.
This house is a study with a roof.
It seems that they are enjoying a bath on a rooftop with the
Absolute
There is an old car.
"Why?"
Now, the DeBea Mansion, which has already been built into DeBea, is also being built.
"I'm Kiyama, the DeBea's room manager."
"And my subordinates..."
"Thank you for coming."
"Yes, I'm Kiyama, the DeBea's room manager."
"Yes, that's right."
"Wait a minute."
"Please, Ryo-san, please answer the phone."
"I'm a customer of the DeBea Mansion."
"Ryo-san!"
"If you take any more orders, we won't be able to handle it."
"Don't worry. I'll take care of the next one."
"Once you get a job at our house, you'll be sent to a subordination company and then you'll be sent to a subordination company for a low price."
"Even if you don't work, we'll give you a lot of money."
"If you do that..."
"You're not going to be able to keep DeBea's room, are you?"
"No, no!"
"This is why you can't be a coward."
"Come back to your mother, okay?"
"R-Ryo-san..."
"I'll take all the orders."
"Okay."
"Yes, DeBea's Reformed Kiyama."
"If you understand, that's fine."
"Well, I'll be the customer of the store."
"Look at me and tell me if I make a lot of money today."
"Oh, Chief!"
"Oh no, why is the chief..."
"Ryo-tsu!"
"Chief, why are you here?"
"What are you doing here?"
"Well, um..."
"I don't even have time to ask you. I can see that you're doing what you're supposed to do."
"You're trying to do something that I don't understand, and you're bothering people again."
"I'm sorry. I was just helping people while patrolling."
"Oh, you're not a detective, but you're patrolling in your underwear?"
"No, this is..."
"Oh, Mr. O'Hara."
"Oh, Mr. Kiyama."
"Hello."
"I'm always grateful for your help."
"Oh, this is me."
"Mr. Kiyama, I'm not bothering you."
"I'm telling you that's not true. Tell me the truth."
"I'm really grateful to you, Mr. Ryo."
"It's all thanks to you that the store that was about to collapse was brought back to life."
"Are you sure about that?"
"Yes, that's why I said I was helping people."
"If you helped people, of course you wouldn't have received money."
"I'm sure you didn't have any money."
"Of course, I had a lot of money."
"Of course you had a lot of money, but you didn't receive a single cent of your money."
"I see."
"What did you come here for, Chief?"
"Well, uh..."
"I came here to think about building a two-storey house."
"I see. So you had a pamphlet the other day."
"Yes, my daughter and I live in a house.
"I heard that when a small kid jumps around, he or she will say something or complain."
"Oh, you're so cute."
"I'm glad I didn't have to look after you, Chief."
"I have three grandchildren, so I know how you feel."
"Oh, that must be lively."
"My son is moving to Kagoshima now."
"My wife is going over there now."
"She's crying and talking."
"That's..."
"That's a little sad."
"Well, then I'll excuse myself for having a lot of customers."
"Ryo, please."
"I've been doing a lot of work as a mechanic lately, so I'm very skilled."
"I'll do my best to do this job."
"I'm looking forward to working with you."
"So you're thinking of building a new house that will transform into a robot-type house?"
"Yes, it was a dream from when I was a child."
"`a robot, a robot"
"I'm so happy to hear this story, and I'm glad that even such a small technology school like ours were able to do it like it should."
"We have about three of these robots in our house, so I can understand."
" Admit it. It would be a dream come true if we get help from Mr. Mikiyama of Reform."
"Please leave it to him."
였ля
Thank you for the cooperation!
Me too!
It's a one-in-one robot-figure-like house.
It could be a new way to discover the world of Japan,
or the world of the anime,
or even a new way to discover the world of the anime,
I'm looking forward to it!
Please choose from this catalogue.
Ryotsu-san, we just got a call from the material company,
and they're saying there's not enough rail for the living room.
The rail for the living room?
It's a B-class product, so just tell them to arrange the number!
If you're late, we won't pay you!
- Okay? - Yes.
It looks like we'll have a nice two-story house, Dad.
I'm glad you asked for it, Kiyama-san.
Thank you very much.
Okay, it's done!
Check complete!
This concludes the third episode of the surprise project,
Robot House.
Complete!
Hey!
Put this on the wall around here,
and deliver it to the company.
Yes sir.
I'm counting on you.
I haven't slept in three days.
Is this wall okay?
Anything is fine.
But before you leave,
please make me a hot coffee.
Yes, I'll put it in right away.
Hey, Ryotsu-san.
I just got a call from Ohara-san,
and he wants to check it again,
so I'd like you to send it back, but...
Ohara-san?
It's near the CEO's desk.
Okay.
Here it is.
Geez,
this isn't a house for two-story houses
with a big project.
I brought you some coffee.
Sorry about that.
I think I put it on the desk,
but it's weird.
Did I put it back here?
This isn't in here...
This isn't in here either...
Oh, I found it.
This is it.
The color of the tile was this color, too.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I'll be right back.
Now we just have to wait for it to be finished.
The weather is better than the new building.
Indeed.
After this job,
I'll be able to go to the company
and face my challenges.
I see.
From now on,
I'll continue my work
and introduce you to the third round
of the "Reform Kiyamono Surprise Suggestions."
Here you go, Mr. Young President,
tape cut.
What's so surprising?
It's nothing.
Everyone,
the surprise project is about to begin.
Here you go,
no, no,
Mr. Young President,
ride on.
Huh?
That's weird.
What's wrong, Mr. Young President?
Where's the reform lever?
Huh?
I don't see it.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Where is it?
That's weird.
Let me reform it quickly.
No, no way.
This one.
Yes, yes,
I'll be right back.
Oh,
I was replaced at that time.
It feels different.
Hmm?
Huh?
Is there a lever here?
What?
What's that sound?
Robot!
What's wrong with Debea?
Did the system of low-level, low-level, and low-level have gone too far?
Ryo-tsu!
Huh?
My long-standing dream is...
It's all gone!
Depp-chan!
Mork's Robot House!
That's it! That's the robot house of the surprise project!
Mork-chan's Robot House!
Yu-san!
What is Debea?
Get out of Earth!
Ehhhhhhhhh!
Jyugem Jyugem
A five-year-old
Shredded
Seedling
Jyugem Jyugem
A five-year-old
Shredded
Seedling
Always sandals
Always scandals
Don't worry
Play with the coonel
Everyday
Tired of it
I rolled it up at the dumpster
and threw it away
Then I threw it away
Siliveness
Romantic
It's just something I had to come up with
From an idiot
To an idiot
With no money
Isn't that nice?
Isn't it?
You should do it however I tell you to
Is that so,
Amazing!
A spark from one side of the boat
The smoke from the head
If I run away
It won't have a back
Isn't a waste of energy
Go to the flower garden
Do it
Vaping typhoon
Let's go!
A workplace
♪ You're ready! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
♪ Jugemu Jugemu ♪
♪ Koko no suriki de kaisari suigyoku ♪
♪ Surikyomatsu Unkyomatsu ♪
♪ Kurai Matsuku ♪
♪ Neru Tokoro ni Sumu Tokoro ♪
♪ Yabura Koji Burakoji ♪
♪ Paiko Paiko Paiko no Shuringa ♪
♪ Shuringan no Gurindai ♪
♪ Gurindai no Onpoko ♪
♪ Ki no Onpoko na no Choukyumei no Chousuke ♪
♪ Kodomo ni Modoreru Candy ♪
I got a candy to bring back to my child!
I can play with it every day without having to work!
Can someone take care of me?
I'm a lively and mischievous boy!
Next time, "Little Ryo-chan"!
See you!
♪ Over there is Kameari ♪
♪ Ah, it must be Kameari ♪
♪ Everyone, come over here ♪
♪ To our... ♪
♪ Town! ♪
Thank you!