"I'm a little lonely"
When you watch TV
Make the room brighter and try to look away
"I'm a little lonely"
I look at the sunset floating in the river
When I kick the pebble, I jump to the shoes
I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I used to do
"It's as it is" I laughed
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I have to win
I have to make a fuss
The cityscape that doesn't change is strangely gentle
From the main street of Tongari-boshi
To Kaishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow is already over
Why is it over?
If I win, I will be happy again
I lost and I realized
Because I'm stupid
Bonus Contest 3
Long-lasting poverty
The collapse of the financial institutions that continue to exist
All the companies in Japan are suffering from business crisis
Yes, I know
It is true
our sales got a rise
We could only do it when the World cup actually took place
The satellite antennaes got popular
But we've lost our goods
However, the reason we are suffering
Is merely the power outage of the government
But the greatest cause is this man
Because he always brings the product
And don't eat the money
He's never going to pay the debt
That man is not a bad guy
And he will be given a bonus!
Can you accept this, gentlemen?
This year, this man will take the bonus!
Prepare yourself, Ryotsu Kankichi!
Yes sir!
Now, we will start the 25th Ryo-tsu Kankichi Bonus Battle.
Wow, that's great.
Kikuchi, did you run away from your wife again?
Yes, this time, my wife is serious.
If I fail to collect the debt...
If I fail again, I will be just a servant for Ryo-san.
Everyone has the same problem.
So, what new weapons have you prepared this year, Bramoya?
Last year, you watched Ryo-san's movements thoroughly in the Peeping Eye operation, right?
Yes.
Before that, you watched Ryo-nabi and...
The new weapon to collect debt against Ryotsu Kankichi, Shaking X!
This year, you have prepared more new weapons than before, right?
Sorry.
I couldn't win against the current situation.
I didn't have time to test and develop new weapons.
What?
Then, this year, I don't have new weapons.
I don't have a chance to do it from the beginning.
Then, how can you collect debt from Ryo-san?
I don't have time to test and develop new weapons.
Don't worry.
I don't have new weapons, but I have a plan.
Plan?
It's called ABCD Enclosure.
ABCD Enclosure?
Yes.
This ABCD will catch up to Ryotsu Kankichi.
I don't understand. It seems to be amazing.
Oh.
Ryotsu Kankichi.
This year, you will not have a single yen left.
You will get a bonus.
Are you sick, senpai?
Shouldn't you go home and rest?
Idiot.
Tomorrow is the bonus day.
If you get a bonus, you have to buy a special machine for the number of units.
You can't sleep.
I see.
The bonus hunting season is coming this year.
There is no bonus hunting season this year.
But what about the people of the shopping street?
There is a special strategy to hide them.
This year, I won't give them even a single yen.
I won't worry about it.
I see.
I didn't imagine I would ustedes from this year to shake into the bank.
It's me.
Oh.
It's Maria.
Ryo-sama, today's your bonus day, right?
Why don't we have dinner together?
I'd like to have your treat.
Sure!
By the way, Ryo-sama.
When are you going to get the bonus?
I've been waiting for you at the library.
Actually, I'm going to deposit it into the bank this year.
To cover up for the debt collection.
Then where are you going?
I'm going to the Sucharaka Bank in front of the station.
I just found the total amount of the bonus.
That's...
Ugh!
- Stop there! - What's wrong, Ryo-sama?
Wait!
You're crazy!
Oh, he got me.
That-that-that...
I'll soon have to kill him for getting the bonus.
Um, I'm under arrest this time, right?
Yeah, of course.
Please.
Okay, good idea.
Wait a minute.
If I arrest him here, I'll have to go to the office.
I'll go to the office now.
Ryo, catch him!
I thought it was definitely a debt-taking machine, but I'll let you off today.
Why? I was trying to steal money.
He's saying that he likes me, the victim.
No way!
There are things that make a country happy, such as gratitude.
I'm really happy today because of the public service worker's bonus payday.
So, it's not a crime.
I won't do it again.
Please.
Please arrest me.
What?
Please.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Stop it, hey!
What are you doing?
I'm going to investigate in the police station from now on.
Please.
Hey, idiot, just go to the verb.
We've been there!
Over there!
I have the bonus!
Don't move there!
It's our job!
Why are they here?
Please quickly go to theas.
I can't go there.
Ready!
What?!
What the hell were you doing?
Huh?!
I'm going to make them go out of control so that I won't sit still.
You're too cowardly to make others stand up!
There's a bonus!
Don't you dare!
I won't let you win!
Please take me with you!
You're not a police officer!
What the hell!
What happened to you?
I think the human set something on me.
How did the human set something on you?
What are you guys doing now?
I was in a low order.
Oh no! I forgot the key I had.
Oh, have you been using the mitad?
If you had, why did you tells us that it's a Wolven?
Let's try to go see the police.
This guy is too loud with us.
I wouldn't dare could die because I tried to get a mitt from him.
How could I maybe get it?
What if it's a spy hired by a gang of money-grabbers?
We'll spy on Ryo-san.
Understood.
And you'll be the one to contact us as soon as you find him.
If that's the case, it's dangerous to be with him.
We must get out of here as soon as possible!
Hey!
You're going to the police, aren't you?
Are you still here?
Wait a minute!
What's going on, Bulba?
I want the key to my desk.
It's in the back of my desk drawer.
Oh, I see, Ryo-san.
So, where should we take it?
Under the bridge at the north of Nagagawa Bridge.
Understood.
Why do we have to hide in a place like this?
Hey, sir.
Shin, keep it down.
Here he comes.
I've been waiting for you.
Oh, you've been waiting for us, huh?
Looks like you're ready to pay the debt.
What?
Why you guys?
It's you, after all!
Take this!
Are you going to do it again?
I won't eat the same thing!
I won't eat it!
Ryo-san, there's no room for you to run away anymore.
I'll be quiet and go to the police station.
Damn it!
Let's get in!
It's midwinter!
Don't be so stubborn!
If you want to be arrested by me, follow me!
I can't believe you're going to jump into the river.
You can run away no matter how hard you try.
My iron-barred ABCD armor!
I can't believe you're going to jump into the river.
I thought I was going to die!
Stop fooling around!
If you're a member of the enemy, you must have some idea!
You're the one who called the enemy earlier!
What do you mean?
You're taking the debt!
How much do you get if you let me go to them?
No, it's not like that!
Then what is it?
I'm the one who's getting chased by the debt!
What?
This is my company.
You're the president?
Yes, I got a bonus.
My name is Ichimonna.
He's not smart.
He's about to go bankrupt due to this accident.
I went to the bank to ask for a loan today, but they refused.
I see.
The employees haven't paid their salaries for three months.
I'm a bad guy.
Why did you think you'd be arrested?
I thought that other people would take over the business.
I thought it would be better if they did.
If the president is arrested, the company will lose its trust and go bankrupt.
I see.
Think about what's going to happen next and act.
I'm sure the president will do well.
I'm often told that I'm not planning well.
President!
Hey, everyone's doing their best.
Keiko was upset earlier, so she dropped out of school.
What did you say?
Hey, Keiko, what's up?
She's my only daughter.
She's in elementary school.
She's in the third grade now, but she's weak.
Oh, wait.
You can't show your daughter this kind of school.
I'm sorry.
Keiko, are you okay?
Dad.
How are you feeling, Keiko?
I just had a little dizziness. I'm fine now.
Oh, really?
Dad, what about that girl?
Huh?
That girl arrested my dad.
Ugh!
What?
To be honest, there's no point in hiding it.
That's right.
Arrested?
Yeah.
Arrested her. She was a member of a fan club.
Do you know about the old sumo wrestler?
Oh, my dad loved sumo.
He said he didn't want to see it now.
I used to like it.
Well, I liked it.
Oh.
Yeah.
That's right. Let's have some snacks.
Hey, snacks.
I don't have any.
What?
When kids come back from school, they have snacks and soba.
No, I can't even eat enough for a meal every day.
When I was a kid, I had snacks.
It's okay.
I don't really want to eat right now.
Plus, you'll buy me a great present for Christmas next time.
Mika's house set.
Oh. Mika's house set.
So you don't have to worry if I can't eat snacks.
Hey, come here.
Hey, it costs tens of thousands to get a full set.
You have debt, don't you?
That's true.
Oh, Mika's house.
Thank you, Mom. I wanted this.
I bought it because Yumi was a good girl.
Come on. Let's go.
I'll buy it for you next Christmas.
Really?
Yeah.
Yay! I hope Christmas comes soon!
You're completely unpredictable.
You'll be the one who gets sad later.
I know that, but...
Hey.
What?
Why are you two so attached to each other?
T-This is the rule of the Taihou fan club.
If we see each other after a long time, we'll stick together and get rid of the sumo.
What?
Hey!
Where's your wife?
She's living with her daughter.
Ouch!
If you go to jail, you'll be left alone, Keiko-chan!
I-I see.
Think about what's going on.
I was hoping that my daughter would be taken care of by her relatives.
Everyone's having a hard time right now.
They need a relative to take care of them.
Besides, it's best for children to live with their parents.
Don't think that you'll ever be taken care of again!
Got it?
Yes.
I won't do it again.
Alright.
So, this is the only problem left.
I'm sure they're trying to get to the station.
What should we do?
That's right!
We have a good idea!
Is this my family's motorcycle shop?
Yeah.
If we use the tools over there, we'll be able to remove it, right?
Got it.
I'll go pick you up in a minute.
Corona
Yes.
What are you talking about? Get us on board!
We can't ride three more people!
Are you going to betray us?
I'm doing this for my boss!
I'm going to become a human being on this machine!
Damn it!
That's right! Become a human being, Ryo-tsu!
You betrayed us with the Bulbaba!
Ryo-sama! Stop making more mistakes!
M-Maria, you too!
I...
It seems the time has finally come to be considerate, Ryo-san.
I see. So Maria and the others were telling you where I was.
Today's a bonus day, right?
Yes, I understand.
I understand. We'll be there soon.
Exactly. Do you understand the horror of the ABCD envelope, Ryo-san?
The ABCD envelope?
A stands for Asato Ai's A.
I'm sorry, Ryo-sama. This is a chance for you to become a human being.
Become a clean body without any impurities, and with me...
I'm not joking!
B stands for Volvo Saigo's B.
I've been hired by the shop.
I've been hired once.
I'll do my best until I'm hired.
And D stands for Honda's Da-no...
D.
That's pretty bold.
And Volvo starts with V, not B!
Don't worry about the details!
Wait. Then who's C?
If it's a name with a C...
It's a name with a C.
Terai?
Nakagawa?
Reiko?
No.
Ohara?
It's not them.
It's not you, is it?
No, it's not me.
It's the C.
It's this guy!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sakonji Tatsunosuke Sanjou!
Where's the C?
If you flip the Tatsunosuke's horn, you'll get it.
How annoying.
Now's your chance to hit your boy again.
I'll show you how to do it.
If that's the case, these non-sold DOKIMEHO goods are all yours, Sakonji-kun.
Thank you very much.
So, you bought them, didn't you?
Huh?
By any chance, you guys also...
I-I didn't get a model gun or anything.
A year's worth of shoujo manga and a bare ticket to an amusement park...
A-a high-class este's invitation...
I knew it!
Ryotsu...
You know this, don't you?
As a mania, you can't miss this opportunity.
Right, Dori-!
Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori!
Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori, Dori!
Almost time.
Our wishes of years are about to come true.
Ugh!
D- damn!
We can't run away with something like this!
S-sorry.
That's right!
Take this!
Take that!
I'm also a card!
This room!
He just fell asleep.
He's weak. Don't make a fuss.
I'm sorry.
I came here to talk about that.
Listen to me.
She's his daughter.
But she's a very mean family.
His company is not doing well.
His salary hasn't been paid for months.
He's suffering from a bad life.
His wife is sick.
His daughter is sick.
But he doesn't have money to buy her medicine.
That's so mean!
He even tried to commit a crime.
Is that true?
Yes, almost.
Is there anyone more unfortunate than him?
No, there isn't.
I've decided.
I'll give you this bonus.
I'll give it all to him.
Is that okay?
A man doesn't have a second word.
You should use it carefully.
Okay.
Do you understand?
Yes, of course.
Ryo!
As expected of you, Ryo.
I was just a little scared.
Ryo, I've got you back.
Being robbed of my model gun is not good.
I'll go get the key.
Save the weak.
It's my way to life.
I'm Ryo.
You're a good boy.
I heard you, Senpai.
I have all the bonuses.
The owner of the town fair is about to go bankrupt.
It's amazing.
It's not easy to do it normally.
I don't have the right to give a bonus to someone else.
You fool.
But...
I just temporarily left it there to fool the debt collector.
He should know that.
I'm going to go and collect it.
I knew it would be like that.
Yes.
Mr. Ryoichi.
Thank you so much for yesterday.
It's not thank you.
Here.
Oh.
Thank you so much.
Don't give me a hand.
It's the bonus I gave you yesterday.
I told you I know.
Yes, of course.
I know what you did.
The bonus is the salary of the employees and the company's debt.
And I gave it to you as a Christmas present for your daughter.
Well, then.
No, my bonus is...
Yes.
Ryoichi's love was not wasted even by a penny.
I used it all.
I told you I know.
That's what I meant.
I'm back.
Oh, Ryoichi's uncle.
Keiko was so happy last night.
Thanks to Ryoichi, Mika-chan's house was changed.
Well...
Yes.
This is a present.
Present!
Th-This is...
My daughter drew it with all her might. Please accept it.
This is my bonus for this year.
Let's play, grandpa!
No, I'm playing with dolls!
The End
If you gather up everyone here
It's like a dream, the final energy
Looking at tomorrow, believing in yesterday
Drawing the universe, standing on the ground
A turtle-like star is spinning, drawing a circle
Isn't that good?
There's no reason to say it!
Damn it! That Honzara guy!
He's not my wife, but he's messing with Kyoko!
I'm getting angry!
In this case, I'll use the technique of the Ryotsu-ryu Migawari to trick him!
Next time, Honzara Migawari!
I'm counting on you!