"When you watch TV, make your room bright and try to look away!"
Come to my place if you're not rich!
I'm not rich, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to my place if you're not rich!
I'm not rich, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds and the red clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Do you understand?
If you understand, come to me quietly!
I'm not rich!
Senpai, are you still here?
What's your favorite bento shop?
Soon!
More coolers, please!
This is the limit!
Senpai said he wanted to ride an open car, so...
I thought it would feel good to hit the wind directly.
However, it's still very hot.
Maybe it was too crowded, lost the tempo and lost electricity.
Well it's not so bad.
Well, that's fine...
But can't you just hurry up?
I'm trying to be a little looser.
Well, is that ok?
I gave up on you.
Of course I'm bought by Yukari-san.
I'm just kidding.
Well, that's fine.
If you flinched, I can take revenge on you instead.
U-U-U Representative Mr.Adётame
This is a very delicious watermelon.
Ok, buy that one instead.
Are you serious, senpai?
Summer is always about watermelon.
Which one should I buy?
Look! A square watermelon!
Everyone must be very happy about this.
Is that so?
Is there something wrong?
I sometimes see a square watermelon.
But the corners are too straight.
I'm worried about the taste.
It's ok. It's a delicious watermelon.
Yeah.
Look.
Don't worry.
I bought this one.
Thanks.
What is this?
Didn't you go to buy everyone's lunch?
You can eat lunch there anytime!
I'll never eat a square watermelon like this again.
I might not like it.
I didn't want to see you.
I want a lunch box.
You guys don't know how wonderful this watermelon is?
It's a square, a square.
It's just disgusting.
It's a little creepy.
It's so bad.
You can't judge by its appearance.
I bought it because its appearance is interesting.
Stop it!
The problem is the contents.
I bought it because its appearance is interesting.
There's no red part.
It's pure white.
You can't judge by its appearance.
The problem is the taste.
It must be delicious watermelon.
Try it.
What?
You eat it?
The shape is different, but the watermelon is watermelon.
It doesn't look like watermelon.
It's...
It's like cucumber.
I see.
That's right.
That's right. We need to change the way we eat.
Let's try putting miso on it.
This is delicious.
This watermelon goes well with miso.
But that's the way to eat cucumber.
This is cucumber after all.
Right.
You were completely fooled, senpai.
I'm so frustrated.
I was fooled by my family when I was a kid and now I'm humiliated.
I'm going to buy a watermelon with everyone's money.
What's wrong with buying a watermelon in the summer?
It's normal for Japanese people to eat watermelon in the summer.
Who decided that?
Some people don't eat watermelon.
I don't accept that kind of guy as a Japanese.
I eat three kinds of watermelon.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
I eat watermelon in the morning when I wake up.
I eat watermelon at night when I see fireworks.
I eat watermelon.
If there is only watermelon in the summer of Japan, I don't need anything else.
Then prove it.
What?
Why don't you just live with watermelon in the summer?
There's no way you can do that.
I'll do it.
If I can do it, I'll get a million yen.
What?
It's fine.
Meiko, it's bad.
If Chief Kohara finds out...
The chief will be out of town from yesterday and will be back in a week.
So it's fine for a week.
What?
Just a week?
However, if you live in the summer of Japan for a week, you can't live in the summer of Japan.
You can eat 300 watermelon when you get older and older.
What?
300?
If you make 300 futur in a week, it'll be 41 times in a day.
Take 8 hours when you're sleeping, and if you look at that, the price per hour will be less than 3 times.
If you can do that, you can pay a million yen.
What do you say?
I'll accept that challenge.
If you can eat 300 watermelon in a week
The Man Who Can Eat Watermelon!
Then I'll put on a surveillance camera so that you don't cheat.
If you get caught in the camera, you're out.
Is it okay to add salt?
The seasoning is okay.
I'll make the drink okay, too.
However, if you eat food other than watermelon, you're out.
Okay, I got it.
The start time is just before 1:00 p.m.
Five, four, three, two, one, start!
I can't do it!
First, it's the right way to eat it!
I'll eat it at once!
Pull it out!
I'll spit out the seeds at once!
Oh, it's dirty.
If you spit out the seeds on a watermelon, you're a pig!
Rusia
I got back from the patrol.
How many did you eat now?
Ten of them.
Five every hour!
This is enough for all five or six of them.
We're going to have to pay that million yen.
Reiko
You really don't understand it yet?
You already ate 80?
If we succeed, we'll get that million yen.
It doesn't cost much, so it's worth two of them.
That's a great way to eat.
This is faster to eat.
I didn't get any seeds.
If you leave it, it'll grow naturally.
That's true, but...
What? You ate 80 of them?
Yeah, there are 220 left.
That's so fast.
I'm done with one, so there are 219 left.
Hey, Ryo-chan.
There's still some red stuff left.
There are still some left.
I can't accept that you finished one.
I know. I'm the one who cares about the details.
Here, Kei-chan. This is your tea.
Thank you, Reiko-san.
Look. I only ate two in an hour.
He's definitely losing his spirit.
Next is the 100th.
I'm getting tired of seeing all this green and black stuff.
I know!
What are you doing, senpai?
I'm changing my mood.
Look! White and red watermelons.
How disgusting.
Thank you!
This is the best 16 soccer ball watermelon.
"Zin" "Gi" "Re" "Chi" "Chu" "Shin" "Ko" "Tei"
All those real words are from Hakkenden Suika
There are more.
Aquarium Watermelon,
The Life-Gender Watermelon,
The Wondering Watermelon,
and the Melon Watermelon
the Ultra- solid Watermelon
"Three Color Glucose Watermelon"
Okay, finally, I have the power to eat!
Well, the inside is just a regular watermelon, right?
You bet.
The End
You ate 30 of them in just a day.
You've lost a lot of speed.
I'll be faster from now on.
Ryo-sama!
I heard you've been eating 300 of them in a week!
Well...
Is there anything I can do for you?
Well, I can't ask you to eat them for me.
I'll have to peel them.
Oh, you're good at cooking!
I made some watermelon-flavored daikon.
You're getting a bit greedy.
Which one would you like?
I'll have one.
But it's not good.
No way!
It's just fruit salad with watermelon.
It's just watermelon with dressing.
How is the watermelon juice?
Yeah, it's surprisingly good.
That's good!
But I'm getting tired of it.
It's watermelon juice.
I'm sorry.
So you only did three of them.
Sorry, I didn't do my job.
That's right.
How about you make some jam?
Watermelon jam?
We need to remove the water from the jam.
So I'm going to use a lot of watermelon.
I'll give it a go, just in case.
I'll count on you.
Make me plenty of it.
Which one?
Want to try it?
Well?
*sniff*
How is it, Ryo-sama?
The sweetness of the watermelon is condensed.
It's hard to eat it as it is.
Come to think of it, I bought bread four days ago.
I put it on that.
If you eat something other than watermelon, you're disqualified.
Huh?
You can only eat jam.
Damn it!
Where is Senpai?
He went out on patrol.
He doesn't like seeing watermelon.
*sniff*
Ryo-san!
A good watermelon is in it.
*screech*
Huh?
I don't care. I want to eat something other than watermelon.
Something other than watermelon...
I'll eat it!
*sniff*
What is this?
What did you say?
It's ramen. Ryo-san ordered it.
What? Me?
Don't you remember?
No way!
*sniff*
Ryo-san!
How are you?
*sniff*
You're trying to eat something other than watermelon unconsciously.
You're almost at your limit.
I have 195 watermelon.
I have 105 left in the next two days.
Ryo-san is the winner.
I can't be careless.
Ryo-san will show his incredible power when he gets paid.
*sniff*
Reiko-san's anxiety has subsided.
Wait...
1 million yen!
For 1 million yen!
He was chased by a threat.
*sniff*
And on the last day, he had one left.
I'll take 1 million yen.
*sniff*
1 million yen!
Wow, Ryo!
He managed to defeat a Tats talll!
*snif*
There's no rest for you.
*sniff*
Please, no more food.
Fine, l'amuse-vous, l'amuse-vous.
*sniff*
Useless.
I know. I'll go to the bank and pay it.
I'll go with you.
It's a waste of money to carry a lot of money.
I'll go patrol.
Hurry up and come back.
How can I use 1 million yen?
I just came back.
What? No one's here?
What's up with Ryo?
Is he slacking again?
If we leave the watermelon here, it'll get wet.
I guess we have to cool the watermelon like this.
Ohara-kun!
Ohara-kun, are you there?
Kojima, it's been a while. What's wrong?
I'll be right back. Please take care of this.
I'm sorry.
Watermelon?
I'm begging you. I'm going to the bathroom!
Did you eat too much watermelon to break your stomach?
It hurts!
What?
You fell asleep?
You're still not coming back?
There's no watermelon!
Where did you go?
What? Is it here?
I'll get ready to eat soon.
It's been a while.
What are you doing?
That's my line.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Give it to me quietly.
Why do I have to give it to you?
Give it to me.
I won't give it to you.
Hurry up and get the watermelon.
I want to go there.
Go on!
Go and bring me watermelon!
Go, go, go!
No, you don't leave it!
I think it's the same thing as the others,
and it's boring.
We need no watermelon.
What?
Take this.
It's the watermelon.
Why are you so surprised?
It didn't have any Elise.
You are not going to skip again, are you?
No, I'm not.
Wait!
Kojima, what's wrong?
Oh, that's right!
That guy took away the thing that was left for you.
Oh, that watermelon?
That's not a watermelon, it's a bomb!
If you give me a shock, it will explode!
The one who is trying to escape with the bomb is the chief of the police in front of the park, Ryotsu Kankichi.
Prepare yourself as soon as you find him.
Also, the bomb that the chief of the police is holding is dangerous to explode if you give it strong stimulus.
We have been careful enough.
He was on his way to the main office after being attacked in an incident.
And then he suddenly wanted to go to the bathroom.
That's right.
I see.
Yes.
When he saw you, he told you not to eat the watermelon.
That's right.
It's a bomb.
Reiko!
Huh?
Hey, Reiko. Are you watching?
Ryo!
I'm going to eat the last watermelon now.
I also prepared a prize so that you wouldn't complain later.
Thank you.
I also prepared a watch.
Where is it?
It's Ryo's senior's room.
I also took a video as evidence so that you wouldn't say that the camera was broken.
Reiko!
You must pay 1 million yen.
I'll enjoy it.
Who is it at this time?
Hello, Ryo?
You can't cut the watermelon.
Reiko, I knew you were watching.
You can't get in the way of the situation.
No, it's not that.
That watermelon is a bomb.
Of course, it's a bomb for you.
The moment I ate the watermelon, 1 million yen flew away.
You're being so ungrateful.
That's not what I meant.
It's a waste to save time.
I'll eat this watermelon.
Ryo!
I'll get rid of these watermelon-filled days.
Here we go!
What?
Secured!
What are you doing?
What's up with you?
What?
I've got you!
You're so annoying!
You're so annoying.
You don't want to pay a million yen?
You're such a rich guy.
Ryozu!
Huh?
Chief!
Ryozu, are you waiting?
Give it to him quietly.
Give it to him quickly.
Are you going to be a good friend of the chief?
What are you talking about?
He's not just a watermelon.
Of course.
If you eat it by 1 p.m., it will cost you 1 million yen.
What are you talking about?
You can't eat it.
I don't know why.
It's the chief.
What are you going to do without eating the watermelon?
It will be broken soon.
That's why you eat watermelon with a knife.
Give it back quickly.
Give it back.
I don't want to eat it.
No way!
Ryozu!
The chief has confirmed it.
Please keep an eye on him.
Stop it!
What's wrong with him?
He is a beach ball.
What's going on?
Damn it!
The police!
I'm going home!
Hey!
Emergency!
The bomb is on the truck with the beach ball.
Where is the再 TRAINED beach ball?
If you say so, there is a beach ball.
Where is it?
What are you doing?
What do you want to do?
Emergency!
Shut up!
Go.
"Cut"
"S-Senpai!"
"Stop it, Yatsu!"
"The last one!"
"Ahh!"
"Huh?"
"What's going on?
"One of them was real!"
"B-by the way,
"we're heading to the watermelon-cutting venue next door."
"Alright, got it!"
"Watermelon-cutting?"
"We're going to cancel it."
"Alright!"
"Watermelon-cutting"
"100 people together, it's watermelon-cutting time!"
"Now then, who will be able to cut the watermelon?"
"Here we go!"
"Ahh!"
"Now then,
"let's start the watermelons-cutting!"
"Stop it!"
"Ahh!"
"It didn't explode."
"That was a relief."
"Now then, to those who didn't cut it,
"let's give them another chance!"
"One, two!"
"Ahh!"
"Oh? There are still some people who haven't cut it yet!"
"Now then, let's have them do their best until they do!"
"Ugh!"
"Ahhh!"
"Ouch!"
"Oh, it's getting bigger, Ryo-tsu!"
"I'm the one who's gonna eat this watermelon!"
"Ahh!"
"What's going on?"
"It's just 1 o'clock right now!"
"Damn it, I didn't make it in time!"
"Ahh!"
"I-It's just a watermelon."
"What's going on?"
"Maybe the culprit tricked us."
"What?"
"What's that about?"
"Did you all get fooled by the culprit's lie and get in my way?"
"I'm sorry, Senpai."
"That can't be helped, right?"
"It can't be helped, but it cost 1 million yen!"
"What are you gonna do about it?"
"Ahh!"
"If it wasn't for the trouble, I would've eaten it!"
"Welcome home!"
"The watermelon's getting cold!"
"Well, if you eat this watermelon in 5 minutes, you'll succeed!"
"You're right!"
"Alright, I'll go get the knife!"
"Oh, there's another watermelon here!"
"It's the one I kept cold in the water outside."
"You brought it here, right, Terai?"
"Eh? This is the watermelon I kept cold."
"What?"
"Just now, I brought it to the water outside because it was on the desk when I went back to the station."
"I-I'm sure mine was here!"
"It's already cold enough!"
"It was already cold enough, so I put it back on the desk!"
"Huh?"
"Then this watermelon..."
"Itadakimasu!"
"Ohh!"
"Ahh!"
"It's 1 million yen..."
"I hate watermelon so much!"
"Ahh!"
Thanks!
"Ahh! Even this summer has come!
Mr. Shitoka
A big, small, big, small, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big,
big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big.
Wow!
Hey! I'm getting smaller!
I thought it was your fault again!
Damn, it's hard to get back to the starting position with this body!
So, what are you going to do, kid?
Eh? I'm a fairy?
Wrong! A small bird is a fairy!
I'm counting on you!
There is a turtle there
Ah, there must be a turtle
There is a turtle
Come on, everyone, to our town
Thank you!