Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look at the sunset that floats on the river
and fly to the corner of Koishi
I kicked the stone and flew to the corner
and asked the head of the taiko who was jogging
"It's still as it is"
He laughed at me
I'm fine somewhere
Even if I get lost, I have money
I'm not angry
The cityscape is mild
The crows are crying
The sound of the ponzu is dull
Yeah!
I'm alone
Can you see it?
From the tapestry of a striped hat
to the taishakuten
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end soon
I lost my happiness again
I'm an idiot who noticed
Yeah!
Finally, the taught me
A handsome boy
I got a job
Huuu
Huh?
Well, what a good day
Why don't you get a job on this day?
Eee
Yeah!
Too early for work, Ryou
Chief
Chief is early for work
What time do you think it is now?
What?
I told you to go to work on time yesterday and the day before yesterday.
No, no, why?
Why is this happening?
Is it because of what I do every day?
Or is it because of the wrong training I have for the chief?
You idiot!
Goodbye, Mr. Ryo.
The Great Strategy
How many times do I have to be late to get home?
If you don't have the guts to work seriously, quit your job.
No way.
When I think of someone like you as my subordinate, I cry out of pity.
You don't cry.
I'm just a role model.
Enough. Get to work now.
Yes.
You're so noisy every day.
Hey, senpai.
What?
That's my seat.
Senpai's seat is over there.
What?
I had to move it.
What's going on?
The chief said that a person who doesn't work doesn't need a desk.
Are you having a problem, Ryo?
No.
Let's get to work.
Hey, Reiko!
What?
I'm working right now.
Don't get in the way of my work.
What do you mean, "working right now"?
You were just scribbling.
What?
Now, get out of my way.
Get out of my way.
I'm home.
I finally got to buy the famous triangle-shaped taiyaki.
Oh.
You did a good job.
I lined up a lot.
Here, chief.
Oh, sorry.
Reiko, too.
Thank you.
Here, Nakagawa.
I'm sorry.
This is my...
Oh, my.
It's mine.
Why don't I have my own taiyaki?
I'm sorry, Ryo.
I forgot.
How dare you take advantage of me!
Stop it, you idiot.
I'm talking about taiyaki.
I don't care, Ryo.
It's fine since everyone's eating.
But I'm the only one who's not eating.
What a child.
No way.
Can you eat before you go to work?
You don't have to make taiyaki for someone like that.
That's a little too much.
Even if you take care of me a little longer...
Shut up.
I'm telling you, "If you can't do your job,
you're making troubles every time."
Why can't you take care of him?
But you've gone.
If I'm gone, no one will be in trouble!
No, I mean, it's better for me to be safe in this escape room!
Do you understand, you big idiot?!
What kind of people are they?
Hey, Ryōki Kanjichi!
Don't get in my way!
Get off the bridge!
I'm free to go anywhere I want!
What kind of people are they?
They're like people wearing clothes in a funeral!
Have a look!
You're so annoying!
Go away!
I'll teach you a lesson!
We're the Shoten Gai Alliance.
We have decided not to sell anything for the last ceremony.
What?
Everyone is in trouble because the sales have dropped.
I can't stand it if they bring the products they usually sell.
I haven't sold anything yet!
Anyway, unless you pay all the money you've been paid,
I won't sell anything.
No way!
I'm back!
Damn, they're too much!
Hey, Honda!
What's wrong?
Mr. Haruna!
What's your problem?
Damn it, Honda!
You stupid dog!
Damn it!
You made fun of me!
Shelima!
Form now and then!
Damn it, I'm stupid!
I'm stupid!
Damn it!
I'm a stupid dog!
*sigh*
*sniff sniff*
Ouch!
What's wrong, Senpai? You suddenly became serious.
I wonder if you've been able to handle what happened yesterday.
Is it because I forgot to buy the taiyaki?
Hmph. It won't last for three days anyway.
Here it is.
All the money you've been paying?
Yeah. I just thought it would be enough for the plastic shop.
Check it out.
Oh, that's true.
Everyone else, please wait a little longer.
I'll pay for the next payday.
I'm really sorry about that.
*sniff*
The patrol results are all good.
If you're a citizen, go straight down this road.
Eh?
Ryo-chan, this case-
Yeah, I did it.
Hey, I got a call.
Thank you.
You're still not going home?
I want to finish this report by today.
*sniff*
Where am I?
Madam!
I'm on patrol at Ryotsu Police Station.
*sniff*
It's been two weeks today.
I wonder what really happened.
Is it because I forgot to buy the taiyaki?
*sniff*
Senior, what really happened?
What?
It seems like the other people here are very serious,
Are you going to get sick?
No, no, that's not it. But what is it?
Well, I have a lot of things.
A lot of things.
A lot of things?
Senpai!
I bought some takoyaki, but you don't eat it!
Oh, you're Honda.
What's wrong? You're so clean.
It's like moving.
It's weird that I clean my room.
No, no, that's not it.
Oh, yeah. Let's do this to Honda.
What? Isn't this your new shirt?
I told you I wanted it.
Is this really okay?
Yeah, I have to organize my luggage a little.
I don't want to make a mess.
What is it?
No, no, it's nothing.
Ohara, I have a question.
Is it true that Ryotsu Kan-Kichi will quit this place?
What?
Is it true that Ohara asked you to take over Ryotsu?
I don't know! I don't know the rumor.
Then what's that all about?
Well, there's that rumor going around in the book.
Even if that's what they say...
Here you are.
Excuse me.
Chief, the signs are gone.
I have something to tell you about Ryotsu.
Just in time.
I wanted to ask you something.
It's said that Ryotsu is leaving the Katsushika office.
What does that mean?
Oh, well, actually, I don't know either.
So I came to the director's office...
Hmm...
It seems that Ryotsu is working very hard here.
I wonder if it has something to do with it.
Well, what do you think?
Hmm...
Oh...
Yes, it's here.
Oh, Mr. Inspector!
Oh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, Ryotsu Kankichi.
Oh, yes.
Certainly, Ryotsu is working hard here.
What is that?
I order the transfer from the Katsushika office to the Ryotsu Kankichi Police Station.
Ryotsu is moving?
Oh!
What?
Ryotsu is moving?
Oh, there was a phone call from the police officer.
It seems that it was decided about half a month ago.
It seems that the power and strength that the people of Ryotsu have lost has stopped in the eyes of the director.
Then maybe Mr. Ryotsu...
Oh, it seems that he was talking about it every day.
So...
Senpai was thinking about various things as a senpai.
But he didn't even keep it a secret from us.
Well, anyway, it's a good thing for the director.
Let's send it out with pleasure.
Yes.
I'm back from patrol.
Is there any problem?
Good job.
Yes.
Hmm.
Hmm?
What?
Oh, no, that's...
Senpai, good news for the director.
Congratulations on your return to the director.
Congratulations, Ryo-chan.
Congratulations, Ryo-san.
Congratulations, Ryo-tsu.
Oh, I see. I got it.
It's not like water. Why didn't you tell me?
Oh, it's hard to say.
I've always been a nuisance at this station and caused everyone trouble.
So when I heard that I was going to be gone, I thought that everyone might be happy.
I thought I wouldn't be happy.
But that's fine.
Originally, everyone was a seed that I planted.
Director Ohara, and everyone else.
It's only a few days before we can be at this Kameari Park.
Please take care of us until then.
Ryo-san, you're going to be gone from the Katsushika office.
I see.
Oh, but don't worry.
I'll pay the bills properly for everyone before I go.
Oh, it's okay, Ryo-san.
Huh?
I talked to everyone, but for the celebration of Ryo-san's return to the director,
I decided to make the debt small.
Huh?
I did a lot of work for Ryo-san, and he's probably the best at Kameari Shoten.
So please give me some money for moving in.
Oh, no. It doesn't have to be that much.
That's fine.
Now, take it.
Yes, sir.
But this and that is...
It's fine. It's fine.
Huh? Where's my desk?
Senpai, please use this.
Oh, is that okay?
Yes. The director gave me permission.
You're only a little while away from being in this Kameari Park.
Please clean up the rest of your work in that seat.
Thank you, Director Ohara.
I'll do my best to work hard.
Hm?
Hmm, I guess this is a more comfortable seat.
Bye!
Ryo-san, I'm sorry about last time.
I bought some Taiyaki from "Sankakuya."
Huh?
If we get forced to leave without eating Taiyaki,
I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
You're too much.
Now, Ryo-san, please try some.
I see.
Well, I'll try speaking my mind.
Mm-mm.
How is it?
Oh, it's very delicious. That's good.
Thank goodness!
Here.
Reiko.
Thank you, Reiko.
Reiko's tea is the best!
Ryotsu.
Yes.
Go to the head office and do your best.
I've been strict with you since the beginning.
But this is for your own good.
I know.
I'm very happy.
I was able to work under a person like you.
It's thanks to you that I'm here now.
I'll never forget your kindness.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Don't say such things.
You're mean, Chief.
I'm not saying anything.
I think so from the bottom of my heart.
Well, fine.
Let's just leave it at that.
Yes.
Thank you.
But, Chief.
You really seem a little relieved.
You're not carrying anything like me.
Don't be silly.
I didn't mean to do that.
You don't have to force yourself, Chief.
If I'm gone, the depot will be peaceful.
Well, that's...
Oh, no.
I can't believe I'm moving.
But the voice of the police officer is very effective.
I just used the voice scrambler to talk, but I was deceived.
Who's going to disappear?
Let's enjoy this state for a while.
I'm going to have fun with this.
Well, I've been looking at Ryotsu lately.
What?
What's wrong with you, Chief?
I'm not sure.
I was just about to be a child by the way, but I suddenly became an adult.
And as I thought about raising this depot, I suddenly felt lonely.
We're the same, too, Chief.
We've been through a lot of bad things, but when I thought there was nothing to be teased about, I somehow...
Ryo-chan is really going to be gone, isn't he?
You mean he's gone?
I've always been involved in a lot of trouble, but now that I think about it, it seems like everyone had fun.
I thought it was normal for you to be in this dressing room.
I can't imagine a dressing room without you.
What are you crying about?
Yo, Komachi, Naoko.
What, you primitive?
What?
Nothing. I was bored.
Oh, a new blue light.
Which one?
The number one man I don't want to marry again?
This time, the Ryotsu-Kankichi Police Station will be moved to the main office.
Then, a souvenir from the Katsushika Library...
What is this?
It's nothing.
You guys...
What?
Even if you're not here...
Wait, what?
I'm not sad.
I'm not sad at all!
That's right.
Go to the main office or wherever you want to go.
You're... you're...
Damn, this is not funny.
This is like I'm a villain.
Huh?
Are you going to drink?
Damn, that's too much.
I can't believe I'm suddenly gone.
Really.
I can't stop you somehow.
You idiot!
What are you talking about?
This is a good point for the main office.
If you think about Ryo's happiness,
it's right to let you go.
I know, but...
I just can't.
I can't do this anymore.
I don't have the bonus money to compensate for it.
I was looking forward to receiving this.
You guys...
Actually about Ryo's matter...
Everyone loves him...
Don't cry!
A grand man like you is disgusting!
Damn it.
How'm I gonna do it?
Again, give me your money!
Give me your money!
"Ryotsu's move is over"
"Ahh, this is not funny"
"This guy and that guy"
"Ryotsu's move is over"
"It can't be helped, it's about time to go to bed"
"Tomorrow, I'll tell the president that"
"Ryotsu's move is over"
"That's it, the plan is over"
"Ahh, this is not funny, damn it"
"I'm going to sleep"
"Before anything happens"
"Let's get this over with"
"Huh, what's going on?"
"W-What is this?"
"Oh, the main character of the day"
"It's the senior's farewell party"
"Everyone who is related to Ryo-chan has gathered"
"W-What?"
"Oh, I see"
"Oh no, it's already a big deal"
"This won't help the plan"
"What should I do?"
"Well, then, it's time to have"
"Ryotsu Kankichi-kun's farewell party"
"First, I'll send this message"
"to my colleague from the dispatch office"
"Nakagawa Keiichi Akimoto Reiko"
"Ryo-chan"
"Senpai"
"Congratulations on your return to the capital"
"Congratulations"
"Ugh, no"
"Actually, I had a dream this morning"
"Huh?"
"I had a dream that Ryo-chan's departure was a lie"
"W-What?"
"If it's true, how happy would I be?"
"No, no, actually, Reiko"
"But that's not the case, right?"
"I'm sure the farewell with Senpai was painful"
"and you had such a dream, right?"
"Ugh..."
"Next, greetings from the members of the shopping street association"
"Next, a gift from the two traffic officers"
"And a farewell song by the subordinate"
"And finally, from Daijirou Ohara, Ryo-chan's direct superior"
"a farewell speech"
"Ryo-chan, it's finally time to say goodbye to you"
"Captain"
"I've been thinking about you since the day we met"
"When you're gone, I feel lonely"
"But I have countless memories with you"
"So I'm fine"
"You should also do your duty... do your duty well"
"Ugh..."
"Well, Chief, actually..."
"So, I'd like to do my best to have a good time with Ryo and Kanki"
"Ryo and Kanki, good job!"
"Good luck!"
"Good luck!
Mr. Ryokan!
Huh?
Ryo-tsu will take care of you this time.
I don't know about that.
But I called you the other day...
I didn't call you.
Ryo-tsu!
You found out?
I'm glad you found out.
I was thinking about what to do without getting caught.
And everyone,
and the Kameari who love me,
and everyone,
don't worry.
I'll be here forever!
Ryo-tsu Kan-kichi will never die!
Huh?
What's going on, everyone?
As you all hoped,
I can stay here forever, right?
I'm glad you're happy, too.
Ryo-tsu!
You rotten genius!
No!
Ryo-tsu!
I'm so happy!
I'm glad you came,
but I definitely need you here at least once.
The Shiroi Hamamikami
"Sandals"
♪ Waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting
for the train, waiting for
the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train, waiting for the train,
waiting for the