Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset floating in the middle of the sea
I kick a pebble and fly to the end
I looked at the taiko player jogging
And they said he was perfectly dressed
The sound of the everyone cheering is so brothy
The townscape keeps changing, it's so nice
Because the shells cry, the fireflies appear
The cocks are running and the veal is so big
People are lying on the grass in the middle of the 잘못ed day
♪ The light of the light of the light ♪
♪ Is the light of the light ♪
Don't eat it while holding it.
No, I can't quit my job at the sushi shop because of this.
Toro.
Yes, big toro.
Toro is no good!
I knew it.
I've been thinking about asking you this for a while.
Why is tuna toro so cheap?
Because it's a small piece of tuna, it's very valuable.
Besides, we only use gold-mine tuna.
Black-mine tuna is no longer available.
I see.
But if you don't know the price, customers will be scared.
The price is decided by the loan, so it can't be helped.
It smells like money.
It's 193 yen!
To make it cheap, you should reduce the average margin.
It's not worth it.
I'll buy it.
It's expensive because it takes a lot of effort.
If the sushi shop goes to catch fish directly, it will be cheap and stable.
That's true, but it's impossible.
No, I can do it.
I think Kanbei has a friend who catches tuna in Amuri.
I'll catch it right away.
Oh, wait a minute.
I've gone.
That's his idea.
Yes, I've been waiting here for so long.
That's right, I've been waiting here for so long.
When do you get here?
I think it's around the house I was talking about.
You're working hard.
You think you can be easy on the superiors.
I bet you can get a little more than that.
It's öyle.
What is it?
So this is Gen-san's ship.
Hemingway?
What is this weird name for a ship?
The last name is "way."
In other words, Hemingway.
It's a name like a bandit.
Is grandpa Gen-san?
Or is he not Gen-san?
What?
What is it?
Don't call me San-chan-go.
Why?
Hemingway is an old man and a sea.
I don't know that.
If you don't know such a famous novel,
remember that the main character of this novel is San-chan-go.
I see.
Anyway, haven't you heard about me from Kanbei?
I have.
I'm a tuna fisherman.
I'm a stupid grandson of Kanbei who came to teach you about the sea.
Stupid is unnecessary.
From now on, I'll teach you the spirit of the man of the sea.
The man of the sea has the scent of salt.
Is that so?
It's more like alcohol than salt.
Yesterday, I put out a ship in the sea of alcohol.
As expected of a master.
You're cool.
I still have something to tell you.
The place where the man of the sea died...
What? Wait a minute.
What?
What's wrong with your face?
Did you fight a shark?
This?
I was killed by a shark named Neko.
That's not cool.
Get on.
Boy, you're new.
Yes.
What's up, Captain San-chan-go?
Why is the super poor man here?
That's my line.
I see.
You're moved again.
It's gross.
No, that's...
It's like a stag.
Shut up.
To become a super rich man,
I need the patience and tenacity of a man of the sea.
My father says so.
I'm just coming to learn from him.
There is no tuna to catch a big man like you.
Shut up.
If you catch a fish with your own power,
you will be able to solve the problem.
What?
You're moved again.
Shut up, super poor man.
If you're with me,
I can't meet you.
I'm going to train on another ship.
San-chan!
Hey, everyone.
Did you bring lunch?
I made three servings.
What are these girls?
They are my girlfriends.
Girlfriend?
They are like old men.
Usually,
beautiful granddaughters make lunch for you, don't they?
The man of the sea is very popular.
Oh,
you're the thin boy San-chan said.
Boy?
Please catch a big tuna.
Please.
Leave it to me.
Can I go with you?
Okay.
I'm going to train.
Boy, take off the rope.
Boy.
Hey, my son.
What?
Is this about me?
Why am I a boy?
And I'm not an idiot.
Old people and the sea have a boy they respect the most.
Is it so?
What's that?
Hurry up, boy!
Yeah, yeah.
San-chan, do your best!
If you catch a big one, please give me a plastic bag!
Is it okay to go to Honborokan like this?
I'm going to be swallowed by the waves before I catch a tuna!
Are you okay?
I feel bad...
You're a coward.
Don't complain.
Boy, don't you have anything?
I don't have anything.
You're a pretty good boy.
Boy, don't you eat?
I'll eat it.
You're a pretty good boy.
San-chan, why are there so many birds over there?
I'll tell you a good story.
When a bird is swarming on the big sea, a legendary fish appears.
It came!
The one I'm chasing after...
It looks like a bad thing, but the engine is a twin turbo.
It's faster than any other ship.
Boy, get ready to go!
It seems that it was hit by a tuna.
How do you know tuna?
It's a long-time fishing rod.
I was watching a fishing expedition.
I thought it would be better to see it with my rod.
All right.
I think it's okay.
Wow!
But...
If the tuna
It was close to 2 meters.
It's not a sea bream.
You don't look happy to catch a big fish like this.
I don't want to catch a small fish.
It's a sea bream.
Sea bream?
It's the owner of the sea.
All right.
What is it?
Isn't it a black tuna?
It's a small fish.
But it's a tuna.
I'll catch it.
What?
It looks like a whale.
Is that a sea bream?
Is it really a sea bream?
What?
It's a sea bream.
But it's a sea bream.
Help me.
I'll catch it.
Damn it!
I will not forgive you.
He's the best rival.
I can't let him go this time.
There are 250 km/h.
It's countless.
How many kilometers do they go?
About 5 million.
That much?
You're going to do that?
You're going to get a lot of debt if you catch one, huh?
Oh, no, one isn't enough.
Boy, I'm going to do this tuna for you.
What? Really?
I'm going to say something cool.
Listen carefully.
I'm not interested in anything other than Aragami.
What do you think?
You're cool, Captain Sanjago!
This is the man of the sea.
Super poor man, I'm sorry, but please push the shutter.
Come on, hurry up.
It's worth 500 people.
Taro is also a top-class product.
It's fresh because it was ordered by Nakagawa and sold.
I heard that you have a debt of 5 million yen.
Hey!
Look!
You can cut it.
Wow!
I'm going to make a profit!
Well, Captain Sanjago's house is around here.
I'm going to make a profit.
What?
Is that Captain Sanjago's house?
Chan-chan, the boy is here.
Huh? Boy? What happened?
You were rich, weren't you?
Well, I've been taking tuna since I was ten years old.
It's really a big deal to have a brandy in one shop.
What a grandpa!
A grandpa!
You don't complain too much about your family.
I don't need a family to be a man of the sea.
I'm a lonely man of the sea.
You say that often, you make girls around here and there,
and they are used to being abused and left.
Did you say that?
Well, you are just like Kanbei.
What do you want from me?
I quit the police and decided to become a fisherman with tuna.
Please let me catch tuna with you.
That's right.
I'm not interested in anything other than Aragami.
Aragami has already gone to Sanriku.
He'll come back next year.
Then let's chase him.
Let's catch Aragami together.
I can't go.
The next day
Shiratori, what are you doing?
Thanks to the picture you took, I'm so moved.
That's why I'm like this now.
Huh?
You're the president of Shiratori Fishing Company?
Hahaha.
You let me know that I'd make money by talking about tuna.
I'll start a fishing company.
How about that, super-poor people?
Would you be my employees?
Hey, kid!
Where is San-chan's super-poor?
Don't you like his house?
Huh?
It's better than my house.
Haha.
Your house is great, but it's not as expensive as that fish farm.
We have a big fish farm that goes to the very end of the earth.
There's always a tuna herd around.
The killer is running around the Sanriku area chasing a prey.
I'm planning to join the helicopter from now on.
Really? Then take us with you.
Oh, do you want to be my staff?
No. I'll sell the tuna I caught to you cheaply.
Captain Sanjago will go too.
No.
Aragami will catch it.
Maybe Aragami is too big to be scared.
That's not true.
Okay, deal.
Then take me with you.
On the boat.
On the boat?
It's like a statue and a ring.
The amount of tuna is not the matter of the boat.
The important thing is to reach the herd quickly.
I'm not impressed.
Anyway.
Let's search the bird mountain.
Look for the bird mountain.
It's faster to search with your eyes than your eyes.
Well, that's true.
Oh, it's working.
All right.
It's working.
It works.
They found a tuna. They're going to catch it.
What are you doing? You're getting let go.
President, we can't. We're pulling the line.
That ship is too fast.
What a bunch of tuna!
This is the first time we've had this many of them.
All right, let's do this!
You're late. We caught all the tuna.
Huh? Who are they?
The ship is sinking because we caught too many.
Hurry up and get them!
We caught 200 of them, so we'll take a few and get 1 billion.
Shiratori, I'll pay you in cash.
I'll pay you after I sell them at Tsukiji.
I'm not kidding. If I don't pay here, I won't sell.
There's no way we can get 1 billion in cash right away.
Help me!
I can't swim!
You're such a hard-working guy.
Here!
It's the ararami!
Captain Sancharo!
What are you doing?
We're going to catch ararami!
I can't.
What a bunch of tuna!
I'll pull the boat!
This is bad. There's not enough rope.
Captain Sancharo!
We have to get them!
But you're still the man of the sea!
Hemingway is crying!
Then you should do it!
What?
You should fight like the sea!
Get them down!
Idiot!
No way!
It's pain in the butt!
You're not going home!
Why so shoot?
Pagoda!
3. A Moose
4. A visceral nols
Yes!
My tribal rival. It was a magnificent battle!
The Sea Man, San-chan finally got Aragami.
I caught a sea urchin!
You fool!
You haven't done anything!
Help me!
I can't swim!
What's a sea urchin without swimming?
Captain Sancha-go was very happy.
He was very happy.
One sea urchin for 100 million yen.
That's a lot of sea urchins.
I just entered the capital.
I have about 20 minutes left.
I'll wait for you.
Of course.
200 sea urchins at once.
By the way,
I've got a story to tell you.
8 years ago,
I was a sea urchin and you were a sea urchin.
What are you talking about?
I'm 8 years old and you're 2 years old.
The transportation fee is all paid by me.
What?
Wait!
Look ahead.
Oh, no.
You...
Oops.
Ouch, it hurts.
Ouch...
You're talking nonsense,
that's why this happened.
It's because you're greedy.
Huh?
Whoa!
A 500 million sea urchin
I'm going to catch you, Shiratoi!
Damn you!
Tuna?!
I can't stop at all!
What's this?!
Tuna!
What's this?
Tuna?
Papa's going to be impressed again!
My 10 billion yen!
Subscribe on our channel for more videos!
I'll do what I want to do
Amazing!
Episode 6: Masamune Uchidaka
Guys, we've brought you into great trouble by now.
Now we're saying our goodbyes to you all!
"What? Do you think you can run away from me that easily?"
"You know how easy it is for me to get lost like this, eh?"
"How about trying to scare me?"
I just wanted to say that.
Hey, wait!
It's a lie!
Next time, "Goodbye, Ryo-san's Great Strategy!"
Please look forward to it!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, to our town ♪
Thank you!