The
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and
try to see the world from afar!
Meow meow
Those who have no money,
come to me!
I'm not here,
but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen
in the meantime
You know, right?
If you know, then shut up and
follow me!
If you know, then follow me!
Reiko is the model Fushihara Noriko's best friend?
Is it the truth?
Yeah,
I often come to Reiko's
apartment to play
Ah!
What?
When a senior knows it,
he will force her to introduce you,
so I kept it a secret!
Oh!
Damn it!
I envy Reiko!
You know!
In exchange,
If you want to be caught, I'd like to exchange my spirit with you!
Hello, hello, everybody-u!
This voice is...
It's been a long time, everyone at the exit!
I feel like you're coming quite often...
Along with some strange inventions!
So, what do you want today?
What a good question, Gorilla-kun!
Today, I brought the greatest invention of the century!
I knew it...
So, this is that invention?
That's right, Gorilla-kun!
This is the hope of mankind!
It's not a novel or a sweet dream!
It's the great invention of the era!
This is a machine for playing Puri-Kura!
No! That's not it!
Then what is it?
This is a machine that can exchange your appearance with the person you want to be!
I see.
A machine for exchanging your appearance?
This is a machine for exchanging your appearance?
No matter where you look, you can only see it as a machine for Puri-Kura!
That's where the amateur Akasaka found it, and he went down the street for 5 minutes!
This is a very wonderful invention!
That's kind of suspicious...
Didn't you bring something similar before?
That's where it is, Gorilla-kun!
I'll use this machine for you!
You're lucky, aren't you?
I refuse.
Why?
This is the first chance to become a human using this historic invention!
No way!
What do you mean, "lucky"?
I mean, you're going to be a test subject!
I'm definitely not going to do it!
Don't say that, Gorilla-kun!
Don't say such a thing!
Shut up!
If you're going to be exchanging your appearance with someone, I can't do it by myself!
That's where it comes in!
You're cooperating with me, aren't you, Nakagawa-kun?
Even I don't want to!
No way!
No matter what, you can't do it!
No matter how much you ask, you can't do it!
That's not the way it works!
My teacher says that he has goodtatitats!
That's what you're supposed to do!
You're here, too?
What?
No, I'm not!
You're here, too?
But I'm glad nothing happened.
What? What are you talking about?
Nothing, nothing.
That's strange.
I'm Reiko.
I'm Ryo-chan.
Huh?
My face is...
What the hell is this?
Why? Why am I Ryo-chan?
Why?
Thank you very much.
Miss!
That's a man's voice.
What's that?
Who are you?
You are a suspicious person.
Protect Miss!
No!
I'm a...
Ouch!
Miss!
Miss Reiko!
What's wrong with Miss?
No!
I'm Reiko!
What nonsense are you talking about?
It's true!
Believe me, Mr. Hirayama!
Why my name?
I know.
You're Mr. Hirayama Shukichi.
This is a song I played at my father's birthday.
Certainly, this is a song that the lady is good at.
But if you practice, anyone can play it.
Please give me a chance.
It's a fruit cake specially made by Reiko.
Oh...
Delicious!
It's exactly the taste of the lady!
Right?
This recipe is unnecessary!
What are you doing?
He stole the recipe.
Hmm...
What's wrong, Hirayama?
What?
What's wrong?
Even if you say that...
You must have watched my dance a lot.
I was always being accompanied by ballet.
Why did you do that?
Hirayama's granddaughter's name is Aya-chan.
What?
She's a fifth grader this year.
Oh!
The pink land cell that my father gave me for Aya-chan's graduation celebration.
I chose that.
Oh!
Only Pinpinmaru-sama and Rei Kojo-sama know that.
What? Are you really Rei Kojo-sama?
Yes, I am.
Why are you dressed like that?
I don't know.
When I woke up this morning, I was like this.
Uh... Uh...
Hirayama...
I'm sorry, Rei Kojo-sama.
I see.
So you've been listening to Ezaki's Puri-kura for a while now.
But he's a tough guy.
He's more than half of his body.
And he's tall.
I'll take him to the dilution lab for now.
Senpai, I made you a stewed skate with fresh folks.
Oh, Honda!
Hey! Hey, Reiko!
Aya-chan, Aya-chan, Aya-chan!
Rei Kojo-sama?!
How come Rei Kojo-sama is in my room?
Oh, I see.
I was Rei Kojo-same now, right?
Oh, you found him and what?
That outfit is...
That's Senpai's shirt!
I just borrowed it.
You just borrowed it?
That's not...
That means Reiko-san and Senpai are...
Maybe that's the relationship?
Finally, she found out.
I found out.
I didn't expect Reiko-san to do this.
You don't like me and Reiko going out?
You're making me feel bad.
Hello, it's Ryo-tsu.
Ryo-chan!
What the hell is going on?
Did you really switch places with Senpai and Reiko-san?
I think so.
Then...
It's Reiko.
Really?
She said it's true.
Really, really, Reiko-san?
Really, really, Reiko-san.
I think Senpai said that we switched places,
and he did whatever he wanted.
And he said he wanted to switch places with Reiko-san yesterday.
Are you telling me I'm lying?
He's definitely Reiko-sama.
He only knew what she didn't know.
It was like that when I was there too.
But Senpai can't get away with that.
No.
No one can trust me while I'm with Ryo-chan.
Yes.
Reiko-san.
Ojou-sama.
It's me.
Wow, you've become a Japanese man.
Come on, Ryo-chan!
Don't play with me like that.
Can you say that to me?
Because...
You really have switched places.
Are you convinced?
No.
It's about Senpai.
It can't be that easy.
Come on, Ejeki!
It seems that the experiment was a great success.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Put it back to normal.
I don't think that's possible.
Why?
You're going to use that machine again.
I'll use it again.
What?
I can put that machine back to normal.
Then I'm going to stay like this forever?
What?
If you do it for half a day, it will naturally go back to normal.
Really?
The words of the genius scientist Korosuke Ezaki are a lie.
That's a lie.
Maybe he was really switching places.
You finally believed in me.
No.
This is like a trick.
Thanks to you, I was able to obtain valuable research data.
I'll be in charge now.
He's still irresponsible.
Today, I have an important meeting with a customer.
I see.
What do you want?
No way in this form.
It's over.
It's fine to cancel now.
I'll go get you a meal.
Ryo-chan?
They're fine?
I wonder if it's okay.
If you do that, it's a special project this time.
But...
Leave it to me.
I'll make sure Reiko does it perfectly.
If you do that...
I've decided.
By the way, the price is...
Price?
That's right.
We're not doing a pre-treatment.
There's a funny thing coming out of it.
My lady.
I got it.
I'll pay you if you can do it.
As expected of Reiko.
You're quick to talk.
This is a contract.
Well, you're on a big boat.
Leave it to me.
Certainly.
It's been replaced.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Perfect.
The other person is a rich lady.
It's a woman officer.
Don't pull over.
Okay.
G.
Are you a foreigner?
I didn't hear you, Reiko.
I can't speak English at all.
It's okay.
Ryo.
Mr. Smith is in Japan 2 of Dai.
I'm not worried because my Japanese is fluent.
What are you talking about?
Anyway, I'm asking you not to be rude.
Leave it to me.
I'll do it perfectly.
I'm very worried.
Miss Reiko.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello, Mr. Smith.
Long time no see.
You're doing too much, Ryo.
I'm very happy to see you.
Me too, Miss Reiko.
Please take care of me today.
I know.
I'll do it.
Well, leave it to Reiko.
Yes, yes.
I'll do it.
Ryo.
Mr. Smith.
Yes, sir.
What?
Are you waiting for someone?
No, I'm not.
Sorry to bother you.
What are you doing?
Please come here.
Well, Mr. Smith.
Reiko is a friend of Noriko Ushibara.
Really?
Do you know Noriko Ushibara?
Well, yes.
Then, you know why she's a friend of Mr. Smith, right?
Yes, of course.
Then, how about America Zadigani?
Look, you're a very loud person.
Well, that's a little...
I see.
You have to do your best, America Zadigani.
I didn't expect you to be a policeman.
I'm very sorry.
I was very suspicious.
I'm sure.
Can I go now?
Yes.
Well, then.
I'm sorry.
Ryo, can you hear me?
We're almost there.
We have to go.
Mr. Smith?
Hey, Ryo!
What are you talking about, Mr. Smith?
Be quiet.
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
No problem.
Hey, Ryo!
Be quiet.
Mr. Smith, we're almost at the destination.
Yes.
We have arrived at the destination.
Oh, beautiful.
Reiko-san, I really hate you.
Well, you're good at this, Su-san.
You're always saying that, right?
By the way, Ryo-chan, is the tea ceremony okay?
I don't think I know that.
Then what should we do?
Don't worry. The opponent is a foreigner.
He doesn't know the ceremony.
That might be true, but...
Leave it to me.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Uh, Reiko-san, is it just...?
What did you say?
I think you're running away from the way I know tea.
Mr. Smith may not know it, but...
Tea has various kinds of flavors, and mine is the all-purpose flavor.
All-purpose flavor?
I hope you understand.
Nice ice cream!
Here we go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Here you go.
Thanks.
What's the matter, Mr. Smith?
Uh, uh, uh, I don't know how to make tea.
Oh, well, I'll make you some tea.
Here you go.
What's wrong, Ryo? What's with that scream?
Mr. Su is so happy to see the tea taste good.
Mr. Su, here you go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, my, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Don't hold back.
Oh, no, really!
Here you go.
Ryo, what's wrong? It's Ryo!
Shut up. It's okay.
Ryo! Hey, Ryo!
Here you go.
Don't hold back.
I'm not holding back!
Just take it.
Oh, I'm at my limit!
Don't hold back!
M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M
I can't!
I'm telling you, I'm at your limit!
You don't have the courage to take it!
Hello? Hello?
What is it?
There seems to be a problem at Room 901.
Oh...
Pardon me.
I'm sorry. Did something happen?
What happened?
Hurry and contact Miss Reiko!
What did you say?
That Mr. Smith is a fake?
He is trying to seduce Miss Reiko by calling me.
Seduce me?
No, no. Not you. Miss Reiko!
Yes, yes, I understand. I'll let you know right away.
Miss Reiko!
Mr. Hirayama!
Oh? What's wrong with Mr. Hirayama?
He said he had some urgent business, so he's coming back.
Oh, really?
If it's planned, he should be in Kabuki Kansho next, but isn't the route different?
The plan has also been changed.
Oh, really?
I've set the goal. I'm going to Okutama and I'm running at 60km/h.
All right.
"Okuyama"
EAGLE
See you're back to normal, Reiko-san.
I didn't know that.
Then, Ryo-chan too?
Huh?
What is this?
Su-san, what are you doing?
You still don't get it?
You've been making me do all this.
Huh?
The another-world collected pomocano
. What's going on, Su-san?
It looks like Senpai's back.
Let's see.
Come on, your family's back!
What's going on?
.
new
Wait up!
Help!
Mr. Momowari?
Senator,
Senpai?
Huh? Reiko, did you go back to normal?
Ryo-chan said so!
Huh?
Ehh!
That's why Susan and the others were surprised.
That guy is a fake Mr. Smith.
He was a kidnapper who was after Reiko-san, senpai.
What?
Is that so?
But, it's a pity to kidnap a senpai.
What a pity to kidnap a senpai.
Right?
But, it was a good time.
I have to thank you, Professor Ezaki.
Oh, by the way, Reiko, what about my apology?
That's not good.
Mr. Smith was a fake.
The contract is invalid.
Ah, that's so...
It was a waste of money, senpai.
Damn!
This is all his fault!
Ezaki!
Well, this experiment was a success.
Why?
Why did Mr. Honda's personality change when he rode a motorbike?
Mr. Kigurashi and Mr. Neruo only get together once every four years.
Why?
Mr. Nakagawa never lent money to Ryo,
but he could easily borrow a tank or a fighter jet.
Why?
I wonder why?
Reiko is a very rich person, but
Why is she working at the power plant?
I wonder why?
How was it?
The Katsushika
Next time, fly!
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Come on everyone
To our town
Yeah
Thank you!