When you're watching TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
It's like someone's calling
After the rain
I walked looking back
I was drawn to the gacha
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I walked on the Akegogai Tile
Only the black part
I saw it
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
I can meet everyone
There is a wall there
There must be a wall there
Come and visit us
Thank you!
Eh?
Meyoto Manzai?
Me and Reyko-san?
No, I can't, my boss
It's a celebration of the annual 30th Anniversary of Katsushika because of the discovery of the Shrine
In contrast, it's the year
I'm glad you did it.
You're a good man.
The manzai of me and the temple at the memorial party is already a standard.
What the hell is that?
Yoshida-san!
It's not true!
Ryo-tsu, who can't stand the natural and unspoken manzai and high-tech drama,
is looking forward to the manzai of the ryo-tsu manzai combination once a year.
There are also many officers who call their parents and siblings from their hometown.
Glasses, glasses.
If it's Kouhaku, I don't want you to say that it's a joke to our Geo, which is the breath of Kobayashi Sachiko.
What's this?
Aren't these stylish glasses, Terai-kun?
No, Ryo-san, this is a bucket.
That's true.
He's breathing perfectly.
That's good.
That was a light warming up.
Sometimes, Ryo-tsu of the tsukkomi shows his bokeh,
and Terai shows his tsukkomi.
Manzai and combination are free to change.
But on the other hand...
Captain!
Sensei!
There are many claims that your manzai is vulgar and vulgar.
I'm saying that I'm ashamed of my dirty jokes, so I'll stop.
Ryo-tsu, I think you're getting into your jokes soon.
I'm not running into dirty jokes because I'm in trouble with my jokes.
I'm going to show off the cold-headed customer's head
at the long-standing feast of the team's hidden greeting.
It's the most effective way to warm up the customer's head when they're cold.
That's why I'm actively introducing dirty jokes to grab the customer's attention.
Please withdraw all complaints.
I, I understand.
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
I didn't know that you were thinking that far.
I can't do this with you anymore.
It's a combination resolution.
That's good.
Don't relax!
A daily conversation is a manzai as it is.
As expected, veterans are different.
You can't buy anything even if you have a lot of money.
That's the customer's laugh.
You two, who don't know how to do it, can't do manzai.
Ryo-chan, I don't think that's the way to say it.
Oh, then you can do manzai.
I'm not saying that you should not appear in Ryo-tsu.
What can they do?
They're making fun of the joke.
They're licking the manzai.
That's not true.
There's no such thing as licking the manzai.
Making people laugh is a wonderful job.
Then, you'll do it for me, right?
Yes.
I see.
I'll register you as a member of the cast.
If you come out, the event will be more beautiful.
If you ruin the name of the station before we built it, we won't pay you.
It seems that we are really going to do manzai.
What? How do you prepare?
I don't know at all.
Um...
To protect the citizens from the crimes that are getting worse every year,
We both need each of you's wisdom and strength.
The other day, this happened.
The director is talking for thirty minutes now.
It's about time to go to work.
I'll really appreciate it.
Leave it to me.
The baseball season has come, hasn't it?
Yes.
I love baseball.
I love to put it on my shoulder and endure the heat.
That's a baseball.
Keiichi and Reiko.
Yes.
You two are next.
Okay.
What should I do, Keiichi? I can't do it.
We can't run away now.
Don't worry.
I'll warm up the audience at the store.
Everyone, we're waiting.
Ryozu and Terai.
Hello.
I'm Ryozu.
I'm Terai.
Nice to meet you.
Anyway, we have to see the results of our practice.
Today is a day of hard work.
So Ryozu is in the team.
Yes.
Do you mean you didn't make him leave?
I did.
I was quiet until now, but there is actually a witness.
A witness?
It's only this talk.
After that, the president rushed to the bathroom with me.
Oh, the president.
That's a lie.
I'm sorry.
The president is the only witness who can speak to my doubts, and he is a suspect.
Ryo, if you say that, you will be at the top of the list again.
Yes.
President.
I'm going to pour this water on each other.
Please enjoy it!
I'm done.
Eh? What are you doing, Kei-chan?
I heard that if you write the word "human" on your palm, you won't get up.
I'll do it too.
India.
What are you going to do if you drink India?
It's a person. A person.
Oh?
Next, it's the two of you.
The heated audience is on the top again.
Ryo-san, you won't scare me, will you?
Good luck!
Next, it's Keiichi and Reiko.
Please welcome them with applause.
Keiichi-san!
Reiko-san!
Hello. I'm Keiichi and...
Reiko.
Kei-chan?
Thank you.
What's up?
Did something interesting happen recently?
Well, you know...
It was fun! It was fun!
What's so fun about it?
It was fun!
Yeah, Ryo-san. You're famous this year.
Well, it's my ability.
Thank you.
Well, this person has something to say.
"Nice to meet you. I am something like this."
"Event producer?"
"I would like you two to participate in the next Asakusa Manzai Contest."
"Contest?"
"Is it a scout?"
"Yes."
"Asakusa Manzai Contest is a young man's new manzai story.
"It is broadcast on TV and if he wants to win, he will be the face of the nation."
"I knew you knew it, Mr. Ryotaro."
"Well, yes."
"We have gathered the participants to commemorate the 30th anniversary of the contest and discover the talent of the new era of manzai."
"But now we have one thing missing."
"But! At this Katsushika-jo, where we visited for the re-writing of the license today, we were able to see the two's manzai by chance."
"I see."
"This is a fateful encounter."
"I cannot say this with a loud voice, but I am the winner."
"I will let you participate."
"Of course."
"Wait a minute, Mr. Ryo."
"Our manzai is just a hobby and it is impossible to do it on TV."
"What?"
"Did you not hear the sound of the crowd earlier?"
"Our manzai has already exceeded the range of a hobby."
"But the audience is almost acquaintances and we are not just receiving the prize."
"What? My manzai is not working?"
"It is so painful."
"I am writing a script of a manzai for the audience."
"So if you are from Alaska, you are from Alaska."
"If you are from Egypt, you are writing a manzai to make the Egyptian audience laugh."
"If you are from Asakusa, you are writing a manzai to make the Egyptian audience laugh."
"I see. I see. So let me go."
"What?"
"You have no talent. Why do you have to do this?"
"Did you receive the dollars from a dúo to every woman who caused the manzai to be popular?"
"I am doing this to get our ass kicked out of this place. That's why."
"Overcome your fate!"
"No way. Mr. Ryo was a bad guy."
"I must say that our com Squeeze is wonderful."
"By the way, what is the prize of this contest?"
"This contest costs about 3 million yen per person."
"3 million yen?"
"You are not the only one who wins this game, Mr. Ryo."
"Yes."
You still have 30 years until the loan you owe me back.
I created a ring for the owner of the farmed parlor!
A ring! What are you going to do!
You bastard!
I'm sorry!
I'll fix it, Ryo.
Good.
Then we'll hear this story later...
Thank you very much!
Thanks to you, I failed so badly.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the second time.
No, no, no.
It was a big success.
It's not like that.
If you weren't there, I could have done better.
I'm so frustrated because I practiced so much.
These guys are the first stage today.
Please forgive me.
It's an amateur game.
I can't believe I'm leaving so many people on the first stage.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ryochi and Mr. Terai.
Mr. Kenichi and Mr. Reiko.
Please participate in the contest.
What?
I'm going to give you a series of manzai.
The contest was originally an unexpected story.
Please cheer up, Mr. Ryo.
Shut up!
If you said OK at that time,
Nakagawa and Reiko would have had a chance.
I refuse.
We're not manzai.
You can't stand out in the contest.
What a waste of money to say that.
It's 3 million yen.
The prize money is 3 million yen.
Mr. Ryo.
Eh?
I can't say it because it's wasteful to say that to two great manzai.
Darn it.
Disappointed as if he drew the toes of a little finger from the shoes.
It would be nice if a senior was crowned for us.
Yes.
That was the story at the beginning.
If you can do that, I don't expect anything from you.
Ryo, that producer is a mess.
The contest is banned.
What?
He worked so hard on the manzai.
Poor guy.
Don't worry.
I'll raise you to be great manzai artists by the contest.
What?
Nakagawa, Reiko, I'll teach you all of me.
I'll teach you all of me.
Wait a minute, Ryo.
Wait until the sun rises.
Heaven will not let you go.
I went to the theater with my mother.
Enomoto Kenichi, Furukawa Roppa, Kamigata Manzai's Entatsu Achako.
We are going to the contest.
No, I can't do it.
What should I do, Reiko?
I'm afraid if you refuse.
I don't know what kind of manzai you are.
I don't know if you will do it for me.
Please.
I love manzai so much.
And I love Asakusa.
I'm sorry.
Reiko, Nakagawa.
Ryo.
I get it.
This time.
Do you?
Thank you very much.
Okay.
I can win these two.
And I will get the prize money.
Listen.
I'll be your teacher.
Don't go against what the teacher said.
If I say I'm black, all the posts and bananas are black.
Got it?
Y-Yes.
I don't like this kind of outfit.
Me too.
There's only a week left until the contest.
We're going to do practical training here.
I see.
First, I'll show you my example.
Yes.
Stretch your arms and push the chicken.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Try it.
I feel embarrassed.
Try it in a less crowded place, Senpai.
Call me teacher.
Teacher?
If you're embarrassed, you can't make people laugh.
Do it now.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Make a small voice.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Make a big voice.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Raise your face.
Don't forget to smile.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Keep the rhythm.
Yes, yes.
Next is the chicken running.
Why is that?
Let's go.
Welcome home.
How is it?
You're a little more confident, aren't you?
Then I'll go to the patron, so I'll leave it to you.
No.
The daily life of laughter is a series of jokes and comments.
Well, first of all, let's drink tea and have a drink.
First, boil water in a kettle.
What are you doing watching a joke?
Yes, that was a joke.
No, it's boring.
You can laugh at one of your partner's jokes.
If your partner is drunk, you can't help but say it.
Yes.
Then I'll do it from the beginning.
First, boil water in a kettle.
Oh, there's no lid in this kettle.
Then this is a bucket.
Oh, that's good, Reiko.
When did you learn to ride a ride?
Oh, is this okay?
That's the spirit.
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
Yes.
Then put the tea in the kettle.
That's a kettle.
Oh, no.
I jumped into it even though I wasn't dumb.
Nakagawa, I was so impatient that I thought I was late for Reiko.
Focus on your partner's words.
Focus on your actions.
Yes.
Oh, no.
What's wrong, Terai?
Terai.
When did you become so big?
That's a light bulb.
It's not the time to be stupid.
It's the third time.
You're a kisser, Terai.
Stop it.
All right, let's go.
Yes.
Let's go Ikezu.
The chance of becoming stupid is rolling.
Yes.
It's continue.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
I'm the new meoto old man, Deka, who'd like to meet you.
What?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Then, I won't let you change your bag!
You can't change it.
You have to change it.
Well then, excuse me.
Oh, it's a nice bag.
Which one is your present?
I got this from someone.
I see, it's a present.
How can you be convinced?
I got it from someone, but you didn't tell me.
You didn't wait for me, did you?
That's not true.
Well then, excuse me. I'll take a look at the contents of your bag.
That's a little...
Then, that's enough.
You give up too quickly.
I'm pushing you here on purpose.
Pushing, pushing.
That's not pushing.
Oh, pushing, pushing.
So, what are you going to do if I push you?
But, I heard that it's not pushing.
So, do it stronger.
Stronger?
Push...
So, I told you not to push.
I'm sorry for killing a snake raw.
Do it quickly if you can't catch it.
You're really rich.
So, I'll get the culprit, right?
Now, arrest him.
Okay.
Oh, no, I forgot the camera.
Then, I can't arrest him.
Please wait a moment.
It's here.
Then, let's arrest the fast one.
It's arrest.
A octopus.
How can I arrest you with this?
So, you have to grab it with your chest.
You can't arrest me with this!
Bring it here quickly!
Okay!
Hey, don't go!
It's okay. I'll be back soon.
I've brought it!
So, what are you going to do with the squid?
You have to grab it with your chest.
Please, grab it quickly!
Oh!
Somehow my body became lighter and the words of the tsukkomi came out naturally from the bottom of my heart.
It was a strange feeling.
I was able to blurt out the words one by one so that the fog in front of me would clear up.
You have to endure these five days of training well.
And you have successfully learned the tsukkomi.
Master, this is...
I have been warming my eyes for many years for the sake of my life partner.
This is the script of the crime.
I don't think I'll get to use it for a while, so I'll submit it to you.
What?
You're giving us such an important thing?
Here, there are plenty of stories that Asakusa's customers will like.
Please give this guy his life in my place.
Master...
I'm sorry to trouble you, but I can't take this script.
Reiko-san!
Why are you saying that without even reading the script?
If we did it, it would be a temporary Asakusa.
I think it would only be a temporary Manzai.
That's why I want to think about the script ourselves.
I'm sorry to say this selfishly.
If you're so determined, then try it yourself.
But the contest is the day after tomorrow.
There's no time left.
There are still two days.
You two will make our Manzai.
I understand.
Yeah.
The excellent Manzai Combi must have its own unique personality.
Find out your own personality.
Our own personality?
I'm sure we'll find it.
Nakagawa-kun is slow.
He's really slow.
Maybe he's scared.
They will surely come.
I believe in their comedian spirit.
But...
That's the police officer.
Really?
They're coming?
I'm scared.
Spirit of the league
What's that outfit?
They've found our unique trait.
We were aware that we are the richest team in the world
and also made it happen to be a magical pair.
Huh?
I will show my unique trait to the customers in Asakusa!
All for our teacher!
Master...
Ah...
No, I'll just buy half a can of the customer's.
My 3 million yen...
Ryo, you don't want me to go to the venue, do you?
Let's watch TV together at the exit.
Gakushin, you watch over them inside.
I'll go home with a pachinko.
What? The winner?
The two of them are the best.
I wish I could watch it too.
Here's the prize money.
This is for me?
Thank you for letting me know.
Now you can go back to the theater without worry.
Wow, it's so big on the newspaper.
I'm glad, Ryo.
All my wishes came true.
What kind of show did the two of them do?
What kind of show?
I just remembered.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why you're laughing.
Good morning.
Please stop.
Please don't make me laugh.
When I watched your show on TV yesterday,
I laughed too much and my stomach was twisted.
I almost called an ambulance.
Did you watch their show too?
Why didn't I watch it, Ryo?
What?
Ryo, you didn't watch it?
Nishi-Shinjuku?
Hektopascal?
Will you peel the onion?
What?
What happened in Nishi-Shinjuku?
What happened?
Nakagawa, Renko, please show me the show.
But...
I'm begging you.
I'll do it for 3 million yen.
What?
I can't die if I don't do it.
What kind of show did you do?
Please show me the show.
Show it to me!
♪ Awaken! ♪
♪ A clock! ♪
♪ Throw it away! ♪
♪ My little finger, ai-ta-ta-ta-ta. ♪
♪ If you draw your eyebrows for now, ♪
♪ I'll take you to the station. ♪
♪ DASH! DASH! DASH! ♪
♪ The main train, ♪
♪ I take a nap on my dad's back. ♪
♪ This week too, do your best. ♪
♪ The swing is too far away. ♪
♪ I'm holding the bucket in one hand, but ♪
♪ it's steaming hot with the heat of the hot soup ♪
♪ The annoyance of the continuous work ♪
♪ is solved by the annoyance and the refreshingness ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ When the hot shower turns blue ♪
♪ I'm fine with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating, Monday ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ My undulating heart is beating ♪
Thank you for watching!