VGP
When you watch TV
Make sure your room is bright and far away
The sunset of the stream
I see in my mind
When I kicked the stone, it flew to the shoe
I wonder if it's going to be a joke
I laughed at the same time
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I'm a Katsushika Kameari
The cityscape that doesn't change even a single yawn is strangely kind
From the waterway of Tongari Boshi
The sun sets to Kaishakuten
Tomorrow
I'm going to
end this way
I'm a Katsushika Kameari
I'm happy again
I lost it and realized
I'm such an idiot
To the world that passes by, Kaki Genki
What?
It's not what?
It's today's promise, right?
Uguisuka?
What?
You idiot
Uguisuka?
It's today
It can't be that you forgot
I already paid for it
I don't forget
I made it
I see
I'll come pick it up in the evening
Hey
It's a mess
I shouldn't be doing this
Uguisuka?
It's a mess
It's raining in full swing.
Senpai, what are you doing?
I'm bending the bamboo pole.
If you look at it, you'll understand.
I'm asking you what you're doing with the bamboo pole.
I'm making a basket for the Uguis.
I forgot about it last month when my father at the bird's nest asked me to.
A bird's nest?
It's that cage, right?
You idiot!
The one I'm trying to make is not that cheap!
It's this!
This?
I made it with a friend before, but my father at the bird's nest liked it very much.
He promised to make ten of them for 500,000 yen.
What? That much?
That's 50,000 yen each.
This one needs a lot of skill.
Even 50,000 yen is cheap.
Where? I just need to heat it and bend the bamboo pole, right?
Then try it!
Sure. It's easy.
I'll show you.
Look at this. It's not as easy as it looks.
Move away!
I have to make nine more by evening.
But I've been bending it one by one like this.
I won't make it by evening.
That's right.
That's enough.
I made ten Uguis.
It's a wonderful idea.
It's dangerous, senpai.
I'm watching you. It'll be fine.
You're going to say that and take your eyes off me right away.
That's right.
Shut up, you guys. You don't have to say "it's okay".
Senpai!
That was a quick fire.
That's why you don't have to pour water on me.
It's your choice.
Senpai, this place is dangerous.
Why don't you use my rest room?
You're so noisy.
What's up with you?
Hey, Reiko!
What now?
Put this away.
It stinks!
Why does Ryo-chan's clothes stink so much?
Senpai has worn that uniform for about ten years.
That's why I can't be popular with girls.
That's enough.
Isn't it?
Don't you smell something?
Senpai!
What are you doing?
We're going to get burnt.
Oh, really?
But, Reiko.
How much are these newspapers and magazines worth?
I was going to get a new one, but I forgot.
I forgot to put them here.
It's not just my fault.
Now, let's get back to work.
W-w-wait a minute, senpai.
What's so noisy?
There's a lot of paper in this room, so it's dangerous.
Can you clean the office?
I cleaned the rest room.
Sorry, Kenji.
Hey, Ryo.
Are you going to stay like that forever?
It's a snowy day.
Nobody's coming.
Besides, I told you to do it here.
I told you to do it here.
I'm sure it's Reiko.
That's true, but...
Hey, I'm here to deliver the newspaper.
Hey, don't open it suddenly.
It's cold, isn't it?
Ouch!
Ryo, be careful.
The hot water in the can won't burn on a day like this.
It's cold, so please close it quickly.
Yes, sir.
I'll bring it right away.
What?
I ordered one can, but...
No, that's not...
Oh, this was one.
I'm sorry.
I brought seven cans.
I see.
Then, leave them.
They'll be needed anyway.
I'll leave them.
I'm sorry.
Besides, it's our 10th anniversary,
so we'll only have two cans left.
Th-thank you very much.
See you later!
Are you putting it here?
Because Ryo is using fire over there.
It's safer over here.
That's right.
But if you make a mistake,
it'll burn in an instant.
Ryo!
I'll put it in the restroom,
but don't use fire over here!
I know!
Sir Ryoji!
Come in!
Oh, it's Mr. Honda!
I'm busy right now.
He's running away.
Can you please take care of my luggage?
I know you're in a hurry.
It'll be a big problem if you get hurt.
Yes, I don't mind.
I see, then...
I'll be in a hurry!
I-it can't be...
Gasoline?
That's right, but...
Honda, hurry up and put it out!
It's cold!
Mr. Honda!
The gasoline inside will burn
around the candle light.
I'll do it!
Anyway, I'm cold.
I'm sorry.
I'll bring the rest soon.
What?
Is that all you have?
Yes.
I sold it at the stand there,
so I finally got it back.
What?
A small fuel shop.
Gasoline burns like an explosion,
unlike oil.
If I make a mistake and cause a fire,
I'll be in trouble.
Ryo!
Don't use fire in the restroom!
I know.
I know you.
I finally got the second one.
I'm going to make more and more.
What?
What was that?
It was an accident.
Are you all right?
Sorry,
my tire slipped.
The road surface is starting to freeze.
It's starting to get hot.
Yes, that's all we need.
Excuse me, sir.
I have a request.
What is it?
Could you take care of the
It's dangerous to carry it in this snow.
Yes, it's fine.
What kind of luggage is it?
It's dynamite.
Great.
Good to know.
Is it a box?
No, there are 144 boxes.
Hurry up and close it.
I'm cold.
Please be careful, sir.
It's dynamite.
It's okay if the box doesn't burn.
It's not okay.
Then if the snow stops I'll come and get it.
That's a lot of work.
The restrooms are full of old newspapers, soy oil, gasoline, and dynamite.
What if we get caught in the fire?
Ryo, you have to be careful of the fire!
I know, I'm telling you!
The surroundings are so noisy, I can't concentrate.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
Would you mind stopping the car at the back of this bus stop?
If we keep going like this, we'll get caught in the snow.
We really can't go, but it can't be helped.
Good. We can't leave it in a place where it's not good.
Is that car loaded with something?
Yes, it's a tank lorry full of natural gas.
I see.
Hey, everyone, get going!
It's not just one car!
Soy oil, gasoline, and dynamite?
And a tank lorry full of natural gas.
If we really get caught in the fire...
I don't want to imagine it!
Reiko, calm down!
I'm leaving today!
What?
Don't stop me, Kecchan!
A-a mountain of matches!
What is this?
It's an old match that we played with when we thought we'd have a place to sleep.
It's just a box, isn't it?
That's what Ryo-chan said.
It's fine. It's a collection because it's got all the stuff in it.
But there's also a box that's in the back.
In the back?
Are you talking about the rest room full of dynamite?
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing up there?
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a!
What the hell is that?
It's supposed to make a noise!
It's a fire!
Next Episode
As expected, Major Bakunin!
Alright, I can see you!
The one in front of the park is there!
Now it's time to end this one with a warm welcome!
Have at it!
Raja!
Whoa!
Yaaaayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy!
A-A natuurlijk!
So, Shion?
I-It's Niyao?
Hahaha!
What do you say you visit me for?
This is a very nice greeting.
It's been a while since I saw you guys in front of the park.
I thought my heart was going to stop.
Come to think of it, what's up with Ryotsu?
He's always so quiet, but he's so quiet today.
What are you doing?
Shut up! I'm busy. I'm going to talk to him.
You!
No one has ever listened to me and lived for free!
I-if I were to be fired...
Ah! Stop it, Captain Bakuryuu!
We'll apologize for Ryotsu's offense!
You two...
Don't you dare talk about Ryotsu.
Y-yes, sir!
Please, I beg you.
Okay.
Thank you, Captain Bakuryuu!
You're not supposed to do that.
And then...
I'm just a light.
Don't scare me, Captain!
But if you make this bigger, it'll be a firecracker.
Too bad, it's out of gas.
What are you doing here, Captain Bakuryuu?
I was planning to go to the military training center,
but because of the storm, the helicopter flight is in danger.
So this is the worst situation.
You're not telling me you're going to ask for a military helicopter, are you?
I'm not talking about that.
I'm just asking for a weapon or ammunition.
Hey, UZI!
I-I can't believe it...
I'm grateful for everyone's help before the show.
Well, goodbye!
See you later, Captain Bakuryuu.
What should we do?
I don't know what to do.
There are so many weapons and ammunition on the roof.
The tankload of gas-filled tanks surrounding us.
Dynamite, soaps, and gas are all over the break room.
And Captain Bakuryuu's weapon is...
I can't take this anymore!
U-um...
Kei, let's leave this place together!
Reiko, calm down.
If we leave this place, Senpai will be left here alone.
If we leave Senpai here, what will happen?
Then the hundreds of meters will be blown away.
Kei, let's stop making Ryo's birdcage.
Right now, the only thing Senpai can think about is a 500,000 yen birdcage.
When the money is together, do you think Senpai will listen to us?
Right, I can't tell anything to Ryo right now.
But...
Don't let it all fall apart, Reiko-san.
We need to get this right here.
Be careful.
I can't protect peace.
I understand, Kei.
Then, I'll bring you some tea.
Reiko!
It smells like fire!
Kei, something's burning!
What?
Ah!
Reiko, the fire extinguisher!
Where? Where? Where?
It's suddenly getting cold.
Ah! My clothes!
I'm sorry. It's all wet.
And the stove.
If it's like this, I can't use it anymore.
I'll bring you a new one.
Hurry up.
Well, well.
What do you want?
I'll go get the clothes, so Kei, go get the stove.
I understand.
But it's dangerous for two people to leave the fire station at once.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
Konnichiwa!
Maria!
Hello!
What's wrong?
I came to clean up the traffic up to here, but it snowed and blocked the road, so I came.
Reiko!
Isn't it just right?
That's right!
Maria, I have a favor to ask you.
I'm sorry, but...
While we're out for a while,
would you keep an eye on Ryo-chan so that she doesn't do anything dangerous?
What?
Only Ryo-sama?
Yes!
I'm happy to!
Maria, take care of the rest.
Yes.
Let's hurry, Kei-chan.
The next day.
Ryo-ohashi!
worried!
werd
I'm sorry I'm late!
I'm very sorry,εν
Oh, right! I brought something really nice!
I'm sure Ryo-sama will be happy too!
Ta-da! A firework!
Winter fireworks are very romantic, right?
Yeah.
Go ahead and do it.
Okay!
Is the exhaust pipe okay?
We can't see the fire truck or the Batcar, so I think it's okay.
I'm worried that I can't see it with my own eyes.
It's safe, Reiko-san!
That's great! Maria-chan was watching Ryo-chan!
Let's go!
Ta-da!
Ryo-sama, look!
Isn't it wonderful?
Isn't it?
Wow!
No, no, no!
Maria-chan, stop!
Why are you doing fireworks in the room?
Because it's cold outside.
Maria-chan, look carefully in the room.
Reiko-san, what is this?
By the way, there are fireworks in the break room and on the roof.
What?
Isn't it difficult to do fireworks?
That's right! That's why I stopped it!
Yes!
Yes! This is a trabajo before the play!
Oh, I'm coming right up!
Senpai, call!
Hmm? What?
Hello?
Oh, is it Kotori?
What?!
So, today is this ceaseless day, right?
I can't just go to take it.
So, I'm gonna go to take it tomorrow!
Hey!!
Bye!
Oh.
Oh. Damn!
Stop it, stop it!
Oh, me, darn it!
-That's a relief. -I guess.
-Doesn't it smell strange? -It doesn't smell like fireworks.
I don't think so, but...
-It must be because you turned off the candle. -I'm sure it is.
Ryo, have you stopped making bird cages?
Shut up! Damn it! I made them myself.
Oh, how scary. You're really a god of the birds.
-Let's take a nap. -Sure. I'll make some tea.
-I'll help you. -I'll help you.
-I'll help you. -I'm already feeling the heat.
Oh, no! I forgot to turn off the candle.
Oh, no! The fire is gone! The gas is leaking!
-The fan! -It can't be!
The fan is leaking!
-What should we do? -We have to open the window.
Let's leave this place quietly.
Thank you for your hard work.
Why are you here on a snowy day? You're so serious.
It's just a job. Why are you here naked?
Well, it's a lot of things.
Ryo, doesn't it smell?
Yeah. Maria was playing with fireworks here a while ago. I was lighting candles.
Oh, I see.
Oh, Ryo, I can do that too.
What? What?
It's something Ryo used to do at the year-end party.
I can do it now that I've practiced.
Oh, that? Okay, okay, I'll do it. I'll watch.
I'm glad Ryo turned off the fire.
If it was on, it would have been a big deal.
I should warn you not to use the fire until the gas completely goes out.
Senpai!
Here we go, Ryo!
All right! Light the fire with your fart!
Terai, your fart is too strong.
I'm sorry.
This is the worst situation.
Why did it become like this?
kg
♪ Fly high and far ♩
♪ The power is greater than anything ♩
♪ Everyone gather here ♩
♪ The last energy like a dream ♩
♪ Look at tomorrow, believe in yesterday ♩
♪ Draw the universe, stand on the ground ♩
♪ Even the stars with a mask will follow ♩
♪ This is good, isn't it? ♩
♪ There's no good reason, is there? ♩
What?
A cell discovered that can't prevent any kind of disease from my body, right?
So if I can create a medicine that works for anything,
it can be worked on.
So I'm the treasure of the world
Next time, Ryotsu GPX
Thanks for watching