SUBTITLES BY: MDM
At the moment I look inside,
An imaginary sun is shining
When I kick a petal,
Even my shoes fly.
From the last of my crowned hat
To your anyhow
The sun is setting
This tomorrow is already ended
'Cause I've lost my happiness and once again
Because I'm an idiot
Hanazaka Ryo
Ryo-tsuu!
What's the matter, chief?
What the hell is this?
Huh? Isn't this the test paper I submitted yesterday?
I can't feel any regret at all.
Thanks to you, I've been warned by the chief.
Is that so? I thought you were really good at it.
Where in this ridiculous world are you good at?
You're just as dirty as ever.
Write your own name in kanji.
Shut up! Thank you very much.
Well, I've been working in Kameari, Katsushikaku, for 10 years.
I've been working without pay,
and I've been secretly taking a patrol car.
I've broken three road traffic laws,
and I've been forced to do it.
My colleague Nakagawa is going to go to the sea,
so I'm trying to stop him.
I-I didn't say that!
I'll be busy with my work from now on,
and I'll never do such a thing again, so forgive me.
No, I mean, forgive me for being so rude.
See? I'm good, right?
I don't think you're really regretting it.
I'll make it worse from the second one.
Well,
I'll write down the following.
This one too.
Who's going to write the following in the police station?
The chief is so angry that he's getting bored.
There's no way I can do that.
The chief has a narrow mind
that can't understand humor.
Okay, we're done.
What do you think of this popular street model?
Oh, it's wooden!
Huh?
Idiot!
It's not the time to make this during my work!
I've rewritten the entire death certificate!
Damn it, chief.
It took me a whole day to rewrite the death certificate.
Huh?
What's that?
100,000 yen.
If I didn't buy this old man's book,
I could've bought the wooden one.
Chief!
R-Ryotsu!
What are you doing?
Did you rewrite the death certificate?
No, I didn't.
I finished it.
Chief, what do you think of toys?
Huh?
What?
You're going to buy 100,000 yen for this?
What a crappy business!
You think so too, right?
Actually,
it's Daesuke's birthday the day after tomorrow.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, that's right.
So I got a wooden stick as a present,
but I don't have it.
I didn't expect you to pay 100,000 yen.
Hmm, that's a good thing.
It's a chance to rewrite the death certificate.
How much is the budget, chief?
Huh?
About 30,000 yen.
I got it!
I'll accept that 30,000 yen.
What?
I'll make a completely different,
no, a more splendid wooden stick.
After all, I'm a master of toy making.
Oh, you are?
No, it's not a bad thing to ask you.
I'll give up on it and make another one.
Chief!
You don't care about Daesuke's future, do you?
What do you mean?
Humans,
from 1 to 3 years old,
are much more dependent on education.
Are you sure, chief?
Education is good for your body.
For example,
you say classical music is good for your senses.
Well, that's true.
That's true for toys.
Plastic toys are good for the body,
but they are not good for children.
Hmm, I see.
Toys are made of wood.
The gentle touch of the wood
affects the mind.
You can't say that.
Daesuke's future depends on this stick.
I got it, Ryotsu.
I'll take it for 30,000 yen.
W-what?
You don't call people to ask for things.
You usually ask for three.
I-I see.
I'll take it for 30,000 yen, Ryotsu.
I can't hear you.
I'm sorry for Daesuke,
I-I'm sorry.
Please,
I'll take it this way, Ryotsu.
You should ask for it from the beginning.
Right, Ohara?
O-Ohara?
What's wrong with your face?
Are you going to quit?
No, I'm sorry.
Please, Ryotsu.
All right.
I'll go get the materials.
I think I made the wrong choice.
I wonder if he's doing it right.
Hmm...
Ryotsu, are you working on it?
Ah!
Oh.
I-I'm sorry, Ryotsu.
How are you?
I'm good.
I-I see.
You can do it.
Chief, wouldn't it be bad to make a nice kitchen for Daisuke no matter how much he loves it?
That's true.
Ryotsu! No, Mr. Ryotsu!
There is a public service, so I don't think you can make it in the break room.
I see. Then please take all the things here to the break room, Mr. Ohara.
What did you say?
I remembered something. Go home.
Oh, wait! I understand! I'll take it, so please don't go home, Mr. Ryotsu!
Call me "master"!
Please don't go home, Mr. Ryotsu!
I can't help it. Then please take me home, Mr. Ohara.
By the way, it's lunchtime soon. I want to eat eel.
If you don't let me eat it, I'll go home.
Nakagawa, please order eel.
Yes.
It's the eel from Izue, Ueno.
It's too far away. It doesn't matter which one you eat.
It doesn't matter.
Goodbye.
Wait! I'll order it.
It was delicious! I just wanted to take it by car.
Good job! If it's done, I won't leave it for free.
It seems to be crowded.
It's for children, so it's dangerous if the corners are sharp.
As expected. No matter what you say, you don't miss your work.
Teacher, your tea is ready.
Please enjoy it until it cools down.
Yes.
Do you want to rub my shoulders?
Ryotsu!
Jiro!
No, I meant Ryofu.
It must be too hot. I'll go home.
Teacher, please let me rub your shoulders.
I'm sorry.
You've completely reversed your position.
I'm sure Senpai is more advantageous this time.
Oh, it's done.
Wow, it's great.
It looks more luxurious than the wooden platter in the toy shop.
As expected of Ryo-chan.
Daisuke-kun will be happy.
Sir, I also installed the bonus function.
Bonus function?
Please try to climb.
Like this?
I hear a sound of a hedgehog.
Please pull the horn.
Wonderful.
I can hear a real horse.
It will be a good education.
It will sell for 100,000 yen.
It still has a great function.
Sir, please try to knock down the wooden platter.
Now, let's do our best to enter the fourth corner.
I will be misunderstood by the far away horse.
I will begin to twist the magic wheel at once.
What's this?
A live broadcast of the field race?
Lazy!
If Daisuke becomes a gambler like you, what will we do?
I will break the device without the machine.
Well, I knew you wanted to do it.
I understood.
It's done.
That's good, sir.
Yes.
I can see Daishke's happy face.
Sir.
Yes?
Pay for this.
What is this?
I ordered sushi from the sushi restaurant for dinner last night.
What?
If you don't pay, I won't let you have it.
If you bring it, you'll get more than 50,000 yen.
I see.
I'll pay, right?
Good luck.
I'm sorry to interrupt you today.
I'll pay for it.
Damn you, Ryotsu.
I'll make you pay for this.
Good morning.
Good morning, Ryo.
You've grown a lot.
I know.
I've been taking care of the eggs I bought.
I've been taking care of them.
What are you doing?
I brought the orchids you grew at home.
Orchids?
They're small.
It looks like they're lined up with rotten dumplings.
You don't have to look at them.
Yes, yes, I don't have to look at them.
Senpai, this orchid is a high-class flower.
It's expensive.
How much will it cost?
If I buy it, I'll pay 30,000 yen.
What? 30,000 yen?
30,000 yen for such a dumpling flower?
I can't believe it.
It's only 30,000 yen for a single leaf.
That means it's the same price as the wood I made over the past two days.
It's the same price as the work I worked hard on over the past two days.
I'm so frustrated.
You don't have to cry.
You saw it, didn't you?
The wood I made.
It's a work of art.
It was a wonderful work.
I know.
It's a plant that grew from such a garden.
So it's the same as the grass or flower that grew on its own.
The world is wrong.
My work is better.
This orchid is a wonderful work.
What?
Well, senpai.
Gardening is popular these days.
What's with the cleaning relatives?
It's about growing grass flowers at home.
Nonsense.
Flowers are for sacrifice.
There's no need for such a high flower.
If the price is the same, I'd be happy to get melons.
You're so noisy.
Shut up!
I won't listen to anyone.
I don't want to sell that kind of thing.
Wait a minute.
30,000 yen per box.
300,000 yen for 10 pots.
3 million yen for 100 pots.
If you can make it at the manager's house, I can make it, too.
This may be a good story.
The End
I can make flowers bloom many times depending on how I grow them.
If you raise them as carefully as the manager, they'll bloom.
Well, yes.
Well, manager.
What?
How many flowers are there in the manager's house?
About 20 pots.
20 pots?
That means 600,000 yen.
It's a lot of money.
Manager, where do you sell these flowers?
What?
I said it was useless.
What's wrong with you?
Well, it's a wonderful flower.
Beautiful.
What?
You're a bad guy.
No, I was impressed by the fact that I was late and the scales fell off my eyes.
Really, gardening is a great hobby.
It's gardening.
It's similar.
Where?
Hey, manager.
Leave that aside.
I want to enjoy the joy of raising flowers like you.
Please teach me.
Then, I'll take a note of my acquaintance's art store.
I'll take a note of my acquaintance's art store.
Something's strange.
I feel like I'm planning something.
You're good, Takuya-kun.
How are you?
Masahiro-kun, Goro-kun, Tsuyoshikun, Shingo-kun, Namie-chan, Ryoko-chan, Yuko-chan, how are you all doing?
I came to give you food.
Eat a lot and you'll become a good adult.
Tomoya-kun, you're good.
Yes, you're a great man.
Ame-chan, Yumiko-chan, let's draw a line with Tamiyo all right?
I got a suggestion from Reiko-chan.
If you talk to the flowers every day, they will grow faster.
I advised him to make them a hundred times faster.
But he named all of them "A"
I don't think it's a good idea to buy so many of them.
It's only after he learned that orchids are expensive flowers.
He's completely going to make them a business.
Chief, how much temperature do you need to keep the greenhouse?
Now it's about 15 degrees.
15 degrees...
Maybe it's better to cover it with a sun-dryer.
I think it's better to do it now.
I bought a Sumition and a Kelsen to keep the insects away.
Do you need anything else?
That's fine.
Thank you.
He's a good guy.
He's been doing a lot of research.
Senpai, if it's for money, people change.
Chief!
Don't suddenly show your face.
I'm sorry.
I was talking about the share price.
He suddenly became a low-ranking student.
That's right.
He was a student
Let's pay him back.
Chief, didn't you hear?
It's a share price.
What?
Share price?
That's an important point.
Right?
What are you going to do to do it well?
My shoulders are stiff.
What?
Damn it.
Are you going to take the revenge the other day?
I want someone to rub it.
It's stiff.
Sorry, Ryozu.
I want you to rub my shoulders.
No, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
What are you going to do about the share price?
If you don't do well, you'll hurt your roots.
It's hard.
So please tell me how to do it.
I'm home.
Ryo, you came here on a day off?
There's a ceremony.
Chief, I bought a new cup of tea.
I see.
Let's drink together.
Ryozu said he'd put it in for everyone.
I'm on a day off.
Why do I have to put it in?
I'm not going to do it alone.
Don't you want to get advice?
It's okay.
I'll do it myself.
Really?
Then do your best.
Ryo is weak to diseases.
Be careful.
There's a case where he was wiped out overnight.
What?
Chief, don't say it.
Please tell me.
Damn it.
He's obsessed with the weakness of people.
It's about lunchtime.
Do you all want to eat sushi?
Sounds good.
I just got paid, so I'll have a luxury time.
No, no.
Even if you don't pay yourself, Ryozu will pay you.
I knew it.
Chief, no way.
If you don't like it, I'll teach you how to cut the stock.
Damn it.
This is overwhelmingly bad.
Please give me four special rice balls.
That's right.
Would you like Ueno's Matsuzushi?
That far away?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I'll take your hot springs.
Listen to the good music and grow high.
Excuse me.
.
Please take the ball.
You guys!
Don't play baseball in the park!
Shinji and Naomi's pot broke!
Don't say that!
Shut up!
Don't play with Ryutaro and Takako!
Wait, you!
Hey!
Now it's the crows!
Don't eat Yukio and Naoto!
Go over there!
Now I can protect you 24/7!
Senpai, how about staying at the police station at night?
No! Gardening is a battle!
It's a battle!
Richiro, good!
Hideki, good!
Nomo, good!
Pae-chan, good!
Ai-chan, good!
Tomoko, good!
Yukio!
Huh?
Yukio got eaten without knowing it.
It's good that you're so enthusiastic,
but I wonder if your body will last until your flowers bloom.
I'm risking my life, senpai.
What?
What are we doing?
Sorry, I got lost.
Don't run all the time in the city!
Lee-Lee!
@lorenz is in danger!
@geun!
@Top Gun-kun, @Michael-kun, @Jo-kun-kun!
Hiiii!
Sh*t, it's Tatsumaki!
Great success, Gabriel!
Please take my cute children with you!
It bloomed!
I didn't know that 50 flowers could bloom.
It's beautiful!
Senpai, you did your best.
All right! Let's see how much it will cost!
It's wonderful.
It's been a long time since I saw such a beautiful flower.
How much is a pot?
It's about 50,000 yen.
50,000 yen?
Really?
That means it's 2.5 million yen for 58 flowers!
Oh, I almost forgot.
What's wrong?
Look at this.
What?
It's purple.
What's wrong with this?
It can be pink or red, but purple is rare.
I'll give you 500,000 yen, no, 1 million yen.
You're a bear!
What a parent-child relationship!
There might be others.
Lend me some.
There it is!
It's purple, too!
It's 2 million yen for a bear.
That's great!
Hey, blue doesn't work.
What?
A blue?
It's a miracle!
It's so beautiful!
It's hard to make a blue flower, even though it's a rose.
It's 500,000 yen for this.
No, even if you pay 10 million yen, there are people who want it.
10 million yen?
Jugemu, Jugemu, Gokou's three-chopped!
That's a long name just for you!
I'm so happy!
Ryotsu, tomorrow the Lan's competition is held at the Kuritsu Plantation.
It will be held at the Kuritsu Plantation.
You should all bring it there.
If you win, you might get a higher price.
Okay, I got it!
50 bars is a lot of money.
I'll take a break.
I just got it checked, and it's 15 million yen.
If I put a whiteboard on this, it's 30 million yen.
No, it'll be about 50 million yen.
This is all thanks to you guys.
I'm good at acting.
I'll stop being a cop and start working here.
Go!
Oh, no!
Don't move!
Jugemu, Jugemu, Gokou's three-chopped!
Nice!
Okay, everyone, I'll help you!
Stop the rear car in front of you!
Go!
No!
I'll protect you even if I die!
I did it!
Oh, no!
So this is the Lan that costs 20 million yen.
Apparently, Marie Antoinette took over the Lan that she loved.
Oh, no!
I'll take my revenge!
I'll do something to their
What's the matter?
May I have your attention, please?
Sir, is that you?
Yes.
Oh, no!
Don't get involved, Okura-kun.
Let's go!
Nyaa! Please wait!
You'll be compensated for that!
T-that was an accident!
Chief!
I don't care!
You do something yourself!
That Volvo Saigo is going to work at the Katushika office.
Then Jody will come and say he wants to fight Volvo again.
Volvo, you have to do something about that nose.
Next time, "Volvo's
fortune telling show".
2 hours later.
Thank you for watching.
D texted me he wanted to come and say he wants to fight Volvo.
It was a little bad throughout.
He wanted to see you, but girls were all so happy that he flashed away.
Thank you for watching, Yaaaaa!
I will be back next time, if you can see me...
Please check the link in the description.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Thanks for watching!