Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
When you're watching TV
Make sure the room is bright and keep your distance
Hello, goodbye
If you're going to say goodbye
You can go home right away
Don't panic, in this small town
Where are you going? Hurry up and turn
Maybe you'll find a better day
Than me
If you're with someone
Let them hear you
Let them hear you all night
I don't hate waiting
Because I'm a Kameza woman
I don't want to lose, I'm a Ginza woman
I've loved you for many years
I'm a Kameza woman
Charlie and Kobayashi's Secrets
Chief Ichinji?
Yes, I heard you're coming to the office today.
Who's next?
Kyoko Fukada or Ryoko Hirose?
Charlie and Kobayashi.
Charlie and Kobayashi?
What's that?
Are they foreigners?
The vocalists of a rock band called Visual K
What?
Chief, what's that?
Chief Ichinji
Hello, everyone at the Kameari Park branch
What a flashy guy
Yes, I hope you'll all cooperate
Charlie, please sign
I've already found it
It's not enough for the fans
It's more strange if you're wearing such a flashy band
If you all want to sign, please do it now
I don't want to sign
First of all, Charlie Kobayashi
I've never seen or heard of it
Ryoko, you're rude to Chief Ichinji
Then, do you know Charlie Kobayashi?
You mean I know him?
Well, that's...
See, you don't know him, do you?
My popularity was a product, after all
The fans were in Sakura
The CD warehouse must have been returned to the office
You're thinking too much, Charlie
You're weak to Visual K in middle school
You know Charlie, right?
Of course, I know Charlie
Yes, I've seen him in TV and magazines
Well...
I don't know him!
It's easy to see
Oh, I remembered
I'm a beautiful girl
By the way, I often saw him in various places
Really?
Yes
Of course he's an Osechi
Charlie
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
He's quick to recover.
Hey, you!
Charlie is a naive and delicate artist.
I'd like you to stop hurting him with such a delicate expression.
I'm sorry.
But this is a very serious matter.
Don't make me laugh, chief.
I've checked all the entertainment information.
And I've given you my honest opinion.
Then, please look at this.
All the visual stuff.
Listen.
Among the visual bands that are the mainstream in Japanese music,
Charlie Kobayashi's "With Narcissist" is...
"With Narcissist" is...
Not this.
That's strange.
It's not on anywhere.
I found it!
Where?
Here.
I see.
It's the visual style that was popular in the boom.
Please call me Shinuchi.
In short, it's the second Senji.
Then, I'll paint the gap between the busy schedule that prevented the recording of the new song,
and the fact that I was the chief of police for a day.
That's right.
It's a chance to meet the fans in person.
Then, I'll take it.
Kan Shiki!
It's good that my gravure is taken by a cameraman called Kan Shiki.
The gravure is a monochrome photo that can be posted on the Katsushika newspaper's newspaper.
"What it was back in the day"
Okay.
The president will decide on an outfit.
"Glass"
How about this?
It's different from the uniform of the Katsushika's newspaper.
It's hard with the visual style.
Yeah.
It's a duty of a man born virtues.
I don't think you guys understand that.
Why?
You're a visual artist.
I knew it!
I was seen that way by the world!
I... I...
Charlie, stop it.
What's wrong with saying the truth?
Are you a budget?
Char... Charlie?
The End
Thank you!
Let's start filming.
Wait!
What's wrong, Charlie?
I'm a little tired.
Let's take a rest here.
Okay.
I'm sorry,
but...
I'm sorry for the photo.
Why?
Nakagawa-kun is also a police officer of this police station.
Actually...
I don't mind, but...
Thank you.
You don't want to be with a beautiful Nakagawa, right?
Charlie!
You don't have the confidence to beat Nakagawa with a two-shot, right?
Senior!
What's wrong with being a civil servant?
You're so cool.
Charlie, don't worry about what he says.
I'm sorry.
I'll be embarrassed, so don't be a Perché.
Ryo!
Please don't stop.
I mean,
What do you mean?
What's wrong with you?
And what about that what you were saying?
Well...
It was a joke.
I can't explain it.
Well...
The next day
Alright, Charlie, you're good.
You're beautiful. You're cool!
I'm beautiful. I'm cool.
Yeah, you're beautiful. You're not going to lose!
You're not going to lose to anyone!
I'm not going to lose!
I lost!
Visuals that are inferior to ordinary people are not visuals!
Charlie!
The next day
You know what?
Charlie, you're the only visual in the country that is inferior to ordinary people.
You're the only visual in the family business industry.
Because you're the only visual in the police department industry.
Me.
Yeah, you!
You're confident ...
I can understand.
You're much more persuasive than usual.
Yeah, this time after Visual Band Festival,
you can record the ringtone of the Nashville building I have been saying before.
Really?
Then, let's have a shoot immediately!
Okay
Ok, then Nakagawa-san, please...
Yes
After all, why didn't you remove Nakagawa's face?
Thanks to you, I had fun.
We don't mind either.
Oh, you're the president of the day, taking pictures.
You're an idol, but you're a president of the day, not a president of the three minutes.
George.
Charlie, we're going to rehearse for Rock Fest.
Oh, Charlie.
You misunderstood the visual system.
No, I'm not a visual system, I'm making fun of you, a person.
You're making fun of me, a person.
What's so annoying about me?
Everything, it's so annoying.
What?
Don't say that to Charlie.
Ryo, shut up.
I can't go home with the misunderstanding for my fans and other visual systems.
So, it doesn't matter about other bands.
Stop it, Ryo.
Ryo.
Okay, I'll be with you for half a day.
It's a patrol.
Well, it's been a while since I walked around the town.
It's not bad.
Okay.
Hi.
Charlie, you're not the only one who comes to me when I say you're a popular artist.
I've been told that fans are in a mood to come to you.
But I'm a commoner from now on, so...
A commoner.
Hey.
I'm a fan of Hena Choco.
Hena Choco.
Well, it's a honest impression.
I'll... I'll...
Charlie.
θα
そうだ
PRO
-Did you find it? -No, it's nowhere.
I haven't even bought one of my books!
Again? Hey, manager!
That's right! I'm sure I sold all of them!
Charlie, that's right. It's good. I'm sure it's true.
They're a great pair, as always.
What is it?
What? Charlie's profile?
Born in 1978 in London.
Oh, really?
Born between an Italian French father and a Japanese second generation child.
He spent his childhood in Switzerland, Netherlands, and Russia.
After his father died, he moved to Japan, where his mother's hometown was.
He was born in the Shibuya prefecture.
He was forced to predict the mysterious.
He's got a feeling that he's trying to smoke his whole body.
I don't like it. Stop with the weird ideas.
Well, let's sign it.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Sir, that's a book for return.
Would you please not touch it?
What? Return?
It's broken.
Please don't do it!
Tell me who stole it.
It's not like I don't know.
He stole an old book.
You used to know a book I couldn't read.
I read it.
I knew you'd have a book like that.
I was practicing it when I was in high school.
And his father had a big book.
A book that dates from the 19th century.
It's a fantastic book!
Charlie, your imagination has changed greatly.
Where are you?
"A-I-U-E-O"
"Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko"
"Sa-Si-Su-Se-So-Ta-Chi-Chi-Cha"
Charlie, there's my CD!
Of course!
I have one too!
"Chuuko Record Corner"?
20 years ago, a poor folk singer who had only one hit left disappeared.
His name was...
His name was Kobayashi Kazuo.
Charlie Kobayashi, you're 20 years old!
No! I'm not!
We're going to have a rehearsal, so excuse us.
Here we go!
Wait!
No doubt!
Kobayashi Kazuo!
I know this record.
I remember buying it a long time ago.
It's one of the hit songs of the pre-war folk era.
It's a souvenir of Kobayashi Kazuo's one-shot and one-shot work.
If these two are the same person, they're about the same age as Ryo-chan.
Yeah, the entertainment world is not uncommon for age differences.
They heat up all the profiles and make visual-based band movements.
They hide their faces with makeup and make their new debut.
They're afraid of that.
But if you think about it, it's a great obsession.
It's not like they're trying to do anything.
But it's important for the world to know that Charlie had a different face.
No, there's no need to worry about that.
If the media is trying to sell a story, they'll refuse it.
What?
Charlie Kobayashi's story?
No, no.
He's doing his best, but I don't think his popularity is that big.
Ryo-chan is the worst.
Ryo-san is terrible.
Ryo-chan is terrible.
He's been a police chief for a day, you know?
I told you he wasn't selling.
But he's a poor man, too.
What's wrong?
Isn't that Charlie?
Oh, no!
Are you OK?
What?
Devil!
Devil Yagami!
Don't say such a bad thing.
I heard he wasn't injured.
But why did he get hurt on such a good road?
As soon as I saw the car, I suddenly...
This road is a dead end!
I was scared to see Ryo-san.
Today?
Isn't that noisy manager with you?
The manager went to the venue first.
That's right.
This is not the time to do this.
I have to go.
The car is...
Where are you going?
We're going to the band festival.
Band festival?
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Hello? Charlie, get out of here.
Hello?
What are you doing?
I can't let you go to the concert because of me.
I'll watch you get into the venue.
We don't have to go.
We have an equipment car.
Please take the other car with the instrument.
I got it.
I'll go with you.
Hey, don't be so quiet.
You idiot.
Get out of here.
Yes, sir.
I haven't said that except for the people of Hashijo.
What does that mean?
We're on Charlie's side.
He's an amazing person.
It's natural that the Japanese visual band is one and the same.
I'm putting everything I have to today's concert.
I'll make you a great hit.
Kobayashi, Kazoo.
I'm Charlie.
Nakagawa, get me to the entrance of the dressing room.
It's probably the back entrance.
I got it.
The entrance is open.
I think it should be around here.
It's that.
Then we'll leave now.
I wish you success.
Thank you.
I misunderstood you.
Don't worry about it.
Nakagawa, get me out of here.
Yes, sir.
See you later.
Kobayashi, Kazoo.
I'm Charlie Kobayashi.
Excuse me.
Oh, you're the driver.
Yes.
This is the left side that went right after this.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
A lot of superstars walked this corridor.
I'm getting dizzy.
Toilet.
Charlie has not arrived yet in this hall?
Manager is at the gate.
Give it to him.
That's Ryotsu.
He must have sent him to Gangnam Brotherhood's house.
The thing has not arrived.
We need you to take responsibility if Charlie doesn't show up.
Where did he disappear to?
I relaxed now.
Okay.
The band two years ago is over.
Where did they go?
Charlie Kobayashi with Narcissist, stand by please.
Oh, Charlie...
Good morning.
Oh, I remember you. You're Kobayashi, aren't you?
What are you doing, Kobayashi?
No, I'm Charlie.
I'm sure you're dressed up, but you're not wearing that outfit today.
That's right.
Come on, change your clothes.
Hurry up.
Can I come in?
Yes.
You guys!
Yeah.
Where did you take them?
I sent them to the back door here.
Back door?
Yes.
I'll take a look.
What? You're not here yet?
I'll be there soon, so I'll be gone for a while.
I've changed the order of the performance, but I can't change the order any more.
I forced you to perform at the request of the president of the otaku agency.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
I'll wait for another five minutes. If you don't come in five minutes, the performance is canceled.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Charlie Kobayashi!
Ryo, you're Charlie. Are you a little fat?
No, I quit smoking, so I think I'm a little fat.
What are you doing?
I'm Charlie.
Then Kobayashi Kazuo will sing.
Tokyo Hustle Man
Please hustle there.
What's the matter?
Ah, I long for Tokyo
Ah, I saw Tokyo in my dreams
Ah, I came to Tokyo
Hustle, hustle, hustle. It must be meaningful.
Two of you, the Tokyo Tower
Two of you, the bus tour
A hustle rendezvous I saw to my dreams
But you're already a wife of a person
Ah, painful Tokyo
Tokyo, Tokyo, Hustle Otoko
Uwaaaaaaah!
This is ridiculous!
What the?
Fly away.
Eh?
Alright, good!
Uwaaaaaah!
Whatever you want, sing!
Hey!
Hey, it's a no-no now!
Hey, hey, heart!
Ah!
You're arrested!
Arrest him!
I'm a man of love!
Yeah!
You look like a dream
Yee-haw!
You are already
My wife!
Ah, Tokyo is so sad
Tokyo
Tokyo Hustle Man
-Yay! -Yay!
What?
So, the reason why we thought it was the back entrance of Kameari Hall
was the back entrance of Kameari Koukaido?
I love you!
I love you three times!
I love you as much as I love Hariko!
-All right! -You're so...
As always, there are many flashy bands.
By the way, what happened to Charlie?
He was a one-shot even after he switched to visual.
Maybe he couldn't go to the band festival because he was too big.
It would be lonely if he disappeared.
That's his luck.
It's his fate.
I don't care, but you should stop wearing that make-up, Ryo-chan.
Don't be silly!
I made all the guests of the hall a good match.
I can easily remove this make-up.
And thanks to this, I don't have to go to the bathroom.
You're dirty!
Ryo-san, I'm in trouble!
What's wrong?
So, let me introduce you the president of the day.
It's Kobayashi Kazuo, the folk singer.
Hey, Kobayashi Kazuo!
♪ Ah, the Tokyo I long for ♪
♪ Ah, the Tokyo I dreamed of ♪
♪ Ah, since I came to Tokyo ♪
♪ I have to hustle, hustle, hustle ♪
♪ Everyone is good ♪
♪ Together with you, we sing about Tokyo ♪
♪ Together with you, we fly about ♪
♪ Ah, the hustle rendezvous I dreamed of ♪
♪ You are my wife ♪
♪ Ah, the painful Tokyo ♪
♪ Tokyo, I love you ♪
Kobayashi Kazuo has reached the end of his long journey of searching for himself.
Ah, what a wonderful life!
Okay, I will definitely go to Tokyo.
I'll pick him up for a drink.
Kobayashi Kazuo
I always give you a short kiss
You were so dear to me
I can't replace it like that
How much will people get in their lifetime?
You are me
I am you
You were the only one who made me happy
Just by laughing
I felt like I was healed from all the pain
It's you again, Professor Tondemo!
This time, it's an experiment of the deep sea suit!
Your invention
I told you it's enough!
Wait a minute
Maybe this is a treasure of the new boss battle
Next time, Tondemo Shinkai SOS
Thank you for watching!