A
"I'm hungry..."
The day after the rain, as if someone was calling me
I walked, looking back, and my mom was holding my hand
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked along the black roadside of the Ake-do-gai
Everyone was a child at one time, but they all forget
They all look like they're proud
"I'm hungry..."
I felt a strange feeling at that time
Everyone was a child at one time, but they all forget
I walked, looking back, and my mom was holding my hand
They all look like they're proud
Everyone was a child at one time, but they all forget
to the town!
Thank you!
"The Lion's Journey to the City"
You idiot!
Ugh!
Poo-chan!
Are you done, Ryo-chan?
I got it!
Ugh, I'm saved.
What's that?!
Where am I?!
Watch out!
"The Lion's Journey to the City"
Ah, a dream.
What the...
What a dream.
I'm sure the chief won't get mad at me for coming out of a dream.
Huh?
Whoa!
What's this?!
Is there a thief on the bridge?!
No, I'm here, so it's not a thief.
This is no time for jokes!
Nakagawa is a thief.
Reiko is also a thief.
The priest...
That's right!
The priest!
That idiot!
How long are you going to patrol?
That means...
I'm the only one in the bridge!
It's my responsibility!
Huh?
Could it be...
Is this still a continuation of a dream?
Hmm?
Ugh!
It's not a dream after all!
Yes, chief!
I was sleeping in the empty room.
I'm sorry!
Well, it can't be helped.
I'll be careful next time.
I don't think the chief will forgive me for saying that.
This is bad.
I have to think of a good excuse before someone comes.
The priest is back!
Huh?
Nakagawa, you're early.
Yeah.
Nakagawa!
Oh, Reiko.
Huh?
Weren't you by my side today?
Ugh!
Remember what you have to do.
Even Reiko...
Good morning!
Whoa!
What's this?
What's wrong?
I'm a little dizzy.
So, while Ryo-chan was taking a nap,
someone broke into the exit and broke into the office.
It's sad to see Ryo-san, who's off work, attacking someone.
That's right!
The priest who went on patrol and left the exit empty is also guilty!
No, rather, the priest who left me lying down and went out is more serious!
Huh?
Oh!
Ryo-chan!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
But, that was quite a big scene.
The priest might be angry with this.
It seems that no one was taken, right?
That's good.
But let's keep this to Chief Ohara.
Nothing has been taken, so we don't have to report it, right?
Ryo-chan?
No.
As I thought.
No!
What's wrong?
Huh? Mr. Tenai?
A gold badge from Chief Ohara.
What?
It's a badge from the head of the district office.
Amazing! It's real gold!
Wanna try it?
Congratulations, Chief!
Well, sometimes good things happen when you get old.
Chief Ohara was so happy that he showed us the badge yesterday.
He forgot the badge and went home.
I'll keep it until tomorrow.
Okay, I'll keep it!
You put it on this shelf, didn't you?
Yes. It was in the corner of the shelf until the patrol came.
He doesn't lock the shelf during the day.
What?
Maybe it's on the floor.
Let's find it.
Okay.
There's nothing here. What should we do?
This is the only thing we have in this room.
If we're pros, we can't overlook it.
It's a big mistake, Tenai.
Mr. Ryo!
It's a gold badge from the Ministry of Labor.
We can't buy it just because we want to.
This is the first prize of the gold and the silver medals.
It's a trophy of the first prize of the Ministry of Labor.
It may be found in the city of Kappabashi, but it's a different story when it comes to the gold medal.
It's a modest prize that has been obtained in the hands of the chief's blood, sweat, and worn soles for more than 10 years.
You put it on the shelf and gave it to Kosodoro.
It's a gold medal after all.
Ryo, that's a terrible thing to say.
It's not.
I'm sure you know that you're not that kind of person.
I should have put it in my locker.
I was lost for a moment at that time, but I thought that the chief would know when I wasn't there, so I was careless.
That's right. The chief's gold badge was stolen out of Tenai's carelessness.
I'll make it clear.
What is it?
Is my face on something?
Or do you like me?
Did I miss out on you?
Don't be so grumpy.
Tenai and I have a lot of jokes and jokes in the manzai.
We know each other well.
Tenai, don't worry about what Ryo said. Let's find the chief's badge together.
Let's find it together.
I can't bother you all. I'm sure I'll get the gold badge.
But if I don't come back, I'll tell Chief Ohara about this.
Chief!
Wait, Tenai!
If you leave it, I'll come back.
Ryo, Tenai is serious.
I'll find it.
I'll leave it to you.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?
Ryo didn't notice it when he was sleeping in the afternoon, and he was sorry, right?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ryo, it hurts!
He's been so serious that he even wrote a journey to thetrai.
If you're in trouble with a terai, you could take responsibility and take care of your wife and children.
Why would I do that to the terai god and my children...
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Oh, he really did it. It's a good trouble for the temple.
Senpai, the temple is nowhere.
He just jumped out of the bridge without any clues.
How is he going to find the culprit?
I'll go over there.
The temple's behavior is sober, but it's a mess.
His great-grandson Tadayuki wanted a new one.
So he went to buy one.
Flash Cam Cam Bone, right?
My child wants one, too.
He's asking me to wait until his birthday.
I need to find a new job before that.
Job?
Are you okay by yourself?
Oh, thank you.
I'm lost.
My grandson who always took care of me is already a child.
Time flies.
Oh, then be careful.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry.
That badge...
What is it?
No, it's a good badge.
Oh...
Oh!
Give me my hat back!
I'm sorry.
What am I doing?
Calm down.
Calm down and think about the culprit's footsteps.
I see.
Someone must be watching near the escape room.
Between two to three o'clock,
Didn't you see a suspicious person near the escape room?
A suspicious person, huh?
Ah, he woke up.
Ah!
Did you wake up?
My child?
I'm sorry.
It was a good help.
Come on.
Say goodbye to Uncle Terai.
Oh, my.
Goodbye!
Ah...
It's about three o'clock.
Did you see her?
The suspicious one.
Oh...
You're even higher, Mr. Terai.
Still high?
There!
Right there, more to the right.
A-a little...
Thank you, Terai.
Weirdo.
It looks like he didn't see us.
-Goodbye. -Shut up.
Goodbye.
Oh, that's when he was delivering some partying in the same neighborhood.
Really?
Yeah.
That's a strange guy.
Oh!
If you do that, he'll pack the rice for you.
Sorry for helping you, Mr. Jirai.
No, it doesn't matter what it is.
If you remember anything...
It's about noon.
Ah, I just remembered that a guy came out from the toilet alone.
Really?
If you remember a line or a hairstyle, please let me know.
He was longer than you.
He had short hair.
He was in a tight knit like this, and he was wearing something like...
- Wearing a jumper! - Yeah, he was wearing something like this.
Thank you very much!
I'll be a help! See you!
Ryo-san!
How are you going to find the culprit with that little information?
There are hundreds of young men with short hair in this town.
I'll hit one by one with hundreds of people.
I won't bother you.
I'm already on it.
I'm investigating in the police station now.
What!?
Ryo-san, you're in trouble.
I'll hit one by one with hundreds of people.
I'm already on it.
You're the only one who can't do this.
Apologize to the chief and ask him to forgive you.
What?
What's wrong, Rai?
H-he's...!
Let's solve this too.
You always pretend you're happy, but I don't care if you really get a cramp.
Why are you hiding?
Ryo...
Excuse me, but please excuse me.
He's running away!
He's a suspicious person!
I don't care how you feel, I don't care.
Kei!
Is Kanshiki home?
Yes, he went home a while ago.
How about you, Terai?
I haven't told him anything.
How about you, Senpai?
Ryo-chan hasn't come home yet.
That's weird.
Kanshiki said that this might not be the entrance to the Aki-su.
Eh?
Then who is doing this?
Wait a minute!
Stop! Stop!
You're so annoying.
Ryo-san!
What's going on?
What did I do?
Then why did you run away?
I ran away!
I'm sick of being questioned about my job!
What?
What happened?
If you don't mind, please tell me.
I quit the company because I was not good at my job.
It's been three years now.
I have no job.
I still have to pay the loan.
But I still owe money.
I divorced a year ago.
My family is living in Kyushu.
I returned to my parents' house.
Since then, I have been living without a place to live.
I'm not afraid of my family.
What?
Ryo-san.
Shiochiri-san is so annoying.
I've been working hard until now, but it's not enough.
What are you doing crying?
I can't believe it's someone else's problem.
When I asked the Katsushika office,
they said that your family had a request to find you.
The family?
Shiochiri-san is divorced and now lives alone.
But I checked the office.
The wife and children said that they would come to pick you up.
The wife and children?
The wife wasn't divorced.
She was looking for Shiochiri-san.
What?
What's wrong?
Wait quietly in the office until your family comes to pick you up.
Thank you, Terai-san.
Ryo-san.
Be strong.
That's good.
Now Terai's opinion is back.
Hey, you can't park there.
The driving is prohibited there!
The middle man who wears a jumper with a short hair.
Terai.
Hey.
*Growl*
You're really a big shot!
They're so bad at talking...
Hey! We're on the move!
You're disturbing the camera, Mr. Oomari!
Excuse me!
Mr. Ryo, give me back my sword.
*Growl*
I was so surprised.
If you were filming a movie, you should have put on your costume.
Oh, the person I saw earlier...
*Growl*
The actor, huh?
Hold up!
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
*Growl*
I'm sorry for being so loud.
I thought we'd be done soon.
That's true.
Actually, Marie and John...
*Growl*
Marie, you're not allowed to come!
Come here!
*Growl*
What should we do?
Then, was the dog the one who broke the safe?
I'm sorry.
Um, I can't find a black gold bag in the bookcase over there.
Do you know about that?
I don't think I have it.
Anyway, we have to tell the priest.
*Growl*
*Cough*
Damn, he's so stubborn!
*Screams*
What the hell is this?
*Cough*
*Screams*
I won't let you get away!
Hey, let go!
No, I won't let go!
Let go, let go!
*Screams*
Damn, he's so stubborn!
Ryo-san...
*Screams*
I stole the
What are you stealing in a place like this?
A helmet or a Juralumin shield?
That's enough, Ryo. Thank you.
Don't apologize, Terai.
We caught the thief's accomplice.
The chief should be watching the badge a lot.
Ryo was the one who caught him.
Ryo, that's right.
Besides, I can't do a deal like that.
We've been through a lot together, Ryo.
But I won't forget what happened today, even if I quit being a police officer.
Terai...
What? It's you guys?
Chief!
I happened to pass by,
and I saw some men in the grass.
I heard they were having a rampage,
so I came to see how they were doing.
Chief! What's wrong with that?
Oh, this?
I tried to look young, but I don't think I look good.
A badge!
Yeah.
Tonight, I suddenly met a friend from my school days.
I was going to show him off,
so I went back to the police station to get it.
What is it, Ryo?
Ryo, you haven't told Terai yet?
I told you, didn't I?
What?
Ryo, what do you mean?
Well...
Ahhhhh!
Hey, Ryo!
Don't sleep in the middle of your work!
Huh?
No, Chief.
I'm not sleeping.
Tell Terai that I'm back to get the gold badge.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
I understand.
And you!
Don't sleep!
She hasn't slept!
See you soon!
...
That was not a dream!
It wasn't a dream!
You knew everything, Ryo-san.
No, to be honest, that's not true, Terai.
I was so sleepy that I was almost unconscious.
What's with those eyes?
They just confirmed their friendship!
Well, I'm glad I found the gold badge.
I'm glad I found the gold badge.
Oh, the chief is here too!
Oh, what are you two doing here?
Oh, you found the gold badge.
That's great!
I've been here all this time.
You knew, Ryo-san, didn't you?
Didn't you?
Ryo-san!
You're different from the usual Terai!
♪ Awaken! ♪
♪ Watch, ♪
♪ Kick it! ♪
♪ My little finger ♪
♪ It hurts! ♪
♪ For now, I'll draw my eyebrows ♪
♪ and we'll head to the station! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The main train ♪
♪ will sleep under my father's back ♪
♪ This week too, good luck! ♪
♪ The sound of the gomorriti ♪
♪ Even though I'm holding a racket in one hand ♪
♪ but ♪
♪ The hot soup and the hot soup ♪
♪ The frustration that continues throughout the day ♪
♪ Let's get rid of it with a clear mind ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ When the hot shower passes by ♪
♪ I get well with a half-naked pillow ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart beats on Monday ♪
♪ No problem, no problem, no problem ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle there for sure ♪
♪ Let's brush about ♪
♪ There's a turtle over there for sure ♪