Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset floating on the river ♪
♪ I took off my love stone and flew to the top ♪
♪ I was laughing at my
♪
♪ I was
♪ I was laughing at my
It's just like the character "Kinomi" from the manga "One Piece".
It's a manga!
Anyway, let's have dinner with him.
Ah, senpai.
Itadakimasu.
It's a strange taste.
I don't know.
I can do it.
It's so noisy.
You bastard!
Ouch!
Damn it! What the hell is this?
Huh?
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
What happened?
What is this?
Mr. Ryo of Gomu Gomu.
What happened to my body?
I'm going to the hospital.
I need an ambulance.
Ah, senpai.
Move!
Senpai!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It's nothing.
Senpai, you became a rubber human after all.
Shut it! It's your fault!
Why didn't you stop it at that time?
Eh? I stopped it, but you ate it.
Hey! I don't care about that.
I don't care about that.
I'm a doctor.
I need to go to the hospital.
Yes!
Let's go, Mr. Ryo of Gomu Gomu.
Okay. I'm going to the emergency room.
Okay!
I'll be right there.
Yeah.
Wow!
Oh, my God!
What's wrong, Mr. Ryo of Gomu Gomu?
Hey, Mr. Ryo of Gomu Gomu!
Ouch!
Ah!
Finally it stopped.
What?
Boss! I'll save you right now.
Really, I'm...
Senpai!
What are you doing?
I can't swim anymore!
What?
Your body became rubber?
That's right.
When I woke up this morning, my arms were stretched and shrunk.
I can't believe that kind of manga story.
Then, Reiko, try pulling my hand.
It's really stretched.
Not only your arms.
Nakagawa, try pulling your leg.
Yes, sir.
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm not used to this yet.
Please be careful.
I-I understand.
But if your legs are stretched,
does that mean your head and face are stretched too?
Yes, that's right.
Thanks to that, you can drown in the river.
You can walk outside in this body.
But why did you become like that?
Because I ate a tree called rubber that I picked up in the sea yesterday,
I became a rubber human.
What?
Your arms, legs, head and face are all stretched.
I see.
Well, you used to be two or six people.
You're still in a bad shape.
You guys should be worried.
Why am I in such a mess?
You idiot!
Because I'm usually in a bad shape,
I become like that.
You're in a bad shape because you ate a tree I picked up in the sea.
You're a big idiot.
Can you live a decent life?
Please stop, sir!
Then, Mr. Honda,
is there any way to get back to normal?
So far, I've been working on my body.
But it seems like you haven't experienced it.
What?
Does that mean I'll be a rubber human for the rest of my life?
Maybe.
You!
I thought it was just a word.
Please stop, senpai!
My legs!
Don't work on Honda!
It's your own business!
I'm a rubber human, so I don't want to be beaten.
You're so rude!
So, I'm tired of being a strange body,
so I'll leave today.
What are you talking about?
Do you think you can forgive me for that?
Hey, it's fine.
I'm taking a day off.
What?
It hurts!
If you have time to rest,
you can think of a way to use that strange ability for the people and the world.
What?
For the people and the world?
Yes.
It might be useful if you use it well.
If you say it's useful for your body,
I won't complain.
Are you serious, chief?
Alright.
From today, I'm a rubber human, Ryo Tsukanki!
What are you doing, you idiot?
Ouch!
I'm not used to this body yet.
Please look at me with longer eyes.
Longer eyes...
Don't do such a stupid thing!
Hey, your body is to blame.
Ugh...
Hehehe, well done, bro.
Now we're rich, too.
Let's get through this quickly.
Stop right there.
Who's there?
I can't run anymore.
Give me your nose quietly.
Heh.
What can you do from a place like that?
Do you think you can wait until I come here?
Do you think I'll wait until you come?
No, I won't let you wait.
Take this!
What!?
Big brother!
Did I die?
I'm fine because I fell from that height.
It's a monster!
Run away quickly!
I said I can't run away!
Let's go!
It's time for the Gomu Gomu!
I can't catch up anymore.
What was that guy?
You're done, big brother.
I had a bad dream.
I-is that so?
Yeah, yeah.
W-what's that guy?
I don't care!
I'll just blow him up!
Gomu Gomu's Diet!
What are you doing?
I'm the Gomu Gomu's Ryo.
Trouble!
I knew it.
Gomu Gomu's Suicide!
Gomu...
I-I-it's a monster!
LOL.
I'm in trouble.
S-help!
What are you doing?
Your fingers!
Yes, nowhere hard.
Leave it to me!
The Gomu Gomu's Suicide!
Ronin!
Your thumb is my life!
I'll attack you a little!
It's okay now. Let's run!
But the fire is already there...
What?!
You don't need to go through the room.
It's okay! Believe me!
The rescue of Bon Bon is complete!
Senpai, you're amazing!
You're so active!
Of course!
Thanks to being a rubber human,
I don't have to be beaten or hit by cars.
Besides, if you use the power of rubber,
your punches and kicks will be a few times more powerful.
If you get used to it, you won't have such a convenient ability.
As expected of Ryo-chan!
You're very adaptive.
Ryo-chan, you did well.
Actually, I've decided that you're going to get a police officer's certificate soon.
Really?
Of course!
As I said, I'm active for the sake of the world and the people.
There's nothing more exciting than this, Ryo-chan!
Of course!
I'll keep doing my best!
Yes, of course!
I'll use this power for everyone's sake!
Here!
Good.
Well, as I get used to it, this body is also very convenient.
Even if I sit down, I can reach the distant things.
As expected, I can't grab the snacks that are gone.
I'll go to a convenience store.
But I want to watch TV.
Oh, yes!
I'll go to a convenience store.
But I want to watch TV.
What is this?
I can't...
I'm sorry.
It costs 3,885 yen.
I'll return 1,115 yen from 4,000 to 5,000 yen.
*Growl*
This is very useful.
If this is the case, I can do anything while staying at home.
*Growl*
Thank you very much.
Ryotsu! Where is Ryotsu?
I haven't seen him since this morning.
What?
I told you to deliver the documents today.
*Growl*
This is the document that Ryotsu asked for.
What was that?
*Growl*
Yes, this is the park.
Ryo-chan?
You saw the video, didn't you?
I have to stretch my arm to move around.
You idiot!
Do you think you can do that?
Go to the station and show your face.
I understand.
Bye.
Bye?
I showed my face.
You idiot!
But,
I installed the camera in the station.
I can't do it at all.
It's annoying.
I caught you now.
Bring your body to me.
No, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I said no.
Idiot!
Go away.
*Growl*
What is this?
This is...
What's wrong with me?
Senpai!
Isn't it dangerous to be so hot?
Huh?
Ryo-chan is working at home.
He's doing great with his rubber rubber ability,
so he's getting a lot of selfishness.
But I wonder if he can work at home.
What?
Honda!
You'll understand as soon as you say a bad word.
I'll understand!
Senpai, where are you?
Honda-san, over there.
Over there.
Huh?
You can watch the
It's really rubber rubber.
Senpai, you're using the wrong ability.
This isn't rubber rubber, it's a raggy Ryo-chan.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Ryo-chan hasn't come yet?
I told him to come today.
I think he'll be here soon.
Oh, look.
Oh?
That's rare.
He failed.
It happens a lot lately.
He's lost his documents,
and his hands can't reach them.
Oh, he'll be fine this time.
That's too bad.
What are you doing?
That idiot can't even help me.
All right, I'm going!
Get up!
Oh!
Good morning!
I'm exhausted.
What's wrong with your body?
Actually, I realized I had to keep moving,
so I couldn't really move now.
I started to get very used to it, so I stopped talking.
I was just kidding.
You're too lazy, you idiot!
You're not a rubber today, you're a fat one!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, thief!
Thief!
Catch him!
- Let's go! - Yes!
Ah, what a pain.
I'll wait for you.
You're coming too!
Hey, no way!
I'm not getting caught!
You're not getting caught.
Hurry up!
Run, run!
Help me, chief!
What are you doing?
I'm going to run away!
Damn it!
Could this be a rubber missile?
Is it heavy?
I'm going to arrest you!
It's not a missile.
It's a rubber ball-throwing.
What?
You're so lazy,
you're becoming like this.
Repent a little!
Hey!
But chief,
it's a convenient skill.
Shut up!
You're so loud.
Listen.
From today on, I won't forgive you for being lazy.
I'll make you work hard until you lose this money.
So get ready!
Shut up!
Yes, this is the exit before the park.
Hm?
Yes, I got it.
I'll be right there.
Chief, it seems that the car thief is running away.
The car is the red car.
I got it.
Everyone, get out!
Make sure to contact me by wireless.
Roger!
You go, too!
Yes!
Damn it, what's this fat ass?
I'll get angry again and get back at the chief.
Oh, that's the car thief's...
Let's get out of here!
Rubber ball-throwing!
You don't know how to do it, do you?
I'll show you the real deal!
F-fine.
All right.
the car thief is passing through this way.
I'm using the car bumper of the car.
If you follow my hand, you'll know.
I know!
What? I know!
Even if you die, don't let go of that hand!
I know!
I'm proud to have caught this guy!
Why are you going through a place like this?
Apparently the culprit passed through by one of the rails.
What a scoundrel.
Chief, what should I do?
Stay there for a while, but don't let go of your hand.
No way!
Hey, how far are you going to run away?
One more step and...
They were selling stolen cars overseas.
Overseas?
I'll tell you what happened.
I don't like this anymore.
I can't stay here until I catch the culprit.
I'm not kidding.
I'll let go of your hand.
Huh?
I can't get my hands back.
Why?
What?
You're in Brazil?
The car theft group sold cars overseas.
I found out that they were going to Brazil when I looked up the destination of the cargo ship.
So... what about my hands?
You're under the Brazilian sky now.
No way.
What should I do?
By the way, are you a little thin?
Yeah.
I'm not even 20 years old.
Huh?
Chief!
I haven't eaten anything for a while.
I've lost my money and I'm being pulled.
Yeah?
If you go back now, I don't know where you'll go.
Nakagawa!
Chief!
Please don't let go of my hand!
Nakagawa!
The rope!
Bring me the rope!
Yes!
Chief!
Help me!
Nakagawa is coming soon.
You step on it too!
Yes!
Oh my goodness!
Chief!
Senpai!
Ryozu!
Don't get me in trouble!
You said you wouldn't let go of my hand, right?
Don't you agree, sir?
W-What?
Oh, you did it! You're under arrest!
You're the most experienced of the Settou-dan!
Ryozu, you did it!
Huh? Ryozu? Ryozu!
Hey, where are you, Ryozu?
Answer me, Ryozu!
I won't eat the mushrooms I picked up anymore, so someone help me!
Please help me!
Damn it, Ryu-senshi!
You really beat my Robodeca-bancho!
In this case, I'll replace the manga magazine, and I'll crush the Weekly Sapphire!
Huh? Who will I let write the manga?
I have a good idea!
Next time on Ryozu Ryu Manga School!
Thanks for watching!
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!