Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset floating in the middle of the river
I kick the pebble and fly to the end
I wonder if I'm going to the taiko that I used to jog
I laughed at the fact that it was still a cake
It's only for the sake of winning even if I'm a good man somewhere
The cityscape that doesn't change even if it's evil is kinder than the night
The sun is already setting because the crows are crying
I'm a grilled chicken
Tomorrow's the same age, I'll fuck you up
But I don't care, I've changed
I'll fuck you up
Reiko's Cute Prince
Senpai, you're late.
Really? The time for the replacement has already passed.
The king must be selling oil somewhere again.
What a hopeless guy.
Yay! I'm here!
I barely made it.
You're late!
I told you to keep the time!
I saw the sunset in Nagagawa,
and when I kicked a pebble, it flew to the sandalwood.
That's a terrible excuse.
It's a shame.
Enough! You idiot!
Well, excuse us.
I'll take care of the rest.
Be careful.
This way, please.
Someone is coming.
If you keep following me, I'll show you this is the way.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe if you enjoy the film!
*phone ringing*
Who's there?
What are you doing here?
Are you lost?
Who are you?
Don't bother me!
Hey, aren't you hungry?
*phone ringing*
I'm not hungry!
You must be hungry.
*phone ringing*
You don't have to force yourself.
I'm not forcing myself.
*phone ringing*
Come here.
You'll catch a cold if you stay here.
*phone ringing*
Don't worry.
*phone ring*
*phone ringing*
Do you like it?
It's very delicious.
*phone ringing continues.
What's the matter?
Eh? No, I'll say something funny. I'm Akimoto Reiko, a police officer. Don't worry.
I'm Jilba, Jilba Castanet.
We'll reward you with a reward. No need to hold back.
No need to thank me. But what are you doing there?
...Huh?
I'll take what I like.
You must be exhausted. Let's let him sleep for now.
......
I have a bad feeling about this.
...
......
So?
Kurokawa
Don't hesitate against illegal intruders!
I won't hold back.
It's so noisy, but it won't happen.
It's not just fat, but has a nerve like Ryo-chan.
But why did you aim at this kid?
-The
Then, the suspicious person entered Reiko-san's room aiming at this kid?
Yes, that's right.
What the hell is going on?
Hey, why are you dressed like that?
Is it a cosplay of the prince?
It's a fake!
A fake?
It's a cosplay of the prince's cosplay.
The prince of the 17th generation of the Ylva Castanet.
Huh?
The Rumba Rumba Kingdom? Is there such a country?
Eh?
I've heard of it.
The country is small, but it's a very rich country with the rich countries of the diamonds and rubies.
Why did such a prince come to Japan alone?
The prince of the 17th generation of the Ylva Castanet.
He was caught up in the girl's affair of a show.
In short, he decided to escape from this country that he wanted to go to.
He was separated from the sheep and took the count's property.
I've never seen anything like this.
Demon!
Why are you like this?
These are horse heads.
I am Mambo, the man with the collar.
I am active as a police pig.
Now you know about me, right?
Then, I will feed you from now on.
I will protect the world and fulfill my wishes.
Aren't you happy?
Mambo seems to be very attached to Sochi.
I will appoint Sochi as Mambo's foster parent.
What?
I like Sochi.
So I will appoint her as my wife.
Wife?
She proposed to Reiko, even though she is a child.
There are many diamonds, rubies and sapphires.
How many diamonds are there?
Hundreds of millions.
Hot!
This is a diamond called "Stone of the Star" which is passed down to the Rumba Rumba family.
You can take it as a dowry for your wife.
I am happy!
Not you!
Senior!
If I can get it, I can marry her!
Um, Prince, may I?
Yes, you can.
I have a request.
I will refuse.
What?
Why?
You don't deserve to be the queen of the world.
Or you are not married.
Then...
No, I am not.
Marriage and love are not related to money.
What?
No!
Money is everything in the world!
What are you saying, Ryo?
Get out of the way!
Get out!
Now, Prince, don't take the side like these people..
Let's play a game.
Ryo?
No, no, no way!
Now, here you go, Prince.
Hey..
A successful man can change his personality easily.
Wait a minute.
I will give you an example.
We'll have to find something good.
Understood, Waltz-Aniiki.
Target has been captured.
Alright, let's launch.
Let's launch.
Can you hear me?
S-Shut up.
You want to see Tokyo?
Well, I came all the way to Japan.
You're hiding yourself in the middle of nowhere.
But you shouldn't be going out like this.
Here.
Ah! Leave everything to me!
Yeah, take good care of it.
You're a prince, aren't you?
I don't know what to do now.
It's alright. I'll go with you.
Kei-chan, wait here for some time.
Understood.
Be careful.
Take care of yourself.
First you should go to the taisha-kuten shop in Shimamoto.
Sounds good.
It's a good chance to take the prince to the Rumba Rumba Kingdom.
We can get a lot of thanks from the Botanobar Palace.
Let's get going.
Right.
3.
What are you doing?
Cheese!
Alright!
He hasn't become a single man, eh?
Wait for a chance!
Wait a minute!
This is the famous Yagiri-no-watashi.
Please come this way.
Wait a minute!
Did you get caught?
Prince!
Take this!
Someone!
Don't come up!
Prince!
Reiko!
Hold on tight!
Prince!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Reiko, they're after the prince!
Even so, they did it in a flashy way!
Why don't you practice?
Prince, I'll take care of it.
If you give it to Ryo-chan, it's the last time!
Don't say that!
Prince, I'll take care of it.
I'm glad no one got hurt.
Well, well.
Well, where should we go next?
Oh, that's right!
Let's go to a place where adults can play!
Adults play?
Yay!
I made it!
What do you mean, adults play?
I failed again!
Alright!
Next, let's bet on this horse.
Number 6, Rumbatango.
I like the name.
No, no!
That's a big-blooded candidate!
Alright!
Use this.
You can win with this.
Prince!
Are you sure about that?
Prince?
Oh, I can't!
I can't!
No matter how much money I collect, I can't win with this!
I won't even buy this racing car.
What are you talking about?
Prince, I don't like you.
You can't solve anything with money, you know?
You're right.
I want you to know that there are more important things than money in the world.
Shut up!
I don't want to hear any more nonsense!
Oh, Prince!
Hey, wait!
Hey!
Hehehehe...
Have you found it?
Your master is a troublemaker!
Boo! Boo! Boo!
Kukukukukuku...
Boo!
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh!
Hehehe...
Ah!
Heheh, it went well, didn't it, Walz-aniki?
There's no doubt in the strategy you've set up, Walz-sama.
All that's left is to put the prince on the ship we're leaving on tonight, and the mission is complete.
Prince, please be patient for a while.
Hmph!
Kukukukukuku...
Pull yourself together, Manpo! You're the police of the Lumba Lumba Kingdom, aren't you?
Bwee! Bwee! Bwee! Bwee! Bwee! Bwee!
What's wrong?
What's bothering you?
Senpai! Reiko-san! It's bad!
What's wrong, Kei-chan?
It seems that an international sniper has invaded Japan after targeting Prince Dilba!
Eh?
An international sniper has killed him?
Yes! That famous Fuga-13!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Chase them! Chase them!
I'm going to put them down no matter what!
That is me, Fuga-13!
Don't stand behind me!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
It's already this late...
Machi, let's change!
What are you doing?!
Machi, look! The prince is running away!
Idiot. What are you doing, idiot?
This song is...
Fuga-13!
If you're here, that means...
Right. Let's change the plan.
We're not going to catch the prince.
I'm going to kill him.
You guys are laughing boxes.
Waltz-aniki!
I'm hungry...
Huh?
What do you think of this red bean?
It's even got a tail.
You there! Give it to the world!
What the hell are you talking about?!
This guy is mine!
I'll give you a bow.
You bastard!
Don't eat things because you want a bow!
You're going to die!
You little...
Ah!
I'm hungry...
Give me a fattie!
I'll give you a fattie!
I'll give you a fattie...
Give me a fattie!
What's the fattie?
What the hell is this?
Finally, you're actually displeased.
When I was little, you were a little handsome, too.
Turned out different.
I...
Uh...
JIGGA! The world is money! Money is everything!
That man is living by mistake.
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Chase me! Chase me!
Alright! Now I can get even the star drops that the prince has!
Here!
Hurry up, Manpo! The prince is in danger!
There's no doubt that he was here.
He should be nearby.
This way!
Wait!
Who's there?
Now!
There he is.
Prince!
Oh, no! There's that man again!
And now!
I can't stand it!
Brrrr! Brrrr!
Fire, catch me!
Shizuku Hoshino!
Where did you go, Shizuku Hoshino?!
Mambo!
I wanted to see you!
Hiya.
Prince!
Reiko!
Watch out!
I'm sorry!
I'm going to arrest you!
You're safe now, Reiko!
Ryo!
Prince, are you hurt?
I...I was wrong.
Ryo!
Prince, you must be hungry.
No, Ryo.
I'm glad you're fine, Prince.
Thanks for your hard work.
Today was all thanks to Reiko.
Prince!
I'm glad you're safe!
Reiko, you're the butler's servant.
I'm pleased to see you.
All the servants of the Bossa Nova have been arrested.
I see.
I'm relieved.
I can go back to the Kingdom of Lumba Lumba.
Now, everyone,
I would like to greet Prince Jilba Castanet, the 17th Emperor.
Today,
I would like to thank you for attending my farewell party.
The friendship between Japan and the Kingdom of Lumba Lumba will never end.
I...
No, I, Jilba Castanet,
although it was a short time,
I learned something important that I will never forget in my next stay in Japan.
When I return home,
I will remember this valuable experience,
and I will swear to be a great king that will be admired by all the people.
Then, I, Prince,
will shake hands with everyone
and say goodbye to you all.
Reiko...
Prince, take this.
Be a wonderful king.
Yup.
Yep.
It's like a long- parfume day.
Long-personbel day?
Huh?
Oh, it's Mambo.
Were youторовr in an airplane?
We're ready to take the JetBlueJet rumahol to Nakagawa straightaway!
We're going to deliver Mambo to the place.
Let's go!
We are going to the Lumba Lumba King's house on a holiday this time!
It was after the rain that someone called me
I looked back and walked
I reached out to my mom
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black roadside of Ake-do-gai
I saw it
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgot
A wise politician with a great face
And a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You will meet everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Let's go!
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
I'm hungry!
Let me eat something!
I can eat anything!
Is it sushi, grilled meat, crab?
What? Strawberry?
Will a big man's stomach swell with such a thing?
Wait a minute
There is something more delicious over there!
The next time, I will buy strawberry for a man!
Nice to meet you!