Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I look up at the sunset that floats in the middle of the sea
I kick a pebble and fly to the end
I wonder if I'm going to the taiko that I jockeyed
I was laughed at that it was just a joke
Even if you cheer up somewhere, it's only for the sake of winning
The cityscape that doesn't change even if you yawn is strangely kind
The sun is already setting because the crows are crying
The grilled chicken is in the way
The beer is in the way
The
The sun is setting
Tomorrow will end soon too
But I lost my happiness again
I realized that I'm a fool
Yeah
"Higurashi Tazunete 3000 Ri"
Please take a look.
The battle stage of the Athens Olympics is ready.
All that's left is to wait for the opening ceremony.
Finally, the Athens Olympics.
Tomorrow's the opening ceremony, right?
It's the festival of sports held once every four years.
What's wrong, senpai?
Once every four years?
It's like something else happened.
What happened four years ago?
Four years ago was the 2000th anniversary.
That's right. The 2000th anniversary problem.
There was a time when the computer was misoperated
when the 2000th anniversary was about to happen.
After all, it wasn't big deal.
No, no, that's not it!
Something important other than that
I think I was a charismatic employee.
It was about four years ago.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's when there was a lot of charisma in town.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It seems that someone came.
The End
What's this document?
It's a file about the unsolved case.
No, no, the Olympics are about to start.
That guy hasn't woken up yet.
That guy? That guy means...
I see! This year is the year of the sunrise!
Let me explain the year of the sunrise for the first time.
The real name is "Higurashi Neruo".
He's a police officer.
He's a member of the Goenmai Police Station.
He used to like to sleep, but he's been sleeping for a long time.
Now he only wakes up once every four years, in the year of the Olympics.
In return, he has a great superpower.
In the short amount of time he's awake,
he can solve many unsolved cases.
That's why he doesn't get fired from the police.
However...
If he accidentally wakes up in the year of the Olympics,
it's a big deal, so you need to be careful.
Speaking of the year of the Olympics, it's the year of the sunrise.
I think Athene wanted to see it too.
What? You're still not here?
Wake him up quickly!
There are so many incidents that require his power!
We told you, didn't we?
Yeah...
Ryotsu, you take him with you.
No, you're the only one who's not here, so go with Nakagawa.
I think the room of Higurashi is...
Wake up, Higurashi!
The Olympics are starting!
What is it, Ryotsu?
Why are you here?
This is Higurashi's room!
Huh?
It's been my room since I replaced Ryo the other day.
Come to think of it,
there was no room for Higurashi when you replaced Ryo.
Then where is Higurashi now?
That's right!
Over there!
What a strange room!
There's a corpse of an unknown person.
It's a place where the corpse of an unknown person is placed, isn't it?
What kind of place is this?
He said he wanted to sleep in a quiet place.
It's quiet here, isn't it?
That's true.
It's probably around here...
Ah, this is it!
Hey, Higurashi, wake up!
He's not here!
What?
What's going on, Ryotsu?
I don't know, either!
I'm in charge of the
haunted room, but...
Where is Higurashi?
Higurashi?
He was sleeping in the haunted room!
Oh...
He was in locker C-3.
Locker C-3...
Oh, by the way...
Um...
The other day, he saw a foreign person
and he took him away.
What?
A foreign person?
Yes.
He's a resident of Saitama, his name is Mr. Megurashi.
His husband, who was in a coma for many years,
heard rumors that he passed away in Tokyo,
so his family came to look for him.
His physical condition is the same as his family's.
Above all, he had a paper written "Megurashi" on the locker.
Idiot!
Look carefully!
It's not a eye, it's a fire!
Oh, it's true.
I don't want you to be so surprised, but...
The person who was there was my officer.
What?
Listen, calm down.
He's alive!
What?
N-Nii-san...
He's so calm...
He's like a different person...
He must have suffered a lot in Tokyo...
He's moving!
It's just my imagination...
The house is closed...
I'm sure he did a good job.
It's okay, dad.
Did he set the power?
No, no one's coming out.
Maybe he's going to a funeral.
A funeral?
Yes, I think so.
I heard he was going to a special ceremony today.
You should have said something like that earlier!
I'm sorry.
If he dies, I'll be taken care of.
No, I think he's already taken care of...
Uh, do you have an emergency contact?
Like a cell phone?
Speaking of which, my little brother's cell phone is...
It's starting.
Oh, who is it?
Please hang up.
It's not working...
What should we do?
Yeah, yeah.
It's not Megurashi.
No, it's not.
Megurashi.
Senpai.
Huh?
What are you doing, Nakagawa?
You're just trying to see if Higurashi will be cremated or not.
This?
This is Megurashi's funeral.
This is it!
Oh!
This is the house.
There's no doubt about it.
It says the funeral place.
Call me right away!
Yes.
If Megurashi was the funeral place, it's definitely our house.
I see.
Call the organization immediately!
Even if you say that, the funeral was just over and everyone went to the cremation site.
What?
Cremation!
Huh?
Nakagawa, let's go!
Yes.
Anyway, if we don't stop it, Higurashi will be cremated!
We can't use the phone for about 10 minutes.
Now our Hikari Cable is open.
Now the family's cremation is ready.
Damn it!
Why doesn't it work?
Oh, Higurashi.
The last farewell.
Brother, I don't have to have painful memories anymore.
Sleep well.
I felt like I moved.
Stop it.
You won't be able to travel to that world without worry.
It's okay.
Yes.
I heard Higurashi's voice.
Brother is saying goodbye to everyone.
Don't burn it!
Huh?
It's hot.
What's wrong with you?
Dad, Mom.
Ichiro!
What are you doing?
I was surprised because it was written in the newspaper that my funeral would be held.
Then, the one burning in here is...
I told you, the person in front is the one passing by the fire!
That's right...
Sushi! Sushi is here!
Your Highness!
Ryo-san!
Did you see what just happened?
What?
There was a sunfish here!
I couldn't see anything.
Is it just me?
Where is the sunfish?
It's Ryo-san!
Episode 8 "The Sudden Trap"
What's wrong? Why are you here?
Hey, BITE!
You're no good!
How could you just stand out like this?
How long have you been in the army?
Since 2004.
It's been 4 years.
What about you, Mooms?
You've been the leader of the new Goma-Kitteco.
I-I feel it!
This is the sign of crime!
The culprit is waiting for the prey in the haunted mansion.
It's pitch black.
I'm scared.
Give me back my wallet!
It's real!
What's going on, Ryotsu?
Where is Higurashi?
I want to know!
I was inside, but...
There's no way out of the incinerator.
It's me.
Slipped at the amusement park?
Don't call me for that!
That's not what I'm here for.
Higurashi has disappeared.
What?
Higurashi is the one who caught Sli?
Why is Higurashi in the haunted mansion?
Maybe it's a person.
Huh?
What?
I'm not scared.
You're just a child.
Right?
It's been a long time, Ryotsu Nakagawa!
You look too good!
I found you in this amusement park.
You were in the crematorium!
Huh?
Everyone's waiting.
Let's go back to the book.
Yeah.
Ah, Higurashi.
What's wrong?
Can't you just tell that this is the haunted mansion?
I can't believe you're in the crematorium.
Stop it!
Don't ever bring up that word!
Hinga.
Take her away.
Stop it!
Do you really need this?
Man, what's going on?
The leader of the monbutsu!
Did you see that, Nakagawa?
Y-Yes...
A teleportation?
You're so stupid to say such nonsense!
I said it's true!
I saw it with my own eyes, too.
I still can't believe it.
He can only stay awake for 24 hours.
If we bring him back to his daily life as soon as possible,
this kind of incident is waiting for us.
I'll call you back.
Yes, this is the exit.
Mr. Higurashi!
What?!
Where are you now?
Huh? Mr. Fujii?
Yeah.
When I woke up, I was here.
I happened to catch someone trying to take a nap,
so I caught him.
Oh, I see.
I'll call you back right away.
Can't you come back from there in a flash?
A teleportation?
You didn't notice it yourself?
You've mastered the ability to teleport!
Huh?
You're right.
But I don't know how to do it.
I see.
That's what I'm talking about.
You go get him right away.
I got it.
Over there.
Huh?
Thank you for helping.
It's a matter of course.
Well, I'll tell you when I'm back.
I'll wait for you with long hair.
Hey, sir.
What is it?
Can I have a moment with you?
To take a nap feels awkward.
Arrg!
Can't be helped.
Just this one.
Thanks.
Fire
What's wrong Higurashi-san?
The fire, the fire
The fire!
The fire, the fire, the fire
That reminds me, I saw the fire earlier
The fire!
Turn off the fire!
Did you make it?
I don't want fire!
Ryo-san, help me!
Oh, it's gone.
Ah!
It moved again!
When it sees fire, it moves instantly.
First, the crematorium, then the fireball of the haunted house, and then the fire of the lighter.
I see.
So where is Higurashi now?
Where is he now?
Yes, the exit to the park.
Kagoshima?
I can see the Sakurajima well.
I can see it erupt.
Erupt?
It's erupted. It's blowing fire.
Fire! Fire!
Don't look at the fire, Higurashi!
Ah!
Higurashi!
Hey, Higurashi!
Answer me!
Higurashi!
It moves instantly again!
Ah!
Yes, the exit to the park.
Higurashi!
Where is he now?
Ah!
What?
Hawaii?
Ryo-san, bring him here right away!
Don't say that!
Senpai, it's not far from my Concorde.
I'll be there soon.
Then, let's go!
I came all the way to Hawaii, but I can't see anything.
It can't be helped.
If you see fire, it will move instantly.
You can take it off.
Ryo-san, what is this?
It's an unsolved case file.
Do you see it here?
By the way, where do you see it?
Let me stand a little longer.
You only can get up for 24 hours!
Halfway through.
You don't have time to rest.
I see.
Wow!
We can see it!
It's the culprit of the 2 billion yen robbery.
Where are you?
I can see the river.
A river?
It's the Northern Senju.
Here!
Okay, I'll contact Japan immediately!
Okay, I got it!
We'll arrest him with a $200,000 bribe!
Why did you find out here?
This guy is on the bullet train now.
He'll be arriving at Tokyo Station soon!
We'll arrest him now!
He's wearing a wig and glasses and working as a barber.
He's working at a convenience store near his house!
The culprit of this case is actually the oldest son of the house next door!
Oh, Higurashi. Welcome back.
Thank you for the food.
It's been a long time.
We'll be back soon.
You're still here? I'm hungry.
What are you talking about?
You can only stay up for 24 hours!
You can take a break.
Right.
Nakagawa, go buy something.
Yes, sir.
I guess we'll have to stay up.
Hey! What are you doing?
What did you say?
The cigarette.
Did you forget?
Higurashi can move at any time when he sees the fire!
O-Oh, I see...
My throat is dry, too.
Reiko, bring me some tea.
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute!
What's wrong, Ryotsu?
From this room, I can see the fire from the gas stove!
I see.
I'm sorry, Reiko.
Could you get us something to drink?
Yes, sir.
I'll be back in a minute.
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask you for a favor.
I'll go.
You're starting the Athens Olympics today?
Yes.
The opening ceremony is about to begin.
I asked you to record a video of your "Friend Who Can Laugh" phone call.
I paid you for your part-time job.
I forgot about it.
I'll show you when I'm done with work.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I have to find someone who's recording.
What?
The opening ceremony is just around the corner.
What's wrong, Higurashi?
The fire! The fire! The fire!
The fire is finally on the fire station.
The fire! The fire!
Ryotsu, can we go to Hawaii again?
Don't go!
It disappeared!
Damn it!
He liked the Olympics more than the three meals!
You don't have a call, do you, Higurashi?
It's almost 24 hours.
I have a little concern.
What is it?
Higurashi's teleportation.
First, he's in a nearby amusement park.
Next, he's in Mt. Fuji.
Next, he's in Kagoshima.
Next, he's in Hawaii.
He's getting farther and farther.
What?
That's it!
It's a bit late, but he's going to be here.
Well, it's related to the Olympics broadcast.
But here's some shocking news from the United States.
The subject of the event is this video from a Mars investigator.
It's about a scientific life form discovered on Mars.
It's a video from the Mars investigator.
What is this?
Higurashi!
Why on Mars?
Do humans live on Mars?
Maybe he awakened to a new ability.
I may have awakened to a new power.
There's something written on the ground.
I'm sleepy.
So I sleep here.
Come to wake me up in four years.
How are you going to wake me up?
Don't worry about scandals anymore.
Cry and sleep. Play entonces.
You swirled it into the end of work report and threw it away.
There's no argument about it.
Be a fool.
You are good-natured and poor.
Am I?
If you want to do, do it in my way.
High afternoon, thunder in my stomach.
♪ The smoke comes from the fire ♪
♪ When you run and run, you're a turtle ♪
♪ That's a good thing, isn't it? ♪
♪ To the flower garden ♪
♪ Chaito! ♪
♪ The mass-produced typhoon ♪
♪ Maidoo! ♪
♪ It's going to blow up ♪
♪ Aka-ra-ka-bombe! Kyu-rai-ku! ♪
♪ Jugemu Jugemu ♪
♪ The emperor is fishing ♪
♪ in his high-school suit ♪
♪ The water is waiting, the sea is waiting ♪
♪ The wind is waiting, the sea is waiting ♪
♪ The place where you can sleep ♪
♪ Yamura Koji, Murakoji ♪
♪ Paipo, Paipo, Paipo ♪
♪ Churinkan, Churinkan ♪
♪ The Kurendai, Kurendai ♪
♪ The Honpoko tea, Honpoko na ♪
♪ The super-famous Chosuke! ♪
What?
Do you want to show the children a good place
and go camping?
Are you okay?
It's scary to look at nature in a sweet way.
I can't help it.
I'll be your strength here.
Terai, do your best!
Next time,
"Papa is camping!"
I'm looking forward to it!
Thank you for watching!
♪ There's a turtle over there ♪
♪ There's a turtle for sure ♪
♪ Come on, everyone ♪
♪ to our town ♪
Thank you!