Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble ♪
♪ And flew to the end ♪
♪ I wonder if I'll be able to ♪
♪ Be a good girl ♪
♪ That's what I laughed at ♪
♪ Wherever I go ♪
♪ I'll be fine ♪
♪ The cityscape is the only thing that matters ♪
♪ And the cityscape is the only thing that matters ♪
♪ It's a kind village ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ So I'll be giving them a hat ♪
♪ The grilled chicken is so popular ♪
♪ Is it? ♪
♪ I'll give you a cap ♪
♪ And a hat ♪
♪ So I'll give you a cap ♪
♪ Yeeeeee!! ♪
That was cute!
Ryo-chan.
This is the udon bowl with instant udon on top of rice.
Udon bowl?
The nutrition is not balanced.
But it's good for the price.
Do you think I like it?
I have no choice but to do this.
I can't stand it.
Stop it, Ryo-san.
Feel my pain.
You lost.
Is it a horse?
No.
Ryo-san is honest.
I was a fool to be on my father's side.
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-san, you idiot.
Did you do something again?
Say it.
Say it quietly.
What did you do?
Calm down, Bu-chan.
Tell me honestly.
What did you do?
You won't remember it even if I told you.
The inspector called you.
What?
The inspector called you?
The inspector?
Your name makes me shiver.
What did you do, Ryo-chan?
Do you remember?
Did you find out that I drew the general's face on the Batocard?
What did you do?
Or maybe that.
Ah, maybe that.
That much?
What should I do? My heart is pounding.
It doesn't matter.
But...
Anyway, come with me.
I'll cut your nose off at any cost.
I don't want to cut your nose.
Director, this is Ohara. I've brought Ryotsu here.
Come in.
Y-Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm truly sorry about this.
It was all thanks to my director's bad manners.
Please forgive me.
Please.
Raise your head, Ohara.
Actually, Ohara.
I came here today to thank you for your words of praise.
The general himself came to see me.
I see.
Let me explain.
Director Ryotsu.
You must have saved an old man who fell off a bicycle the other day.
Director Ryotsu. You must have saved an old man who fell off a bicycle the other day.
An old man?
Oh, I see!
Director Ryotsu.
Ouch!
I'm fine.
See you later.
I fell off again.
Ah!
Help me! Help me!
Who's laughing?
Are you alright, old man?
I hit my back.
I can't get up.
Stay strong.
Alright.
Here.
My back hurts.
This isn't good, Akira!
Stay strong!
Go away.
I'm sorry.
That's enough.
Don't say that.
Well, I guess I was once often told to stay here.
Do you have any regrets?
You said so many things to me, but I didn't say nothing.
That piece of paper!
It hit right in front of me!
Why?
Hm? I've got some business in the Edo area.
I'm going home with my father.
Oh, so you're the same as your father.
Well, if you say so.
I'm a policeman who is close to the free trade.
I'm sorry.
Thanks to you, I was saved.
I see.
You're getting old, so don't overdo it.
By the way, may I ask your name?
It's not that important.
My name is Ryozu Kankichi.
See you.
This old man is the richest man in Japan.
He's a rich man.
A rich man?
No, he's just a poor old man.
A wealthy man is dressed like that when he visits his company with no money.
Don't judge him just by his appearance.
I see.
A wealthy man is very impressed with your performance.
He's said he will be a sponsor of a commercial to recruit more policemen like you to become a policeman.
I see.
So, I'll take your recommendation.
You become the sponsor.
I'm going to be in a movie.
Ryo...Ryotsuga?
That's right.
I'll be the role model for all the police officers.
I'll be counting on you.
Ha ha.
I got it.
If that's the case, I'll take responsibility.
I'll do it.
Speaking of money,
He's the one who built that honest group.
Do you have a relationship with the Nagagawa concert?
Of course.
You must know my father, too.
I don't know him at all.
Of course.
So, what kind of person is he?
I don't know much about it.
But he's a business man.
He's a business man.
He doesn't have a wife or kids.
I heard that he'll donate all his assets to the facility.
How much is his assets?
I don't think it's one or two trillion yen.
If it's that big, it's no big deal.
One or two trillion is more exciting.
Listen, Ryotsu.
Don't let him get away with it.
I know.
Listen.
Don't be so stubborn.
Hey, old man.
Are you okay with your waist?
Don't call me old man for a reason.
Thank you for the trouble.
It's okay.
We're almost at the real thing.
That's right.
Do it well.
Don't yawn!
Let's start the real thing!
3, 2...
Shut up!
Don't draw the head!
You can't draw properly, you idiot!
Ugh, you're so noisy!
Leave me alone, you big-eyed old man!
Huh?
What do you mean, "big-eyed old man"?
I said "big-eyed old man" because you're a big-eyed old man!
What?!
It's because you don't draw properly!
That's because you're always so "gami-gami", "gami-gami", "gami-gami",
I get so motivated when you say that!
-I see. -You can't say that!
-Alright! -I said "gami-gami"!
-Pull the camera! -I said "gami-gami"!
-Take those two! -I said it!
You said it, you big-eyed old man!
You always worry about me!
That's the problem!
I'm already a great adult!
What?
You really don't want your parents to know that!
It's okay! Just leave me alone!
So, you're going to appear in the movie?
No, the director liked my acting,
so...
I changed the script right away.
If you're the director,
you can just do what you normally do in the office.
Well, okay.
Oh, it's time for the commercial.
Yeah.
Oh, this is it!
It's well-made!
You split the paper!
Shut up!
Oh, the director's here too!
Wow, it's pretty good for a TV show!
Amazing!
I can't believe you two are acting!
It's okay.
You always worry about me,
so I'm already a great adult!
What?
Are you okay?
I'm okay!
What?
Wow!
-Your smile is amazing! -It's a great commercial!
-Really! -I'm looking for a police officer.
What?
Are the director and I parents?
I-it's not a joke.
Who would be the father of such a fool?
I'm not joking either!
But why did it turn out like this?
I don't know.
It's usually you.
No, it's the director.
I hope nothing happens to him.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I know.
Then, there's nothing at all to say.
"You two can leave. Bye."
If you two will become real parents,
That's ridiculous.
Who did such a thing to us?
I want to ask,
what did you...
What?
You two worked really hard.
But...
Why are you always back on your word?
I decided to tell you.
It's not time to lie.
It's time for the fire to cool down.
You can lie, Ohara-kun.
But, to lie is...
If the police finds out about this,
the police's trust will be in shambles.
Then, you'll be held responsible.
You understand, Ohara-kun?
Y-yes.
That's good.
Then, there's one more troublesome thing.
What is it?
The rich man wants to invite you two to his home.
You're not his parents.
R-really, Ryotsu?
I don't understand.
If you go through this gate,
you'll be with your father and child.
It's not a relationship between you and Ryotsu.
I understand, Taro.
Pa-Papa...
K-Kankichi...
You must be having a bad dream.
Well, this rich man is honest.
When he saw you two at first sight, he was convinced.
This is the true father and child.
There's a bond between parents and children that no one can hide.
Y-yes.
So charming.
R-right.
Oh, Ryo-kun...
Well, I'm deeply moved by what you said...
This is our great family.
I only have my hoe, but I should be careful.
My home.
K-Kankichi...
O-ok!
What do you mean?
The house where all parents live.
Oh, I was going to ask you a question.
What do you mean?
they will think I am their home and let me be.
I see.
This or that is hard.
Hey, Ryotsu, you are a way too dirty mimicry.
But, sir…
Ryotsu, sir?
No, Ryo…
you must use both hands.
We have to use our hands.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can't do anything bad, K-K-Kichi.
But, but, but, but...
This Yuno-mi has a 200,000 yen banknote.
What?
There's a banknote on everything.
Even for tropical fish.
What are you talking about?
We always give you a discount so that you can tell the value of things.
Is this really the price for everything?
Of course. It's all fair.
They've been living a business life, and they don't have a wife or children.
I heard that if they die, they'll donate all their wealth to the facility.
There are no children.
The money will rot.
If you do it right, I'll be the one to get the money.
You idiot!
What if 250,000 yen is broken?
It's 200,000 yen.
Hurry up and blow it up.
This carpet is worth 10 million yen.
No, no, no.
You've been raising K-Kichi for so long.
You must be really tired.
Well, that's right.
This idiot son of a bitch is really struggling.
I can't hide my feelings even if I say it on my face.
These two have been going to the Beigawa River these days.
The Beigawa? No!
You know what?
These two went to the Beigawa River the other day.
This is why I heard the police made a consequence against them.
I see.
The Beigawa and Ryotsu have gone to be걸 a rubber was in the field again.
This is bad.
They're strong enough.
If my grandpa found out about the school, how would he feel then?
What kind of child was Kankichi?
He was the best at school, and always in the class.
That's good, but who would be the best at the sports festival?
There was a frog.
Oh, a frog!
There was a fly.
A fly?
Because flies are fast.
There was a bee, papa.
A bee...
Because it's hard to get stung by a bee.
How kind of you to say that.
Of course, papa.
Thank you, Kankichi.
You're welcome, papa.
Kankichi...
You're a beautiful boy.
I'm so happy to see my father in Japan.
Let's go to the bath together!
To the bath?
Why the bath?
The bath is the origin of my father.
He's naked like this.
He's still a baby, but he doesn't hide anything.
This is the ideal for me, to talk with my son and grandchildren.
Papa, papa.
I'm going to wash your back.
Oh, sure.
Then, I'm going to wash Kanemojita's back.
I see...
Papa, you have a big back.
That's a bad thing.
As a man with a big heart like this,
I'm a good boy, so I don't mind small things.
Oh, I see.
So you're saying that you want me to forget that Ryotsu went to the church.
That's not good.
Hey, Kanemochida-san.
If a child does something wrong,
it's natural for a parent to scold him, right?
Of course, that's right.
Right?
For example, during work...
No, no, no!
Hey, do it stronger!
Yeah!
I got it, papa!
Let's change, Kanchichi.
You like hot hot water, don't you?
I'm dying!
없어!
You're going to get cold if you don't remove my shoulder!
You should stop like this for the best of the best!
Wow!
I got it wrong!
You're going to get cold if you don't move!
Kanchichi!
I'm telling you, I'm seriously attracted to you!
You're not?
You're so mean!
Now, let's have a drink after the bath.
- A drink? - No!
If there's any alcohol in the bath...
That's a good feeling.
- Let's have another drink. - Let's go!
I feel so good when I see you.
I wish I had a son like you.
"Honest Life"
This is the motto I've lived for 80 years.
Honesty is the best.
I'll never forgive anyone who lies.
"Honest Life"
This is a word without a meaning.
But...
What do you think of me?
You can lie, Ohara.
If the police find out about this,
they'll be shocked.
Then you'll be responsible for this!
Actually, Mr. Money.
What?
Speaking of my father,
there's an old man named Ohara at the police station.
This old man is so noisy.
He's a fool.
And he's a fool.
He's annoying me every day.
What?
That's not good.
You can call a fool a fool.
I can do whatever I want.
You think so?
You're so smart, old man.
Hey, Ryo.
No, Kankichi.
You don't have to call me that.
OK.
But,
I won't say it,
but I need to thank him.
He's a fool and I love him a lot.
He's like my father.
Like his father's words.
To be honest, I'm not a very good policeman.
I have a lot of work to do, and I also play pachinko and horse racing while I'm working.
But every time I hear him say that he's stupid, I remember my father here.
Look, my father always says, "Don't lie even if you get a mochi."
"Be honest more than a man-eating chicken!"
So I shoot him without hiding anything.
That's great.
What a honest man.
Father, can't you let me have Kankichi as a servant?
A servant?
I refuse.
I have a responsibility to take care of this papa.
I like it more and more.
Please, please, please.
I did it! The plan was a success!
Please raise your head, Kanemochida.
I'm the one who has to lower my head.
I'm truly sorry.
I did something wrong.
Everyone was lying.
P-P-P-Papa!
That's enough, Ryotsu.
I don't have any family with this man.
I'm not a parent or anything.
I'm a stranger to the red.
What do you mean, papa?
I'm the boss that this man was talking to.
I've been playing a fake parent and child for the sake of the police.
Wh-Wh-What?
You're wrong! You're wrong!
Papa has a habit of saying things that make no sense.
You see, he looks just like me.
Hm? Hm? Hm?
I was an idiot.
I don't want to be called an idiot.
I was taught how to act like an idiot by this man, so I woke up.
Papa!
That's enough!
This trip was a great help.
I'm the red stranger.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
After the rain, someone called me
I looked back and walked
I reached out to my mother
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked on the black road
I walked on the black road
I was a child once, but I forgot
A politician with a great face
A blue lady in front of me
Look up at that corner
I can see everyone
There is a camera over there
I'm sure there is a camera
Come to our town
There is a camera over there
I'm sure there is a camera
Come to our town
To the town of the old man
Thank you!
The young people in the town are lecturing me?
Do you think I'm that old?
Can you see me?
I'll prove it!
Please watch!
Next time, "The funny man with salt"
See you!
There's a turtle over there
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!