Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ When you watch TV, ♩
♪ light up the room ♩
♪ and try to get away from it ♩
♪ Hello, ♩
♪ goodbye ♩
♪ If you want to, ♩
♪ just stay overnight ♩
♪ and you'll be home soon ♩
♪ Don't panic ♩
♪ In this small town ♩
♪ Where are you going? ♩
♪ Just turn around ♩
♪ Maybe ♩
♪ there's someone better than me ♩
♪ If there's somebody ♩
♪ Let me know ♩
♪ Let me know all night long ♩
♪ I don't hate waiting ♩
♪ Because I'm a turtle woman ♩
♪ I don't want to lose, ♩
♪ a gold woman ♩
♪ I'll love you for all my life ♩
I can't stop myself from smiling, the one and only woman of Kamen Rider!
On the corner of laughter, Ebisu-kun!
Ryo-chan, what are you making this time?
It's a character doll of the TV series.
Until now, you were making a model gun with a wooden grip, weren't you?
Yeah, but I had to stop because it was time-consuming.
If it's a character doll, you can make one of the same type of metal, and it can be mass-produced.
This month, I'm spending all of my life on this.
But you're really good at carving.
When I was a kid, I was a genius at carving with a pencil.
I can make anything.
Then, what about a bear souvenir from Hokkaido?
It can be made in five minutes.
The face of the chief can be made in two minutes.
Two minutes?
Well, look.
I'm called the Michelangelo of the bear, and I can't do anything.
See? It's done.
Wow!
It's exactly like it.
That's why I said I was a genius.
You should make a little more expression.
Your eyes are a little bit dull.
The bottom of your nose is longer.
All right.
It's done.
You look like a real genius.
Huh?
A real genius?
Who's a genius?
No, no, no.
I said you could make it.
The second one.
What?
What's this?
You were doing something else, Ryotsu?
No, no.
This is a bonito.
A bonito.
Oh.
Then, try it.
What?
It's a bonito, right?
Y-Yes, it is.
This bonito is the best.
Eat it all.
Don't leave any.
Of course.
Ryo.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It's delicious.
By the way, Nakagawa and Reiko,
I've brought a new member who's been transferred from the police department to my house.
Ebisu, come on in.
Yes.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
I'm Ebisu.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nakagawa.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Reiko Akimoto.
Ebisu is such a lucky name.
Yes.
You can say hello to me.
I'm eating you.
Reiko, water.
Water.
Yes.
Here's some water, Ryo.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you laughing all of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm a laughing person.
There's a limit to a laughing person.
My parents are such a bright family.
I couldn't stop laughing since I was a child.
Thanks to them, I can't get back to my smile.
It's good that you're bright.
It's too bright.
I can't stop talking about you.
I'm trying to be serious but it's too much to
It's so funny.
Ebisu, why did you become a prostitute?
Yes, because of this personality.
I don't want to be a prostitute.
Here, it's katsudon.
You must be hungry.
If you eat it, you'll be a good girl.
Why is katsudon so popular in this kind of situation?
Ebisu, don't laugh!
I'm sorry.
But I'm going to talk to my mother in my hometown and make her laugh.
What is this guy?
Shut up!
Hey, don't do that!
Yes, sir!
I'm in such a state.
Then you're not a police officer.
Really?
You're really something, chief.
Then, Gariotsu, go patrol with Ebisu.
Right!
With me?
Of course. You'll be the instructor.
This laughing bag? Instructor, huh?
Thank you.
It started again.
Don't laugh. I'm going to patrol.
Hey, patrol!
This guy is useless.
I'm going.
Hey, get a hold of yourself. I'm going.
Walk properly.
I'm sorry.
I don't feel well.
You're really something.
I'm not free.
Is that person okay with his work?
If you leave it to Gariotsu, he'll be able to handle it.
Gariotsu, it might be hard.
What's so funny now?
You're not going to patrol, are you?
I'm sorry.
Don't be
Sorry...
It's just that...
I can't get that car.
Eddie soany, is it?
What's wrong with the sedan?
Are you sick?
You're laughing at me for nothing.
I'm in pain, you're laughing too hard.
I need help.
You should do something.
I don't know what I did.
Excuse me...
This is not what I intended.
I'll clean it up.
I've been doing it for a while, but I've been indiscriminate lately.
I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble, too.
If you go to ask for a rakugo, what are you going to do?
Well, I just saw the signboard at the theater.
It's a mysterious Kobu-en.
Why is the name Kobu-en?
It's strange. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can't go because I'm in trouble.
What's going to happen if I go inside?
Then, if your father Sanpei is alive, you're laughing.
The manga is also laughing for two hours just by touching the boy's jump.
You're having a hard time.
I have been educated to be lucky to laugh.
I will blame my parents.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter? Why are you laughing all of a sudden?
I'm sorry. I can't stop laughing.
You're making a fool of yourself.
Don't mess with me.
Hey, what's wrong?
I was hit by a laugh in the face.
Of course. The people of the lower town are short-tempered.
Don't be nervous and follow me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I laugh when I see you.
It's an accident.
Are you all right?
Somehow...
Don't laugh.
I'm sorry.
Sir, I'm sorry, but this is...
Can you deliver it to the Onigawara village?
All right.
Ebisu, deliver this light.
No way.
I can't go to the funeral with this face.
Just leave it as it is.
I'll verify the accident.
But...
Go.
Yes, sir.
I'm in trouble.
I'm the worst at being nervous.
No.
But it's my first job since I've been fired.
I have to endure it somehow.
I'm sorry.
It's me.
It's nothing.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help this time.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Also.
Hey Mama, that child looks great.
Master Kofuku's
No more!
Good, good.
It's good that you're not badly injured.
Even so, Ebisu is late.
Thank you, I'm late.
What's with that face?
You got hit again?
I always buy a gift certificate except for the lucky seat.
What a useless guy.
It's not funny at all.
I'm sorry.
Even Ryotsu couldn't get it.
He's walking with the bomb.
But he can't patrol.
His work in the station is difficult.
Let's go to the other place.
Um...
What's wrong, Ebisu?
Don't be so flustered.
Actually, I'm about to faint.
The toilet is in the back.
Go to the toilet.
Escape.
And this is how I call you.
I'm sorry...
I will ask you again.
Alright.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Let me walk with you.
I'm going to get a heart attack!
Hey, Reiko! You're not the only one who's laughing!
It's because Ebisu-san laughs so much!
I can't believe my jokes, which have been made fun of by the others, have been accepted so much!
It's the best!
I can't stand it!
Hey, don't laugh! You're just making your father laugh!
Even if you say that...
Ebisu-san, are you sure you don't have to go to the bathroom?
That's right!
I'm a little short, so I'm going to say "I'm short!"
I'm going to burst!
What's going on?
I don't like it. What have I done?
You're laughing.
It 's because you 're going to the bathroom!
It seems that Ebisu 's laughter draws good luck to everyone.
Even if you laugh at your dad's funny jokes, you won't get good luck.
What?
Hey! It's a joke!
Hold on.
Even if I can't patrol, I might be able to use this.
It's almost time to pee and pee.
Ebisu-kun, would you like to go to the library with me?
Yes.
What are you going to do, Chief?
It has nothing to do with you.
Nakagawa, Reiko, you guys take care of the rest.
Yes.
Hayashi, don't smell anything.
Hey, I'm going out too.
Senior!
Ryo-chan, you're...
Chief-chan, you're...
How about this?
Friday, today's lunch is a fried egg.
Saturday, it's been a while since I went home, so I'm going to eat gobu-sata.
That's not funny.
Sunday, I'm not going to wake up until noon today.
Why is this dad joke so funny?
It's true.
Monday, I'm not going to read anything other than Jump.
I don't think you can read anything.
That's right.
He's using Ebisu to make dad jokes and make us get angry.
Ohara-kun, what are you doing here?
Chief!
Actually...
What?
I'll get angry no matter what kind of joke you say.
Really?
Yes.
As long as Ebisu-kun is here, you will definitely get angry.
I'll try to make you laugh too.
I see.
Then, one more thing.
I forgot my hat and I got a hat.
I got it.
I've been making so many jokes.
How is it?
I told you.
Then, one more thing.
Wednesday, I'm going to the garden to plant trees.
I can't stop laughing anymore.
It's so painful.
Thursday, I'm going to put on an umbrella in the rain.
He's going to die.
Wonderful, Ohara-kun.
I can't stand it anymore.
What?
Is it okay for a police officer to make dad jokes while he's working?
You want to be laughed at too, don't you?
No.
I'm jealous because we are the ones who are taking over.
Right, Ohara-kun?
That's right, chief.
It's not like that.
Ebisu, you are also you.
Come here.
I have a stomachache.
I won't eat.
It's okay.
We took over the job.
Chief, it's okay.
Our jokes are holding everyone's laugh.
Even if Ebisu-kun is not here, it's okay.
No, it's not.
That's right.
Then, one more time.
The train announcer said this.
Please wait a while until you arrive in Chiba.
That's a bad joke.
The worst dad joke.
Really.
Hello.
I said please wait a while.
It's not funny without Ebisu-san.
Let's go, everyone.
Ebisu, you didn't join the police to become the head of the club, did you?
Well...
You did it to protect the safety of the citizens and fight against evil, didn't you?
Yes.
Then don't laugh again.
That's impossible.
It's the same as being told not to breathe.
Shut up.
If the police were laughing, the citizens wouldn't trust you.
I'd like to ask you something.
Yes.
What is it, grandma?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so flustered when people are in trouble?
What?
Mr. Omawari.
Is there a Sky Mansion around here?
Yes.
It's that brick-colored building.
Oh, is that so?
Thank you very much, Mr. Omawari.
Look.
It's because you're flustered that you're like this.
Listen.
Don't laugh.
If you can't do it, you're out of luck.
I guess I'm not fit for the police.
I hate parents who are so flustered.
You're probably depressed, but you're smiling.
I'm already...
Stop being a cop.
Mr. Omawari, this is bad.
The robbers are coming.
The female employee is a hostage.
Robbers?
I shouldn't laugh at this time.
That's right.
What?
The robbers are hiding in the fourth floor?
Okay, I got it.
I'll be right there.
Nakagawa, come with me.
Reiko, contact the office.
Davis.
Senior.
How many criminals are there?
One.
But he has a gun.
One?
Okay, I'll convince him.
Hey, criminal.
It's the police.
The brick-colored building is already surrounded.
We can't escape.
Give up and behave yourself.
Shut up.
There's a hostage here.
We'll be caught easily.
It's dangerous to jump into it.
Damn it.
Is there any good idea?
What?
Okay.
Let's convince Davis.
What?
Me?
If you, the laughing Jogo, convince him while laughing, the culprit will be Hirumu.
In the meantime, Nakagawa and I will do something.
But don't laugh at me.
It's okay. Go away.
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to convince you.
Who's laughing at me in such a tense state?
You're kidding me.
If you laugh more, this guy's head...
You said there would be a hole in the wall, didn't you?
Don't laugh.
I'm serious.
Even if you say that...
I said don't laugh.
Why did you say that?
Because it's really funny.
I didn't know this was a model gun.
Damn it.
What? It was a model gun?
Didn't you laugh at me?
Stupid culprit.
Don't laugh at me.
Damn it.
There's still a trump card.
Look at this.
Dynamite!
Damn it! I can't jump in with this!
Hahaha! He even prepared dynamite!
Hahaha! But he forgot the lighter and couldn't tell the
video line!
Hahaha!
I forgot it.
Ah!
Hahaha! I can't believe I really forgot!
Hahaha!
Help me!
Very good.
Hahaha!
Haha!
What happened?
Hahaha!
Its done!
Haha!
Hahaha!
I was laughing too much and fainted.
You're really amazing.
What? Ebisu quit?
He made a lot of money, why?
He said that the police wouldn't let him.
He quit the police because he quit the police service.
What?
There was a department that wanted him because he played a role in Ebisu's performance yesterday.
He was assigned to that department.
I didn't know there was such a funny man.
Maybe this is a laughing voice.
It's not just a joke.
When an incident happens on the land,
it's all over the place.
The special detective is the leader of the Three Glasses.
Kaipan Dekan.
It's been a while.
The chief of the police station in front of the park.
So it's you, Kaipan Dekan.
What are you here for?
We have new friends in the special detective department.
So we're here to introduce them.
New friends?
Come in.
Laugh all you want.
Hello, everyone.
This is Ebisu.
So you're the one who said you wanted Mr. Ebisu.
Of course.
He's my chief detective.
You're working in this outfit.
Unbelievable.
I can't stop laughing.
That's why.
I knew it.
This is the only place where you want Mr. Ebisu.
I'm counting on you, Laugh-Dekan.
Yes, Kaipan Senpai.
Thank you, Mr. Ebisu.
It was funny today.
It was so fun.
No problem.
Please take care of Mr. Ebisu.
How will it reflect in your eyes?
After a fight, you always give me a short kiss
You, with tears in your eyes, were so dear to me
In that way, how many things can I get
With such irreplaceable things?
In my whole life, how many things can I get?
You are me and I am you
That's all that I need to be satisfied
You, see, just laughing
I felt that I was healed of any suffering
Were you all looking forward to the Trump battle?
Wasn't it interesting?
All right, everybody, get invited.
It's the Trump competition.
Wait, you don't notice that the anime is all about Trump.
Next episode, "Fight! Trump'sterrorism Changingcorporation"
Thanks for watching!