"The Valentine's Day"
Ryo, it's almost Valentine's Day.
Huh? What do you mean?
That's a ridiculous custom made by a guy from a candy shop to sell chocolates.
Oh, right. It was a day that had nothing to do with Ryo-san.
I want chocolates, too!
Somebody, give me some!
"The Valentine's Day"
When you watch TV, make your room bright and look away!
Come to me, you poor thing!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky.
The white clouds.
It'll be all right eventually.
Come to me, you jobless guy!
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Come to me, you poor thing!
Look at the red clouds.
The red clouds.
It'll be all right eventually.
You got it, right?
I got it! I got it!
If you got it, just keep quiet and come to me!
"The Valentine's Day"
You're fast.
You're already 21st century.
What's wrong?
When I was a kid, in the 21st century, I thought all cars were driving in the tube.
I've seen it, too.
I never imagined it'd happen.
"The Valentine's Day"
But, in reality, cars are still rolling on the ground and driving on the same road as pedestrians.
This is the reason why accidents happen.
I wonder if only cars will never happen in the future.
I hope no accidents happen.
"The Valentine's Day"
Senpai, I found a bicycle that's not likely to have any accidents.
I found a bike that's not likely to fall.
What?
A large back mirror that can be seen to the far rear.
The direction that is not likely to be seen.
A protective ring for anti-bombing.
Furthermore, a protector is also worn.
If you do that much, it doesn't seem dangerous.
I feel like I saw that bike somewhere.
Really?
I feel like it's sealed with a memory I don't want to remember.
I'll go.
I'm worried.
I'll put it on.
I'm home.
It looks like a child in this house.
Ishiatama Tetsuiwa.
No.
It's Tetsuo Ishizu.
This is the house of Chief Ishizu.
Ishiatama Tetsuo Ishizu is a policeman who belongs to the Kathushika City Transportation Department.
He is usually quiet, but when it comes to traffic safety,
Traffic Safety Demon
Ishiatama Tetsuo Ishizu привез 7段交通安全指導士班
Ishiatama Tetsuo Ishizu
The Traffic Safety Demon has returned.
I was taught traffic safety before, and I had a rough time.
Oh, that Isshizu-buchou?
I thought I saw him somewhere on the bike earlier.
He looks exactly like Isshizu-buchou's White Horse.
What do you want from my son?
The White Horse of Yankee!
The Jutsu of Hata-tsukumi!
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry. I thought you were a nuisance for being told that you were being stalked by a strange man.
Ippou Tsuko, you should come and apologize.
Yes, sir!
Ippou Tsuko?
I'm sorry.
Ippou Tsuko? You mean...
That girl's name?
Yes. We have six sons.
The eldest son is right-handed, the second son is left-handed, and the third son is straight-handed.
Ippou Tsuko.
The second son is straight-handed.
Ippou Tsuko, you have an interesting name.
My name is Ippou Tsuko.
Don't you know?
Ippou Tsuko.
You could call me Ippou Tsuko.
I'm sorry.
Ippou Tsuko-kun.
My name is Ippou Tsuko.
Is it exclusive to the market?
Hmph!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You really do change a lot.
What's that?
It's the flashlight that was on the armor's head.
Is it really that important?
It was the one who gave me the opportunity to take the road to traffic safety.
What?
It's embarrassing to say this, but I used to be the leader of the Thunder Tribe.
The Thunder Tribe?
Yeah, the old rebel tribe.
It was the Black Meteor Tribe.
Hmph! That sounds pretty bad.
I've committed a number of traffic violations.
But I was confident that I wouldn't cause an accident.
I was confident in my technique.
However, one day...
...I was hit by a car.
The car that was chasing us had an accident.
It was the old rebel who had been trying to make us stronger.
Old man!
Isshisu...
Traffic violations are forbidden.
Sir, even if you're fine, you're annoying everyone around you.
I understand. I understand so don't talk to me anymore.
Traffic violations will never be allowed...
Never ever! I swear on this flashlight!
Old man...
Old man!
And then I became a police officer.
On behalf of my old man, I took away traffic violations from this world.
You were following in his footsteps.
Could it be that it was just a flashlight?
You mean you're an atlantic?
No, I'm still a little over 90 years old.
Oh my.
But my friends didn't keep quiet.
Especially the sub-leader, Watanuki.
After that, he was always following me around.
What are you doing now?
Well, one day, Sakai disappeared and went abroad.
He went abroad, but...
Hmm?
It seems like his eldest son has returned.
This engine is a Porsche.
It doesn't look like it.
I like the professional stubbornness of Porsche.
Huh? This house didn't have a garage, did it?
Are you going to park on the street?
Haha, there's no way I'd do that.
Sigh...
It stopped.
Dad!
I'm home.
Dad! I'm home.
Welcome home.
Why did you come out of the garage?
That's my garage.
There's no parking lot nearby.
What a safe device.
I'm glad you came, so I'll give it to you.
Please wait a moment.
Could it be...
It's called a "running car".
Yes.
Well then.
In 1935, road safety driving, 7th class 작.
The Asahina-sensei R bicycle.
Ishizutetsu has passed.
The appearance was..
I'll give him a car.
You'll wait for me outside.
Yes.
There seems to be nothing at the entrance...
How are you going to certificate.
Hmm?
Hey! What's that?
Hey! It's dangerous if I stand in front of the garage!
Which is more dangerous? This is the rubber part. It's like a wall.
It's dangerous if I stand in front of the garage!
Put on a 32-point seatbelt properly.
This is troublesome.
It's comfortable to ride.
But what is that board under the accelerator?
It is equipped with a stopper so that the speed does not exceed 50 km / h.
It's dangerous.
What happened suddenly?
The traffic light is not visible in the outskirts.
Certainly.
Where are you going?
Wait a minute.
I know the outskirts.
It is a traffic safety driving market 7.
In recent times, there are many places where traffic lights are in the way.
It's okay to increase the green, but it is also necessary to be careful about traffic safety.
Certainly.
What is it this time?
The pedestrian crossing is on the way.
Is this what you do every time you get in a car?
I have to do it when I notice it.
If an accident happens without doing it, I will regret it.
That's right.
Accident?
This intersection is a blood vessel intersection where accidents have been happening since before.
I'm giving my opinion, but it's not being improved.
I will organize traffic, so please contact me.
I understand.
Senior.
Thank you.
Fortunately, the injury is not a big deal.
I see.
That's good.
You're still alive.
Shizu.
Then I will go to patrol.
Thank you for your hard work.
This car.
First of all, don't run away.
Stop!
I can't stop.
What is that mark?
Watanuki.
Watanuki!
Looks like you didn't get hurt, my old friend of the Black Meteor.
You survived?
I went back to Japan after a while.
To take revenge on you, the traitor.
What are you doing?
You can't break my black magic!
I don't care.
What?
Do you think I don't know your weakness?
Weakness?
I know.
I know that you swore to destroy the traffic law on that Patroid.
What?
That means...
What are you doing?
I'm losing my strength.
Just as I thought.
I'll get him.
From now on, I'll break the traffic law!
Break it!
I'll beat him to death!
What is it?
The Patroid of Captain Hizubu was stolen?
That Patroid of the roadside?
Does the culprit know about it?
No.
Yes. He's a friend of the old motorbike, Watanuki-san.
Oh, he's the one who came to talk about Chief Ishizu.
He was a sub-leader of Black Meteor.
And Chief Ishizu?
He lost his motivation completely.
He's been like that since then.
Even my mood changed.
It was a big shock.
I'll cheer him up a little bit.
Hello, Chief Ishizu.
Chief Ishizu!
Oh, it's you.
Oh, please be strong.
You were stolen the Patronite.
I told you, didn't I?
That was a promise Patronite.
Now that it's gone, I'm out of energy and everything.
Huh? Then who's going to be the traffic safety instructor from now on?
I'll leave it to you young people.
I'm retiring.
Chief Ishizu!
What? An accident?
What's going on?
That's the Patronite of Chief Ishizu who got stolen!
Hey, get up!
Don't think you can get away with a big Honda!
Don't think you can escape!
You're just a salesman, but you're not a big guy!
What did you say?
You're not a big guy, you're a killer!
Stop!
It's a quiz. The blue signal is "proceed", and the red signal is...
Stop! Stop!
It's my fault for ignoring that!
Damn it...
Wait, Chief Ishizu!
The culprit knows!
Let's go get Watanuki together!
Let's go, Chief Ishizu!
Chief Ishizu!
I'm so done...
I'm not old enough to get into it yet.
That's right...
I'm serious! You're the one who can't get a hold of me!
No way! His motorcycle skills are amazing!
The only person who can compete with him is Chief Ishizu when he's serious!
That Chief Ishizu is considering retiring...
We have no choice but to keep him in check.
I'm gonna beat you up tonight.
Move it!
I can't be tied to a traffic light!
We found Watanuki! We're going after him!
We're going after him!
A black meteor appears!
Alright, we're coming!
It looks like there's a lot of cars going into the car tonight.
It's probably a black meteor.
It's the one who stole my dad's light bulb.
I can't park!
Daddy, aren't you going out?
Don't you want to go to the police station?
You're supposed to catch the bad guys who break the traffic laws.
You're supposed to catch the bad guys who go crazy on you.
*Screams*
Wasanuki!
Are you happy that you got your friend back?
*Screams*
*Cries*
W-what is this...
*Screams*
*Sounds of pain*
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
Chief Ishizumi! Why are you so quiet?
But...
If we don't have that flashlight...
Even if we don't have it, we can't make a traffic violation!
Dad, this is it.
This is...
I made this because I was so lonely after the flashlight was gone.
I couldn't make it well.
You really suck at this.
I'm not good at this.
But I'm good at this.
Thank you.
My heart is now filled with the fire of the flashlight!
*Screams*
35 years since the first traffic violation.
It's been 7 years since the first traffic violation.
Ishizu Railway is over!
*Screams*
Damn it!
Today, the Black Meteor will destroy the steel rail!
*Screams*
Why does it run so fast?
It's clearly 40 km/h.
Hey, it's too fast to run away!
*Screams*
The speed limit for this road is 40 km/h.
The criminal is on pursuit, so it's okay!
*Screams*
That's not true!
Traffic safety is the most important thing at any time!
Hm? That's...
Watanuki!
You showed up again, Shizu!
But I can't catch you!
I'll save you!
What?
I did it! I caught you!
I-I'll kill you!
That's it! That's it!
Stop it! This road is 40 km/h limited!
I'm not going to let you beat me!
Bye-bye!
Watanuki!
What are you doing?
I'm chasing you!
But at high speed!
What?
You're making a mess!
Whoa! What are you doing?
I'm speeding up!
Stop it!
This is 40 km/h!
Go!
If you speed up any more, I'll...
I'm over 60 km/h!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
You did it!
Chief Ishizu must've missed it!
Woo-hooo!
Wha- wha-, wha- wha-?
Watanuki!
What?
Gently return the particular parts!
You're finally getting serious about it, Ishizu!
Shut up!
D-dude!
Whoa...
Whs...! Help me...!
Whoa! Whoa...
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
How far are you going!?
This is not a world where we can live together.
As expected from the seven-level traffic safety guide.
7.5 meters
So you managed to catch me in Sadogashi?
I don't remember how we crossed the sea.
It must have been tough.
It was tough, Ryo-sama.
Chief Ishizu...
Did something happen again?
That is...
This is...
This is like Chief Ishizu's home.
Is this Chief Ishizu's doing?
Yes.
Hey, Ryo, Tsukankichi!
What did you do to Chief Ishizu?
I didn't do anything.
Because Chief Ishizu was so excited in the morning that he made a show.
And he changed the name of the traffic police to his own.
My name is Seisho School Zone!
Naoko is still better.
I'm the 10th in the school district.
What!?
By the way, I'm a pacifist.
Oh, here it is.
A two-wheeled car with a motorbike.
A bicycle with a motorbike.
A traffic stop.
Could it be?
Is that my name?
Yeah, that's good.
Then, everyone, get changed and gather!
We will now start the traffic safety guidance.
Traffic safety guidance...
Please forgive me for that!
Don't run away!
The car won't stop suddenly!
Can't have a new car, right?
When I turn to park my car,
I felt a strange feeling at that time
So I walked only in black
I saw a child once, but everyone forgets
A politician with a great-looking face
A blue aunt above his eyes
Look up at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come here
Our
Our town
Thank you!
Do you know a trolley bus?
It's a vehicle that takes electricity from a river and runs on the road.
It's like a combination of a train and a bus.
I used to run a lot when I was a child.
And I have unforgettable memories of the toro bus.
Next time, "Toro Bus Story"
Thank you for watching!