What所謂の雛鳴火?
de-de-te-テレビを見るときは When you watch TV
部屋を明るくして 離れてみてね light up your room and look at the distance
だれかが呼んでるような 雨上がりのことを When someone comes to you after it starts to rain
I walked towards my mother looking back
I felt that strange feeling back then
So I tried walking on a black street
To the Aged Gai tile
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a proud face
And the blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look
At that corner
You can see everyone
There is a turtle over there
Ah, there must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Run! Turtle King!
He went into the last straight in the fourth corner
Nerima Gallop is in the lead
Fujiteru Begin from the outside
Will Nerima Gallop be able to escape?
Fujiteru Begin, Fujiteru Begin, Fujiteru Begin
He's out
Fujiteru Begin is the winner!
In a moment, my salary for this month will be...
Pa...ka...
Is there a turtle among these?
Because I look like this
I'm a turtle
To think you're sly, idiot
behind the curtain
That will never be me
How pitiful
A poor citizen
I'm so miserable
But a police officer is a human
And for us, the salary
Is even more量
Does he even feel the need
For paying a salary?
That's right
Nakagawa and Reiko
Are not so good at making money
That's why they say that
Like me
I have to pay money monthly
Every two weeks
Try to live a life of only cup ramen before the break.
It is natural to try to increase the small amount of money by 1 yen.
Then, don't gamble on the field or the forest.
You can also make a lot of money.
The director says so.
There is no purpose and it is not my business to just save money.
Then you should find a purpose.
That's right, Ryo-chan.
Like saving up for marriage expenses.
Like buying a car.
There is also the idea of having a "my home".
Marriage, car, my home.
Oh, I don't like it.
How can you save money with such a dreamless thing?
What are you talking about?
Marriage, car, my home are all great dreams.
That's why it's a dream that the common people see as a celebration of the life of the life-saving band.
It's not something that can be felt by a bigger man.
You're a little too much.
I'm sorry.
You are too much.
Anyway, I will not allow you to do any previous job of salary.
You do something on your own.
I see.
I'm really a sleeper.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, I will not allow you to do this.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
What must I do?
I'm sorry.
5 billion yen!?
It doesn't matter how much I earn.
I believe that winning as the owner of the racing track is a man's dream.
Here it is!
No matter how many tricks you play in the race, you can only get it.
It's better to be the owner of the horse than the horse.
Then you can earn money.
Why didn't you notice such an easy thing?
I'll do it! I'll be the owner of the racing track!
What? You're going to buy a horse?
This shiny hair, this supple waist, this guy will become a famous horse that can run the Fuji TV.
I'm not mad at him.
Are you saving money for that?
Are you serious, senpai?
I'm serious, very serious.
I save 100 yen a day for food for saving.
That's a lot of money.
That's why you're so poor.
I'll be a nutritionist.
So how much is this horse worth?
It's 18 million yen.
18 million yen!?
So how much did you save?
Yesterday it was 8790 yen.
Now it's 1799210 yen.
I have a headache.
Senpai, shouldn't you not push yourself?
That's right. You better save it.
Shut up! Are you going to blame my savings plan?
No, I didn't mean that.
If you think about my way of saving, you can save 18 million yen in 10 days.
What?
No way, 18 million yen in 10 days?
I can't believe it.
You're so ignorant.
Fine, I'll explain.
My way of saving.
I'll save it today.
For example, I'll start with 10 yen for the first day.
I'll add 20 yen the next day.
Then I'll add 40 yen the next day.
I'll add more and more.
I can save it without any difficulty.
Look at this chart.
Yesterday it was 8790 yen.
Now it's 18 million yen in 10 days.
That's amazing.
In a way, yes.
You're surprised, aren't you, boss?
Don't tell anyone.
This savings plan is my speciality.
Do you think you can save it seriously?
Where will you get the 900 million yen in 10 days?
Leave it alone. I don't care.
It's almost time for me to be the owner of this horse.
I've even thought of a name.
In other words, Kameari King.
What do you think? It's a strong name, isn't it?
I wonder if the king and the king are both kings.
Probably.
It's strange.
Suddenly it's getting harder to save.
It shouldn't be impossible to calculate.
I was prepared to be a little tight.
Let's calculate again.
I knew it.
Why?
Is there a problem with the plan?
Uh?
Kameari King!
Kameari King wins!
A strong 8-9-7 win!
He wins the derby!
Will he give up?
A man's romance!
5 billion yen!
A senior?
That's right.
He's putting money, tools and treasures into the market and selling them.
Good morning, everyone.
Ryotsu, what's wrong?
What's wrong with me?
You look pale. What kind of life are you living?
What do you mean?
I live with 5 yen a day.
5 yen?
Is there anything you can buy with 5 yen?
No.
I bought a pack of biscuits for 210 yen.
I counted them, and there were 31.
That's 5 yen a day.
Chubu chubu chubu chubu chubu.
Other than that, I only have water and grass.
Grass?
A big box and a lot of grass.
Are you a rabbit?
Why are you doing such stupid things?
When I was in class, I started working as a barber.
Then who do you want to be?
That's right.
He's a man who lives together with the class.
Bring it and I'll show you what I store.
I thought you were aушка.
What do you mean?
Bring it with you.
The price is limited, so we don't need to do anything.
I don't need to worry about that.
Recently, there are only plastic bottles, so there are fewer bottles and cans.
It's an ice cream stick.
I'll sell it to the children for half the price.
Is there anything else?
No, I can't.
Why? I'm stuck here.
The
Senior, don't be so discouraged.
Senior?
No, it's not good. I'll pay you back with this money.
What? That horse has sold out?
Yesterday, someone asked me why I wanted it.
Damn, you were so late.
It was a pity.
I want a horse, sir.
36,000 yen.
36,000 yen?
Are you crazy?
You think you can buy a horse for 36,000 yen?
I'm crazy. Look at my eyes.
All right.
I like that man.
I'll sell it for 36,000 yen.
Is it true?
The father is different from the brother.
This is also a famous horse.
Oh?
Even more, that Fuji TV Silver, which I bought to celebrate the fall, is the same as my birthday.
It looks fast.
I'm buying it. It's because he's my brother.
Now I'm a horse owner, too.
Nyahahaha.
Hahaha.
Senpai, if your parents are different,
it means you're completely different.
Yeah...
That's what I think when I think about it.
I bought it for the atmosphere.
Is this really a competition?
My legs are short and I'm fat.
Yeah! That old man tricked you!
You little...
You already ate it?
You're eating well.
I'm asking for some more.
No, no!
Come on, let's practice to earn 500 million!
You did it!
Reiko, get out of the way!
Ryo, please forgive him.
He didn't do it on purpose.
I'm not a fool.
You're a good guy.
It's a start training.
The match is decided by the start.
If you're late, it's over.
That's where...
You're just a morning girl.
Don't listen to me.
You bastard!
It starts at the same time as the gate opens.
Okay?
I'm going to do it.
I'll do it.
All right!
I'll do it!
Look at me!
Ryo...
I'll do it!
You're going to be a star in Nakayama Sports Stadium!
Alright, you have to run as fast as you can to the sign over there.
Got it?
Let's go! Ready, start!
Move your weight quickly and push hard with your hind legs!
Push hard with your hind legs!
You're almost there! Keep going!
Huh? What's this guy doing?
How can he be so good at making a difference to a human?
Are you up for it?
What?
What? Can't you run because you're hungry?
Then why don't you eat the grass over there?
What? You don't like grass because you're a horse?
You want to eat ramen?
Welcome!
I'll have a ramen.
A horse!
Not a horse, I said a horse!
What? You're Ryo-san! Don't surprise me!
If a horse talks, I'll make him a comedian, not a contestant.
Make him a cup of ramen.
A horse makes ramen?
It's an age where anything is possible.
Huh? What?
Don't heat the soup too much.
Are you a cat? Are your noodles hard?
Yes, yes.
I don't want a horse to come and eat ramen.
Hey, wait!
Thank you.
What's wrong? Hurry up and eat.
Huh? What? Pepper?
Here you go.
What kind of food do you eat?
I've fed you what you should eat.
This time, you can run.
All right, get ready.
Ready!
Who told you to sleep?
Don't sleep! Run!
It's not time for a nap in kindergarten!
If you don't want to run, I'll shoot you in the face!
This is like a special training.
Oh!
A horse!
It's a real horse!
Ryo!
Put it on that horse!
Put it on!
Is that okay?
No, no.
This horse is training to become a racing horse.
I don't have time to play with children.
That's fine. Put it on.
That's right.
If you don't come out, I'll tell the chief that you're skipping again.
Huh? Are they going to threaten the police?
What? Do you want me to put it on?
I'm the best!
Hey, hey, it's the order.
Huh?
All right.
All right!
Ryo!
He looks best when playing with children.
What?
Uh!
It's not a joke!
He's got a real hand!
I'll put everything on the racing horse!
bucks!
Not bad, baby.
You're awesome!
I'm glad I was able to drive this way.
What is he doing?
I'll beat him.
I'm not that dangerous.
With my super face!
Hey!
It's my chance!
I'm running!
I'm scared.
I'm going to win.
I'm here.
So what are you going to do with this horse?
Are you going to let it go?
I can't even ask a professional.
Then what are you going to do?
I'm going to look for a part-time job that this guy can do.
Alright!
Let's go see the hero who rides the horse and runs!
Start!
My neck!
It's a part-time job, but do you have the guts to work?
What?
You don't like running?
You're not fit for a race car.
I'm starting to understand horses while we're living together!
If you can't do a part-time job, you should make a field here and harvest.
What?
You can't afford to work as a plumber?
Besides, I'm not good at cleaning.
Do you want to be sold to a butcher?
Then don't complain and just do it!
Start without complaining!
Alright!
What? You want to take a break?
You idiot!
You haven't even gone a meter yet!
I don't care about you anymore!
I'll make you a horse, so pick up anyone you like!
Shut up!
What on earth are you saying?
Hmph!
We'll be right back, and stay calm.
Okay.
OK.
Huh?
Oh?
Somebody!
What?
Somebody help me!
Oh no! The car fell!
Satoru!
Help me! There's a child inside the car!
What?!
Mama!
Satoru!
Get down!
Alright, I got you!
I'll save you!
I can't do this. I'm so hungry I can't do this!
Damn it!
Mama!
Kingo!
Pull!
Hang in there! Just a little more!
We did it!
Satoru!
Mama!
Kingo!
We saved the lives of the children!
Mama!
Kingo!
Satoru!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I won't let you go no matter what happens!
Mama!
Excuse me.
What?
I've been watching your performance.
What performance?!
The husband likes your horse...
...and will definitely suspension it to you.
What?!
Well then, you two...
No matter how much money you put into it, you'll get it, right?
You and Kingo will be one big burden!
Right?
What?
Hmm?
Oh, it's a white wine!
What was that refreshing emotion earlier?!
♪ Awaken, clock, kick, little finger, ai-ta-ta-ta ♪
♪ For the time being, if you draw your eyebrows, to the station, dash, dash, dash! ♪
♪ Eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes, eyes ♪
♪ The train is fast, and my father is sleeping on his back ♪
♪ This week, too, the "go-kuro" and "go-muri" are "go-motto" ♪
♪ The bucket is being filled up, but the gyudon is hot and steaming ♪
♪ The remaining work is annoying, but it's annoying, and I'll resolve it quickly ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ If you take a hot shower ♪
♪ I recover my energy with a sleeping pillow ♪
♪ Every day is no problem ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ It's Monday ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
What?
My picture won the award of gold at the art exhibition?
That's right, that's right.
If the viewer sees it, they'll know.
Besides, Mr. Kukai,
you said that my picture I drew was a paper in the sky.
In the next episode of "Tensai-Gaka Arawaru",
I'd like to announce a取代.
♪ There's a wall in there ♪
♪ Oh, there's a wall for sure ♪
Thank you for watching!