♪ When watching TV ♩
♪ Make the room brighter ♩
♪ and look away ♩
♪ After the rain, as if someone was calling ♩
♪ I looked back and walked ♩
♪ I held my mother's hand ♩
♪ I felt a strange feeling at that time ♩
♪ That's why I tried to walk on the black place ♩
♪ on the Akegai line ♩
♪ and I walked ♩
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
Politicians with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn and look at that corner
Everyone can meet everyone
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
The infinite universe
It is said that there are unknown intelligent life forms there
No, maybe they are
They may be right next to us
Time stop!
Finally, the day I've been waiting for has come!
Where are you going, Ryotsu?
I'm patrolling, chief
What is this circle?
Nothing, chief
Oh, you didn't go to buy game software, Ryotsu
Game software?
No, I said something bad
Ryotsu!
Let me go, chief
Today is the launch day of Doikura Five, which I've been waiting for
Idiot!
What are you talking about while you are working?
Do you know what position you are as a policeman?
I know!
I know, so I put up with the fact that I have to line up in front of the store at night and I paid the night shift
That's obvious
Don't be so mean!
If you buy it, I'll be back in 30 seconds, chief
Shut up!
We are here, and I think it will be no problem if you get out of the way a little
If it's a store in front of the station, it's faster to go by bicycle, isn't it, Ryotsu?
Yes, sir!
I'm sure your shift was until noon, Ryotsu
Yes, chief! It's only two minutes to the time of the shift
I don't know if I can go home after the shift
Well, do your best on your shift
Yes, sir!
I'm telling you to continue your shift seriously!
You're so mean, chief!
Ouch, ouch, ouch
What?
Hey, guys, something...
Reiko! Nakagawa!
Terai!
Chief!
It's stuck...
What's going on?
Did you find out the cause of the breakdown?
I knew it, it's the power supply
Maybe this mean it's broken
Why not...
Okay, here we go
Three more corners down to the nearby most standing
You are always in a hurry to have your drinks, so you are short of fuel
I also wanted to drink it
What are you doing?
It's crushed!
Sorry!
Terrible
What's this?
What's with this guy?
So this is what you were doing earlier?
Where did you get this huge fish?
Stop it, Rookie!
This isn't a fish, it's an spaceship!
A spaceship? If this is a spaceship, then you guys are aliens!
You're not like those unsold manzai-combi-like people!
You're an alien, aren't you?
You're not like this, are you?
There's no such thing as an alien!
But why is this guy the only one who's moving when the time stop machine stopped all the movement on Earth?
The time stop machine?
So this is what you guys are doing?
It's not good to be seen as us, so we stopped time.
So you guys are really aliens?
That's what I've been saying!
You're the one who told us!
You're very annoying!
Ouch!
Is it the fuel data?
No, it's not.
This isn't the fuel.
Didn't you just say it's the fuel?
Why?
What's that here?
Beer, Japanese sake, soju, whiskey?
Is it mizuku kidding, m verdant, though?
I guess it's Mr. Sparrow's seaweed salad.
I thought it was the food at the bar.
And, from the list of elements,
I'm sure we can make almost the same amount of real fuel with the same amount of fuel.
If you help us, we can leave immediately and move the time we stopped.
Wait, so the time has stopped.
The game software is not sold yet.
All right, let's help them.
I'll take care of it.
It's like looking at a diorama of a real thing.
Where is the fuel?
There's a limit to where we can go, so we should be able to get it there.
Oh, no!
The car has stopped, so it's okay.
It's going to be drawn as soon as the time starts moving.
Ouch!
What the hell is this?
Oh, it fell from the air.
I'll help you now.
If you move the things that have stopped, the future will change, so the time is banned.
I won't let you go.
You aliens don't have a ninja.
Damn it, it won't move.
We can't move things that have stopped in the air.
Come with us!
Is this okay?
No, this is a futon.
You guys should put it on top of it.
This will be a cushion.
Where's the Molokyu?
If there's a Molokyu...
You guys are doing something else.
Is that the Molokyu?
I see.
No, it's not.
I'll do it like this.
I'll help you.
You guys help me too.
What's this this time?
This isn't a Molokyu.
I want you to take me to a place where there are Nennets.
I'm tired already.
On Earth, there's a saying, "You can't eat what you can't work with."
Okay, that's good.
If you do this, you'll be caught as soon as you start moving.
Are we going to go on a trip again?
If you can't...
Shut up!
The kids are drowning.
Damn it.
No good.
The water's completely frozen.
If this happens...
For now, it's urgent.
What a bad person.
By the way...
Here's a bonus.
I brought a coach from a nearby swimming school.
Put this next to you.
Okay.
It's fine if you put this as a gun.
Now the list is all set.
I'm glad we were able to get to the point.
We can continue our journey now.
I'm glad I met a good person!
Pay the money!
There's no such thing!
What?
It's the middle of a space trip that relies on everyone's love and kindness.
I'm on my way to the space trip, so I can only rely on you.
Oh, well.
How much is it all?
You look peaceful, so I'll leave the money here.
I put it all in.
I can stop it with this.
I've done a lot of things for you.
I won't forget this favor.
You don't have to forget it, but if you pay the money you just exchanged, you'll double it and come back.
I know, Rookie.
Then you have to move the time after I say yes.
You really got in the way of me earlier, Chief.
Okay, that's it.
I'll forgive you with this.
Z ك:
It's unbelievable that you saw a human fly like that.
Anyway, let's hurry.
You did a good job.
Where is the friendly person?
There.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
AAAAAAAAH!
Uwaaah!
Help! Help!
It's too hard!
W-What happened?!
...
A-An error!!
The... the Katsudon I ordered...
The Katsudon hasn't arrived yet?
It seems like it hasn't arrived yet.
Can we check without the Katsudon?
S-sorry.
It's me. I don't think I can pass today.
I don't think so.
You're the worst! I told you it was early!
I need to change my license...
Dad... isn't that you?
Masayoshi...
Wait, Dad! Where have you been all this time?
Dad! Mom and Grandma are worried about you!
Dad...
Alright!
Hey!
I'm sorry about that!
I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry!
Hey! I'm the one who made you cry!
Damn it! I don't want to lose!
How much is it, old man?
It's sold out. What a shame.
No way!
I won't forget this award!
Shut up!
Mom!
It's mine!
I won't lose!
Old Man!
When was your happiest time?
When you were eating delicious food?
When you accomplished something with study and work?
When you achieve something by doing something.
When you spend time with your family and lover.
This is the story of a man named Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
He is going through such a small happiness.
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Nothing good happened recently.
I lost in the race.
Damn it!
I can't get a ticket.
What the hell are you doing?
I don't have money, but I'm hungry.
Ryo-san, that milk is old.
Tell me that quickly.
I think it's yogurt.
Damn it!
Are you okay, senpai?
I put things on the floor.
Biscuits?
It's Reiko's.
I'll have lunch with her.
If you eat it without permission, Reiko-san will scold you, Ryo-san.
It's delicious.
I'm home.
Ryo-chan, is that...
Don't be so stingy.
This biscuit is delicious.
That's a snack for pets, Ryo-chan.
What?
Why do you have such a thing?
My cat is constipated, so I bought it at the pet shop this morning.
It's empty.
If I put it there, I can imagine that I might eat it.
I can imagine that I might eat it.
You're not a baby.
You can decide for yourself if it's good or not.
What?
I don't know what's inside the milk.
But I can't eat it.
Damn it.
Are you hungry?
Are you okay, Ryo-chan?
I'm hungry.
What? A lunch box?
Hurry up.
Go.
Okay.
Ryo-chan.
It's too late.
If you take medicine all at once, it's poisonous to your body.
I think you should go to the doctor, Ryo-chan.
Can you say that you're too hungry that you ate too much of the food for the pets?
Go inside.
It's a lunch box.
You shouldn't force yourself to eat, Senpai.
That's right, Ryo-san.
Don't worry about it.
It's better to eat a lot as long as you're strong.
Yummy.
Senpai.
Ryo-chan.
Ryo-san.
Go to the doctor, okay?
Your face is not pretty, senpai.
I went to the restroom 10 times.
It's commonplace.
You're eating too much, so you're coming out too much, senpai.
I see.
I thought I would lose my stamina if I came out, but
maybe I made a mistake.
Ryo-chan.
Take your water.
There.
Here you are again.
I can't give you any stimulus.
Ryo-chan!
That was a little stimulus, but it's still good for me.
I'm sorry. My hand slipped.
I'll blow it up when it's fully opened.
What's this?
That's...
It's a water pipe, senpai!
A water pipe?
I was told that there was a water pipe construction at 1:00 this afternoon.
I forgot!
It's only 1:00 now.
I can't use the toilet anymore!
Ryo-chan...
What's this?
There should still be water in the water tank in the toilet.
Terai!
It's a water break at 1:00.
Terai just poured water.
But it was the last drink.
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
I've been holding back on using the toilet for a long time.
How long does a water break take?
Three hours.
Three hours...
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
Ryo-san!
This is the waste dump.
And this is the area where the water breaks.
We have no choice but to go outside the water break area.
If we go to the third exit, we can borrow a toilet.
It's about 500 meters long by straight line.
I'll send you a car, senpai.
No.
It's stupid to sit on the seat.
It reacts sensitively to the slight vibration of the car.
It's better to walk on my own.
Be careful, Ryo-chan!
I'm sorry.
It's like carrying a nitro bomb.
You guys...
You're good kids, so let's walk along the three ends.
A group of elementary school students are approaching about 30 meters ahead of Senpai.
Please prepare yourselves.
The other students' behavior is unpredictable.
Ryo-chan...
Ryo-chan.
I'll look after them with my belt!
What's that?
A dump's approaching at tens of meters from the rear!
Please be careful of the vibration!
What is the point of being careful of the vibration?
I'm somehow safe...
Senpai!
Uh... this time...
Bingo is heading that way!
Why at a time like this...
I can't keep up with this movement...
Ryo-san!
Senpai, this time it's Danjizuma!
What?
It's a good thing, right?
What should I do...
I'm so screwed!
I'm so close to the limit...
Thank you for your cooperation!
Ryo-san, calm down!
A little more...
Just a little more...
I'll do my best...
Alright!
I'm patrolling!
No way!
No!
The key's stuck!
Senpai!
He's losing his mind!
No! Nakagawa-kun!
Let's find a house that'll lend us a toilet!
Yes!
Toilet...
I'm so sorry!
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
Toilet...
Toilet!
Damn it!
No...
What should I do!?
I have to find a house that'll lend us a toilet!
No!
Huh?
What kind of dream?
Take this!
What?
You too...
Good.
I am glad you found another house.
We're waiting.
No, no, don't hold it back!
Hurry up!
No!
Don't come near me!
-Senpai! -Ryo!
-Don't come any closer! -Come on!
There you are! Get lost!
-Ryo! -Senpai!
At last!
Help!
I can't take this!
You're hungry, so don't eat anything around here!
Take care of your stomach!
I'm hungry, so I'll eat something.
You built a new home? That's great!
Where is it? Is it on the border?
I don't know.
Can't you come by car?
Hey, where is your home?
Next time!
Haruka Nara's Temple Rites.
Look out for us!
My Home