♪ ♪
♪ When you watch TV ♪
♪ Make the room bright and look away ♪
Everyone is non-cooperative.
After all, it was impossible for us to feel it.
Don't say that now.
Reiko-san!
That's right. How about selling homemade cakes and cookies?
If we cooperate together, we can make it in time.
I'll pay for the ingredients.
Reiko is good at that.
She's good at that.
She's so noisy that she's sleeping.
You're bad, Yaban-chin.
You're here again, you salary thief.
That's my line.
What?
Ryo-chan, please cooperate.
Cooperate?
With them?
I don't like it.
With us?
That's right. Who's cooperating with you?
Well, you two.
Komachi-chan and the others are in trouble because the ingredients for tomorrow's bazaar are not collected.
Bazaar?
♪ ♪
♪ Someone is calling ♪
♪ There is a turtle over there ♪
♪ There must be a turtle ♪
♪ Come on, everyone, let's go to our town ♪
Thank you!
Charity Bazaar
An announcement from Charity Bazaar.
This is the first time I see something like this.
This poster has been posted a month ago.
Po-po-po-poster!
This is it!
Ha!
Ha! This is such a poor handwriting!
What is it?
It hurts!
What is this?
So lame!
Bad sense!
Of course, this won't make the food gather.
Komachi Kiss!
Reiko!
Please do something about him!
The worst! The worst!
I'm super angry!
It hurts!
Ryo-chan, Kei-chan and I also cooperated.
Ryo-chan has a lot of toys that he doesn't need.
What?
I'm not kidding!
This is my precious treasure!
There's nothing I don't need!
I make a lot of money by doing buzzers.
You're stupid!
This is a charity buzzer!
You donate all your profits!
Donation?
Why can't I do that?
Egoist!
The worst man!
What?
This fatherless combination!
Ehh...
Man!
Well, well, Ryo-chan.
This buzzer is to help the old people in the town.
When I'm suffering from a bad stomach,
nobody gives me a penny.
What's the point?
Don't worry, Reiko-san.
No one buys such things.
You don't have to help me.
Huh?
Don't be silly!
My collection is limited-time premium goods that fans will drool over.
There are hundreds of thousands of them here.
There's pictures, some of that kind.
They'll be filled with figures and limited-timeramas.
Hey, we don't need any of your wasteful cooperation.
Can you please follow my lead?
Don't come to the bar tomorrow.
We can't before us.
W-W-What?!
Tch.
I get it now, Ryotsu Kankichi!
gegeben
Shut up!
Our orders are a no-no!
Onee-chan, is it really okay for us to sell these?
What are you...
We bought everything for this special occasion.
As expected of you, Senpai!
To help the local residents,
please help the charity bazaar.
Welcome!
We have a lot of things!
Please take a look!
What is it?
As I thought.
It's a small bazaar, but it's full of things.
Please take a look!
We sell rare and expensive goods at a very low price.
This is the bazaar of the bazaar, Ryo-chan.
How is it?
Mister!
How much is this?
It's a limited edition.
8,000 yen.
What?
8,000 yen?
Hey!
8,000 yen is cheap!
How much is this?
It's 500,000 yen.
If you miss this, you'll never be able to buy it again.
That's right!
It's a big deal!
It's really a great deal!
Senpai, it's a little too expensive.
Don't be silly!
It's a free gift.
And it's very expensive.
Welcome.
How are the platters?
The soap set is cheap.
And the towel set.
The seaweed and bonito are also good.
They don't sell at all.
Don't you think you have plenty of time?
Ryo-chan, Kichi!
What are you doing here? I told you not to come!
All these things are just leftovers from the house.
No one will pay attention to such a trifle.
Shut up!
It can't be helped.
Everyone only donated this.
Naoko!
Well, after all, no one really helped you guys.
That means...
What?
You're saying that you're the one who collected the better things.
Of course.
You can say anything you want with your mouth.
Well, then let me show you my ability!
Let me see!
Gotcha!
You shouldn't be eating so easily!
What's going on?
What did you give to Buzzer?
A towel set.
A towel? What did you say?
Oh, a towel set.
Honda!
You did give him an F40, didn't you?
What?
Y-Yes, I did.
A Ferrari F40...
50 million is ridiculous.
And you're young, Nakagawa.
What did you give him?
A towel set.
Naoko donated 50 bags of branded products, didn't you?
I guess you're right.
What did you give him?
A towel set.
What did you give him at the Buzzer in Kameido?
Well, well...
It was a million yen worth of home appliances.
Yes, a million yen worth of home appliances.
What did you give him?
He gave me a towel.
Oh, really?
What?
A towel set.
What did you give him?
That's a lot of money.
But you should have given him a fullgomery.
That's the right thing to do.
Oh, that's too much money.
I have to give him a towel set.
And he said I shouldn't give him one.
The first我們 expensive item in Japan,
you should give me a towel set!
Stop it. I finally got a bonus.
I think there's a high-class cognac here.
What's wrong with that?
Don't hide the goods from the guests.
Let's spit it all out at this time.
Let's also take this gold pie.
This is a high price because it's a muku.
It's a high price.
I think this will make you a good man.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Devil.
What did you get?
A pair of soaps.
Is that a problem?
Honda.
You donated a Rolex watch, didn't you?
Yes.
I also gave you a bonus and gold pie.
You're a big man.
By the way, what did you ask for?
I was thinking about it.
Please give me that.
There's a comfortable golf set.
Wait a minute.
I can't do this.
Can I bring you something like this today?
Can I?
That's...
I'm on duty.
Who did you tell me I saw the mayor on a job?
What if the mayor hears us?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you.
Even though I haven't used it yet.
I'm very grateful for your cooperation.
Please forgive me.
Please forgive me!
It's my fault!
My fault!
I still have to pay the loan!
Onii!
You're really a senior.
If you do this, you'll make a lot of money.
I'll show you my real buzzer!
Come on, come on, have a look.
This is the department store on the corner.
Akagiya-san, Shirakiyasan, Kurokiya-san.
I'll give it to the lady with the beanie.
500,000 yen is a good deal.
That's a charity buzzer today.
I'll give you that much.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Rolex.
How much is this?
It's 10,000 yen.
10,000 yen?
Is it real?
You can't sell fake things in the police.
Here's 10,000 yen.
Thank you.
What's this fishing rod?
What's in here?
This is 10,000 yen.
Really?
Really.
I won!
I sold it!
Me too!
What's this?
Here you go, darling.
Thank you.
Here's 10,000 yen.
That's easy.
That's right.
Please push the button.
I still have some food.
Thank you.
Here you go.
I'm hungry.
And this is a present for you, вып
Thank you!
Cheers!
Thank you.
Is this really 10,000 yen?
Yes.
It's free, so it's a foundry.
I'll take this.
Please do.
What's the matter?
There are so many plant goods.
The traffic traffic 20's got it from their boyfriend.
I got it from a friend.
That's right!
This is something that's not opened.
How do you know what's inside?
Because I have the same thing.
You'll know when you get a lot.
Be the man who sent it.
Because I don't need it.
Hey!
I don't feel like I'm a man to you.
You're a loser.
You're in the way of a non-popular person.
Go over there.
What?
This is the power of public transport.
No way!
A woman from Katsushika is popular.
What are you doing, Honda?
What's wrong with the store?
That's...
There's no more stuff to sell.
How much is the sales?
Well, well...
About 250,000 yen.
All right.
Shine your 알
Shine
Hello, poor people. Long time no see.
There you are!
That's...
Shiratori Reiji!
Come on! Get out of here!
Ah! Oh no!
Oh, I got caught again.
Hello, super poor Ryo-tsu.
Please turn my Porsche into a parking lot.
I'm not a parking lot driver!
Huh?
Reiko, thank you for inviting me today.
You're a charity buzzer, aren't you?
If you tell me, I'll help as much as I want.
I-I see. Then I'll help you.
Please tell me as much as you want.
Um, the card is a little...
What? You can't use it?
You're as stupid as ever.
I hate waiting for you!
Oh!
By the way, Reiko.
I made a
If you want to help so much, why don't you do it?
It's almost sold out.
I just want to help a charity.
It's 3,000 yen, though.
It's 3,000 yen, right?
Uh, hey, it's not the money for toys.
It's 3,000 yen, though.
If you come to my company later, I'll exchange it for cash.
Cute Cinderella.
What's this?
Lend it to me. Lend it to me.
I want it so much, I'll give it to you.
Please!
Look!
Huh?
I have 28 years!
Well, then this is the key.
Now you're the owner.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
This is my Porsche!
Unfortunately, the ownership of this car is now 300,000 yen, and it's transferred to him.
Don't mess with me!
Hurry up now!
Hey, look!
My Porsche...
I'll go get the high-heeled belt later.
Damn it!
You're starting again!
In that case, I'll have you help me out.
Aromani's suit!
Purnari's watch!
Miragamo's shoes!
All of them are 100,000 yen!
Thank you for the purchase!
Mama!
Now we're 100,000 yen up!
Hehehehehe...
Welcome!
Huh?
How about a homemade cake?
Ow!
It's a mini-pato-shaped cake!
Please buy a cake!
Wow!
It's so pretty!
So pretty!
Now, you're here, but...
Sorry.
Sorry, but this is funny.
Oh, it's no big deal...
Yay!
He win!
Kei's live Sachio suit!
which is super hot!!
I wonder how it feels, the fresh beacon of sweat and fumes!
That's a real thing?
It's not a costume or something!
Look closely!
There's a name tag!
It's all in here, right?
That's our uniform!
Wait! What are we going to do with our uniforms?
Let's go home!
Thank you for the gift!
Thank you for your cooperation.
That criminal!
I'm going to be a fool this time.
Chief!
You idiot!
Go get it!
Yes!
I'll cool your head down!
Nice try!
Don't think we're done with this game.
Are you still going to do it?
Today, we're going to introduce you to a wonderful product.
Here it is.
This is a gotaku with no perforations.
What is this?
This is a gotaku that Decaplio used in the Titanic movie.
What?
Is it that amazing?
It's a lot more expensive than you think.
How much is it?
It's 4,800 yen.
What?
This is cheap!
I brought it from my senior's room.
What is he going to do next?
Next up is this seat belt.
This is a gift from a monkey-hungry actor.
Now you can wear a huge-hungry belt.
I'm wearing a belt today, too.
That cheater!
Let's just leave him be.
I don't want to lose to a guy like him!
You're going to help me?
Of course I will.
Say anything.
Actually...
There's something I got for my birthday.
How much are you going to sell it for?
Ummm...
3,000,000 yen.
What!?
Isn't it too expensive?
I wonder if so.
How about 1,000,000 yen then?
Oh, my.
What?
8 million!
You only have 8 million yen.
Don't you have any other money?
8 million!
You and Reiko are very close.
There's not much left to sell.
There's more!
A Japanese-style room, a Western-style room, a kitchen, and a toilet.
It's all for one person.
It's a real bargain.
It's true that 25 million yen is cheap.
Please sell it.
Me too!
I don't know.
Now it's 3 million yen.
This is a property that used to be a police station, so it's very sturdy.
How about a helicopter?
It used to be a police station, so the bathroom and the dining room are big.
I sold it!
Sold it!
He's so persistent.
I think we can just split it.
That's right. There's nothing left to sell.
I definitely don't want to!
Hey.
I'm not going anywhere.
Senpai!
This is the last game.
I'm looking forward to it!
So, how do we play?
Baseball.
Baseball?
It's not just a baseball.
The one who loses the rock-paper-scissors buys the other person's clothes.
This will be the final.
That's great.
But if you want to play, I'll go with you.
I'm looking forward to it!
Then, let's play baseball!
Let's start the game!
Okay, let's get started!
Baseball!
If you want to play baseball,
you have to have a chance like this.
What's that?
Safe!
A good night's sleep!
I won!
You lost!
You won.
The one who won will pay, right?
I see.
Yes, 10,000 yen.
Oh!
I'll beat you.
The buzzer boos!
What's going on?
What's with that?
I don't know.
I won!
I lost!
Yes, 10,000 yen!
Now it's the final!
Alright!
If you want to play baseball,
you can get a blind shot like this.
And the winner is...
YAYAYA!
The winner is...
YAYA!
He did it!
Take that!
Here's 10,000 yen.
Can you take it out now, Komachi?
If you don't follow the rules, I'm going to win!
I'm taking it out!
You can take it out.
Komachi...
Wait!
Not just the
"Kokannomokkori"
Special Detective Kaipande
is here!
You!
I understand the situation.
I'm here, so it's all good.
Let's go!
Seishi!
I'll sew your skin instead of Lady's.
No way!
What?
I don't want to!
You can't help it!
In the end, the game didn't work out.
The buzzer earned 200 million yen,
and the old people went on a boat trip around the world.
They went on a luxurious trip to Myanmar.
And...
Shizu, I can find you.
See, you.
Come here, Kaipande.
Get me married.
You don't have a wife, do you?
Oh, you!
Qualifies with the yerba?
Yeah.
it's the going of the report.
Yes, sir, sir!
No, no, no, no, no!
I don't want to comin' here.
I don't like this!
Mr. Saiki, how are you going to take responsibility?
Don't worry, President.
Next, if we hold the "Katsushika Shoin Salvation Charity Bazaar",
200 million or 300 million will be gathered immediately.
I'll pay for it, so don't worry.
And the revenue will be a lot.
Idiot!
Someone please save me!
"Katsushika Shoin Salvation Charity Bazaar"
The Olympics are almost here!
It's about time for me to wake up!
I used all the money I had from the sun!
Wait! If I use the super powers of the sun,
I'll have a huge profit after I pay back the money!
I'm smart!
Next time on "Toumin Keikan Futatabi"!
Thanks for watching!
♪ Over there is a turtle ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a turtle ♪
♪ Everyone, let's come to our town ♪
Thank you!