Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Receiving the wind of the coming season ♪
♪ The brightest, the best harem ♪
♪ Crossing the new era lightly ♪
♪ Diving to the city in yellow ♪
♪ I wanna dive into the paradise ♪
♪ Rather than wearing all the trendy stuff ♪
♪ The face is 100 times more decided ♪
♪ Let it bleed ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Start running and let's go ♪
♪ The dream will never stop ♪
♪ Let's go to the city tomorrow too ♪
♪ Let me run ♪
♪ Everybody can do it ♪
♪ Even if it's a little dark ♪
♪ I don't want to say it ♪
♪ Don't be excited ♪
♪ Strong and high, strong and down ♪
♪ I can't hide, I can't hide ♪
♪ That's me ♪
♪ It's all about my body ♪
♪ It gets in my way, it gets in my way ♪
♪ I don't want to answer the phone ♪
♪ It's all about my body ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm doing ♪
Dad...
You're so annoying.
Dad, that was Hideo's call.
Yeah. He said he'd call you, so I hung up.
You're so mean!
No matter how much you call me, I don't do that often.
Hideo ran away from America, where he was supposed to go.
I don't know about that.
Dad...
If Hideo came back from America, there's something important to talk about.
No, no, no, I'm having a cold...
I'm going to sleep...
Dad!
Oh my... it's hot.
It must be the cold...
I like you.
You got a wedding dress, huh?
Hey, Reiko!
What?
What's wrong, Ryo?
You tore your head.
Try it on.
Oh.
Show me what you can do!
Oh, you're good at sewing too.
I'm glad to have a wife.
You were reading this book?
Well, girls like wedding dresses.
But Ryo, how about you get a wife?
I don't need one. I only want the first one.
I'm enjoying my life!
But I feel a bit saddened when I see you enjoy your life.
But you're asking if I need a wife.
You're a poor man. Tell us the truth.
Shut up! Let go of me!
Oh, no. No, no.
That's good enough.
Good job, everyone.
I'll go to the library and come back.
I'll leave the rest to you, Nakagawa.
Yes, sir.
Good job.
I'll go home and get some rest.
Good evening.
Hey, Hiromi.
Long time no see.
What's this?
Did you come to see the chief?
Hello.
Chief?
Chief, where have you been?
Chief!
What's up, chief?
You were here?
Dad, there's something important.
Let's have dinner together.
No, I still have work to do.
Dad, I can't...
I can't do anything.
I have important work to do.
Chief, you just said you were going home.
I changed my mind.
What's wrong?
Your daughter is here to pick you up.
I know. You're embarrassed.
You're old, too.
It's because of me.
It's more important for me to have dinner with my boyfriend than to eat with that old man.
You should be happy to see him.
You should be happy to see him invite me to a party.
Dad, I...
Shut up!
I don't care about you!
I'll go to patrol.
Dad...
Hideo...
Hiromi...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. My father didn't listen to me at all.
I'm out of time.
You've been dating since you were a student?
Yes.
Are you proposing to me?
I'm happy to propose to you.
So what do you mean you're out of time?
Hideo suddenly changed his mind.
I wanted to talk to you before that.
My father is so stubborn. He doesn't listen to me at all.
Hey, Hideo.
Hey, Yo-chan.
The director is a kid.
It's okay. We'll try to push him.
Thank you.
I couldn't go to the main gate.
I was so impatient that I couldn't think about my father's feelings.
Impatient?
Are you going to move out that far?
No, I'm going to Hokkaido.
Good. Good food and good beer.
Why are you talking sohausly?
You're not going to play, are you?
Oh, I see. You're going to the capital.
You made a mistake like you had to leave your death certificate.
No, I'm not.
Hideo's company is Hokkaido.
I'm sorry to say this, but I work for a company like this.
Well, then you're an atin.
Please.
It's a computer game software development.
After I joined the company, I've been traveling around the U.S. and Japan.
I thought I'd finally be able to relax, but now I'm in Hokkaido.
I can't do anything for you.
Don't worry about it.
I'm fine.
Even if you can't be with me, I'm very happy.
Hiromi...
Hey! Hey!
Yes?
Your company is developing a game called "Campus Fairy Quest".
Why do you say that?
Because you like games.
There are only a few people who know about it.
Why don't you meet with the manager and give me a project?
C-Can-Fair?
If you like games...
How about a bug-in version of "Nukupuya-san 2"?
Oh, a bug-in version?
What about "Omunage Police"?
I got it before the reservation.
How?
How about "Angel Hazard"?
I have it, and I cleared it.
What?
Then, what about "Poyo-Yon Super"?
I cleared it and I gave it to someone.
Why?
Well, well...
Then, how about "Tekken Den Memorial Aqua Note Training Festival"?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Okay, leave it to me.
I'll go and meet the manager.
Really?
Yeah.
So, I'm counting on you for the game software.
Yes.
Okay, bye!
Bye!
Hey!
Good news!
Yes, sir!
Run!
Hey, what are you doing?
Please don't bother, Director!
I need to find his mind!
If you don't tell me, you won't be able to listen to me!
What?
Hey, Kakuta! Let go of me!
Father...
No, Mr. Ohara!
I don't know! I don't know! I can't hear anything!
Chief! I'm not a child! Stop it!
I don't know!
Ryotsu!
Mr. Ohara!
Chief!
I don't know! I'll go patrol!
Honda! Don't let him run away!
Yes!
Chief!
Mr. Ohara!
Please listen to me!
You're like a child!
Okay, that's what you want!
I did it!
Father!
Chief!
Get him!
Hang in there until the next bus stop!
Stop it! Stop it!
Ohara!
There's no time to waste!
You're suspecting me!
감사호!
Eh...
Lady...
So what?
I'll report you to the police.
I'm very sorry...
This is for you!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Ms. Ohara!
Since you're going out with this...
Can we go?
Let's get out of here!
Chief!
Father!
Listen to me!
Chief, I won't let you go!
How persistent they are!
There!
Ryotsu, it's a net!
It's a flood!
Let's get out of here!
Sendou, go to America!
America?
Remember!
Action!
That was tough.
I'm sorry about that, Chief.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
How's Kakuta doing?
He's back at work.
I see.
But he's also very determined to follow me to the end.
I want to help him somehow.
So what are you going to do from now on, Ryotsu?
Well, I guess I'll have to leave you alone, Chief.
Huh?
I'll do it by myself.
Watch me.
I'll give you a wonderful wedding that will make you feel better.
Oh, no!
Then we have to go to America!
I'm sorry, Ryotsu.
But you have to stay here with us.
Well, I can't go.
But you have to do it for me!
Oh, no, I can't go.
Take me to America!
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
Come here!
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm sure your father will forgive you.
I'm sorry to say this, but it's so sad to see Hiromi go to get married.
Ryotsu, you're right.
Let's make sure she's ready.
Please continue to talk to her.
Leave it to me.
I'll keep talking to her.
Move!
Oh, no.
You didn't swim in Tokyo Bay, did you?
What?
Listen, dear.
It's about Hiromi.
How about you forgive her?
You know Kakuta is a young man who doesn't have a right to ask for permission, right?
No, I don't want to hear that from him.
Then please meet with Kakuta once.
What?
Please meet with him, talk to him, and then decide.
Dear!
If you don't meet with him now, we'll talk about the ceremony on our own.
What? What right?
It's my right!
I'm Hiromi's mother!
Do you think you raised her all by yourself?
No, no, no.
I didn't mean to.
Then please meet with him.
I don't care.
I don't care if you don't know who the horse is.
If you want to do it, do it yourself.
Dear!
What a troublesome person.
What right do I have?
Who did you do it for?
Do it yourself.
Hey, is the reservation full?
I want to do it in a week.
What?
Forget it!
I'll never ask you again!
Damn it!
Where's the next one?
Hey, you can't use it anymore?
It's perfect.
I didn't know you'd work so hard.
It's true.
If this happens, I'll be in trouble.
I see.
By the way, was he there?
Yes, I'm Asakusa Kamen Kaku.
Are you the president?
Please wait a moment.
Hey, Ryo, long time no see.
Are you going to open the hotel?
Ryo suddenly said that.
Is it because you opened it a week ago?
It's okay.
The venue is ready.
But it's still under construction.
What?
February 1st, 4 years ago.
Your house is being demolished.
Who was the person who sent you to my house?
I can't remember.
I think there's something I need to tell you.
I got it.
I won't tell you.
I'll make a big one like the one in Kinsho-dono.
I'll make you a big one.
I'm counting on you.
How's the party?
It was a little bit awkward.
What? It's a little bit more.
Yaaay!
What are you doing in the middle of work?
It's a pity.
I'm off work right now.
Then go home now!
Chief, I'll tell you before I go home.
I'm going to the wedding, and I'm alone.
I'm counting on you.
You're a beautiful bride.
Don't say that!
At least, I'm a little bit happy.
Dad, come to me.
Oh my...
Father!
It's okay, Hiromi.
I'll make it up to you.
Dad will definitely come.
But...
Don't worry.
You're cute, so it can't be helped.
Honey!
I'm so hot!
Hiromi, call the doctor!
Hiromi!
Yes!
Anyway, warm up today and sleep well.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Hiromi, you should go to bed.
Tomorrow is an important day.
Can I do it?
Mom, you should rest.
Because it's my fault.
I was worried about you.
Dad didn't sleep well last night.
But you...
Please.
Because I only have today.
Until tomorrow's wedding,
I want to be Ohara's daughter
and your father's child.
Hiromi.
Hiromi!
No!
I won't allow you to get married!
Hiromi!
No!
We don't have time for that.
I mean...
I'm happy for you.
I'm relieved.
My fever is gone.
Dad?
Thank you very much for your long time.
Today, I am marrying Hideo.
I want to marry you.
I wanted my father to be happy.
But I couldn't.
I wish I could think about my father more.
Hiromi.
It's about time.
Don't worry about your father.
Mother will be back soon after the ceremony.
The ceremony starts at 12.
Hurry up.
Yes.
I'll be back soon.
The chief is not here.
He fell down because of the cold.
Hiromi.
I wish I could think about my father more.
I...
No, I'm cold.
I'll go to bed.
Father.
No.
I still have work to do.
I don't care about how Hiromi feels.
I'll be brave.
Father.
Did you come to pick me up?
Yes.
What will you become when you grow up?
My father's wife.
I see.
Your father's wife.
You want to go to a police school?
No, no.
I can't let you get involved in such a big job.
Go to college.
You have a lover.
Hiromi, you're pretty.
It's about time.
Can you wait just five more minutes?
Father.
Hiromi.
Uh.
Hiromi!
Hiromi.
Yeah?
Let's do our best to make your father happy.
Yes.
Asakusa!
It's Kame-Unkaku! Hurry up!
I've been dating Kakuta since elementary school.
Since I was a student, I've been with him since I was in high school.
I'm so happy.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Wait!
Dad!
This is bad!
Stop!
Chief! Where's Okano?
Chief!
Shut up!
Everyone!
I'm the bride's father!
I was against this marriage!
I didn't even think about making Hiromi sad.
I've been avoiding Kakuta.
If my subordinates didn't force me to give him the ceremony,
I would have to starve for the rest of my life.
Thank you for today, everyone.
And Kakuta.
I'm sorry.
Dad...
Hideo!
Hiromi!
Please take care of my daughter.
Y-Yes!
Leave it to me!
I'll take a picture!
Smile!
Okay!
Pose!
What a nice picture!
It was a nice ceremony!
Good!
Let's go there!
Let's go!
Chief!
It's time to go home.
Your cold.
What?
I'll have to complete the job.
I got it.
Let's go.
No matter what.
I have to go.
Tang tang!
I'm going to chase you home and take back my paper bag that I brought by mistake!
Huh? Why do you have to go out with me to get it back?
Because your photo is in it!
Next time, "Take back Maruhi's photo!"
Thank you for watching!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Even if it rains today,
Tomorrow won't be sunny
Bye bye, let's wash our hands
Say goodbye to the things you don't like
Oh yeah, live as you like
Live as you like
There's something good
Outside the door
The sun is calling