"Hand in Hand"
When you watch TV, light up your room and look away.
Come to me, you poor thing.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds.
You'll be alright eventually.
You know it, don't you?
If you know it, then stay quiet and come to me.
"Hand in Hand"
Here is the Yuki-guni Expo.
"Hand in
I'm glad you're here.
Who's there?!
Oh, Ryo-chan!
You were there?
I wasn't there.
Make sure you check before you drop me!
You idiot!
I'm late, so don't say that!
Master...
With your enormous stamina,
why don't you center yourself for people?
Go on, what do you mean?
From snow.
Go help snowman around town.
Yes, sir.
haupt!
Ryo-san, you saved me.
You need to work on snow best.
Shit!
Damn it! I'm not a bulldozer!
Well, don't say that.
I'll treat you to lunch later.
What? Really?
Yeah.
Okay, then I'll do it!
Ouch!
Who's there?
Strike!
You guys!
I'm sorry!
My butt hurts!
Damn it!
Wait!
Yeah!
Come here!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
I did it!
Great success!
You guys!
Damn it!
Look at them!
Leave them as they are.
If you make a hole here, they'll get caught.
Okay.
Okay, it's done.
It's a perfectly done hole.
You did a good job.
Of course.
If you get caught, I'll do it again.
I've lived like this since I was a child.
Ryo-tsu.
Yes, sir!
Stop snowboarding and do something stupid!
What are you talking about?
I snowboarded on the surface and brought it here.
Help me!
It's your own fault!
You idiot!
What are you doing?
You're going to be buried in there forever.
Please stop.
There's no point in making a fool of yourself.
It's a joke, Ryo-tsu.
You're not stopping, are you?
We just finished the patrol.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's raining again.
Yes.
It's going to be raining again tonight.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
There was no other problem.
But you're poor, Ryo-chan.
You shouldn't have taken a night shift.
Shut up.
I'm not really poor.
I'm just being with you.
You're so stupid.
If you're with me on a day like this,
I'm sure I'll be left with a lot of meals.
Damn it.
Well, I'm so lucky that I give up.
Excuse me.
See you.
Damn it!
This is going to be serious.
Come on, let's hurry back.
They're all so arrogant.
Then, Ryo-san, I'll be leaving at 8:05.
Wait.
What is it, Ryo-san?
Your house will take three hours from here, right?
That's why if you don't go soon, you won't make it to the last train.
I said wait.
You're missing out on something important.
What if you get on the train and you can't move on the way?
No way.
You'll be locked up in the snow on the train.
You won't be rescued until tomorrow morning.
The electricity will stop, the heating won't work, and you'll freeze.
Poor thing.
No way.
It's already 8:00.
You won't make it on time.
You'll be late.
That's terrible, Ryo-san.
So you're going to be with me until tomorrow morning, right?
Ryo-sama.
Oh, Maria.
Ryo-sama, I heard you're on a night shift tonight, so I brought you some drinks.
Oh, I'm so happy. I'll welcome you.
Oh, are you with me, too?
Well...
Then let's have a hot pot party tonight.
Hot pot? Sounds good.
Sounds good.
Oh, this looks delicious.
Ryo-sama, don't stick your tongue out.
Sorry, sorry.
Oh, that's right.
Let's call Honda.
Oh, Honda.
Actually, there's someone who really wants to meet you at the station.
Who is it?
He's so plump and slimy.
Oh, is that so?
Are you coming soon?
I'll be waiting.
OK.
So there are four of us.
I think we'll be able to spend a good night with this many guys.
I'm sorry to upset you.
The train is stopping in the direction of Shinko for some reason.
Please wait for a moment.
What?
Are you kidding me?
That's terrible.
I came to this place after all that snow.
That's not true.
What's wrong with that meat?
What's wrong with beef?
It's a plump, slimy, and plump female cow meat.
I thought you were saying in a troubled voice, "Honda-san, eat it!"
Don't joke around! I'm really going home!
Would you like to eat a little?
It's okay!
You're so ridiculous. I'll let you eat it later.
Ryo-san, I don't want to eat beef no matter what.
I thought it was interesting.
Senpai, something's going on!
So, let's eat it!
Let's eat it!
The concentrated wire that attacked Kameari district in Katsushika has finally exceeded one meter and is starting to damage.
Yes, this is Katsushika.
Ten houses in the third district?
I understand. I will leave immediately.
Oh, no! Two houses in the third district!
It's a flood on the first hill!
We can't handle it alone.
I just got a call from the head office.
I need to contact all the office workers.
Roger that.
Katsushika
Hey, Honda, hurry up!
Hmm...
Then, I'll use this...
Hehehe...
By the way, the other day, my bike...
Oh, Honda, what's up with changing the topic suddenly?
It's nothing.
There are terrible people in the world.
The other day, a garbage bag was placed on the seat of my bike.
And it was a garbage bag.
That's terrible.
Speaking of terrible, the manju I put in the refrigerator was gone before I knew it.
I was going to eat it with Ryo-sama.
But...
That's true.
That's terrible.
By the way, the luggage I received from my family is gone.
What?
What's wrong, Honda?
No, no, no.
This is also said that there are terrible people.
Hahaha...
Well, we just want to avoid that kind of thing.
That's right.
Ryo-san says good things sometimes.
Sometimes it's unnecessary...
What?
Hehehe...
Hahaha...
Citizens!
The weight of the snow is afraid of the collapse of the house!
The caravan will turn, so please evacuate calmly!
Chief!
Nakagawa, how are the residents evacuating?
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I'll be done in about 30 minutes.
I see.
By the way, I don't see Ryotsu.
Komachi-chan and the others contacted the evacuation center many times, but no one came out.
That's him.
He probably skipped it anyway.
He's a completely useless guy.
Ah...
Ouch!
I did it!
I beat them all!
Senpai, it's unfair.
It's unfair.
You gathered so many pillows.
That's right.
Why do you have so many pillows?
But I remember the pillow throw of the school trip.
Yeah, I enjoyed remembering my childhood.
That's right.
All right.
What should we play next?
Eh?
Are you still doing something?
Of course!
I'll do it until I get sick!
Six days later
Whaaa!
It's pitch black!
Could it be too early to wake up?
It's past 8 o'clock already, and it's still dark.
Huh?
It's weird.
It's power cut.
Huh?
It's not open.
Ugh!
What's up?
There is no light?
And it doesn't open the window.
It's weird.
Ugh.
It's still late at night, so it's not a big deal.
It's already past 8 in the morning.
What?
That's so weird!
Ryo-san! What have you been up to?
R-Ryo-san, look at this!
Oh, come on.
What's this?
Oh, no. It's completely covered in snow.
What's going on outside? Maria, turn on the TV.
Yes.
Honda, contact the office!
Yes!
No, it's not working.
It's still off.
What about the phone?
No, it's not working.
Damn it.
The water pipe is frozen or broken.
What?
My phone is not connected.
What should we do? It's completely broken.
What if it gets stuck like this while I'm asleep?
What should we do?
At last, the concentrated around Kameari was recorded as the biggest in Tokyo, so it was more than 5 meters in the winter.
But for some reason, the area around it is only limited to Kameari.
We can't even get an idea what's going on outside at this rate!
Anyway, let's dig into the snow and see what's going on!
I'm counting on you, Ryo-san!
Senpai, please get help quickly!
Please call me.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be back.
No!
The door won't open!
You guys, lend me your hands!
I-I got it.
Ouch!
What is it?
Ryo-sama, please close the door!
Hurry up!
What is it?
It stopped.
Maybe the exhaust pipe is in a very poor condition.
The weight of the snow is balanced on the entire building.
So the exhaust pipe is in its current shape.
But if the door is opened and the balance is broken, the exhaust pipe will not be able to withstand the weight.
We are in a bad time.
What the hell!
We can't escape when we're completely isolated!
Damn it!
What should we do?
This is a serious matter.
Yeah.
It was correct to launch an evacuation plan as soon as possible.
I didn't expect a 5-meter stone wall.
Nakagawa, you lead the carousel and the gun.
Go to the carousel in the town.
Got it.
Reiko, patrol the town to see if anyone has run away.
Roger.
But what is Ryo-san doing?
What is he doing?
He is late even at this time.
The carousel is closed.
Senpai, let's put the stove on.
Idiot!
If we put the stove on when it is closed, it will become a cold.
But if we do not do it, we will freeze to death.
I'm not sleepy.
Hey, don't sleep.
If you sleep, you will die.
I'm very sleepy.
Please wake up.
Hey, Honda, don't sleep.
You are not going to sleep.
Ryo-san, wake up.
Don't fall asleep.
It was really snowing beside Kameari District.
It seems so.
Here, this is the stuffing.
Reiko, good work.
Thank you.
We will change it.
It really helps us.
By the way, didn't you see Maria-chan, Reiko?
No.
No, he didn't come here.
Is that so? I haven't been able to contact him since last night.
Anyway, it seems that Honda and Terai didn't go home.
Is something wrong?
I'm not sleepy anymore, but my face feels a little tight for some reason.
Oh, is that so? It's your imagination.
I see.
I'm hungry.
If that's the case, I should have left some of the pot yesterday.
I used up all the ingredients I brought.
I want to eat yakiniku, nabe yaki udon, curry dashi ramen.
Stop it! If you imagine it, you won't be able to bear it anymore.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
That's suspicious.
Terai, take off your blanket.
Why?
Take it off.
It's cold.
It's chocolate.
Terai, you're mean. You were going to eat it by yourself.
I just realized it.
Shut up. I won't let you eat this chocolate as punishment.
Instead, I'll eat it.
Senior, that's unfair.
That's right. We should share it.
That's right. It's mine.
What are you talking about?
If you eat it, the fight will continue.
That's why I'm going to punish you.
I'll eat it too.
Me too.
I won't let you eat it.
Owie.
Take it.
There's no chocolate.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's not good.
If this is the case, we should have eaten together.
No.
Oh, it's okay. I can still eat it.
It's a little dusty, but it's delicious.
Ryo-sama.
Please put the snow from the city down here for now.
But even if we collect the snow from the city,
I don't know if we can make it in time with just the park space.
Oh, that's...
This is a light bulb in front of the exhaust.
That means...
Senpai, you didn't expect...
I was too hungry because I used up all my energy.
No one's coming to help me.
I wonder if we're going to die like this.
That's right.
I want to die so that I don't have to think about it.
Mr. Honda, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
What's wrong?
I was the one who put a trash bag on Mr. Honda's bike yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I was the one who ate Mr. Honda's buns.
It looked so delicious that I ate it without thinking.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who opened Mr. Honda's luggage without permission.
Is that so?
Yes.
I opened it by mistake without seeing where it was sent.
I'm really sorry.
No one makes mistakes like that.
That's right.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I can't go to the bathroom.
What?
Then will you forgive me?
Of course.
I don't really care about trash.
Mr. Honda.
Ms. Maria.
Ms. Terai.
Thank you.
You guys are great.
It's wonderful to talk about the truth and deepen friendship.
Mr. Ryo.
I thought about it.
I said to open Mr. Terai's luggage.
I'm sure it was a senior.
What?
By the way, Mr. Ryo said that he could eat the manjuu in the refrigerator.
Was that so?
At that time, I was going to throw away the trash when I went out to eat with Mr. Ryo.
That's right.
I don't have time, so I'll put it on a motorcycle and clean it up later.
Is that so?
Calm down, everyone.
Calm down.
Cool your head with this.
What ...
You're waiting for help in such a place?
If it's like this, you'll get out of here at once.
This is the escape site?
Is Ryotsu really also in here?
Yes.
After all, Ryou hasn't returned, so maybe he'll stay in the snow.
Ms. Maria said that she couldn't reach you because of last night's afraid.
Maybe ...
Temporarily, there is a possibility that you won't be able to contact Mr. Terai and Mr. Honda.
If we can't contact them, it's highly likely that they're with us.
Yes. If we don't hurry, the exit might collapse due to the heavy snow.
Ryotsu...
Listen, I'll go alone and open the door.
So dig up the snow and escape before the exit collapses.
Roger!
Alright, let's go!
Yeah!
Go!
What's going on?
This is bad! It's collapsing!
Ryotsu!
The exit...
Now there's no place for us to go back!
We have no choice but to go to the ground!
Are you alright, Ryotsu?
I'll never see a man like you again!
You're in trouble!
Nope.
It's only three or four meters down when the exit's collapsed.
It's a good time to go outside.
What's happening?!
Master Ryo, let's dig in another direction!
That's right.
There's a lot of heavy snow here.
It might be piled up.
Alright, then I'll go this way!
There's so much snow!
It's snowing everywhere.
How many meters did it pile up?
It's no good.
It's snowing all over the world.
We're going to die here.
Don't say that.
We'll be saved.
We can't die here.
If this happens, we'll have to go up.
Where is it?
Give me an answer.
Mr. Tera, Mr. Honda.
Maria.
It's up.
We have to go up.
Senpais aren't here.
Let's look around.
Yes.
Look.
It's bright outside.
It's out.
We're saved.
What's this height?
The chiefs are there.
It's me.
Ryotsu.
Why are they there?
Idiot.
I'm worried about you.
Chief.
Don't worry about me.
What's this sound?
Chief.
Good.
The whole world is covered in snow.
Yes.
Ryo.
Hasn't it been shaking?
It's a high place.
It's shaking.
Ryo.
The ground is strange.
It seems to be moving away.
Ryotsu.
We're going to the rescue team right now.
Stay still.
What?
Please say it louder.
No.
Don't say it loud.
What?
I told you.
If you say it loud, the snow...
I can't hear you at all.
Please say it louder.
I told you to say it loud.
It's going to flow.
You'll be sorry.
Well, it's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Ryotsu!
I thought I was dead.
Hey, Ryotsu!
Chief...
How much trouble can you bring yourself to do this?
You're going to be snow-capped for the rest of your life!
That's not my fault!
Chief!
Help me!
Why?
Why is Ryo-san's...
Ryo-san's eyebrows are black?
Why does he look so pale?
Why?
Why does he run so fast even though he's wearing sandals?
Why does Ryo-san always have his arms around his neck?
Why?
Why does he look so flabby but still be loved by everyone?
It doesn't matter, but...
The title of this anime has been going on for so long...
"Katsushikaku Kameari Kouenmai"
I wonder why?
Why?
"Tenkyoku Oyaji"
What's up, Tenkyoku Oyaji?
Are you selling new products again?
A car with automatic control function connected to the canopy?
Sounds interesting!
"Put it on!"
Where did this car go?
And it doesn't stop!
It can't be a defective product!
Next time, "Where is this place, Tenkyoku Oyaji?"
Please watch!
Thank you!