Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ that floats in the middle ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble ♪
♪ and flew to the end ♪
♪ I was jogging ♪
♪ in the taiko club ♪
♪ and I was laughed at ♪
♪ for being a child ♪
♪ Even if I'm fine ♪
♪ somewhere ♪
♪ I can't help but grumble ♪
♪ and get angry ♪
♪ The cityscape ♪
♪ is so gentle ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ and the birds are singing ♪
♪ Are they all ♪
♪ playing yaki-tori ? ♪
♪ I wonder ♪
♪ what's going on ♪
♪ in the town ♪
♪ I'm on a trip ♪
♪ to the taishakuten ♪
♪ The sunset falls ♪
♪ I wake up tomorrow ♪
♪ and it ends ♪
♪ I laughed at the year end ♪
♪ and said I was happy ♪
♪ I lost it ♪
♪ and I realized ♪
♪ that I'm a fool ♪
♪ I got nothing ♪
♪ сlub take it away ♪
♪ in the town ♪
♪ That I'm a fool ♪
♪ You got it wrong ♪
♪ I know you're a fool ♪
♪ and I won't tell you ♪
♪ what's wrong ♪
*pant*
We did it! It's complete!
What do you think?
It's the most difficult manga to draw in Japan.
It's called "Manga Kanagase"
It's a model of 250th scale in the capital.
Wow, you've done a good job with the details.
The governor's office has the governor as well!
Senpai's modeling skills are already at the level of a master!
*pant*
Ryo-chan, we have a guest.
What? Me?
Cut! Cut!
Hey!
I didn't get any surprising reactions!
Ouch!
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Alright!
Good, good.
That face, that reaction!
Okay, okay.
*pant*
Hello, hello, hello!
Good afternoon, everyone!
I am something like this.
*pant*
Ooyama Bakuchi?
Hirouchi-yon!
*pant*
Are you Okura-pro?
I've never heard of you.
You're a famous producer among the fans!
I am.
And I have here with me
the world's most famous director,
Akira Kamerada, the great legend!
*pant*
Speaking of Akira Kamerada,
he's the one who hit the dance city and the dance intersection!
*pant*
He's the world's most famous director!
I can't believe it!
Is that so?
The world's most famous director,
who is proud of Japan,
is saying that he wants to borrow your skills for modeling!
*pant*
Hey, hey, stop!
What do you mean?
You can make the next movie's director
to do it.
I told you to make him do it!
I'll do it!
I'll ask him!
Director Jo, please!
Director Kamerada's director,
is so popular,
that he'll be popular everywhere!
Popular?
He is so cool, isn't he, Ryo-chan?
And if it is the new work of Director Kamerada,
people all over the world will pay attention to it!
So, what kind of new work is this?
Yes, the dance city,
the dance intersection,
the dance craftsman,
the dance Monji-yaki,
and the dance series' conclusion!
Conclusion
"Dancing Big Kameari"!
"Dancing Big Kameari"?
You're really into dancing big, aren't you?
Yes!
The stage is near the future.
The Japanese capital has moved from Tokyo to Kameari just a little.
That Kameari has become a criminal city.
This is about the brave police officers who face the cruel crime.
It's a big action melodrama with love, friendship, tears, laughter, song, and a big chorus of "chan-chiki-oke-san"!
I don't know why, but it seems like you're going to do it.
Yes.
As you know, Director Kamerada is a thorough strategist.
He doesn't use CG at all.
So I'm going to show you the new Kameari city of the future.
I want you to imagine that.
Of course, the reward is perfect.
By the time it hits, the 1% of the revenue will be yours.
1%?
That means, if you earn 10 billion, 10 million, and 1 billion,
100 million?
That's not bad.
Then I'll do it.
Here, sign here.
Yeah.
The shooting is in a week.
Until then,
I will definitely,
definitely,
have to make it in time.
Is this okay?
Then, take care.
It seems that the typhoon came and left in a blink of an eye.
Even so,
is it okay for a week, senpai?
What?
For 100 million!
I'll do it!
Senpai! I'll help, too!
Let's ask Sakonji-san and Borubo-san to help us!
Let's get it!
Finally, it's finished.
We did it, senpai.
I made it for a week in a hurry.
A millionth-in-a-lifetime future city Kamen Rider.
It's a party that's a new beginning.
This is a hard 100 million yen.
It's hard, isn't it?
That's right.
It's completed!
It's a wonderful weapon!
The image is coming up!
We're going to start shooting soon! Stand by!
Yes!
Stand by! Hurry up!
The image that came up is disappearing!
Oh, right, the assistant director is also doing it.
That's right! The assistant director is in the middle of work to be beaten up!
Don't drag me into unnecessary things!
Why are you so popular with girls?
Hurry up!
Ready!
Scene 13, take 1!
Start!
Cut! Yes, OK!
Hey, are you ready?
I'll cut it for a moment. That's my movie.
All right, the image is coming up!
Next is the scene of the big bang on the wall!
I'm going to shoot the scene!
What? The big bang?
There's still another scene to shoot!
This is the only way to translate this image into a film!
Break it down!
The future city that I made in a moment of time,
just a few seconds ago...
Cut!
Director Jo, prepare a dog!
Dog? That's not in the script!
It's not in the script!
The image is coming up!
Dog! This scene needs a dog no matter what!
What kind of image is this?
Hurry up! Dog! Dog!
Cut!
Scene 13, take 1!
Start!
Cut!
Director Jo, prepare a dog!
Can't you hear me?
No, director!
Director! Director!
What's wrong?
If you don't call me Kyosho, I won't move.
It's a hassle.
Kyosho, I've prepared a dog!
It's hard for Ryo-chan.
She has to be careful about how to call.
No.
No?
Oh, no?
They say the image is different.
Can someone find a different dog for me?
What?
No.
I don't want to.
No, no, no.
Isn't it amazing?
My image is still the same, is it?
Then which dog do you really like?
Oh, that.
Don't turn about with your greed.
It's so hot that it's gonna get on your face!
If you eat it, you'll get a bite of anything!
You're the one who's gonna die!
Me?
Why would you do this?
For 100 million yen, Ryotsu.
Yeah, Ryotsu. If you lose your temper here, it won't work.
Besides, you look good in it.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You guys are so easy-going!
Let's go!
Alright, here we go!
Action!
You're not even a dog from that far away.
What's the difference between you and other dogs?
Run at full speed!
Here we go!
That's it, Kuraitsu!
You're gonna get your revenge!
I won!
Alright, here we go!
The drowning person is coming!
The rescue dog jumps in!
Alright, action!
What?
I'm getting all sweaty!
That was a close call!
Hey, hello there!
You're all right?
Hey, Ryo.
The stuntman isn't here!
What? An accident? Can't you come?
What should I do? The director might get angry and leave.
If the movie doesn't get finished, the promised amount will be zero.
Please do something, Ryo-chan.
I'll do it.
So I'm going to be the one to do it.
Listen, I'll shoot you flying and falling upside down.
I'll show you the expression of fear.
This is the camera art.
Ryo-chan, you can fly as far as you want.
Senpai, I don't need to worry because the mat is new.
What?
In a word,
I thought you were a good guy.
Are you ready, Ryo-tsu?
Oh, yeah.
All right, start shooting.
Action.
Here we go.
Fire!
All right, now.
Take off the mat.
What are you doing?
Camera, look at that face.
Let's do another take.
What the hell is this?
That- uh...
We lost the director?
We even coat that clown's hands?
My work at Hollywood became a priority.
It rubbed off my reputation with a fight in Japan.
What should I do?
What about the movie?
If it doesn't come out as planned, then it's all over.
Until the movie's over, I'll get my ass kicked.
What?
I've been through so much trouble, but I'm going to make it all pay off!
If the director isn't here, I'll be the director!
But the sponsor...
The camera director is gone, so everyone got off.
If the sponsor got off, then the fee is...
You can't pay for that!
Hey, what are you going to do, Ryotsu?
Ugh...
If this goes on, I'll find a sponsor myself!
A sponsor?
Look! I'll make it all pay off!
What?
A movie sponsor?
You mean me?
This Kameari Shopping Street is a movie sponsor, right?
That's right. Instead, the entire shop will appear and become a commercial.
Hmm...
It's not a bad story, but what kind of content is it?
That's...
This is a bit boring.
After all...
There's no need for a movie sponsor.
I want an action scene like a Hong Kong movie.
How about a car chase?
It looks good to promote our model.
I want more people to come and see it.
How about a musical?
Huh?
What?
контрligt
You idiot!
I'll make you look like a nude for the sake of art!
Yeah, I'll take it off too.
Who wants to see your nude?
The audience will be shocked!
You're really okay, Ryo-chan.
Leave it to me!
Listen, just take everything off, it doesn't matter what it is.
Everything?
Yes, just everything!
Okay...
I understand.
Later, we'll make a video of Reiko's scene and then we'll go on the back route.
Alright, crank in!
Yeah!
Main stage, start, action!
This isn't happening in the meeting room!
It's happening in the candy shop in Kameari Shopping Street!
Thief! Wait!
2...
Cut!
Okay, next!
Why do we have to take a bath in this city?
Well, well, well, this scene is a very important scene.
"A
We're going to show you the greatest masterpiece of the century,
the long-awaited "The Dancing Great Kameyari"!
This movie was actually made 15 years ago.
It was said that it was impossible to make a movie about it.
Today, thanks to the full cooperation of the Kameyari Shopping Street,
it has finally been completed, overcoming many difficulties.
It's a movie that makes you want to keep talking about it.
You're really a senior.
Now, please enjoy the great masterpiece of the century,
"The Dancing Great Kameyari", which can even be talked about on the grand stage.
The
The incident didn't happen in the conference room!
It happened in the Kameyari Shopping Street, the confectionery shop!
Ehehe!
Ta-da!
Here it comes!
Mmm, I'm so excited!
Damn it!
The confectionery shop had a huge supply of sponsors.
I'm ready to avenge my father!
Hahaha!
You're going to make it, aren't you?
I'm going to make it!
Yes!
The confectionery shop has a huge supply of sponsors!
Kyaa!
Ugh!
Where are you going?
Hahahahaha!
Here it is!
The Kameyari Shopping Street, Tsurukami-ken's ramen set meal
costs 650 yen, including ramen, rice and dumplings!
Is it worth it?
What's with that?
Here is another set meal!
A set meal set by all the customers in Tsurukami-ken!
The Kikuchi-sen-yuten is on sale every Thursday and Sunday!
There's a whole day of dancing with a big party!
Eh!
In Tsurukami-ken, you can get the half-day service in the afternoon from 11:00 to 2:00!
Ah!
When you go shopping at Kikuchi-sen-yuten, you can get a set meal for 500 yen each.
When you save up 20 yen, you can get a cash-back of 500 yen!
Oh!
The Kameyari Shopping Street's electricity is so cheap,
I bought it because it was cheap, but I was late.
The culprit... Where is the culprit?
♪Rurururarara♪
♪One step in the circle of action♪
♪The wings grow and the fight begins♪
♪Janken San Kyouda♪
♪Rurururara♪
Atsui-seki!
Shut up!
Refresh your fatigue by taking a bath at the Kameari shopping street.
We're waiting for you at Kamenoyu.
Nakagawa Ikenyon and F-Cup Rave's photo book.
On sale at the same time as the movie.
What? Ryo-chan made a photo book secretly?
Without our permission,
we're going to take a walk on the back road.
We're going to take a walk on the back road.
No unfurl!
That's terrible!
A crazy-looking man.
No unfurl!
A sh concerning bill.
Were you filming at a place like that?
I told you to shoot everything.
Editing costs time to process...
You're really going to make a cover later, right?
You're really going to make a cover after this, aren't you?
Oh, my God!
Yay!
This is the real "Dancing Big Kameari"!
I won't lose to you, Ruriri!
This is the "Dancing Medium Kameari"!
This is the "Dancing Super-Summoning Kameari"!
Kameari!
This is bad...
What the hell is this?
Do you hate this?
I'm not kidding!
You're so crazy!
I have a dream of 3 billion yen!
It rained on a rainy afternoon
As if someone is calling me
Looking back I reached out
To walk with my mother
I felt
Some kind of strange feelings
I felt at the time
I walked on the black tile
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgets
A politician with a great face
An old lady with blue eyes
Look up at that corner
You'll meet everyone
There's a turtle there
There must be a turtle
Come to our town
There's a turtle there
There must be a turtle
Come to our town
Thank you!
Honda was dumped and started to disband?
And then, you have a child and a student?
What's that?
I can read that too!
Alright, how about this?
"Honda was dumped and went on a great rampage"
Next time, "The Great Worm, Okuno Hosomichi"
See you!
"There's a turtle there"
"There must be a turtle"
"Come, everyone"
"Come to our town"
Thank you!
To Be Continued