When you watch TV
Make sure to keep your room light and keep your distance
It's like someone's calling
After the rain
I walked looking back
I was drawn to Gacha
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried walking on the black tile of the arcade
I tried walking on the black tile of the arcade
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall over there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Komachi Big Break
Everyone come to our town
There must be a many children
Who are you
Komachi Big Break
That's why I don't have a wife.
What? I don't want to hear that from you.
That's right. You're saying too much.
That's right. That's right.
I'm really sorry.
Look at this before you start talking.
Wow! Nagagawa!
You two look good together.
How is it, Komachi?
Compared to Nagagawa and Reiko, who have this refreshing image,
what do you think is the most miserable thing about you?
If you ask me, I think it's...
I think so too.
No way.
You're completely destroying the image of the Katsushika office!
Ryo-chikan, Kichi-me, look at me now!
I'm going to do it when I have to!
Wow!
W... What are you doing, Komachi?
You're so pretty!
How can you be?
I think that can happen anytime.
It's your turn, Imetsu!
Now you can have a look at me.
Phew...
I feel like I've been reborn.
I didn't know that gathering everyone's attention was so exciting.
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
I'm the cameraman of the weekly YYBOY.
Cameraman?
Yes. Actually, I'm going to do a project called "A cool girl found in the city".
I'd like you to take a picture with me.
Sure, just one.
Thank you.
What? Best 1?
A cool girl found in the city?
The first in the calculation. Isn't that amazing, Komachi?
What's going on? I didn't know that a mountain fox like this would be chosen as the best 1.
What do you mean by a mountain fox? It means that people in the world are looking at it.
Oh, Director.
Hey, Komachi.
I'm Kasushi.
You've contributed a lot to the image-up of the magazine.
I'll be counting on you from now on.
We're all very proud of you as a same-sex worker.
That's right.
What?
There she is.
Where?
I found her.
In this house.
Damn it.
Look here.
You idiot.
What?
She was a hero.
I'm in trouble.
What's going on?
How did this happen?
It's a big mess.
Everyone's here to interview Komachi.
What?
What a fool.
It's the era when idols close to you are more popular than the stars you don't have.
I... I'm in trouble.
Please come this way.
Yes, you can.
No.
Please make this much for me.
This way, please.
You're already in trouble.
Yes.
Here you are.
That's theって.
You've put it there.
G folders now.
She's a real soba girl!
Isn't she nice?
That's a piece of cake.
Give it back to me.
I've got it.
I'll...
Then I'll leave it to you.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
The owner is quite the poet.
It's in this house.
I've just been told.
I found this.
You don't have to worry about such a thing.
I'll leave it to you.
Please come this way.
It's a good idea.
I see. I heard that you are very popular
Sugiyama, please have some coffee
Yes
No, I'm fine with coffee
Anyway, it's time for the neon light
What?
It's neon
Neon
Oh, I see
I see
That's funny
Well, Ryotsu-san, I think you'll be satisfied with the character
You are not the character, you are me
I'm just your heart
Yes, I know
What? I'm in the commercial?
You have a high voice
You still don't know what you're doing
I'm still in the process of getting hired
Don't tell anyone
Anyway, since I became the manager, I'll sell you a lot, so leave it to me
Why are you the manager?
It's a general order to improve the image of the Katsushika office
General order?
Yes
I'm busy, but I can't go against the general order
I decided to be a man and take off my skin
General order?
Hm, I think so
We stopped him
Then, I'll get to the real game
I'm Akutamaki
I'll arrest you
Komachi is also drinking
Gakken drink
Come on, here you are
Is that Komachi?
You're'm just like a stranger
Well, but you're a happy child
I'm Akutamaki
I'll arrest you!
I'm drinking too!
Hey, show me again!
That's right!
How many times do I have to see it?
I'll arrest you!
That's right!
You're so cute!
You really are a girl.
You're much more beautiful than my daughter.
Yes, that's right.
Hey, did you do my commercial?
Yes, I did.
I've been watching it many times.
Hey, Kasuya.
Hey, Komachi.
My relatives are all from the village.
I'm going to celebrate tonight.
That's embarrassing.
Mr. Ryozu, could you take a picture of Komachi?
Well, I'll think about it.
That's great, Komachi.
Komachi is my campaign girl.
Leave it to me!
Hurry up.
Why are you so busy?
Let me eat breakfast.
If you don't like the food, I'll give it to you.
Komachi eating too.
Katsushika Mai
Thank you very much.
It's a sweet potato.
Sweet potato?
It's very heavy.
This looks delicious.
Sweet potato.
You're a bad boy.
I'm not as bad as you.
What are you talking about?
If you don't get up, you'll be arrested.
I'm so tired.
I really feel tired.
This isn't going to work.
That's right.
This can be used to improve the image of the Ministry of Commerce.
This is the end of today's mission.
Please leave the information.
Thank you for your hard work!
Komachi-chan!
Arita will do her best too!
Yes! Thank you!
I'm tired...
Thank you for your hard work!
Idols are also very hard!
Komachi-san Watcher also appeared,
and it seems that the internet homepage also has great access.
But why are they so busy?
Maybe because it's the image-up month?
Ryo-chan says so, but it's somewhat suspicious.
I'm sorry.
Ah!
Komachi-chan, it's your work!
No! I'm tired.
Don't say that.
Komachi-chan is an idol in Japan now.
Idols are not easy.
Why don't you let him rest a little?
No, I have to earn money when I can.
Eh?
No, no, no, I have to earn money.
I have to earn money.
Come on, Komachi.
Come on, come on, come on.
What?
Huh?
License?
Hey, what are you doing with this?
That's Komachi-san's license contract.
I signed it with my senior's name.
I knew it.
Ryo-chan made money by using Komachi-chan, right?
No, it's not that...
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
You don't have to say anything more than me.
You're so greedy.
What's with this Yamazori?
He was quite an idol.
What?
I also let Mashiro do a lot of things.
Like you.
You can't be an idol if you don't know how to act.
You're lying.
You can't pretend to be an idol and play with a pure heart.
Komachi-chan.
I don't know where the watcher is.
There she is.
What?
What's...
What's going on?
That idol Komachi-san is hugging a man.
I'm in love.
What?
Where did you two meet?
Where was your first date?
I was planning on getting married!
Why did this happen?
This is the Kameari Park Exhibition Hall.
As you can see, a lot of mass media is pushing for this.
I'm so worried!
Ono Komachi has found a lover!
His partner is the Chief of Police, Ryo-tsu Kankichi, who works at the Kameari Park Exhibition Hall.
He said he met Komachi-san when he was cleaning the Katsushika office.
They always go on dates at a French restaurant called P in Roppongi.
Did you really say that, Ryo-san?
Of course I did!
That's right, you gorilla!
What?
This newspaper also has comments about Komachi-chan's parents.
They said they met at the wedding.
That's just a rumor about his father.
But if you write it like this, it's hard to solve any misunderstanding.
No way!
This kind of thing is a rumor that's been going around for a long time.
That's the story of the planets they've never been to.
I don't mind if you write it like you've seen it there.
Ryo-sama!
Hey, Maria!
What the hell is this article about?
It's so much to say about me!
What?
That article is just all nonsense.
You idiot!
Ryo-sama's sidekick!
Wait, Maria!
Calm down!
What a surprise!
The new fact has been discovered!
Ryo-san's lover was Komachi-san's fiance, Ryo-san's idol, Junsacho!
No!
Ryo-sama!
Maria!
No!
What's your name?
I'm Maria!
What?
Ryo-san and Junsacho are in a relationship?
Yes.
What's your relationship?
We've been together before.
Maria!
What?
This is nonsense!
No, it's not!
Listen up, everyone!
Maria is a man!
This is a shocking confession!
Ryo-san and Junsacho's lover was a man!
A man?
What does that mean?
A man is one who is playback, a man thinks whatever he can.
Ryo, is what Maria said true?
No, it's not true.
What about me?
You forgot about Komachi.
In this difficult time,
a hero loved by both men and women,
his name is Ryo Tsukkankichi.
Kokomo.
Ryo is everywhere on TV.
Not only on TV.
He's also on "Women Weekly".
He's not on TV anymore.
I feel sorry for Komachi.
He's on "Men's Fashion magazine".
"Ganimata Tanso is the charm of men".
"The era is Ryo-tsu".
Today, we will introduce the Ryo Tsukkankichi's
Ryo Tsukkankichi goods.
It's called "Kankichi Tsunagari Mayege".
I'll put it on.
How is it?
Great.
It's manly and wonderful.
And now,
I'll put on this Kankichi sandal.
It's a must-have item to show manliness.
Now, please call us.
From today, you are also a Ryo Tsukkankichi.
What should we do?
Please cut Ryo-tsu.
Kankichi is popular now.
It's very cool.
Ryo Tsukkankichi to the Best Genius Show.
Tokyo's specialty, Ryo Tsukkankichi.
Ryo san.
Source key holder.
Ryo san of sleepiness.
I'm sleeping.
Don't touch me.
Ryo tsukkankichi of gentleman.
When today's Ryo Tsukkankichi.
Science Chi KNo lights.
This is a photo album of Ryo Tsukkankichi.
Many people have been interested in Ryo Tsukkankichi.
That idiot.
What does it mean?
I'm in trouble!
Oh, my.
I can't stop thinking about the left and right.
Oh, Daisuke is here.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Grandpa!
Oh, Daisuke.
You've grown up.
Let me hold you.
Here.
There's something good for you, Grandpa.
What is it?
It's fine, Grandpa.
Please stop it.
Ryo-chan, the hero who is loved by both women and men.
I will defeat the weak!
The times have been waiting for me!
You've become a very popular person, Ryo-chan.
I'm like my senior.
So there are more and more people who want to pet gorillas.
I see.
What are you thinking about?
It's the end of the century.
It's a sad thing.
Chief!
The TV station wants to interview Ryo-san's boss.
What?
Me?
I'll do it!
Start!
Well, um...
Ryo-chan and Ryo-chan...
I've been in trouble since he was assigned...
No, no, no.
Ryo-chan and Kanchichi are the mirror of the TOH Katsushika.
This is also a story.
It's the result of my daily education.
Don't forget Tonda Gomez, Tonda Gomez!
Toh Katsushika
Hey.
What's this?
Ryo-chan and Kanchichi are both here.
It was a small town until recently.
What was that?
Ryo-chan and Kanchichi!
Please shake hands!
What?
Please let me touch the eyebrows of the actor.
Okay, go ahead.
It's hard to be popular.
If you want to be popular like me,
you'd better buy these Ryo-chan goods.
What?
You're in a good mood.
I thought it was someone else.
Well...
Who was it?
I remember Fukie-san was an idol
and something like that.
But I don't remember who it was.
I don't remember.
How is it, Ryo-san?
It's a pretty good work, isn't it?
It's like looking in the mirror.
Ryo-chan and Kanchichi's original
one-in-a-half figures are perfect.
But Ryo-san,
I'm sure it'll be okay this time.
I was a failure before.
There's no mistake this time!
If you want to make money now,
you'll be able to sell anything.
I'll make a million copies for the time being.
I'll invest all my assets in this.
First of all,
I'll use a TV or magazine to do an overall commercial.
Ryo-san,
I'm counting on you!
A girl was waiting.
I was crying. A man cried.
Ryo's Kankichi Original 1/1 Complete Figure.
Tomorrow, it will be available all over Japan.
Today is finally the day it will be released.
Senpai is very determined, but is it really okay to make a million of them?
Look! On TV, Ryoko Yoshikawa is interviewed about Ryo's figure.
What?
It's about Ryoko, who is popular and sensitive.
So, you can buy the popular Ryo-tsu figure right away.
What? Me?
If you say you want Ryoko, it's a panic.
Yes.
I don't like Ryo because he's a little grumpy.
Ryo is ugly and stinky.
I don't like him.
I'm not interested.
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
This is...
That one word of Ryoko...
It's a good idea.
That's not a boom.
You can't go because you're greedy.
Oh no!
What's wrong, Terai?
There he is!
What's going on?
This time, I'm being chased by the media!
What?
This figure and his face make me feel bad.
This time, Terai's boom?
Hello!
Sorry, it's time! Please wake up!
That's right!
Oh, look.
A bird is flying!
That's ridiculous!
I'm so stupid! What happened to my part?
Now, I will give you a present.
Now, the prize is 8 million yen for Nauna Young's popular "Erai-san Keyholder".
I told you, there's no such thing.
If you make a mistake, don't send me a postcard.
Got it?
I won!
An idol climbing documentary?
What's that?
What? The part-time job for that film is 8,000 yen?
Leave it to me.
I will show you the video with my sense of power and realism.
Next time, I'm a video cameraman.
Thank you for watching.