You can see the full version on our channel!
If you enjoyed the video, please subscribe to our channel!
♪ Uka-bun ♪
The Two Dangerous People
Did you see that, Nagagawa?
It sticks perfectly in 0.4 seconds.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
I see.
It's thanks to Super Cement X.
This adhesive is too strong to be sold in Japan.
It's a great product.
So I got it from the United States.
It's 30,000 yen a piece.
It doesn't matter what kind of material it is.
I don't have to choose.
If you apply a little bit of this,
Even a heavy object like this...
It's just like this.
It's amazing.
It doesn't come off at all.
It's too strong and scary.
So you have to use it.
You can only get it at the supermarket.
What if you put it on by mistake?
There's a set of neutralizers.
If you don't have this, it's a big deal.
It's really a modeler's specialty.
Kei, wait a minute.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
The work is fast.
There's little protrusion.
It's all about Super Cement X.
What?
You idiot.
Hey, don't steal Super Cement X.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Let go, let go.
What are you doing?
Nakagawa.
Help me.
What happened to you?
Nakagawa, take this off with neutralizers.
I thought there was a kotatsu on the front of the kotatsu.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Please take your time.
Oh, the neutralizers are gradually decreasing.
Idiot. Use it carefully.
What's going on?
Oh, sir.
I spilled the strong adhesive and the kotatsu got stuck.
I keep doing that all year round.
If you peel it off at once, it will come off.
Stop it.
The meat will come off.
Well, I have to peel it off with neutralizers little by little.
It's better to leave it for a while.
I think it's better to leave it for a while.
I finally became a free man.
Well, I'm going to get a bottle next time.
Yeah.
Oh, it's almost done.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Super Cement X.
What's that?
It's in my pants.
It sticks when you touch it, chief.
What's with you?
Do something about it.
You won't let me do that.
Ouch.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Super Cement X.
It's working.
I don't know what will happen.
What?
Huh?
What the...
What is it?
Let go of my hand!
You're a disgusting bastard!
No, I mean, sir.
I'd like to talk to you, but...
The glue is stuck on the wall...
Idiot! Get rid of it!
I know...
Hey, Nakagawa.
The neutralizing agent.
Oh, that's right.
Well, well...
Ow, ow, ow!
Sir, it hurts!
It hurts!
You idiot!
I told you we'd have a meeting at noon,
but you're...
Well, well, sir.
Senior,
do you have any other models
with Super Cement X?
Oh, that's Nakagawa for you!
Are you going to get rid of it?
Well, I think he's...
Oh...
I'm sorry, sir.
I was thinking about it,
and I'm going to Tibet to train.
You idiot!
Sir, you can't fight in a place like this!
Nakagawa,
will you get rid of it?
I can't do anything about it...
Do something, Nakagawa!
You're going to spill the neutralizing agent,
so this is what's going to happen!
No way!
No, you have to be careful.
You can't pull out Super Cement X
from my hand.
You're the one who didn't seal the lid properly,
and I'm going to say you're amazing,
so I'm going to get in trouble
and get beaten by a cat while I'm showing it to you.
That cat's going to come to the station
because you're the bait.
That's why I'm in trouble with growing up a cat.
If you think it's bad,
do something about it right now!
Are you listening? What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you!
0.4 seconds.
Then you're coming to the meeting.
Why are you bringing me here?
Sir, are you really going to the station like that?
I don't want to walk around the city in this outfit.
You're not going to join the meeting.
Anyway, I don't want to.
That's right.
I'm going to get the culprit and put on a handkerchief.
Reiko, you're rude.
You're going to be the culprit.
You're stupid.
Whoever sees you will think you're the culprit.
Then,
how about you hold this old fridge?
Well, it's a natural style.
Is that so?
Then I'm going to the meeting,
so I'll leave the rest to you.
Please be careful.
...
Kei-chan,
why don't you eat some Soka-senbei instead of being angry?
...
Why isn't this heavy stuff in the box?
You're an idiot!
Whose responsibility is it?
...
Sir, stop!
What? There's no time?
I want to pee.
...
I don't think you can do it.
I can't. I'll do it in the back.
You idiot! The police are going to take care of it!
I have to hurry.
Welcome.
Sorry, can I use the bathroom?
No, it's in the back.
Chief, hurry up!
Be careful.
It's here! Hurry up!
Wait, Ryozu!
What is it?
It's not fair for two men to go to the bathroom.
There's no way. We're connected.
It's leaking!
Ryozu, wait!
This is my social status.
What are you doing?
Don't touch it.
I have to open the zipper and pull it out.
Shut up! I have to touch your dirty stuff too!
What should I do?
The chief invited us.
I didn't invite you.
If you come this far, the chief will be okay.
I understand. Don't shout.
Put your pants down and get ready.
This is my way!
You're still here?
Yes.
Chief.
What?
This is the situation, so you seem excited about it.
N-no way. Hurry up!
Oh, no!
What do you want this time?
I want a bigger one.
I want to visit you.
Don't be stupid.
I'm already at the exit.
Shut up!
Don't pull me.
I'll leave with that stimulus.
I'm leaving.
Let's go, Ryokun!
Wait a minute, chief.
Just a little more.
I forgot the fridge.
It's okay.
I'm too tired to carry it.
I'll leave it.
Wait a minute, chief.
I haven't put on my underwear yet.
Chief!
No wonder you're sticking out like a log after all the time you've been flying around.
Well, this middle-aged man is walking holding hands closely, though.
This middle-aged man is walking holding hands closely, though.
Don't know why you're doing it this way.
It's not unnatural to walk while dancing like this.
Like that.
Quick, quick, slow!
Not unnatural at all, is it, chief?
Don't point your finger at me!
He hit my hand.
Hey, Ryo-san!
Huh?
I've been looking for you, Ryo-san!
Everyone's been waiting for you since noon!
Why aren't you coming today?
What are you talking about?
I won't die!
What?
You're going to make a fool of yourself
for losing yesterday, aren't you?
Fine!
I won't invite you.
I won't!
If you keep acting like this,
you won't understand what you're doing.
You're completely different from everyone else!
You're lying to me.
Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?
My joints are breaking!
I won't see your ugly face anymore!
You're so annoying.
Oh no!
Today was the day of the Kue Kue!
What did I do?
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, chief, I'm sorry.
Today was the day of the Kue Kue!
Kure Kure?
What is that?
It's not Kure Kure.
It's Kue Kue.
I don't care about that.
I'll do it after I'm late for the meeting.
It's popular, so it'll be sold out.
Shut up!
Get out of my way!
Ryo, get out of my way!
How can I get out of your way?
Oh, chief, it hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts, Ryo!
It hurts!
Don't fall over, you idiot!
Why, chief!
Speaking of which, you're the one who...
But you're in this position.
Chief!
You!
Why did this happen?
That's my line.
Oh, god...
Listen, Karin.
He is so bullied, doesn't he?
Chief is ville.
It doesn't matter if Chie had a good mind about me, or if I'll get exposed to a girl.
The invitation was a shame, but I'm happy to be here.
If you disobey me, I'll kill you.
But you always say...
That's right.
Keep quiet during the meeting!
Ouch!
Yes, yes, I understand.
You keep on hitting me, I remember.
Ohara-kun, what's wrong?
Well, Ryotsu said he wanted to hold a meeting to study.
I understand Ryotsu-kun's intention, but that's what we want to say.
That's what we want to say.
Oh, wait, what?
When did he become like this?
Right, Ryotsu?
Ehehehe...
Next, it's about the "Hittaguri Incident" that has been happening in the city.
The possibility of the victim being the same as the witness is high.
Hey, Ryotsu, Ryotsu!
Wake up!
Ouch!
What's wrong, Ryotsu-kun?
Oh, I'm sorry!
I was just so nervous...
Damn it, Ryotsu-kun.
You've made me come to this ridiculous meeting, but you can't make me do anything, right?
That's right.
W-what's wrong, Ryotsu-kun?
Why are you suddenly taking my hand?
Huh?
Oh, it's you, Daijirou-chan.
You've come to the Hancho meeting, because you don't want to leave me.
If you do something like this in front of everyone, we'll be exposed, right?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
W-w-what's wrong with you two?
I-it's a misunderstanding!
Oh, that's fine, Daijirou-chan. We've been exposed, so we're in love.
By the way, you've been holding hands for a long time.
When I came, we were hugging in strange clothes.
No, no, no! This is...
Daijirou-chan's hands are so plump and lovely!
Hey, stop it, Ryotsu!
Ohara-kun, I understand you well.
But we're in the middle of a meeting right now.
Don't overdo it.
Chief!
Oh, I see. I'm glad, Daijirou-chan.
Damn it, Ryotsu!
It ended unexpectedly early.
Idiot! It's all because of you that I got promoted next week!
Nehehehehe!
Oh, Chief!
Don't you feel hungry?
I'm not hungry!
Huh?
Well, you're hungry, aren't you?
Here, I'll have the curry.
Sure.
I'll have...
Let's see...
I'll have the Kitsune Udon.
Yes, curry and udon.
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'll have my own.
It's hot!
No, thank you.
Damn it, you did it on purpose.
It's hot!
Chief, look at this.
Huh?
It's hot.
Chief, you're not going to eat?
I told you I'm not hungry.
I'm sorry I ate all of it.
I didn't think about the chopsticks.
I ate it.
Chief, what are you going to do today?
The work hours are over.
I'm going home.
What?
Are you going to the countryside?
I've been rolling around all day today.
I want to take a bath.
Ryo has a bath, too.
I'll take a bath.
I just want to stay in my room.
I don't want to stay in your messy room.
I'm going home anyway.
Are you serious?
He drives a fine train like this and goes home every day, right?
Shut up.
You're walking for 15 minutes right now, and you're late.
You don't understand my suffering.
I don't know.
Ouch! What did you do?!
I didn't do anything!
How dare you touch my butt and give me a fling?!
Well, you're a police officer, aren't you?
R-Ryozu, did you really touch it?
How can you touch it in this state?
I-I see...
Hey, are you a member of the police?
You're a two-member police?
What do you mean?
Miss, you must be mistaken.
This man has been in this state for a long time.
Oh, come on!
What do you mean I'm such an over-conscious woman?
I'll be rude!
What?
You're holding hands with men, aren't you?
You pervert, pervert police officer!
Pervert...
Police officer!
Daijiro Ohara.
I'm a first-time police officer in front of Kameari Park in Katsushikaku.
I've been a stupid subordinate, but I've been loving people for ten years,
aiming to become a police officer loved by people.
But, but...
I'm a pervert police officer!
Ryozu!
I-I'm so frustrated!
I'm not a pervert!
Shut up!
It's terrible!
It's too terrible!
I'm a pervert!
Chief, we're in a real danger.
Chief, we'll be home soon, so cheer up!
What?
It hurts!
Ouch.
Ryozu.
You bastard.
I'll get you!
Ouch.
What?
Come on, Ryozu!
Yes.
That's right.
Auntie, I want to borrow a bicycle.
What?
Ryozu, are you okay?
I just put my luggage there to harvested things.
You can't see ahead, chief, give me an order.
Alright, got it!
Go, Ryotsu!
Let's go!
It's pretty good.
I'm a professional on a bicycle.
Anyway, look ahead.
I know.
Watch out! There's a obstacle ahead!
Turn left!
Yes, sir!
I turned left!
You idiot! I turned left!
You should have told me!
You just need the tools. I'll handle the handle.
I thought you were a craftsman.
It hurts!
Wait! I can't run anymore! Stop!
You idiot!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Ryotsu! Brake! Brake!
Brake!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I'll catch you!
What? How can you catch me when both of your hands are blocked?
Huh?
Oh, this is it!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I took off my eyebrows!
I've been a model for 28 years!
I'll catch you!
Don't underestimate me!
Help me!
That's it.
It's amazing how you guys can catch a frog in that state.
If you get me, any kind of impossible will be possible.
Thanks to you, my body is damaged.
But you should thank Kei-chan.
He's been trying to help you.
He got a day's worth of food from the US.
Hey, idiot!
Sorry about yesterday.
It's okay.
I was so angry about that, too.
I was the only one who was angry.
I caught you!
I caught you! I caught you!
Now I can finally be free.
Anyway,
I'm going to go to the bathroom, go to the bathroom, go to bed, go to sleep, and everything will be the same as you.
It was the worst day.
I'm so glad I was able to return to normal.
I happen to be able to arrest a criminal with this.
Okay.
I'll take this to prevent you from making models while you're on duty.
What?
No, sir.
Give it back.
It's 30,000 yen per model.
I don't know about that.
Get away, you little!
No way, I don't know about my modeling life.
I made models while I was on duty!
You're the one who made this!
Senpai, move!
No, Ryo!
Ouch!
It's not my fault!
Senpai!
Let me go!
Hey, hey, wait a minute!
Chihuahua! Chihuahua!
Someone take me!
What? Was Uncle Borubo a ninja?
And that ninja uncle
is taking a look at you and telling you you're a ninja school?
That's no good!
You have Jody, don't you?
Wait a minute.
A skinny, fat, sexy ninja.
This might work!
Next time on "Gekichin Ninja-Z"
Thanks for watching!
Today's theme, "History of a Ninja"
- Part 2 - "H
istory of a Ninja-Z" - Part
3 - - Part
4 - - Part
5 - - Part
6 - - Part
7 - - - - - - - - - - - - -
♪ The fluttering ♪
♪ Yaaaaaah ♪
♪ The beating ♪
♪ Debe-debe ♪
♪ The clashing ♪
♪ Bagi-bagi ♪
♪ The action ♪
♪ Yaaaaaah ♪
♪ The flying ♪
♪ More than anything else, it's full of power ♪
♪ Everyone gather here ♪
♪ The final energy is like a dream ♪
♪ The final energy ♪
♪ Tomorrow is the third day ♪
♪ Believe in yesterday ♪
♪ Draw the universe ♪
♪ If you stand on the ground ♪
♪ The planet Kameari will come ♪
♪ Draw the circle ♪
♪ This is good, right? ♪
♪ There's no reason to say it's good, right? ♪
Translated by Shion