When you're watching TV, keep your room bright and keep an eye out for enemies.
Those who have no money, come to me!
I don't have any, but I'm worried.
See the blue sky and white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Do you understand? I understand, I understand
If you understand, come to me quietly
I'm sure there is a turtle there
There must be a turtle
It's autumn
Hey Ebisu
Oh
It's been a long time since I've seen Ebisu
Yotsu senpai
Why are you laughing?
Is there something good?
Actually, I'm currently on leave of absence
What?
I was so depressed that I wondered what to do
Don't be depressed while laughing
I'm sorry
You're still laughing as usual
Stop it
By the way, I said I quit the police
Didn't you get scouted by the special police department after that?
So it was like this
You don't have to cry
Guys!
What are you doing?
Yeah
Don't cry
It's the way that I am
De persone
Did you make a great deal of money last year?
Hey, I'm not going to be able to get out of here.
I'm sure you're going to come out, too.
Hey, I'm not going to be able to get out, either.
There's a cat and a cat.
Hey, you're not laughing, either!
But he's a model!
He's being laughed at by his host!
Now!
I, Kai Pandeka, am back!
You did well, Owarai Deka.
Yes!
You're not Owarai Deka.
That's a pretty good name!
I was quite fond of your name.
So, you didn't think you could quit.
It's ok if I quit at the scene.
What?
I have to keep in touch with those insiders every day.
I wash my face great every day,
and my belly button shrinks too much,
and then I have to go to the hospital again and again.
No, you can't.
I don't wanna eat any of your food.
You can't.
Oh, Senpai, this is my house. Would you like to have some tea?
What? The original Ebisu Shrine?
Your house was a shrine?
Yes! It was built by Tokugawa Ieyasu,
and it's a shrine that the Ebisu family protected for generations.
Huh?
Whoa! What's this huge statue?
What statue?
These are all statues of Lord Ebisu.
They're a collection that our ancestors collected from time to time.
Some of them are designated as important cultural relics,
but there are also some that aren't.
The big gold one in the middle?
That's my grandfather's, but it's a Mecchi.
Huh?
I'll go get some tea.
Oh, sorry about that.
Huh? This is the Mecchi.
So which one is the important cultural relic-type Lord Ebisu?
Hmm...
Oh, this one?
Oh?
He seems chubby, but the look on his face says he's not one.
He seems like he'll show a turn of bench cabin again…
Ah! Ah! A-a-a-a...
A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a--
It—it—it's so bad.
Oh no, this is bad.
I guess I'll have to take it back for repair.
Huh?
This is all that's left.
We'll need to kill them.
I guess he won't notice anyway.
Senpai!
Huh?
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
Ebisu-sama is a god who calls good fortune, right?
I was trying to get some help from you, so I was just doing my best.
Haha, you did?
You even stepped on the god, but you still got what you wanted.
Hahaha...
Hey, don't laugh!
S-sorry, senpai.
I'll have some tea.
Ah, sorry.
I just remembered some work.
I'm going home.
What?
Senpai is working?
Hahaha...
That's so funny!
Let's go home quietly for today.
Let's see...
Like this...
I guess I can fool him somehow.
I just need to leave him alone.
Huh?
W-what's with that crowd?
What's going on?
What happened?
It seems that Ebisu-sama's statue has been stolen.
What?
Ryotsu-senpai!
Giku!
Senpai!
No, I didn't steal it!
Huh?
Hahahaha, what are you talking about?
There's no way you can steal 100 statues of Ebisu-sama by yourself, right?
Hahaha, I don't want to do this anymore.
What, did you steal that whole thing?
Yes, I did but I lost it.
That's so funny!
I'm sorry!
Hahaha...
Well, for now, I won't tell you about the statue I broke.
That was also a disaster for Ebisu-san.
But it's strange.
Hmm...
There was a safe nearby,
but it wasn't there at all.
Then, the only statue that was stolen was the Ebisu statue?
That's true, it's strange.
The culprit is a thief who specializes in statues and art.
Hmm...
Oh?
The stolen statue of Ebisu-sama seems to have been found at the time of the fire.
What did you say?
What is it?
Hahaha, I'm not mistaken!
They are all my statues of Ebisu-sama!
Hmm, I don't understand at all.
There are millions of pure gold statues and important statues inside.
There are also things like cultural relics.
Why did the culprit throw them away?
Well, more than that,
Senpai, why do you have bananas?
I was eating them on the way.
Oh?
What's wrong, Reiko-san?
Look at this.
There's a hole in it.
What?
What did you say?
It's true.
Everything is carved and there's a hole in it.
What does this mean?
Haha, what is it?
It's strange.
Hmm.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Hmm...
I feel like I'm being watched by someone.
I guess it's just my imagination.
What?
Hmm...
What's up?
I'm so glad to have an important Ebisu-sama back.
That man is so careless!
Oh no!
I should have just left it in the bush.
What's this?
I found it!
Oh, this is an old map.
What is it?
"When the water of the waterfall disappears, the key to the Uraedo Castle will not be opened."
What is this?
How is it, Nakagawa?
I have no idea.
When the water of the waterfall disappears, is it a metaphor?
Is there a time when the water of the waterfall disappears?
Besides, what is the Uraedo Castle?
Do you know anything about it?
I don't know.
I've never heard of it.
I see.
If it's Nakagawa or Reiko, do you know anything about it?
I thought I knew something about it.
Then, why don't you ask Mr. Daemon, the fourth chapter?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Mr. Daemon is famous as a common historian, so he might know something.
This is a great discovery!
Don't make a loud voice all of a sudden.
What is a great discovery?
This is a drawing of Ieyasu.
What?
Look.
The letters and faces are Ieyasu's.
No way.
It's true.
There is a picture of Ieyasu's letter to his vassal.
It's exactly the same as the face of Ieyasu.
Look.
Which one?
Hey, isn't this a photograph of Haruka Iyama?
What?
I...I mistook it.
This is it.
Don't put it together.
Look.
It's exactly the same.
No way.
This is for sure the drawing of Ieyasu himself.
By the way, what is in this map was the statue of Lord Ebisu.
The original Ebisu Shrine which kept this is the only correct Shrine built by Ieyasu.
I see.
Yeah.
This might be a treasure map.
What? A treasure?
This is my theory.
Ieyasu defeated Shizuoka in the battle of Sekigahara,
After the battle of Hara, you also know that the winter and summer people of Osaka destroyed the Toyotomi family.
I've seen it in the movie and the drama.
So Ieyasu secretly carried his treasure from Edo Castle.
Wait wait wait! Could it be...
Tokugawa's manatee that Shigesato Itoi was looking for on TV?
Probably.
So how much do you think it is?
Right.
It's a military fund that will take back the country.
So when you calculate that amount,
it could be about one trillion yen.
One trillion yen?
One trillion yen per day?
5 yen!?
Where on earth is that hidden?
It's not just this map.
Maybe there are several maps, and they're not all in one.
The treasure must be sleeping here.
It's not that simple.
If it's like that, it's hard for Sato Ito and Shige Sato.
What are you doing?
Hand over that map and the Ebisu statue.
If you hand it over, I'll save your life.
What?
Who's going to hand it over, you idiot?
Yamuoe, it seems you have no choice but to take it with force.
Hand it over quietly.
You're so naive.
You bastard!
What?
What's this?
If you think it's a history book, it's all idol photo books.
Stop it!
It's my collection!
What are you looking at?
Hurry up and do it!
Stop it!
It's a photo book I worked hard to collect!
That's...
Stop it!
It's a photo book I worked hard to collect!
It's a premium product.
This is...
That's...
It's so nice!
Bastard!
Go after them!
One trillion yen goes to me!
Yes!
It's the biggest!
A-A lot...
Hey, he looks like a ninja.
As Sasuke-bei said, he's a tough opponent.
Yes.
Listen, collect his data immediately.
Understood.
One... One trillion yen?!
Is that money really being buried?
There's no doubt about it.
The mysterious ninja corps is aiming for the buried gold.
They're aiming for their lives.
But how are we going to find this map and Lord Ebisu?
Don't worry. I'm sure of it.
We'll start action tomorrow.
Please wait a minute, senpai.
What?
What are you going to do about your work?
Idiot!
You're scared of the money, so you're looking for the buried gold?!
No way...
The day you succeed,
you'll get 10 billion yen.
One trillion yen each.
Huh?
Even if you say that,
the amount is too big to be noticed.
Oh, come on.
You're all so poor.
Listen.
If you have one trillion yen,
you can buy a whole company that makes your favorite documentaries.
What?
You can be the president right away.
You can rewrite the scenario of the documentaries as you like.
You can do this and that with Saori.
What?
Saori?!
These things are...
Volvo.
Take half a trillion yen to Captain Buck.
Then, your marriage with Jody can be immediately accepted.
What?
If that's the case,
you can do this and that with Jody every night!
Things like this and that with Jody?
Oh, no!
Urgh!
-Honda. -What?
You can buy a lot of expensive bikes like Do-Cutty and Ben-Bay you've always wanted.
Really? That's amazing.
Senpai, what kind of things do I have?
You'll figure it out yourself.
I knew it.
You're so smart.
Anyway, you can say goodbye to your everyday work.
You'll do it with me, right?
Why are you dressed like that?
The enemy is a ninja, so this is a ninja team.
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
Are there any other shrines with a temple like this?
What?
Yes. There are six other shrines in Kanto, such as the Ganso Banzaiten Shrine and the Ganso Fukurokuju Shrine.
Do you know where they are?
Yes, I know.
These are the seven shrines that include my house.
The closest one is here.
Here.
Ganso Banzaiten Shrine.
Let's go.
No need to go there.
What are you?
I'm Haruka Bente, the only daughter of the Ganso Banzaiten Shrine.
What?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruka Bente, the only daughter of the Ganso Banzaiten Shrine.
You're quite the type.
What's that?
Senpai, what's this?
Can you show me that?
Sure.
It looks like the statue of Lord Ebisu.
There's a hole in there.
There's no hole in there.
Hey, didn't you find an old map in here?
Yeah, but I couldn't get it.
Oh, I knew it.
Show me.
You're the type.
Oh, it has the same face.
What?
When the seven shrines are gathered, the door to the back of the Edo Castle will open.
The back of the Edo Castle again?
Yes.
What's that?
It has nothing to do with you.
Don't put your head in there.
You're already done.
You can go home.
What?
Go home now.
Sh! Sh!
Yes, yes, I got it.
Did that cute girl go to the Ganso Banzaiten Shrine?
Well, I guess she did.
Oh, did Haruka go there?
Yes.
Hey, can you lend me this Bente and the map for a while?
No.
Huh?
It's unfair to lock Tokugawa Ieyasu's buried gold alone.
I don't know.
Why do you know?
There's the face of the real Ieyasu, so if you think about it, anyone can understand.
I see.
I found the map in this a week ago and looked into it.
You're so smart.
Maybe the uncles have the same map and know it.
I'm a lucky person, so I thought there were six more.
Well, you've gone too far.
I thought so, so I came here.
Hey, I want to be a friend.
Please.
I can't help it.
I'm a little short on money, but I think it's better to join hands at this time.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I did it!
Now, let's go to the next Ganso Bishamonten Shrine.
Yes, yes.
Hey, hey.
She's a bad girl.
Let's go!
What?
Were you stolen?
I was forced to go to Ichidan, where I saw a suspicious ninja three days ago.
So I was taken to the Bishamonten Shrine in front of you.
It's them.
They're the ones who started it.
Do you know them?
I was about to be taken to Ebisu-sama, too.
I see.
It can't be helped.
Then let's go to the next Ganso Bishamonten Shrine.
That's a waste of time.
In the Shrine where the seven-worshipped people worship,
other than the Bishamonten Shrine and Daikokuten Shrine,
five of them have been stolen within a week.
What did you say?
There are two of them in Ebisu and Bishamonten.
The enemies are Bishamonten, Bishamonten Bishamonten,
Bishamonten Bishamonten, Bishamonten Bishamonten,
and Bishamonten Bishamonten.
What should we do?
It seems that Daikokuten is still safe,
so let's go to the original Daikokuten Shrine.
Then, give me the map that Ebisu gave me.
Yes.
I did it.
Here it is!
What is this?
It's just a luxury house.
I don't know why.
Is there a shrine in this place?
That's it.
Huh?
What is this?
It's not a shrine, right?
The owner of the original Daikokuten Shrine was just worshipping the great god of business.
He was a businessman.
He made a lot of money by selling his shares and land.
He abandoned the shrine five years ago.
What did you say?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
07.
So...
I thought I might be able to take a little of Lord Daikokuten's statue...
I refuse!
Huh?
I can't lend it to a man like you who doesn't know where the horse's bones are!
Eh?
I'll do something about it!
You're useless!
Go home!
What?
What's that for?
Hey.
I said I wouldn't lend it to you.
If you're wrong, don't come steal it!
To be honest,
Actually, last night, a suspicious guy sneaked into our house,
but I made him a pawn in our security system!
I ran away with them, with my tail wrapped around my neck!
Damn it!
How did it go, Senpai?
No good. I can't take it at all.
What are you going to do, Ryotsu?
Well then, what should I do?
Hmm...
So, Senpai, what are you going to do?
First, we'll use the hang glider to get into the sky.
That's illegal entry!
We'll blow the door with the main grenade.
We'll destroy the Kibutsu!
We'll put the country to sleep with the sleep gas.
That's a crime!
I'll just borrow it for a bit.
No!
Huh?
What?
What are you doing?
a ninja!
Those guys?
Who are you?
What a rough bunch of people.
We flung out the flag!
Now, we will take the flag by itself!
We'll take the flag, my dear.
Senpai!
Go!
Closh, Closh,
Are you alright?
Senpai!
That hurts!
Ooh! That door!
It's open!
Close the door!
Enter!
This is bad!
Be quiet!
We are policemen on the scene!
Leave them alone!
I'll get you!
That's convenient.
Let's go!
Yes!
What's wrong?
The ninjas are gone.
You did a good job.
Wait, we're the police.
We heard the noise and ran.
There's no such police officer!
Go!
The
It's a mess outside.
Good evening.
What?
It's a mess outside.
Good evening.
What?
It's here.
What on earth did you do?
In the midst of all that noise, I met Daikoku by chance.
I asked him to lend it to me, and he did.
N-No way!
That old man.
What did we do?
Anyway, we got the statue.
Now the treasure is ours.
That's not good.
You did a good job.
Now we can go back to the Shishi.
We have all the statues.
Damn it!
How cowardly!
I'm sorry, but I'll take the hostage so you don't get in the way.
Why am I the hostage?
Honda! Haruka!
I'll help you!
Senpai!
Damn it!
Don't panic.
What?
I put a transmitter on Honda.
Really?
As expected of the former Greenberry.
This rope and all.
Okay, let's follow him!
There are seven maps, but the mystery won't be solved.
What does it mean to have a star at the end of the seven stars in the old temple that came out of this Daikoku Temple?
Isn't that it?
Hokuto Shichise.
What?
I see.
Let's put them together in the shape of Hokuto Shichise.
That's not good.
You should give the enemy a hint.
I'm sorry.
The six maps are connected.
This shape matches the position of the Shichifukujin Shrine.
Then, the star at the end of the seven stars is...
That's the North Pole!
Oh!
I see.
The last one is the North Pole.
I'm sorry.
The North Pole is five times the height of the two stars at the end of the North Pole Shichise.
The position of this star is...
Chuzenzhiko!
The mystery has been solved.
Then, this map shows the Keigun waterfall.
I see.
When the water of the waterfall stops, the key to the Uraedo Castle opens.
What?
What!
Wait, Don.
P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P
What?
What's the matter!
So, Konji!
Bowler-san!
Y-You bastards!
The people outside have defeated everyone.
Well?
Give us the scent of the treasure!
That's what I should do?
Go!
Yes!
Minpo, give me this flower!
Damn! The treasure map disappeared!
I think they went to the Ke-Gon waterfall!
Ke-Gon waterfall?
Oh, I see.
Was it a repair accident that the lake in the library was like that lake?
Then we will look for the inside of the lake.
What?
What they took is fake.
The real key is in the lake.
I'm not good at flying.
I'm sorry, Nakagawa.
No, the good guy's treasure is romantic.
Senior, it's Ke-Gon waterfall.
They are trying to stop the waterfall water as the book says.
It's useless.
Senior, how is it?
Oh, it's right at the bottom of the lake.
What is this?
This is Aoi's treasure.
It belongs to the Tokugawa family.
I did it! I finally found it!
This is the hidden treasure.
The key to open the top of the lake.
Alright.
The treasure.
One trillion yen.
Kiii!
What?
Oh, no!
I'm going to be sucked in!
Senior, what happened?
The line at the bottom of the lake is missing.
What?
Look!
What's that?
The water from the lake is missing.
What for?
It's to move something with the power of the current.
The waterfall water has stopped.
Senior, this is bad.
The water from the lake has stopped.
The waterfall has stopped.
What?
This is the water from the lake.
When this is stopped, the key to the top of the lake will also be unlocked.
The waterfall water has stopped.
The water from the lake has stopped.
The one around the back of the lake won't open.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
oh! The water is completely out!
No way, they really were trying to get rid of the water in the palatines?
But it's strange. Nothing happens.
Orai Dojo doesn't appear either.
Yes, Ryo.
Oh, Ryo.
Oh no!
The Golden Castle appeared in Odaiba!
What?
What on earth is going on?
I didn't know such a castle would appear from the underground.
What is that?
It's a ninja!
Could it be that it attacked Ryo-chan?
Yes.
Hurry! They'll get ahead of us!
Ryo-sama!
What's going on? What are they doing?
Th- that's...
Okay, start the engine!
Go!
The treasure is ours!
W- who are you?
I am Kirigakure Saizo's grandson, grandson, grandson, grandson,
Kirigakure Komatta!
I knew it!
Hmm, Kirigakure Komatta.
Speaking of Kirigakure Saizo,
He is one of the descendants of Sanada Yukimura, who died in the Osaka summer camp.
I knew it!
Our secret weapon, Ieyasu, will not go a step further until we take back the treasure stolen from Toyotomi family.
Don't talk to me, old man!
I won't let you touch my treasure!
Hehe, how naive of you.
Limpo!
Tsunami Jutsu!
Huh?
Where is the tsunami? Is it Sasanami Jani?
Hey, I'm going to be fooled!
Oh, no!
No!
Gunman
I know it's impossible.
What are you saying!?
Love the sea and protect justice.
Who called this? Poseidon.
I'll put you in the bag, and you'll get a pair.
I'll go to the beach. If it's about the sea, leave it to me.
I'm sorry. The Yashinoki Cut is the trademark.
It's Dolphin Deka!
Oh! Dolphin Deka!
Ryotsu, I've been here for a long time.
I'll get rid of this.
Oh, please!
Dolphin, come on!
Oh, there are more dolphins!
I imitated Morning Musume and added more.
What? Just a few dolphins?
They're not my opponents.
What did you say?
Dolphins, you have to teach those mean old men a lesson!
Go!
Take the mask!
I mean, the dolphin!
Take that! Take that! Take that!
Natchi!
Natchi?
Gomaki! Gago!
Give us the dolphins! Give us Natchi!
It has a name too.
Are you okay, Natchi, Gomaki, Gago?
I'm sorry about today.
Farewell!
Let's change the end!
It's a jet bike!
This is it!
Now, get on!
Honda, drive!
Yes, yes, yes.
All right!
You two, hold on tight!
Let's go!
io
No problem!
What's that?
Ninja Martial Art!
Tsunami Jutsu!
Now you two understand!
What?
You shouldn't read my name!
Qin Long Live!
Let's go!
Ugh!
Alright!
We're here, Master Ryo!
Good work!
That was scary...
W-what's with this guy?
When you hold the handle of a bike, you change into a person.
Now, we're finally at the Uraido Castle!
Let's find the treasure!
What on earth is going on?
Who is that woman behind Master Ryo?
What? Is the gold coin just outside?
Where's the treasure?
Is it really the Angel Kingdom?
Anyway, let's head up!
Yes!
Huh? Who are you?
Nyan Paralitto, right?
I am...
the grandson of Sarutobi Sasuke,
and will always be his grandson!
Sarutobi Sasukebe!
Sarutobi Sa...
Sasukebe?
Sa!
Not Sasukebe!
Sasukebe!
Prepare yourself!
What?!
Who is that guy?!
What?
What's going on?
Oh!
Master Moon!
It's not only a flurry of magic!
The moon's energy is running through my back!
The stick of justice, Yamiyosaku!
If it's a sky incident, I'll leave it to you!
The master of the moon,
Gekko-Deka!
I'm back!
Same goes for Minas-Deka!
Hey, Gekko-Deka!
I've been waiting for you!
Damn!
Teach me the sweetness of modern weapons!
Fun!
I-It disappeared!
Ah? What's that?
What?
Ah?
Take this!
Uri!
P-P-Pinas!
No, no, no! I don't need it!
Don't be so rude!
No, no, no! I'm being respectful!
Here!
We've been getting less and less paid lately.
Ah?
We only get specials for free!
Really?
Ah, what?
That's right!
Does he have appeal to me?
Oh, my.
Hey, you're the one who's not paying any attention to him!
The hell!
You silly artist!
You're not paying any attention to me!
Don't touch the rope!
Hey, you just better have your revenge!
Do you have to be so friendly?
You bastard!
Whatever!
Huh?
It's working!
Oh, no.
What's wrong with Ryotsu and the others?
I don't know.
What was that just now?
W-What was that?
It's huge!
Huge!
It's the same guy who stole from us!
I-I'll ask them first!
Who are you, you bastard?
I am the grandchild of the gramophone player from Omiyoshi Seikaidarumaru's grandchild
Kyousuke Mikoto of Omiyoshi Seikaidarumaru!
Sen-senpai!
Dang it.
To think that from the beginning,
I have no idea when I'm gonna be here.
Who?
Look, here it comes!
This isn't just a 5-pan mukkori.
When an incident happens on land,
you can solve it with just one Kaipan.
The leader of the special police and the Zambagalas.
Kaipan Deka.
I'm home!
You know,
you don't have to come out for nothing because you're a special!
Seba!
Hmph!
You're going to pay for this!
Ryo!
Who is that woman?!
Even though you're my friend,
you won't let another woman get away with this!
No!
Maria, you're mistaken!
Your intention is wrong!
You are the daughter of the Seven Furos of the Shrine!
You just used me as a help!
Is that true?
I'm serious, I'm serious!
Is that so, Mr. Honda?
Yes, well, usually when money comes to you,
you'd be less interested in those personal matters.
I'm sorry, Lord Ryo.
I was misunderstanding you.
If you understand, it's fine!
If you understand-
Ryo, that's kind!
So kind!
Oh, this is always the case.
Anyway, thanks to Maria, I was saved.
Now, let's go!
Yeah!
No, I won't scare them.
I won't give you the treasure!
Why are you here?
I've taken care of all three old men!
N-No way!
Everyone, get them!
Yes, sir!
I won't forgive anyone who does anything to you!
You're amazing, Maria.
If it's for you, even if it's just fire or water.
I should have put you in the team from the start.
That's right.
Let's go!
Is this the entrance to the treasure room?
Humph!
No!
I won't be scared, no matter how I push or pull.
This is a gift, isn't it?
Damn it!
You came all the way here!
Ryo-sama, is this...
Huh?
I'm Iyoko.
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
What are you doing?
Make it even more intense!
Ah!
Senior!
What's this?
I-It's definitely...
It's Tokugawa Ieyasu's one trillion yen treasure!
You've done a great job.
What?
Senior!
Ah!
H-Honda!
Mr. Honda!
Huh?
Don't move at all!
If you move, this guy's life will be gone.
Ah!
Mr. Honda!
Damn it!
You guys are still here!
Ow!
Honda!
What?
You're Haruka!
That's right.
I'm the leader of the ninja army, Haruka Sanada.
S-Sanada?
Are you the descendant of Yukimura Sanada?
That's right.
We are the Sanada clan.
I've been looking for Ieyasu's treasure for generations.
Damn it!
What's with you?
You're so busy!
Huh?
Senior!
I just remembered.
There's no daughter in the original Benzaiten Shrine.
It's my son!
Ah!
Even if you remember now, it's too late!
Now, if you want this guy's life, give him the treasure.
Ah!
I understand!
I've never been so lucky to have a treasure like this!
I'll give it to you!
What's with you?
What?
I did it!
I'll get the treasure!
Yes!
Hey!
Again!
Why is there someone waiting when I'm told to wait?
I'm sorry!
You've been imitating me.
Damn it!
Give me the treasure!
Ah!
What's with you?
I've been looking for Ieyasu's treasure for generations.
Wow!
That's amazing!
It's a million yen treasure!
Who will give it to me?
Ah!
No!
Oh, my!
I do it!
I'm not going anywhere!
Run!
Don't think you can run away!
Ryo!
Senpai!
The shuriken was broken from the start.
Mitsuri!
You just have to hand over the treasure quietly.
Prepare yourself!
Ryo!
The treasure!
What's this?
Bamboo horse?
Denden daiko?
Bamboo bamboo stick on rice?
What's this?
It's all children's toys, isn't it?
No way!
Good work, the rest of the Toyotomi family.
I was a hostage in the Imagawa family when I was young.
So I rarely played with children's toys.
After I left, I tried playing with them for the first time.
I've never played with children's toys so much.
I thought it was fun.
But when my friends saw me playing with them,
I lost the will of the Shogun.
So I secretly built a castle in the back of the castle
and decided to play with them here.
What?
Hand it over!
The Toyotomi family's treasure was used for construction costs
and to build a castle in the back of the castle
or to make it sink.
I used it all to make a big deal.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's not funny.
Don't be silly!
Ryu-san!
Senpai!
You're more tired than a bone!
The castle is going to collapse!
Was that an important pillar?
Run away!
Come on!
I got it!
It's too bad, Ryotsu!
What treasure is Tokugawa?
Wait.
I'll build that castle that was made of gold!
That was a pickaxe.
That's what I heard.
What?
No way!
And then, as usual, Fuji TV is asking you to pay for the broken car.
Damn!
I'm going to fall again!
It's too funny to be a senior!
Shut up!
It's raining like someone's calling me.
I walked while looking back.
My mother was holding my hand.
I felt a strange feeling at that time.
So I walked on the black roadside of the arcade.
I saw it.
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten it.
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes.
Turn around and see that corner.
You can see everyone.
There is a camera over there.
There must be a camera.
Everyone, come to our town.
Thank you!