Episode 1: The
I'm hungry.
Ah, Senpai.
Your luggage has arrived.
What? Food?
A relative of Shibamata brought it.
Ah, the tempura shop's father.
It's a bit heavy, though.
Ah, a sword!
Eh?
Ah, I remember that I left it at my house long ago, so I took it back.
What is it? A cookie mold?
It's not a good quality thing.
You put clay inside and take the mold.
Where did you buy this?
It's on the street.
There was a thing like a catch sales that was selling at a shop aiming for elementary school students' school graduation.
It's selling things like a handkerchief, a medicine that makes a sound by putting it on a cup, and something that makes children happy.
It's selling things like a handkerchief, a medicine that makes a sound by putting it on a cup, and something that makes a child happy.
This mold, clay, and gold powder were a set, so it was about 30 yen.
Gold powder?
You put it on the molded clay.
What do you do with it?
You show it to the old man in the mold shop and get a point.
If you collect points, you get a big mold.
Eh?
Now that I think about it, it was a messy old man.
I'll have to check it out for now.
Old man, you did it!
Who? Who?
Hmm, it's no good to have one gold.
It's 200 points.
Eh?
It would be better to use more red or blue silver.
Old man, I did it too!
Oh, amazing!
This is 5000 points!
Eh?
Really?
Aoki-shi, it's nice to use 5 colors.
After all, the evaluation is decided by how much money you spent on the work.
It's a severe evaluation.
However, if you give up and try to go home, you will get a good point.
This is 1000 points.
I did it!
I'm still watching you work hard.
You're so naive.
It's a food to keep you from going home.
If you get more points, you'll work hard to collect them.
I did it!
It's 7000 points!
Change it!
Boy, it's a waste to change it now.
With 3000 points, you'll have a big mold like this.
That's true.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Please take care of me.
Hahaha, do your best.
The next day, the mold was gone.
It's a great house.
I'm jealous.
There were many patterns that disappeared around the fourth day of the number of points.
When I threw away the number of points and forgot, it will come again.
Because the child is an idiot, I will be caught in the same hand again.
I see.
I have been complaining about the number of points for a long time.
This is a different person.
What?
It's different from the uncle.
Well, I don't remember well.
That man is a bad man.
It's not the old man.
It's different from the old man.
Don't worry.
I see.
I'm glad.
I let him rest assured and it disappeared well on the fourth day.
Somehow it looks like the bad luck method in modern times.
I have also left it behind to know the identity of the other.
It's like Ryo-chan.
Hey, boy.
Go home quickly.
No.
It's going to disappear around tomorrow, so I'm going to stop the house.
Boy, I'll give you 100 yen.
What?
Really?
Yes.
Yay!
I got it.
It's a button.
When I turned around, the old man was no longer there.
It was already an art technique to disappear.
Well, I'm not talking about this today.
I can't eat a sword.
It can't be helped.
I'll drink tea and confuse my hunger.
What?
What is this?
When you watch TV,
make the room bright and try to look away.
Come to me, the poor man.
I'm not here, but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky.
The white clouds.
I wonder what will happen.
They will come longer.
It is the time for you to find the Então it is like this.
Come to me who doesn't have a job.
What's wrong?
Why don't you worry?
Don't worry about it
Look, the red spider is burning
I wonder what will happen to it
You know it, right?
You know it, you know it!
If you know it, then shut up and follow me!
The Magic Pagoda
What is this?
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
The Pagoda...
There's a hole in it
Damn it, I can't drink tea with this
Well, that's why Ryo-sama is upset
If it's tea, I'll buy it
I don't really want to drink tea
I just wanted to drink tea and get hungry
You don't have any pay for this month?
There's only this left
Can't you buy a candy for 5 yen?
Maybe you can buy bread ears
Bread ears will make me full
If you're a mouse, you'll be full
What?
Don't be silly!
I'm sorry
Huh?
Maybe it's better to be a mouse
If we're all so mean
It turned out to be aуль
What the hell is going on?
I told you
It's better to be a mouse
Koume
Koume Hanayama
She is a higher-up in heaven
She is on a recommendations list
Of course, you can use magic.
Koume's old man is working for the Heaven Police.
Well, I don't care about him.
What did you say?
Everyone, long time no see.
Really? You're doing fine, Koume-chan.
It's been a while since the spring training camp.
Hello.
Hey, you don't have to greet me, just get back to normal.
Ah, I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
You're a pain in the ass.
I'm finally back to normal!
Ah, I'm sorry.
You came to play a lot.
It was my first time meeting Maria.
Nice to meet you, I'm Maria.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
You're so pretty.
Are you Ryo-san's girlfriend?
Don't be silly.
That can't be true.
Ah, someone's phone is ringing.
Huh? Ah, it's mine.
Even the high school girls in Heaven have their phones, don't they?
It's definitely from my old man.
When I go to the school, he tells me to call him regularly.
He's so noisy.
You're a protective old man.
Yes.
Yeah, I'm at Ryo-san's place.
And Maria has a very beautiful son-in-law.
What's going on?
Huh? I think I heard something.
Grandpa!
Grandpa Bachi!
Where is Maria, who is very beautiful?
Oh, you're Maria?
Y-Yes.
Please come in.
I'm Rika Hanayama, the head of the Heaven Police Department Security.
Nice to meet you.
You're really a beautiful woman.
Y-Yes.
Are you free now?
Would you like some tea at my house?
It's right upstairs.
I'm picking up girls here.
Maria, you don't know that you're a man, do you?
I don't think so.
Probably.
You're such an idiot.
Wait, if you're good at cooking, you might be able to eat a lot of Heaven's food.
Just a little bit, please.
Ryo-sama.
Maria, go with him.
What?
You don't know what you're talking about.
Instead, I'll go with you.
What?
Ryo-sama!
You don't need me.
Maria is fine.
If you don't go with me, Maria won't go to your house.
I can't go with you.
I have no choice.
I'll take you with me.
So, how are we going to Heaven?
Just you wait.
My cacca, my cacca!
Hoi hoi!
Oh!
See you later, Koume-chan.
Yes.
Just say it to the chief.
Hold on tight!
I really went there.
So this is Heaven?
Apart from the cars flying around, it doesn't look any different from the ground.
That's not true.
Heaven has a lot of tourist attractions.
Look! That's Heaven's famous thing, the Heaven Tower!
It's really cheap.
That's Heaven's famous thing, the Heaven Castle.
This is even more suspicious.
Heaven's Nezumi Land.
Hey, hey, is this really okay?
Heaven's Rainbow Bridge.
Heaven's TV.
They're all just fiddling with the buildings on the ground.
That's not true.
The earth's earthlings are fiddling with it.
How do they do that?
Heaven might be able to see the ground,
but Heaven can't see the ground.
That's right.
I'll show you.
Don't say such things.
Lord Ryo?
What a violent old man.
I told you.
This is your house, huh?
That's right.
It looks like a small, old house.
Thank you for your help.
What? It's still a town.
Heaven and life are the same.
I'll make you some tea.
I want to eat the food of Heaven.
Okay.
He's a nice guy.
I don't want you to tell him.
Maria, can you take a look at the painting I drew?
Yes.
How is it?
It's beautiful.
I didn't know you had such a hobby.
You're not good at painting.
I'll destroy time until I can cook.
I see.
It's a town that's a long time ago.
It reminds me of my old friend's house.
Hey.
You can do it in a little while, so wait.
Okay.
I'm bored.
Why is the night view like this?
I don't know.
My night view is fine.
I wonder if my grandfather put it.
That old man.
That's right.
The night view of the living room is broken.
Can I take it?
I don't think so.
Then I'll take it.
Ryo.
Tell your grandfather to prepare the table.
Okay.
I'm here.
Maria.
Ah, Maria is beautiful.
I've never seen such a beautiful woman.
What?
I'll grab the heart of the beautiful woman.
Grandpa.
The food is ready.
Hurry up and prepare.
At this rate, we won't have a date.
Ah, Maria.
It's a UFO.
What?
Where?
Where is the UFO?
Senior.
What's wrong, Ryo?
Huh?
I was beaten.
It's that old man's work.
Damn it.
I couldn't eat the feast.
A gift from heaven.
What is this night view?
I can't help it.
I'll have tea with this guy.
Hot.
What?
Hot!
Stop the fire.
Actually.
A little faster.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Ah, hot, hot.
Ah, I'm going to get a burns.
Let's get a burns.
I was saved.
What are you?
Yes, I'm a magic
Magical night view?
Yes, I'm a magic night view.
The secret is to increase the money.
What? Really?
If you doubt it, I'll show you.
Put money in the basket.
All right.
5 yen.
That's all I have.
I'm just trying.
All right.
Increase, increase, money, increase.
Yes, yes.
Great.
Hey, what if I put it in again?
I'll try to increase it again.
All right. Try it.
Increase, increase, money, increase.
Yes, yes.
If I do this much, it's still 80 yen.
What did you do?
I did it.
It's not going to be 100 times at once, is it?
The double is the limit.
The original price is too low.
Then.
What?
Is it 10,000 yen?
No.
The manager told me not to lend money to Ryo-chan.
Just one minute.
No, it's okay for 30 seconds.
I'll pay you back soon.
But I don't have any cash with me.
What?
Lately, I can use cards at any store.
I don't need to carry it.
What a mess.
I'm the same.
If I don't have money, Ryo-chan will borrow it.
Damn it.
That's why the rich people are like this.
Terai.
You have cash with you, right?
Yes.
I'll definitely pay you back in 30 seconds.
So can you give me one full card?
But...
Can I believe you?
I understand. I'll lend you.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Ouch.
I'll pay you back soon.
I don't have any cash with me.
Hurry up.
What?
What's wrong?
I think I dropped my wallet.
What?
I think it's from the patrol.
It's my money!
Don't drop your wallet, you idiot.
Shit!
It's a time of magic.
This is a treasure.
Hey, can you use any other magic?
That's what I'm talking about.
I can turn a stone into a diamond.
A stone into a diamond?
I can't do that.
I'll go and bring you the stone.
Ah, Senpai.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Ohara-buchou
I just got a call from the temple, but the night view is broken.
Yes, the hole is open.
Let's change it while we go to the library.
Are you going to do it in the back?
Ah, me?
Yeah, I don't mind.
This is it.
I'll bring you a new one soon.
Senpai, Ohara-buchou just...
Wait, wait.
Don't you know the night view over there?
Ohara-buchou brought it.
What?
He said he'd change it.
You're doing your own thing.
He's really attached to that night view.
You did something wrong.
What are you doing, Buchou?
That's not just a night view!
Give it back!
It's a night view!
Hey, where's the night view?
Night view?
Where's my night view?
My...
Night view...
Where is it?
Where's the night view?
What?
Night view?
Where's my night view?
If it's a night view, it's over there.
Oh, my!
Night view!
Ouch!
Hey, hey!
Ryozu, Kankichi, you...
Are you okay, night view?
Hm?
If you look closely, it looks completely different.
Damn it!
Night view!
Wh...
What was that?
He's finally broken.
Night view!
Where's my night view?
Buchou!
Huh?
Night view!
Where's my night view?
Right here.
Oh!
Night view!
Oh, I didn't expect you to be so happy.
It was worth bringing a new one.
Huh?
A new one?
Hmm...
What's up, Ryozu?
It's not this.
I brought it from the station.
I brought it from the office.
Then I left it in the beauty room.
Beauty room?
No!
What's wrong with him?
No! No! No!
No!
Where is it?
Answer me!
No! Where is it?
Where did it go?
No!
No! No!
Is there any other gun?
I think I brought a rugby club's handgun.
It's a rugby club.
I'll pour magic water on you.
It's magic water.
This is it!
This is my handgun!
Gear gun!
Hey!
Take it!
I told you it's mine!
I'll kill you!
You're in my way!
Are you okay, gear gun?
I'm sorry to make you drink water.
Okay, I'll let you eat the stone.
What?
You're going to make it into a diamond, Logan!
That's right.
I'm going to make it into a diamond.
I'll fire it with this katana.
Here you go.
You've tried all kinds of things, but you're not going to die.
I'll show you haiku!
You're not going to die from this.
This is the in the first edition's
best looking cutie-pie.
You can't even taste it yourself, Logan.
I never had a chance to taste it before.
Oh, you want to eat it yourself, Logan?
You don't have Master's armor.
I have a lot of luck.
He's a busy guy, too.
I'll be leaving soon.
Eh?
It'll be a little longer, right?
But I have work to do.
Oh, right.
I'll show you something rare before I go home.
If you give me the diamond in that nightclub, I'll get Maria's heart.
I got it the other day.
Here.
Eh?
Ah!
What is it?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What is it, old man?
I'm sorry.
Where is the nightclub?
I gave it to Ryo-san.
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was a magic nightclub.
Damn it!
You're always in my way!
It's over there, right?
Then bring it to me.
Here.
Looks like he hasn't really used it yet.
I need to change the personality.
Change!
Oh, no! Why is it here?
I'll bring the diamond back to its original place.
Maria!
I'll be back soon!
Let me rest for a little while.
Oh, please.
Please.
Eh?
Ah!
I feel something strange in my head.
I-I can't believe it.
No, it can't be.
Ah!
I just heard that Maria is a man.
Eh?
Man?
It's a mankind.
Oh!
Hahaha!
Nee!
Ah!
We ate it.
Hey! How much is it?
It's 4562.75 yen.
It's cheap!
I will come to eat it again.
Then, I will pay you.
Just like this.
And then...
"Call the jewelry inspector!"
He should buy it at a reasonable price.
That's what you're saying?
You're so impressed by the diamond, aren't you?
Sir, you're kidding...
Please, do it properly!
What's wrong? You have to be more careful!
Why?
Sir...
That's right, there should be a stone that you changed to diamond first.
This, this...
What?
Hey, you, do something about it!
No!
You can't trust me!
Hey...
It's not done yet.
It's too late!
Hey, the jewelry...
The treasure!
No, let me go!
Hey...
I just walked through the black place
Everyone was a child once, but they all forgot
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
I can see everyone
Let's go!
There's a wall over there
There's definitely a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
"Electronic Plus is in love with Lemon?"
"You finally woke up to a manly feeling?"
"What? No answer for an email?"
"No way! No way! Emotions can't be transmitted by an email!"
"A man should hit and crush the person directly!"
"Next time, I'm going to fall in love with Lemon!"
"I'll be in your care!"
There's a wall over there There's definitely a wall
Everyone, come to our town