"The End"
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
It's like someone's calling
After the rain
I turned around and walked
I reached out to my mom
I felt
A strange feeling
So I took a red-and-white tile
And walked only in black
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a big face
And blue-eyed old ladies
Turn around and look
At that corner
You'll see everyone
There's a wall there
There is a turtle there
Come on everyone
To our town
Thank you!
"The End"
You read such a stupid manga
You're in a hurry!
You're noisy
Ryo-chan is not always
Unlike the most of the time Ryo-chan reads
Because he's always delicate
"The End"
I'll lend you one!
It's a happy ending after all!
What?
The first time you met a man and a woman?
Actually, the woman is single.
You're suddenly kissing?
Is there such a convenient story?
I'm already married!
That's right.
B-Boss!
Ryotsu!
What are you going to do by reading comics while you're working?
No, this is that girl...
Don't blame people!
No, that's a misunderstanding, Boss!
I'm sure you read the book!
Mr. Ryotsu!
The president wants to see you!
The president?
The president wants to see you?
Don't tell me he's not going to fire you?
I don't know.
Anyway, let's go!
Hey, Ryotsu!
I'm waiting for the farewell party.
Thank you very much!
Let's go, Boss!
Yeah!
I'll catch you!
Hey, you guys!
What's going on?
Ryotsu!
Kankichi!
What are you doing?
Mr. Ryotsu, you're being too cruel to me.
Yeah.
It's terrible to use Maria as a maid.
What do you mean?
What's the matter?
Oh, why are you here?
Ryotsu!
Oh, Sandy!
I missed you!
No way!
What's wrong with you, Gorilla Man?
A blonde woman like that?
Ryo-san, it's been a long time.
Senpai, are you okay?
What are you doing to Ryo-san?
What are you doing?
Kissing my Ryo-sama?
My Ryo-sama?
Ryo-san, is this person a girlfriend?
Maria-san is not a girlfriend, but a boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
This person is a man?
Everyone is surprised at the beginning.
Then, Ryo-san, did you have a hobby?
It's a misunderstanding. Maria is just falling in love with me.
That's terrible, Ryo-sama.
You lived together under the same roof.
I traveled together, Ryo-san.
Travel?
Why is Ryo Tsukankichi so popular?
I don't understand what foreigners and Japanese think.
I won't forgive you.
No way!
Maria-kun.
When Ryo-san went to America for her training trip,
Sandy was a police officer who took care of me.
What?
To give her back,
I invited her to Japan for her training at the Katushika school.
But...
What misunderstanding?
I drank with Sandy until morning,
and I even went to the court to arrest the boy who was a spy.
Is that so?
I was so wrong.
Sandy is Sandy, too.
I have to say it in a meaningful way.
Really?
Maria is too much.
I see.
It's impossible for such a beautiful blonde girl to follow me from Ryo Tsukankichi, New York.
So, I want you to take care of Sandy as the guide,
the head of the police, and the chief of the police,
the chief of the police.
Okay.
Sandy,
do you want to visit Tokyo for free time today?
Yes.
Where do you want to visit?
Tokyo Disneyland?
Hodaiba?
I like the mood of downtown Tokyo.
For example, Asakusa?
Asakusa is my hometown.
I have a house there.
Really?
Yes.
You can stay at my house while you are staying here.
Senior.
Senior, that's not good.
What's not good?
Sandy.
But I have a hotel reservation.
Cancel.
Let's go to the hotel and have fun.
But that sounds more interesting.
Okay.
I decided.
I'll go to Asakusa today.
Honda, pick up a taxi.
Okay.
See you later.
It's about 5:30 pm on Saturday.
You have to wear a mask.
Bye.
See you next time.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
Part 7 Time Lapse
Wow!
I wish I could live here yourself!
I'd rather not live in a doghouse.
Honda, well done. You can go home now.
No, I'll stay.
Why would you stay?
Maria asked me to.
To make sure there's no mistake between you and Sandy.
That's not true.
Go home already.
I can't.
I want to hear Sandy's story as a Japanese knight.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
It can't be helped.
It's too small for me to sleep.
Hey, who's there?
It's Kankichi. What's wrong?
I brought a guest.
Sandy!
Hello.
I'm here.
Isn't that a foreigner?
He'll be in trouble in this house for a while.
Sandy, don't hold back.
Dad, this is bad!
Huh?
Kankichi brought a blonde.
Excuse me.
What?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sandy, from New York.
Oh, I'm here.
What's going on?
Kankichi, what's going on?
You can't tell by looking at me.
It's a foreigner's dream.
Don't be a fool.
Sandy is...
I see.
You're the police officer who took care of me when I went to America.
You're a gentleman.
I'll leave you to it.
You speak Japanese very well.
You're good.
You're polite.
I teach Japanese and tea and flowers in America.
Sandy, relax.
It's a dirty place, but don't hold back.
I'll do more.
That's right.
It's a really dirty place, but don't hold back.
You don't have to say that.
Sandy, are you hungry?
That's right.
Okay.
Let's have lunch.
Croquette and pork cutlet, please.
Okay, okay, that's fine.
You idiot.
You're a foreigner.
You have a different diet from Japanese.
Kankichi, what are foreigners eating?
You went to America, right?
That's right.
Is it okay to have hamburger, bread and coffee?
That's it, mom.
And I want a knife and fork, too.
That's not what we have.
Can't we use a knife and a hammer?
This is not a mountain pass.
Go buy it right away.
You'll be proud of Japan.
Really? Then I'll go.
Kankichi, you're back in America.
Well, I've lived here for two weeks.
I'm not different from Americans.
My father doesn't know about the world.
He doesn't know where America is.
He doesn't come from Tai Tohoku.
Listen, I'll explain with this croquette.
This is how Japan looks like.
This is Tokyo.
My father's house is around here.
America is just ahead of Hokkaido.
It's here.
It's pretty close.
I slept in the plane, so I don't know.
I arrived in about an hour.
It's probably around here.
Wow, that's a pretty big hamburger.
I don't know about the taste, but it looks good.
It's my first time cooking in a restaurant.
Then I'll enjoy it.
It's delicious, Mom.
I'm glad you like it.
Is there anything on my face?
No, no.
Foreigners have blue eyes and look like dolls.
I don't like this person.
He's a poor idiot without a degree.
Well, don't worry about it.
No.
Don't say that you're good at saying your stupid things.
You look good, Chichou.
No, you're a fool.
I'm here for you.
Don't try to beat me.
I'm the best, come on.
That's my senior.
Head to your parents.
Turn around.
You're a fool.
I'm ready to fight!
I'm ready!
I don't want to bother Sandy!
You can't go.
No, no, it's okay.
My father and my brother are good at fighting.
They're really close.
I guess people in Japan and the U.S. don't change.
You and Kanki are too much!
I'm sorry.
Why are you running so fast?
What are you talking about?
You're too fast to keep your balance.
You need to keep your balance.
He's speeding up!
What a wild run.
I don't think she's a woman.
It's a floating turn!
You're doing great, Sandy!
I'm riding it lightly.
I'm not going to lose!
All right!
Oh!
It stopped just in time!
That's great!
Japanese bikes are very easy to ride!
Very good!
Sandy, would you like a shake?
I want your autograph.
Thank you.
Wait a minute!
A shake is 100 yen.
The autograph is 300 yen!
No, no!
It's okay.
This is the Japanese custom.
It's a collection.
A shake is 100 yen.
A sign is 300 yen.
Two-shot photos are now 500 yen.
How about it?
I want to take a picture.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Don't push it, don't push it.
The person who paid for it is waiting over there.
You can get closer.
Is this the way?
Yes, the next person.
Yes.
Yes, laugh more.
Senpai runs to make money soon.
But it's nice.
Ryozu and Sandy.
I see.
Hi, Ryo-san.
I want to take a picture with Ryo-san in two shots.
Oh, really?
Someone please push the shutter.
Yes.
Then I'll go.
Wait a minute.
Please.
Isn't it nice?
Honda-san, why don't you do the cupid of love for two people?
That's no good.
It's bad for Maria-san.
No matter how much Maria-san likes Ryozu-san, he's a man.
Well, that's right.
Ryozu-san is our benefactor.
Next time, Honda-san will take care of the two of them.
That's right.
All right.
Well, Sandy-san.
Do you have someone you like?
Yes, well.
What kind of person?
That's right.
She has thick eyebrows and has a tough face like a gorilla.
That's like Senpai.
And she has a life-like life force like a cockroach.
Yes.
As expected, Senpai.
That's right.
She's got a lot of muscles.
What?
Is Kankichi the ideal type?
I think Senpai is the one who said she has a person she likes.
That's a mistake.
No.
Sandy's eyes that stare at Senpai are the eyes of a woman in love.
Dad, maybe this is a chance.
Well, if Sandy becomes Kankichi's wife and comes to our house.
She'll be able to do that and do this.
And she'll be able to help Tsukuda.
Dad, can I have a taste?
It's bad!
It's far from 300 years of taste.
It's still sweet.
I can't take it anymore.
Dad.
Don't cry, Sandy.
The road to Tsukuda is long and steep.
Let's go one step at a time.
Dad!
Good, good.
I can't stop.
What's wrong with you?
Well, that's...
Mom, you check Sandy's feelings.
I'll check Honda and Kankichi's feelings.
I got it.
Sandy, I'm asking you.
Do you like Kankichi?
Of course.
Really?
There's not many men as wonderful as him.
I love that idiot.
Thank you.
Mom.
I'm the ideal type?
Yes, Sandy has made it clear.
So, how do you feel?
Even if you say that, I hate him.
He's a foreigner.
Idiot.
There's no woman in the world who would give you to an ideal man.
Get married.
Get married?
Yes, I can.
I can definitely do it.
What if I propose to you?
You're a fool.
Sandy, I love Kankichi.
What?
I see.
Sandy, come here and show him your kimono.
What?
Huh?
Oh, that was funny.
listener: We're in love.
listener: I need to go to the dojo with you.
What?
Do you want to go?
Yes, I will.
Well, if you're really the ideal type, it's Masamune.
It's like a manga that you hate, Ryo-chan.
Well, that's what happens in the world.
Alright, I'll do the Nakodo.
Are you okay? I'll do the English speech.
Oh, I see. I understand.
I'll do my best to do it by the time the ceremony is over.
Senpai, congratulations.
Only Americans can understand a global man like me.
Hey, Ryo-chan, what did you say about the proposal?
What did you say about the proposal?
I haven't proposed yet.
What?
That's not good. You have to propose now.
That's right, Senpai. Let's go.
If it's Sandy, I'll take you to find the venue.
You went to find the venue?
I said it's too early, but you're too busy.
I can't help it.
Ryo-chan, let's go.
Okay.
You're going to find the venue.
Let's go.
Where is this place, Sandy?
What is it?
It's the wedding venue for Sandy and Kankichi.
Eh?
I don't like that, Daddy.
Is that a Japanese joke?
It's not a joke. I'm a serious man.
I found it, Senpai.
Please cancel the proposal.
Ah!
There's a Comiaki car in America!
But you said you like Kankichi.
I said that as a human being, not as a man.
What? No way!
Let's go.
I'm sorry. I was just in a hurry.
Don't be silly. I didn't intend to marry Patsukin from the start.
Let's go.
Senpai...
Honda, hurry up. We're going to drink today.
I'm sorry we only have a few souvenirs.
No problem.
Thank you all very much.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of the president.
Please come again.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I was late.
Ryotsu won't come, father.
We got so excited.
He's not the kind of person to lose.
But I'm his father, so I'm sure.
What? You're not going to Arita?
Just do as I say.
Roger that.
I just saw one of the husbands and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe I'm about to be killed.
MOVE!
MOVE.
GO.
Cross the street.
Dispatch!
Get out of the way.
Move!
Shut up! I'll arrest you if you don't do as I say!
Y-yes sir!
Finally, we're done for.
Bye...
Ryo-tsu...
Ryo-san!
Thank you, Ryo-san.
Goodbye...
Goodbye, Sandy.
Idiot!
You're a police officer, but you're the one who stopped a car on the highway!
I got you!
Ryo-san!
Ryo-san, it's terrible that you can marry someone who is like me!
W-wait! It's a misunderstanding!
I will not allow this!
Why me?!
Just run away!
Just wait!
Both of you are pregnant for three months!
What?!
Awaken, clock, kick it, little finger, a-ta-ta-ta
For now, if you draw your eyebrows, to the station, dash, dash, dash
Main train, one-eyed on my father's back
This week, the best of luck, the best of luck, the best of luck
Even though I'm holding the bucket in one hand
The hot soup and the cold soup
Even the annoyance of the continuous work
I'll get rid of it easily
Every day is no problem
If the hot train passes by
In the half-moon pillow
I'll recover my energy
Every day is no problem
I love myself like this
The heart is flying
On Monday
What?
The manga of Otohime is going to be animated?
Why am I not the leader of the Robodeca?
What?
The toy wants to release character goods
I want to ask the original author
Maybe this is a chance to make a profit
Next time, make money in the anime
Thank you
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you