I guess it was a headliner.
Ah, here comes the summer again this year,
Im turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around,
Im turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around, turning around, turning,
Here it's the big wave coming,
I'm pulling away, causing a ruckus!
♪ Slipping into the southern wind ♪
♪ Big chest, small chest, little big butt ♪
♪ I'm a little aggressive ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, this year too, summer has come ♪
♪ It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ This year too, summer has come ♪
♪ It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here ♪
♪ Big waves, small waves, little big butt ♪
♪ Slipping into the southern wind ♪
♪ Big chest, small chest, little big butt ♪
♪ Ah, ぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷりぷり♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Slipping into the southern wind ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Slipping into the southern wind ♪
Great work, everyone.
Oh, I'll leave it here.
Takatan Osmo
There! Go Takanoyama!
There! Go!
Yes! Yes!
Takanoyama!
Takanoyama...
I was the strongest.
I'll never complain about Takanoyama.
I don't want to miss the best of Takanoyama.
I don't think I can understand the real fun of Osmo if I watch it on TV.
So you're the real Takanoyama.
Hey! If you're the real Takanoyama, you'll see him walking in a yukata sometimes.
Then I'll watch it too!
But why don't you watch it?
It's not so easy to get the ticket for Osmo.
Oh, really? I didn't know that.
You can't get a ticket unless you're a top member of the National Assembly.
If you watch the Osmo in front of the National Assembly,
it's my life.
What a dream.
It's a dream of my life.
I think I'm going to the shopping street.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to patrol.
It's unusual for Ryo to leave soup.
It's unusual for him to leave soup.
Come on, come on.
The Kamiari shopping street clothing sale.
It's a big summer sale.
The main item is a ticket to OZMO.
It's a full seat of the town.
It hasn't come out yet.
The ticket to the ticket.
It's pretty low.
This is bad.
Ryo is trying to do clothing sale.
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too much.
What's the matter with Ryo?
You don't know?
He's a very lucky person.
He went around Hokkaido the other day.
Last year was a four-day trip to Guam.
And he's got a good computer.
What are you doing?
I'm not going to clean up the mess.
Come on.
All right.
Here we go.
We don't have time for that.
It's a good thing this is a government name.
I knew you'd shout it out for a long time.
I feel like you're having a hard time.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
The Bao got a kill.
Yeah.
He got into trouble again.
Great.
Cho.
It is a good friend.
It's a good friend.
I wonder if I can say that.
Oops, I dropped the ticket.
What? What's wrong with that?
I have a wide face.
Ryo, you're amazing.
Not really.
That's...
Well, how's that?
Does anyone want to buy this ticket?
Sumo is Japan's national sport.
Cherry blossoms, mountain, and Fuji.
You can't say you're Japanese without seeing sumo.
Hey, mister!
Don't you forget the heart of Japan soon?
But this is a ticket to Masseki and Senshuraku.
Salaryman,
you can't buy this ticket with such a low salary.
No one's here?
Oh, I guess not.
Never mind.
Let's go inside.
Let's go see it together.
Yes.
There's only one left.
Oh, right.
I forgot the important person.
No.
I have to invite the owner of the ramen shop.
You're overdoing it.
You're right.
It's just a bit weird.
I'm kidding.
Why don't you invite the manager who's taking care of you every day?
Manager.
You're going, too, aren't you?
Well, well, well.
If you want me to invite you, I'd love to.
That's right, manager.
I remember you had a high-class brandy.
The one you were proud of for being given a promotion.
No, that's...
The brandy you drink at Masseki is delicious.
It's a bit weird, but it's delicious.
You can bring it to me.
If you bring it to me.
All right.
This is decided.
Now, let's get to work.
The admission fee has become very high.
I can't help it at this time.
I'm a little excited.
That's a great hand.
It's true.
And the National Assembly is quite big.
Well, it's the National Assembly of Japan.
What?
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you're a beautiful woman.
This is no problem.
No problem.
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
Foreigners.
You've been to Osumo, too.
The Osumo that I met recently was very popular.
Osumo is popular overseas.
I can't believe I can see it in Masseki with a grand atmosphere.
Who's the one who gave me the ticket for this place?
Just a few days ago, someone asked you to get a ticket to Masseki.
I'm sorry.
I heard So сы
thought you were just an ordinary person.
Huh?
What?
So what?
If you're not satisfied with the tickets, you can go home.
No, no.
It doesn't matter if you're not satisfied with the tickets.
I really appreciate you.
Then let's go.
Everyone has tickets, right?
Yes.
All right.
Don't be late for me.
My ticket is...
Hey, wait!
Idiot!
The wind of Ryogoku is also very strong.
So three of us can see it slowly.
Forget about that guy.
Let's go.
Huh?
Yes.
What?
Wait, that...
I was saved by the flow of the Sumida River.
Did you jump into the Sumida River?
Of course.
It's easy to lose your tickets.
I can't believe it.
It's coming.
Oh, hey, hey.
Oh, I love the raw food, I love the raw food.
Here you go.
It's pretty small.
Well, it's close to the roadside, so it's fine, fine.
Oh, what's that?
It's snacks and alcohol.
Oh, you're thoughtful.
You're a real master.
You can get souvenirs when you go home.
There's a plan for the chief.
This will be a solid meeting.
I'm not here to do a meeting.
I'm here for the Sumo match.
Oh, that's a pretty good pair of glasses.
It's a must-have for the match.
Hey, chief, you're smart.
Show me, show me, show me.
Wait, wait, I'll go first.
Who are you doing such a good job for?
Oh, that again?
All right, all right, I'll show you.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I knew you didn't eat anything good.
Oh, it's that blonde cutie from earlier.
If you don't want to watch Sumo, give it back.
It's fine, it's not a Helmon.
That's not the problem.
Well, well, let's toast, for now.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Cheers.
Don't you forget something?
What?
Something?
Thank you to Mr. Ryotsu.
Oh, what?
I don't think that's the right way to say it.
Oh, come on.
Oh, really?
Oh, wait, wait.
You know, he's in a bad mood.
I'll go home first, so I'll give you a souvenir.
Oh, all right.
I'll say it, I'll say it.
Thank you, thank you, Mr. Ryotsu.
Cheers.
From now on, Ishikata, Yokosuka, Takanoyama, and Hyōi.
I'll be your friends.
Oh, look, look.
Takanoyama, Takanoyama.
I can see the strength of your body when I see it live.
I'm looking forward to the best of Musumi.
That's right.
What kind of great technique will the Yokozuna of Zen-shou show us?
I'm looking forward to it.
I see, so this is the Makunochi bento.
Why don't you calm down a little and watch Sumo?
I'm out of lunch.
Hmm.
Can I eat sushi for Reiko?
I-I don't mind.
Sorry.
Senpai, you're eating silently.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's better to give food quietly.
East sea of Mayu.
Sea of Mayu.
Hmm, the sea of Mayu has two digits, so it's very energetic.
It's energetic.
It's different from TV, so I can feel the energy.
Hey, I got it, I got it.
Yes, there, there.
Pull, pull, more, more.
Hey, if you're sick, you know.
What?
Shut up.
You can eat this grilled chicken for you.
I got it.
Hey, don't call me by that name.
Oh, no.
It's over.
The sea of Mayu.
It's amazing.
I've never seen it before.
Idiot.
I didn't see the game.
Well, if you eat silently, you'll get angry.
I'm not angry at all.
You're so detailed about the question.
What?
I'm done.
I'm going to the bathroom.
What the hell is he doing?
I'm just making a fuss about it.
It's not true.
Don't worry.
I saw the scene.
It's good.
Good.
Then I'll take it all.
You're all right, aren't you?
It's mundoDoe.
It's also no big deal.
Hey, Isshou.
Your sister is there.
And you're here.
Are you all right?
I forgot.
I'm sorry.
Actually, that day was when you said, "I'm going to the bathroom."
Well, to be honest, it's about time.
I'll see you around.
I've just been exhausted from the games and the g-
Wha-?
Look who's here.
Oh, sorry! You alright?
Uh...
There's been more mountains of mud lately, so be careful.
Okay.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Are you hurt?
I-I'm fine! It's nothing!
Really?
I'm really sorry.
This is a bit strange, but I'm pretty sure I can go past this door right here.
I thought I'd come.
I'm in trouble.
I can only see the same thing from any entrance.
Did something happen?
No, I don't know where I am.
Chief!
Huh?
This way!
Oh, Ryotsu!
I was just taken away.
I see.
There's a lot of damage to the ship today, so be careful.
Thanks for your hard work.
I almost got lost.
Let's go back.
Hey, Ryotsu.
I'm just in front of the store.
Let's buy some souvenirs.
Hurry up.
It's the last fight of the day.
Hmm, what should I buy?
Hmm, it's a simple one.
As expected, Takanoyama's is big.
Hmm, this is not bad.
If it's young goods, it'll sell well to women in the book.
Hmm, this is a good one.
I'll buy one as a souvenir.
Oh, sorry, but how much is this?
Huh?
What's wrong, Chief?
Is something wrong?
Did you buy something?
I don't have a wallet.
That's strange.
I'm not sure...
I don't like this.
You left this at home.
What a fool I am.
I bought the ticket and took a train...
Oh, come on.
I'll lend you one.
But you can't have the purpose...
Huh?
What is it?
This is not my wallet!
Oh, that's mine!
Isn't it my wallet?
Huh?
Wait!
Eh? A woman's wallet?
It's Suri! Suri, somebody come here!
N-n-n-nonsense! No! No!
Where's Suri?
-It's this guy! -This guy is Suri!
-I told you it's not him! -Come here!
Ah! Chief, let's run!
Stop!
You two, stop!
B-but why do I have to run too?
Ryozu, what's going on?
What's going on?
I don't even know myself!
I see! It's that time!
That woman! She's blaming Suri for everything!
Dammit!
Where could she be? She should be around here!
Ryozu, explain yourself! Ryozu, stop!
No! If we keep this up, we'll both be caught!
Chief, for the sake of justice,
can you be a little more polite?
I-I-I-I'll take your leave!
W-what?
Shit! It's that time!
Where? Where is it?
Excuse me!
Oh?
Wait!
What the hell is the two of them doing?
Don't tell me they're lost?
I'm afraid they might be lost.
Maybe I should go get them.
All right. I'll be back soon.
Thanks. I'll be back. I'll be back soon.
Anyway, we can eat lunch now.
That's right.
Hey!
Ryo!
Senpai, what are you doing?
Get out of the way!
Oh no!
Excuse me!
Let's go!
Yes!
This is Three.
No! Not like that!
But we're friends, right?
That's why I...
I don't know what you're talking about!
Where is it?
Where is that blonde?
I sacrificed my head.
I'll catch you no matter where you are!
Ouch!
Oh!
Saori, are you okay?
Yes.
It's Three!
That's Three!
Oh my God!
We're being arrested!
Wait!
Senpai!
Help! Help!
Wait!
Ryo! Ryo! What are you doing?
I got you, Three!
No!
I'm not letting you get away!
Oh no!
You bastard!
Just get it off me!
Get your dirty hands off me!
Shut up!
You switched your hands!
You're being arrested by Three!
Make this clear!
What did you say!
Even though he's three,
you should let go of that girl right now!
Yeah, but hey!
Let go!
Three is this blonde woman!
It can't be her bad nature.
She seems like a bad person.
Stop judging her by her face!
That guy is not Three.
He's trying to save me!
What are you doing?
The girl is the culprit!
Oh, yes, yes!
But...
What? Where's the evidence?
Damn it!
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
See, that's my way of talking.
Ryo-ryo-tsu!
You've abandoned me.
Well, well, well.
For the sake of the culprit's dignity,
I can't help but make a little sacrifice.
And if I run that much,
I'll be able to get rid of the lack of exercise.
No way...
What's this?
You put so much of it in my jacket.
You have a cute face.
That's my wallet.
You're being careless.
You're not in the right place.
Even if I were to tell you...
I'm always the one who's always bothering you.
Is that the attitude you have, Chief?
Well, I'm sure I'm the one who's always bothering you.
But at least,
I'm not the one who's always bothering you.
I'm the one who's always bothering you.
What did you say?
Ouch!
The gate's closing!
Chief, hurry up!
The first link is still remaining.
It's the final match between the two of them.
It's bad.
At least, we need to see that.
Ryo-tsu!
We'll talk about it later.
Hurry up!
Let's go!
It's the first game of the day.
I'll see it no matter what it takes.
You totally forgot what you came to see with my ticket.
We got it! We got it!
No, we managed to get through it somehow.
If this match gets seen,
it's worth coming to the National Stadium.
Go, go!
It's there! It's there!
Where is it?
What?
I can't see anything.
Senpai.
Here.
I can't see.
Let go of me.
The best of the best.
What's wrong?
It's over.
It was a fight that I will never see again.
What a waste.
The final decision is to beat and beat and beat Takanoyama.
Takanoyama wins.
What a waste.
What do you have against me?
You're just a kid, but you're always saying small things.
What?
What did you say?
You're a girl.
Damn you.
What did you say?
You're a bastard.
I'll beat you.
You're too much.
Don't you have any manners?
You're so noisy.
I'm sure she would have had no manners.
What?
What's this?
I'm so embarrassed.
What do you mean?
There's no concept there.
What do you want to do?
I have to wait.
I almost fell.
But I'm here.
I am going.
Now.
It's going to be my turn.
I am going.
Ah, now.
I want it now.
Raaaaaah!
Red, stop! Blue, advance!
Let's cross the road of disaster!
What? That's common sense?
Are you guys keeping that common sense?
Alright! I'll guide the traffic safety!
Next time, "Dashin Bosou Daibakusou"!
Thanks for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!