Komatsu - Rosen
"When you watch TV, bright the room and try staying away!"
"Would you like to be a guest?"
Those who have no money, come to my place!
Even if I'm not here, they worry.
I'm so worried
Look at the blue sky
and the white clouds
I'm sure they'll be alright
you jobless guy
I'm not here,
but I'm worried
Look,
the red moon
is burning
I'm sure
they'll be alright
You know that, right?
If you know that,
then shut up and follow me!
I'll teach you how to buy a ticket!
I see
Don't stand behind me!
I'm sorry,
I want a cup of tea from Mr.Volvo
Mr.Reiko...
Mr.Volvo is so big
that he has a heart of a drunkard
I'm not scared
I'm just not used to the Greenberry era
Are you a chicken or a chicken?
You're a Alpine
You're a999
You're a88 1 00:01:48,001 -- 00:01:48,000 Isn't it about time I was fired?
Oh, it's a mail from Jody!
"You're already in Japan?"
"My dear Bobby, I have a favor to ask of you today."
"I'm going to go there from now on."
"But Ryo-tsu, what is Jody's favor to me?"
"Ugh, I don't know about that!"
"I've known Jody for a long time..."
"It's about time for us to make a decision."
"I don't know if I can make it..."
"Bobby, I made a Japanese-flavored meat and potato dish. Would you like to try it?"
"Aaahhhm!"
"It's delicious, Jody!"
"Welcome, Bobby!"
"It's Jody!"
"He's just making a noise."
"He's going to die if he gets married, for sure."
"Bobby!"
"Yes?"
"Bobby, wait!"
"Hi, everyone!"
"This is Jody."
"He's the one you've been waiting for!"
"Jody..."
"I missed you, Bobby!"
"Huh? Is this Jody's Doberman?"
"Yes, I recently started to buy it."
"It's a two-year-old male, and it's called Bobby."
"Huh?"
"Yes, I named it the same name."
"It's not lonely when you don't see Bobby, is it?"
"Jody..."
"He's happy to be named by a dog."
"He's very well-behaved, isn't he?"
"He's a very good boy!"
"Look at him, Bobby."
"He's a good boy."
"This time, I brought him here because I thought he could take a long break."
"But suddenly, he's going to join a month-long public training."
"What? Then, what do you mean by asking him to join us?"
"Actually, while I'm doing the training, I want you to take care of him."
"Take care of him?"
"I'm sure he's well-behaved, so I don't think I'll bother you."
"Can you do me a favor, Bobby?"
"I got it, Jody. I'll take care of him."
"Thank you, Bobby!"
"I've already sent his luggage to Bobby's apartment."
"Then, please!"
"Bye-bye, Bobby!"
"Hey!"
"You know, the meat-jjajangmyeon place is a long way away from here!"
"Jody..."
"Seeing his happy face, I couldn't tell him that my apartment is banned from pets."
"Bobby, stop!"
"Stay!"
"Sit down!"
"Ah! It's the manager!"
Ah!
Hello.
Ah, Mr. Bulbo, welcome back.
What is that?
I received a nice pot of rice from my friend.
That much?
Yes, it's from a fisherman.
Ah, Mr. Bulbo.
I have something for you.
It's like a moving luggage.
I'm sure the local people have sent something.
Thank you very much.
Bobby.
I'm sorry for making you feel so awkward.
But I had no choice but to do this.
This is a pet-free apartment.
I'm sorry for making you feel so awkward.
Please be quiet.
If the neighbors find out, I won't be able to stay here.
Oh, it's a food.
You must be hungry, Bobby.
Okay, wait a minute.
Well, where is the food?
Hey, Bobby.
Doesn't it look delicious?
What's wrong?
Aren't you hungry?
I don't know.
What do you want to say?
Oh, I see.
It's hard to eat it if it's in a can.
See, this is good.
Do you still need something?
I was just trying to eat it.
Oh, it's time to eat.
Oh, you're eating with this plate.
I'm sorry for being rude to you.
You finally ate it.
But this is a good place to sleep.
You have a bed for the dogs, too.
Okay, you're ready to go to bed, Bobby.
Hey, Bobby!
Toby, your bed is here.
Get off. This is my bed.
What are you doing? This is my bed.
You said it's my bed again.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
I told you to protect it.
I got it.
I'll just sleep tonight.
Tomorrow, I'll go to the bottom.
What are you doing, Bobby?
You're a bad boy.
Jody will be sad, Bobby.
Bobby.
Mr.Borobo?
Mr.Manager?
The neighbors are saying that dogs will cry.
Yes.
I'm weak.
I'll be finished if they see me like this.
Bobby.
Bobby, that's dangerous.
Let's exchange it.
Do you like the ball?
Bobby.
It warms me up.
Winter is not the end.
Come in, Sagonji.
Borobo.
Hati !
It hurts !
Bobby thought it was a toy.
It wasn't my fault that I forgot to pack all the weapons.
But, he's so cheeky.
He was so sympathetic.
Mr. Shoji.
Please, hurry up.
Hey, don't walk around, and sit down.
Sit down.
You bastard! You think you can't sit in a dirty seat?
Huh?
Get out of my way!
Bobby!
Sit here.
Listen, Bulbo.
When you see a dog that is weaker than you,
you misunderstand that you are the boss.
If you are a owner, be a good owner and be firm.
Sorry.
But I thought he was lonely because he broke up with Jody.
I can't be strict with him.
That's not the point.
Let him do whatever he wants.
After all, the pet is the one who has to suffer.
Yeah.
Senpai, I'm not good at dogs.
I'm sure it's forbidden to pet here.
I'll run away.
Bobby!
I'm not allowed to pet in Nico Nico Ryo.
Hold it!
Bobby!
Which way should I go?
This way!
It's Jody's dog.
You're right.
I knew it.
Ryo.
What's wrong?
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
Nothing.
Bobby.
I'm scared.
So it was like that.
You see, you've got a flying pet.
You do have a flying pet, too.
Jody will be gone for a while, Bobby.
Yes.
Jody!
Hello, Bobby.
You two are so nice.
Yeah.
I miss you.
I should be okay with you.
Don't worry.
Keep practicing...
Wait. Bobby, it's Jody.
Oh, I see. See you later, Jody.
What are you talking about? You're not even a tenant.
Gyoza! What should I do?
Don't ask me.
Um, how about this place?
It's a mansion where you can live with your pet in front of the station.
Pet... mansion?
Um, where's the owner's room?
Oh, here.
Yes.
What can I do for you?
Actually, I'd like to move into this mansion, but...
I see. I can't let go of your hand right now, so can you come to my room on the top floor?
Come on, let's go together.
Okay.
What a luxurious house.
What's wrong, Bobby?
Look, there are a lot of friends here.
There's even a pet food convenience store in the pet shop.
It's a mansion for pets.
You can relax here.
I'll buy Bobby.
Bobby, look.
What are you scared of?
This...
It's a horse!
It seems that the pets that are bought in this mansion are not just dogs or cats.
Stop it!
You're way too dangerous.
Oh, Mr. Shingao.
What are you doing here?
Um, um...
Where's the elevator?
There's none.
If the pets get in the way, it'll be a big deal.
There's no elevator.
Even though it's such a big mansion.
Huh?
Then you're going to live on that slope.
Above all, it's a mansion designed with the best idea in mind for animals.
Wonderful.
By the way, where's Bobby?
Huh?
Oh, he's over there.
He said that the pets will be like the owner, but isn't that too fast?
Huh?
That's great.
If we don't go out now, the pets will be able to walk for a long time.
What's the use of Doberman being so interested in Chihuahua?
He's becoming more and more like the owner of the zoo.
Huh?
He's just excited just by looking at a lot of animals, right, Bobby?
*A dog is barking*
Bobby!
Oh, Bobby ran away.
*A dog is barking*
*B súper chihuahua*
Ah! Sayori-chan!
Who's there?
Who put a dog on the second floor?
Ah, ah, ah!
Sorry!
That's my dog.
It's a rule to have one dog and a cat at a time.
Hey, are you okay over there?
It's suddenly getting hot.
It's a tropical animal area ahead.
What is this?
The corridor on the third floor is a river for the animals living in the water.
Tell me that first.
I see. It's the right slope.
Sayuri ran to the fourth floor.
What is this?
Grandpa!
So that dog was also a pet.
I was saved for the time being.
I thought so, too.
It's a waterfall!
What's going on there?
No, I'm just...
Oh, right.
There's a lost Doberman on the fourth floor.
It's not a dog from your house.
It's Bobby!
It's the fourth floor!
Don't worry about me!
Bobby!
Bulba, this way.
It's a heavy door.
What the hell is this place?
Is it the North Pole?
Is it the South Pole?
It's so cold.
The air conditioner is too strong.
It's too much to make a pet in a place like this.
Be alive, Bobby!
Someone's down.
Hey, are you okay?
It's Tsurukamaken's dog.
Hey, get a hold on yourself.
If you sleep, you'll die.
Ryo, if you come to deliver a message...
I'm going back to Tsurukamaken.
Suzuki.
You're so annoying.
It's frozen ramen.
Then let's eat it.
This is no time for jokes.
If you keep doing this, I'll die.
I'm sorry.
Are you Suzuki?
Yes.
I'm going to the convenience store downstairs to buy penguin food.
The ambulance is ahead of the penguin food.
Really?
Yes.
Bobby!
What's next?
I'm going to get caught up in this.
What's wrong with you guys?
I'm going to the convenience store.
I'm not your father.
Don't leave me.
Something's coming.
It's an elephant!
It's going to be crushed!
I was saved.
What's this?
I'm glad you're safe.
Were you there just now?
I'm sorry.
Did you see my Bobby?
I don't know.
I don't think you've come any higher.
What's on the top?
This is a tree.
Tree?
Bobby?
Wait, Porvo!
You better ask for help again.
I'll look for Bobby.
I'll find Poppy. If you want to go home, go home alone!
I'll listen to you.
Ryo!
If you go or go back to hell, you'll fall down.
Is this Safari Park?
What the hell is this place?
It's a monster, but they're all pets.
Okay, they're all good kids.
They're good kids.
It's not a pet, it's an invincible adventure.
Poppy!
Bulba!
Zeke & Versus
Run, Poppy!
Poppy!
I haven't bathed for a month, and I don't care if I do guys.
Hello.
It'll be canceled if you're Sr. Jirozami.
Needle...
Is it your lion?
I've been raising it since I was a kid, so I'm used to humans,
but I've been trying to make it bark at strange guests.
I can't get close to an Akihito.
Bobby, will you accept me?
You crossed the border with the Hundred Beast King.
Of course.
Ryotsu, how did you do it?
You're eating all the good stuff, aren't you?
You poor guys.
If you're not salesmen, what have you come all the way here for?
Oh, I forgot.
Where's the owner's room?
This is again...
Where's the owner?
Welcome.
Did you like my pet mansion?
No, I mean...
It's a dream to have come all the way here alive.
You still have to like it.
Then let's show you the roof of pride.
This is my ranch.
This was my childhood dream.
You don't have to force it into the middle of the city.
You can live in the countryside.
I was born and raised in Tokyo.
I can't throw away the convenient city life.
Ryotsu, I'm sorry for taking so long to take care of you,
but I think it's good for you and Bobby to live in a place with real nature.
I think that's the best thing for Bobby.
I think that's the best thing for you, too, Bulbo.
You've become Bobby's great owner.
Aaaaah!
A disaster-stricken animal-saving escape shooter!
What's this?
Aaaaah!
Hi, Bobby!
J-J-Jody, how did you come here?
The engine trouble on the ship made the departure delay.
That's why you need to have her on leave.
Huh? Are you sure, Jody?
Bobby!
Well then, Bobby, let's go on holiday!
H-H-Holiday?
Uh, J-Jody!
Bobby!
Where are you going?
L-Listen to me, sheep!
At that time, I felt a strange feeling
So I tried walking on the black tile of the arcade
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgot
A politician with a great face
A blue aunt above her eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You'll see everyone
Let's go!
There's a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone, come to our town
Thank you!
He's a goodiam
Isuteru
Isn't Tetsuo Nishizu an old man in a armor?
Ah, he took the정을播
To the city of the future!
Thank you!