ternamentale
When you watch the TV, bright the room and look away
For those who have no money, come to me
Come here!
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky
White clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I'm not here, but I'm worried
Look at the red clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
I'm not here, but I'm worried
If you know, just follow me quietly!
겠
That's the way.
So, I think there was a potholder I want.
I think there was a potholder I want.
You did not call for a phone call today?
Hey, the phone call!
Show me
you did not call for a phone call today?
you are the one who tied the kebab
What's wrong?
I'm talking about you.
You did some bad business with hackers and the internet.
Sorry.
The computer course will be held in Katsushika today,
so I was invited as a teacher.
What?
You're a teacher of elementary school?
Plus is a professional hyper elementary school student
when it comes to computers.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Deng.
Mr. Deng, you're here.
Welcome to the Katsushika library.
What's wrong with you?
You're a poor student.
Plus is a professional hyper elementary school student.
Aren't you embarrassed as a police officer?
Shut up!
Today, I'm going to teach Mr. Deng the internet
so that the old man and I can understand it.
What's wrong with this?
That's right.
The world is in the age of the opponent.
The opponent?
You don't even know the opponent?
You're the worst.
That's why you're no good.
Is the opponent supposed to be IT?
What?
Is IT the IT of the IT revolution?
Yes, that's IT.
So it's not IT, it's IT.
Don't say that.
Then do you know what IT means?
That's...
Mr. Ohara's touch.
What?
No way.
Did you intend to learn the internet without knowing that?
Don't make fun of me.
IT...
No, when it comes to IT...
When it comes to IT?
Yes.
I want to meet you soon!
What?
Information Technology.
It's information technology based on computers.
No way.
Mr. Ohara was about to say that too.
Did he slip away?
The joke you wanted to accept, I'm afraid it slipped away.
Really?
That's a common sense.
That's an Chan-shinkin common sense.
No, today's joke slipped away.
No, it was quite interesting.
Plus, I don't know the computer
I don't know the character
I don't know the joke
Mr. Ohara's teacher is difficult.
Isn't he?
Really remember me.
If you do, you can be a good customer of my company
and my father's company's products.
And I'll be a good customer.
It's a comment that I don't think is very elementary school.
Anyway, please come here, Mr. Electrician.
Mr. Ohara, please bring the land cell.
Yes.
No, it's okay.
No, I'm sorry.
No, it's not.
Mr. Ohara.
That's why I said it was okay.
What? You developed a new hyperland cell again?
Yes.
The security system has been improved to operate as if only the person other than the person touched it.
I have a computer that is like a workstation.
The mecha is solid.
There are no notebooks or pencils.
I can type everything on the keyboard, so I don't have any paper or pencils.
What do you do when you catch a cold and go to school?
In the past,
Chiki-chi!
Let me transfer the notes!
We don't do that.
We borrow data from friends when we need it.
Let me take the data.
No.
It's going to change.
Oh, there's a solo version.
Solo version?
The solo version has left and right finger movements different from the keyboard, so it's good for finger movement.
The more you use your fingers, the better.
You're particular about strange things.
Mr. Electrician, please give me an instruction.
I'll answer you.
All right.
I got stoned.
It takes three minutes to complete this.
I have to go to school after this, so I have to hurry.
I leave the rest up to you.
I'm interested to know how you teach people.
Nagagawa, let's take a look inside.
Okay.
No.
No, it's not that easy for that mecha-stupid old man to understand the internet.
Even if this is impossible for him, I think he can climb up to the sixth level of Mt. Fuji.
He explains it well in other places, so that's a given.
He's not cute.
More importantly, I've overdone 5 minutes more than I planned.
Can you speed up so that I can make it to the school?
Huh? You hyper-young kid, Nakagawa, speed up more.
Yes, sir.
Wait, Nakagawa! Fly!
- You... - I won't take your time!
Lemon!
Oh, Kankichi.
What are you doing here?
This dog injured his leg and is bleeding.
What should I do?
I'll take you to the hospital.
Okay. I'll take you to the hospital.
Kankichi...
- Nakagawa! - Did you call me?
Nakagawa, go to the nearby dog hospital. I understand.
Wait a minute. My...
What's going to happen to the school?
It's an emergency!
Which is more important, your wound or your school?
I'm sorry I'm in a hurry. I really want to save the puppy.
I'm so sorry!
Nagagawa, help her!
Come back!
Nakagawa, help her!
Why did you call me?
I was worried about you.
What?
Why did you call me?
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
If you don't help me, I'm not going to save you.
I am not afraid of any dog´s barking.
You don't say.
Yeah!
That's good.
The owner got in touch with you right away.
Yeah, I wrote his phone number on my necklace.
He called me and ran away in 5 minutes.
Oh, an email.
Who's that girl?
Is it your email?
She's right in front of you. Let go of her!
Ghiboshi Lemon.
She's my relative who lives in Kanda.
How old are you?
Don't ask me in the mail every day!
Ask me yourself!
Say hello properly!
Geez...
You're a salaried man, aren't you?
10?
It's not 10, it's a plus.
It's an electric pole plus.
Listen to the email address.
Don't send me emails every day!
Ask me yourself!
Please.
Lemon, do you have a cell phone?
Plus is asking.
Don't make Nakagawa your messenger.
I have one.
I'll lend you some.
It's okay.
I'll just send you a text message.
I'll send you a message.
Huh?
I'll send you a text message.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello?
Did you send me an email with the company address
because you got an idea for a new software?
Got it.
I'll check it now.
I see.
It's pretty interesting.
Let's consider it at the next project meeting.
He's like an adult.
He has three companies.
He's one of them!
And now you tell me one part of it.
How do you think?
I know the answer.
I'll buy one of them.
But I have kids.
And I have three.
That's all I need.
How old are you and the girls?
Up to four years.
Four years.
I think that Lemon, who knows the taste of food with one bite, is also a very strange kindergarten child.
Lemon-chan, since you're here, let's send you to Kanda's house.
I'll do it.
Huh?
He's a big fan of historical dramas.
I see...
Hello?
Something's wrong. It's off again.
It's off again...
Lemon, the bath's open. What's wrong?
I got a call from earlier, but it's off again when I get to the second floor.
Is it a prank call?
It's an e-mail, isn't it? Let me borrow it for a moment.
I knew it.
Who is it?
Electricity 10?
It's a plus.
It's not 10, it's a plus.
What's wrong with the plus?
There are many e-mails from a person called "plus."
Hmm, what does that e-mail mean?
It means that you can exchange letters on your mobile phone or computer.
If it's a letter, it's okay. But the plus is a really strange thing.
mail is sent every day, so Lemon is confused."
Every day?
"Every two hours, he asks me what kind of flowers I like, such as the date of birth, the blood type, and so on."
Perhaps Plus fell in love with Lemon-chan.
No way. Plus is 9 years old and Lemon is still 5 years old.
Oh, I don't think it has anything to do with love.
Lemon doesn't know how to send an email, so can't you tell him that it's useless to send an email?
Yeah, I'll do it.
His kimono is cute, too.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? You came into my room without permission.
I knocked it properly. If you want, I'll knock you again.
Is that OK?
What do you want?
Oh, well, that's.
It seems that you have finally developed a sense of a normal boy.
There's nothing more to say that I'm doing normal.
What do you mean?
When I think about Lemon, I can't do anything.
rawn
The heart pounds.
Why do you know that?
You're not sick?
Don't worry.
If a boy falls in love, everyone falls in love.
I was like that when I was a kid.
Love...
I have a big strike zone.
From the cute "Micchan" to the cute "Tome"
Is this what love is?
So, why did you come here?
I know you like lemons.
Don't send me emails.
He usually replies to me, but he doesn't reply at all.
Of course. He has a cell phone for security.
I don't send emails.
Oh, really?
I was worried that you would hate me.
I heard about your youth and hobbies in the mail.
I want to know about that directly.
That's...
That's right.
You are my relative, so ask Lemon.
Don't say the same thing.
Why do I have to ask?
If you give me an answer, I'll give you a laptop.
What?
Really?
Yes.
It doesn't matter if it's a laptop or not.
I see.
So, what should I ask?
I'll send you a question from the computer.
Please wait.
Good.
Please answer all 50 questions.
Please.
Okay, leave it to me.
What's your favorite flower?
My favorite flower is a tulip.
Then, the last question.
What's your favorite type of man?
Well, that's no comment.
No comment.
Thank you for your cooperation.
See you.
Hey, you two, make a good love.
Huh?
Hey, Plus, what are you doing there?
I was dumped by Lemon.
What?
I asked Lemon to go out with me many times, but he didn't say yes.
You're good! Did you meet him directly and talk to him?
No, I didn't.
I put the answers to 50 questions you asked me in the computer
and made a love simulation of you and me.
A love simulation? It seems like it's a plus.
So, no matter how many times I do it, Lemon will give me a hard time.
Hmm, that sounds interesting. Let me see that simulation.
Huh? It's a real-time one.
First, the date is a movie.
A historical drama that Lemon likes.
I know what Lemon likes.
Next is the meal.
Lemon is noisy about taste.
It's okay. There's a data of super-unique taste.
Hmm, you're holding it down.
Next is the zoo above for Lemon who likes animals.
I've only done the research beforehand, so it's not easy.
Oh, it's evening.
This is Odaiba.
You're pretty good.
I looked at the sunset on the Ferris wheel of Odaiba and gave her her favorite tulip bouquet.
She even make a confession to me that she'll go out with me.
However...
I was dumped in the street.
What is this?
What's wrong with the input?
It's a lonely game.
All right, enough!
It's not a game.
Don't be disappointed in this kind of simulation game.
But...
I have a lot of love experience.
I have a lot of experience.
Men should hit each other directly and crush them.
But you're a loner, aren't you?
If you hit me, I'll crush you.
Ugh!
Shut up! You're too much!
Anyway, meet Lemon directly,
talk about your feelings and ask him to go out with you.
No! That's impossible!
I can't talk to him when I see his face.
He's always so cheeky but he's so pathetic.
Then write a letter.
Write a letter.
I don't have anything to write.
It's all keyboard input.
What kind of elementary school student are you?
Here.
I'll lend you something from the post office.
Write it.
Are you going to write with a brush?
Lemon likes to write about the times.
I think he'll have a good feeling about a letter from the department.
I've never written since I was in kindergarten.
That's right.
I used the Word Pro's library as a reference.
What are you doing? Don't rely on such things.
It doesn't matter if you're poor.
It's important to write with your feelings.
I understand.
Okay.
Then, I'll clean the fax.
No! You hand it over to Lemon.
What? By chance?
Of course!
You can't put it in the post office.
No!
Then, I'll put it in Lemon's room.
What if you get hurt?
If you come this far, you'll be hungry.
Miss, Ichiro-san has brought a guest.
Yes, pass it.
Excuse me.
Please, take your time.
Wait!
It's 4 o'clock.
Don't go home!
You've got a human-like behavior for the first time.
Sit down.
What's wrong, Kankichi?
Lemon is...
I told you not to talk in e-mail.
Here, give me the letter you wrote.
Hurry up!
Shut up and give it to me!
Are you a Karakuri Doll?
You always say something so selfish.
You talk too much in front of your favorite girl.
Kankichi.
What?
You stopped your computer again.
Not again.
I'll buy a new one.
If you don't mind, I'll fix it.
Huh?
It's not working because it's full of capacity.
I'm cleaning the inside of the computer with Defrag now.
You don't have to buy a new one.
It's OK.
I'll delete the data I don't need and make an empty capacity.
It's enough.
You don't have to buy a new one.
I see.
Oh, it seems to be fixed.
I can still add memory.
So I'll add my computer's memory.
Let's add 20GB of hard disk.
Please.
You're so knowledgeable.
You're a junior high school student.
I'm not just a junior high school student.
I run three software companies.
Oh.
But I like a girl like you.
I'm going to see Kabuki next week.
Will you come with me?
Huh?
You're invited to a date.
Say yes or no or say yes or no.
Oh.
Don't reply to e-mail.
I see.
I just come by when I have a condition.
May I?
Condition?
Safely
Only on Lemon's side...
Why does it have to be your side to come here with the troublemakers that is such names?
Wait!
I'm sleeping with some troublemakers!
What a great chance!
Monster, send Lemon his favorite gender.
N- No!
I'm too shy to listen!
Oh yeah, why not send this by e-mail?
Or, via text mail.
And no calligraphy, no ink.
Plus, what's up?
Um, um...
Lemon, please tell me your favorite type of man.
He's like Kankichi.
Is it over already?
Oh my god!
System error. Please restart.
Subtitle by Subdiver
So I walked through the dark side of the Akegai
Everyone was a child once, but they all forget
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above their eyes
I'll turn that corner
I can see everyone
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
What is this old man?
A new policeman?
Although he is old, I am older than him
I will tell you everything, so follow me
Next time, a wonderful story of the super old policeman
Thank you!