Translated by 方 Hou.
I look at the sunset floating on the river.
When I kick the stone, it flies to my shoes.
I wonder if I'm going to save money.
I laughed at the fact that I was still a child.
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere, I can only win.
There is a city that does not change even one grumble.
The cityscape is strangely gentle.
From the waterfront of the Tungari-boshi to the Taishakuten.
The sunset falls.
Tomorrow will end like this.
I lost my happiness again in the Katsushika river.
I noticed.
I'm a fool.
Ryotsu! Shisu! What?
Take this!
This guy!
Does this child care about anything?
Stop stupid imitations!
Immediately release the hostages!
Shut up!
Try to move even a step from there!
I'll take this guy down from here!
Help me!
What should we do?
If that's how it's going to be, we should really do it.
Anyway, let's calm down for now.
Hey!
Why do you have to do such a stupid thing?
Ryozu!
Super!
This is definitely faster!
Ryo-chan, you're going to go around the water and catch the culprit!
Good! Let's distract the culprit!
Hey!
What do you want?
Say it!
Get me 50 million yen in cash!
50 million yen in cash?
I got it!
Is 10,000 yen fine?
Or is it an old 10,000 yen note with no number?
That's the car!
I'm going to go!
Get the car ready!
Got it!
Don't forget to fill the gas tank!
Huh?
Is there anything else?
Is there anything else you need?
Anything else?
That's right, you horse!
What?
No more!
We did it!
It's all right now!
Hey, calm down!
You bastard!
Jump!
Hang on!
You bastard!
Stop running!
Okay, I got this!
Hey, stop!
I got this!
I got you!
What?
He's got me in a middle position!
So fly!
Run!
Ryo!
Ryo! Ryo!
Don't worry.
He'll be fine even if he gets hit by a tank.
But...
He was fine until now.
I'm sure he'll be fine again.
Yes.
That was tough.
Ryo...
Hey, Reiko. Don't worry.
I'm fine as you can see.
He's still not coming out.
Is he really fine?
He's right here.
That was a big shock.
Hey, what are you doing in the middle of nowhere?
Senpai!
It's him.
He's hiding somewhere and trying to scare us.
I'm sure.
I don't like it.
Is everyone making fun of me?
No one is.
I'm sure.
I'll be right here.
Huh?
That's...
Chief, we're in trouble.
We're in trouble!
Senpai, he usually comes back right away.
Let's look for Kawara.
I'm so frustrated.
Oh!
It's the police!
He's wearing a jacket and sandals.
I've seen him somewhere before.
Huh?
It's me!
What? Me?
I've seen him somewhere before.
I have?
What?
It's only me.
What's going on...?
Huh?
He went back to...
I didn't know that he just died.
It's bullshit!
Just do your job!
I...
I'm not done yet.
We're finished!
Hello, dear?
Oh, hello there.
It's here!
Don't come, you monster!
I knew it.
You're still alive.
You have legs, right?
You can still go back.
Really?
What should I do?
It's easy.
I'll put you in the water.
Okay.
I'm back to life.
Of course, you're free to go.
This is good.
I'm back to life.
We're free to go.
We don't look like humans.
But we look like real ghosts.
You didn't see me.
I'm invisible.
Can you do anything else?
I see.
I can fly.
I can get into other people's minds.
What?
I'm jealous.
I don't have a body to go back to.
I've been a ghost for eight years.
If you can go back to your body,
you don't have to use this.
You don't have to use this.
Ryo!
-Senpai! -Don't hide!
Show yourself!
I'll go this way.
Thanks for the help!
If I die,
we'll meet again.
Senpai!
That's your captain!
She's here!
Ryo!
Ryotsu!
Oh!
No!
Ryo-chan!
Reiko-san!
Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu, open your eyes! Ryo-tsu!
No! I have to go back!
Wait. I'll try it right away.
Reiko-san! Reiko-san!
Hehe, that's it!
Reiko-san!
What?
Ah, Reiko-san.
Oh no, I suddenly remembered something important!
Excuse me!
Ah, Reiko-san!
I'm Reiko!
Yes, yes, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sister.
Well, this is heaven.
I had a bad night, so I simply fell down.
I will clean up after this.
That's not very nice of you.
Ryo-san, so you got a favor?
I always cause trouble for Ryo-chan, so I get a special gift.
After all, everyone's rich.
What?
It's got the effect of Ryosan that made Reiko lose her cool all of a sudden.
Well, what are we going to do next?
Next, we are going to tell you something about the viceroy of the Kankichiyusha prefecture that's been saved by the police on his arrest.
Uh, I've heard already.
As much as I know, Gakushika's Office has decided to pay a special bonus for your achievement.
- We have decided to give you a bonus. - A bonus? That's great!
We'll send you the video from the Katsushika library.
Where's the camera?
Ryotsu is a famous person and everyone loves him.
The Fukes are very popular, and he is called Mr. Katsushika.
Ryotsu, I'll never forget you!
You're so annoying! I can't stand it!
Senpai is dead...
It means that the world is full of darkness.
I feel sorry for Maria. She was so shocked that she fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
Now, I'll show my gratitude to the new president, and I'll give you a wooden sword.
A wooden sword, everyone!
You have to give it to me first.
Yay! Everyone's on board!
I'm sorry.
I was wrong to announce this earlier.
The
W... what is this?
What are you doing!
Everyone, get your clothes off right now!
It's the president's order!
No way!
What's going on?
But the president's order means...
Yeah.
If this goes on...
What was I doing?
Hey, be careful, Reiko.
What?
No!
I'm thin, so I'm not confident about this.
You're confident, but you're definitely a pervert.
Good!
Then, let's do this instead of salute.
Hohoho!
Poyo!
No!
Pervert!
Hey, you turned into a pervert in front of the president!
But perverts are perverts!
That's right!
I forgot!
Actually, you can see the big picture of the president's uniform.
If you're going to obey the order, I'll kill you all!
Naoko!
Hang in there!
Hehe.
You're a pervert!
What?
What did you say?
I mean, it's true!
You're a pervert!
You're a pervert in your face, and you're a pervert in your personality!
What?
You're actually a pervert, but you're cheating on me with your chest pads!
Huh?
I know that.
You really liked Ryozu Kaikichi, didn't you?
Who are you, you pervert?
You're a pervert?
You're a pervert, so you're a pervert!
What?
You did it!
No, I didn't.
You're the pervert who's acting like a pervert!
What did you say?
You were a pervert in the bathroom the other day, too!
Don't look at me like that.
I'm a pervert!
Oh, no.
I left my plastic bag in front of the hair salon.
Chief!
Sir?
You woke up.
What am I—
Now everyone, let's pay our respects to our chief!
Yes!
Ho-hey!
Ho-iod!
Idiot!
Episode 1: The
I have just received a message from the Katsushika office of Tenya Wanya.
The body of the retired Lieutenant Ryotsu was stabbed by a dog due to a fire.
What? It's the evening? Why are you in such a hurry?
You should go back to your body as soon as possible.
Ouch! Why did you hit me?
Chief!
Idiot!
This is dangerous, Chief!
I'm not a chief. I'm a god of death.
A god of death?
Yes. I came to pick you up. Follow me.
Wait! I'm not a god of death!
I'm here, even if you're not.
Now, listen to me. You're already dead.
That's a mistake. The ghost I mentioned earlier said I'm not dead yet.
Phew. Time's up.
No way! No way!
What a bad guy!
Ryotsukan Kichi.
Born in Yorozuya as the eldest son of the Tskudani family of Tokyo and Taito prefecture.
Father, Ginji.
Mother, Yone.
Born on June 14, 1910.
He was caught by the police and was thrown on a train.
He fell into a river and died.
There is no doubt.
No doubt?
Is that possible?
I don't want to go to heaven yet.
Idiot! Who's going to heaven?
You're going to hell on the third day of your life.
I'm not joking! I'll fix it!
Come on!
No!
Die honestly!
Damn you!
I'll rewrite this guy's data.
Hey, Ryotsu!
Don't wait, Ryotsu!
Wait, you fool!
Wait!
It's a dead end.
This will make someone get in trouble.
Ryotsu!
What?
What is it?
Come on, Ryotsu!
Hey, Ryotsu!
What the hell have you done to yourself?
You?!
You?
Come on, come on.
You think I'm a crazy guy?
I've never been so crazy.
Let's see...
The future president,
Prime Minister, 3 billion a year,
and a life of 1,200 years.
No way.
Even if my life is long,
I can't be disqualified.
I'm so tired of my life that I haven't gotten used to it yet.
But I think I made it in time.
Namu, namu, namu, namu, gachan, gachan.
Namu, namu, gachan, gachan, gachan.
I can't believe that Ryo-san would end up like this.
I can't believe it.
Ryo-san, why? Why?
Why am I so sad after I died?
I'm going to cry.
Why didn't you pay the debt before I died?
What the hell?
You're so selfish, you bastard.
There are quite a few public funds gathered.
This is the person who died, of course.
In other words, it's my money.
You idiot!
You're such an idiot.
You're not getting away with this.
You're going to be scolded even after you become a Buddha?
I don't like it at all.
Why did you die, Ryo-san?
Chief, you're talking about me?
Okay, I'm sorry to worry about you.
Ryo-san, Kankichi, I'll be right there.
I'll be back soon.
Hey, you light bulb thief!
Hey, light bulb thief, wait!
I found you.
Come with me.
Why does the god of death have a stun gun?
The world over there is also linked to the progress of reality.
Come on.
Look at this.
I'm going to live to be 1200 years old.
There is no hope for you.
You idiot!
You put a lot of data, so the computer of the god of death led to an error.
It's impossible.
What?
You must go to hell today as you are destined to do.
No! The light bulb thief is going to escape!
Did you hear that?
Don't say that, you fool!
This is my money!
Hey, Ryocan! Wait!
The bus is...
Wait!
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
It's faster to fly in the sky!
Damn it!
Wait!
I'll start the bus.
I'll start the bus!
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
I can't stop now!
Wait!
I'll start the bus!
Why did Ma-san...
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
I can't stop now!
Damn it!
Wait!
What happened?
I can't stop now!
I'll start the bus!
Damn it!
Wait!
I'll start the bus!
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
What?
No!
That's my bus!
I can't stop now!
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
Stop it!
I can't stop now!
I don't want to!
Damn it!
I have to run fast!
You two finally said goodbye.
He'll put the plumber and game software we've gathered together in your account.
And the video.
Then, I'll close the lid.
Manmaidam, Manmaidam, please don't hesitate to appear.
Damn it! Where's my body?
Take this!
That was a close one, Ryosu.
What?
Not yet!
I'm not done yet!
Then, I'll open the lid.
My body...
Give up this time!
Not yet!
I did it!
What?
Ryosu!
Senpai!
Someone, put out the fire!
Why?
This guy is a nuisance to come to hell.
I won't bring him here again.
Someone, put out the fire!
I'm going to die again!
The End
Captain, what took us so long?
Please leave!
Where are you going?
I don't want to go anywhere like that.
Please stop!
Captain!
The next episode is "Dangerous Kids".
The End
I'm sorry.
"The Power of Power"
I'm so excited!
Hello, everyone.
Draw it a little in the ground
The
To