"Kotoshi mo Natsu ga Kita"
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here
Ah, summer has come again this year
The big waves are coming
It's spinning around
Ah, summer has come again this year
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here
Ah, summer is coming again this year
The big waves are coming
It's spinning around
The big knees are spinning around
♪ ...and we will be able to make the most of it♪
♪ Ah! Buri buri buri buri buri buri buri♪
♪ Ah-ho ah-ho ah-ho ah-ho ah-ho♪
♪ The scent of the south wind♪
♪ Ah-ho ah-ho ah-ho ah-ho♪
♪ Nagisane burupuru burupuri♪
♪ Burupuri ♪
Ah, he's still here!
A
I
I'll have it charged for 20,000 yen in 5 hours on this precious day.
What's with the cup noodles?
They're on payday.
Damn it.
Hey, this guy has been acting since summer!
You're a thief, aren't you?
Thank you for your hard work.
You don't need it.
The thief will be delivered to the police.
This is the Japanese common sense.
If you come to the police station later, you'll get a reward.
I'll give you a bowl of noodles.
You don't need it.
That was close.
It's a survival before payday.
Even a cup noodle is a precious food.
That's not good.
It's too bad.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the prize for the lottery.
We bought 40 of them.
Really?
You're not even in a hurry.
You should learn from your mistakes.
You're a Japanese soldier.
What?
I'm not an idiot.
I'm not a Japanese soldier.
Then you're a Bosnian.
You're not a Bosnian.
You're a Bosnian.
through.
You're all rascals.
-Let's look it up. -I see.
There are four left.
This is...
wrong.
You're thinking the wrong way!
Work according to your expectations!
Ignore, ignore.
Everything's wrong.
Of course.
There's no one like you.
The Goddess of Fortune is...
Right.
Maybe the same lottery was left last year.
Did you look it up?
This book has the lottery numbers of the year.
I see.
It's the first one.
The reason why I hate lottery is...
because the winner hides it.
Not even one, not even two.
Not even three.
It's worth 3 million yen!
By the way, in Japan,
the media is always like this.
They don't announce the winner.
It's the fault of the Japanese.
Hey, chief.
It's not good to be quiet even though you're getting it.
That's right.
If you go there, the one who plays pachinko and kiba is good.
Whether you get it or not, your emotions will come out honestly.
Pyo-chan, you lost the pachinko today, didn't you?
Shut up!
It's the luck of time.
Chief.
How was the lottery?
It was...
I think we should talk about the lottery.
Let's talk about Bosnia and Herzegovina.
Chief.
Are you hiding something?
Nothing.
I see.
The way the winner acts is...
First, he suddenly becomes silent as soon as he gets it.
Second, he turns the topic around and stops talking about the lottery.
Chief, please show me the lottery.
I got it wrong.
If you got it wrong, can I see it?
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm more suspicious when you're not sure.
I'm not sure.
I'm saying I got it wrong because I got it wrong.
I'm sure he's talking about it.
I feel like I'm not sure.
What?
No.
Then, please break it right now.
What?
You're not sure, right?
If you're not sure, I'll break it.
No, I'm collecting the lottery.
When did you start doing that?
Your eyes are lying.
Show me.
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm going to break it.
Why are you lying?
Are you okay, Ryo?
Senior.
What I did just now was not worth 100,000 or 200,000 yen.
I called it a considerable amount.
Hey, give me your book.
Yes.
Which lottery did you buy?
It's the same as this year.
This one.
Good.
Read the prize money.
Read it from below.
I'll give you a chance.
Here.
5 pieces, 500,000 yen.
Wrong.
4 pieces, 1,000,000 yen.
This is also wrong.
Next.
3 pieces, 3,000,000 yen.
I got it!
I got 3,000,000 yen!
Wrong!
A small citizen like you will be surprised.
You will definitely get 3,000,000 yen.
Wrong.
I got it wrong.
The bank will not give you a check for a prize of more than 1,000,000 yen.
The prize will be given today.
If you don't go to the store today, it will be invalid.
Ujiho.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to drink.
Until 0:00 AM.
I'm sorry.
I actually got 3,000,000 yen.
You did it, chief.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't hide anything.
I see.
It's the bad habit of Japanese people who don't do anything wrong.
Seriously.
You should show your happiness with your body like an outsider.
Like this.
I got the lottery!
I won!
Woo-hoo!
That's right!
Gattemo's Gacaret!
Woo-hoo!
Good!
Well, that's how much I would like you to show your happiness.
I got it.
You're not really an outsider!
I will call the family medicine bureau and let them know you won.
Look.
I found out you got the lottery by chance, didn't I?
You are like a great golfing player.
Is it common sense to party and celebrate?
The common sense is to celebrate together.
But...
Or were you going to save three million?
I didn't mean that...
Then leave it to me.
Oh, I'm Ryotsu, the head of the park.
I'm going to hold a party for 200 people tonight.
Please prepare a special shabu-shabu.
Shabu-shabu?
Hey!
I'll go and inform the office directly.
R-Ryotsu!
I was lucky to win the lottery, but...
It was unlucky that Ryo-chan was there.
Is the club president off today?
It's been a long time since the day after that day.
It's about time to get better.
I'm sure he was shocked.
Senpai, you're overdoing it.
You should have stopped with the shabu-shabu.
You have to set it up until 8 o'clock.
The club president is coming!
What?
Good morning.
I'm sorry to bother you.
How much did the party cost?
Not a penny.
Sorry, I won't talk about that anymore.
I'm getting hot again.
Anyway, I've been addicted to the lottery since you were there.
What?
The American lottery.
What is it?
You have to choose 6 numbers from 1 to 51 and you'll get it.
The prize is 5.5 billion yen.
5.5 billion yen?
I'm so housewife.
Of course, I know.
But how can it be that easy?
But as Ryo-chan said, perhaps there's a law in the past.
He collected the statistics from 5 years.
And he's also been to the lecturer's studio.
He's in charge of theicios combination of numbers.
He's up to no good except with his work.
You finally came out, Lady.
Why you.
He's making fun of the lottery ticket, but he's still buying it.
Don't say such a hard thing.
You're worth 5.5 billion yen.
Ryo, we got a notification from overseas.
Okay, I'll keep giving you a prize until you win.
Chief, you want a bite of 5.5 billion yen?
No, it's okay.
Chiefs should follow the dream of living in Japan.
I hope so.
Is it right?
The number of the last lottery was...
2, 16, 17...
It's correct so far.
Next is 23, 2, 34...
It's correct!
No, I'm just happy so far.
I'll let you down later.
I knew it.
I chose the 4-5 curve,
but why didn't I choose 45?
Why didn't I choose 45?
Could 45 be...
Could it be...
45...
I got it.
I got 5.5 billion yen.
I did it!
Even so, the lottery is amazing.
The prize money is 5.5 billion yen.
Right, Ryo-san?
What?
What's wrong with you?
What's up?
Your face is pale.
Comforting one's own body, because it's cold,
he has a fever.
On the other hand, how is it?
What about Lotokuji?
What? What do you mean?
You were looking up Lotokuji's number, weren't you?
Surprising!
Anyway, let's talk about the compensation.
Huh?
Well, the winner's behavior is probably...
...to change the topic and not talk about the lottery.
What about Lotokuji, Ryotsu?
Well, leave that to me.
I'm on duty, so please don't talk to me for a while.
And you suddenly become silent and talk to me.
Hmm?
I don't like it.
I'm not a talkative person.
I got you.
What do you mean?
What?
You got me, didn't you?
What do you mean?
You got me, Lotokuji.
You got me for 5.5 billion yen.
I'm sorry.
You got me.
You're exactly the same number as the number you chose.
Huh?
Hey, Nakagawa!
You're so annoying.
You're so dirty!
But we were thinking about winning together, weren't we?
Stop it, Ryo.
You got me.
What did you mean by that?
Come on.
Myложro...
You got a lot of money, Ryo.
I got 6,500 million yen.
I think you're good.
I do, too.
I'm glad.
I'm glad...
That's all.
It was a good game.
Thanks.
I'm going to win the prize!
Give me chocolate!
You're not as lucky as I thought.
I'm not as lucky as I thought.
Look at that.
I'm going to win the prize!
Give me chocolate!
It's rare to see someone so proud.
I hope you're happy.
I'll let the media know.
Please wait!
I told you to let everyone know.
That's right.
I want you to be nice to Japanese people.
Hello, this is the exit of the Kameari Park.
Then, I'll be in trouble tomorrow.
Hey, Ryo!
You're popular overnight.
Damn it!
I thought I was a fool and fell in love with you.
I got a letter from Kou.
What?
It's from MK from Chiba.
You're the only one who has 5.5 billion yen.
Don't fight!
Kouma...
You're my wife.
I've been waiting for you.
You'll always love me!
That's right! I'm going to marry Ryo-sama!
Wait a minute, Komachi!
Don't worry, Naoko!
I'm going to marry Ryo-sama!
Ryo-chan was the number one man who didn't want to marry in the office until yesterday.
Shut up!
If you want to marry, you'd better spend 5.5 billion yen!
What did you say?
You're being rude!
Beep!
Hey, Ryo-chan, do something!
Ryo-chan!
If you don't go out, this party will be over!
You guys!
Get out of here!
I haven't received 5.5 billion yen yet, so I don't have any comments!
But...
Don't make excuses!
That's right!
I'll answer to you if I get the money.
I'll also announce how to use it.
So everyone, go home today!
Go home!
See you!
Bye-bye!
Good-bye!
What?
Yeah!
Okay!
I got it!
What's wrong?
There was an ad from America.
The ad is 5.5 billion yen!
What?
You have a loud voice!
You can get it on the media!
Is it a newscast for the media?
Of course!
Anyway, I'll go get it!
I'll leave the rest to you!
Okay!
But don't worry!
You can take it!
You got this!
I-I'll bring it!
Yeah!
Wait, I'll go get it!
Wait, I-I-I can't!
A-An ad...?
Of course, I can't...
Wait, I-I don't think it's a newscast.
Other mages, you just keep saying the same thing, don't you?
Maybe you're just playing games!
A bad ad, huh?
I won't wait until you give me the money.
-What's this? -This is a branded product I ordered for 3 million yen.
Hahaha!
Master, this is not a branded product but a branded product.
Haha!
-Sanzai-yu! -I'm sorry.
Let me introduce you.
This is Sato, who will be working as my staff today.
I'm Sato. I look forward to working with you.
Hello, I'm Nakagawa.
I'm Reiko.
I'm Ohara, the head of the club.
By the way, you always take care of Nakagawa and Reiko.
I'm sorry I don't have much, but please take it.
This much?
Are you sure you want to take it?
Of course.
Ryo-Ryo-tsu!
Don't use so much.
Go and save money!
Sanzai-yu, here's your money.
What?
I've used 3 million yen at the party recently.
Please take it as a apology.
What?
Is this really okay?
Here you go.
Oh, right, let's do that.
Sanzai-yu, 3 million yen.
To the room in the back.
Okay.
-You're doing this? -What?
I wanted to try it when I became rich.
I can't stop eating!
Please, director, I'm begging you!
You're an idiot!
You can't do that!
You're a rich man.
I'm just trying to get my money.
You're trying to get your money?
Ryo-tsu, have you decided on a way to use it?
Yes, I did.
I ordered it on the day I got it and it's going to arrive today.
Huh?
It seems like it's here.
What did he order?
He ordered a real combat helicopter.
And it's gold.
You're stupid.
If it's real, it's more than 1 billion yen.
I'm surprised.
Of course, you can't buy a real one.
This is a 1/1 scale radio-controlled helicopter.
It's real and it's gold-plated.
It's a specialty.
It's worth 5 billion yen.
I'm in pain.
Director!
Did you get that?
Yes, I already did.
Alright, let's fly!
I hope you're not going to be late.
It's flying like crazy.
Senior, what are you going to do?
I can't wait.
It seems like it's piloting a real helicopter.
If it's worth 5.5 billion,
I'll give it to you as a donation.
You're right.
He's more right than me.
Alright, let's go to the park.
Please give me a meal.
I'll give you a meal.
This is my lucky charm.
I'm the only one who can do this.
Please give me a meal.
I'll give you a meal.
What a mischievous little young man.
But you're so стороны.
The tickets that we bought are worth 5 billion yen.
Ca..5 billion yen?
Get it!
Personally?
As you can see, it's all my fault.
Eheheheh!
It's so fun!
And this guy too!
Eheheh!
Eheh?
Oh, no...
I...
I don't have a...
I don't have a Prop...
AAAAAAAAHHH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!
Ryo-chan!
My...
My 50 billion yen helicopter!
Um, my big money is...
Ryo-san, you're in trouble!
The lottery costs
30% of the United States' federal tax!
Pay the 50 billion yen tax!
Huh?
30% of the 50 billion yen?
5.6 billion yen?
Kachin...
Ah...
You've earned 5.6 billion yen,
and you're using it so quickly.
And you've earned 5.6 billion yen,
And you're using it so quickly.
You're such an idiot.
And you're such an idiot.
* estratégie
* stratégie
Let's smile anytime
Even if something crazy happens
Please smile cutely
You can go out with a nothing face
Hey, please smile
You're not bad
You've been like that all along
Please smile anytime
A woman who's been through a lot isn't beautiful
So you should smile right away
If you're not a child
Hey
Please smile
You're not bad
Hey
Thank you for watching