Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I'm watching the sunset floating in the middle of the sea.
I'll fly to the place where the love stone was broken.
I laughed at the captain of the taiko.
I'm fine somewhere.
The crows are crying and the rain is falling.
Is there an overcast sky?
From the tips of the cap's flow,
To the brothers and sisters in the temple.
The sun sets.
Tomorrow is over soon.
But the pain and happiness is gone.
sensei
Show your favorite comedy
Soon, Minamisenju. Minamisenju.
The exit is going to Ueno to the left side.
Seeing you "30327".
You're so stubborn.
I'm curious about the first-class cash of G2.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, right.
Hey, young man!
This is a priority seat.
I'll give you two seats from this year.
Wait a minute.
Shut up!
What did you say?
Here we go!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
No, no.
You're welcome.
You're feeling good after doing a good job.
This is a good place to get a first-class cash.
First-class cash?
Good night.
Hey.
We're sleepy.
We'll stay here.
Okay.
There's an zum-
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh.
I'm in a hurry.
I gotta sleep now.
What?
Alyoshen?
On the roof of a car waiting for the bus.
I'm clear.
Hey, hey, hey!
Come to me!
Ryo-san!
Is this a race?
Yes, it's a race.
Patrols are hard, right?
Well, you can do your best.
Ryo-san, if you get it right, please treat me.
Okay.
Tch, was that a police officer?
Look.
Idiot!
What's the point of fighting a high school student?
W-wait a minute, chief.
I'm not bad.
That's a fair defense.
He said it was an over-defense.
You're really...
But...
Anyway, I'm not allowed to go home for a week.
That's all.
Chief!
Senior, it's no use going any further.
It's because the chief put his head down in many places when he lived at home.
Damn it, that kid!
All right, if that's the case...
Senior, are you going to revenge?
I'm going to make a plamodel thoroughly.
That father is not allowed to go home.
Damn it, that kid.
I'm going to make a plamodel thoroughly.
What a good kid!
You guys are all...
Well, you asked for it.
We are...
Jijiranger Green!
Jijiranger Yellow!
Jijiranger White!
Jijiranger Blue!
Jijiranger Red!
All five of us...
...are the Jijiranger of the Super-Bashii!
Hey, you're not gonna wait?
What's with you? You're so annoying.
Anyway, when you got on the subway, you were sitting in the front seat.
Then what's the point of saying that?
Moreover, you were supposed to be banned, but you even hung up on your phone!
Even if you're allowed to, we won't let you get angry!
You're going to be sent to the police station in front of Kameari Park!
You're so annoying!
Shut up!
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Hey, young man, I think you really made us angry.
Green, you can't do this!
Yes, sir.
What?
Hey, you!
You want to fight?
I finally got my revenge for what I did yesterday.
You're not going to fight with that?
You're so naive, young man.
Come on, let's fight!
What are you doing?
It's the last blow.
Hey, young man, don't hit me!
You're going to be punished, young man!
Hey, you!
Stand up!
Come here!
You come here!
The Banquet!
Ugh!
Even if the convenience store clerk forgives us,
we, the Hikari team, won't!
Let's go!
What if the little children who love you copy you?
Cool your head and reflect!
Then, everyone,
justice will always win!
We are...
The Searching Hikari Team G-Ranger!
Hey, wait!
It's a secret!
You!
You're not going to stand up and read a book at the bookstore, are you?
That's not so bad!
You'll have to buy a book that has the same contents as the regular ones,
and lock the room when you get back home.
Then you'll get a clean look at it.
Don't be so rude!
You're not going to stand up and read a book at the bookstore, are you?
Well, let's do it.
But I'm tired already.
Oh! The Hikari Team!
How is it?
Cool! Cool!
Thank you!
Justice always wins!
We are the "Gigi Rangers of the Underworld!"
So cool!
Would you like to take a picture with us?
Here's the cheese!
These are the members of the "Gigi Rangers of the Underworld" who are causing commotion around the world.
They are trying to show off their morality and rules to the young people who don't follow their rules.
Some of them praise them, but some of them complain that they've gone too far.
They also say that they are being pushed to the toilet in front of Kameari Park.
We can't let them pass.
As soon as we find them, we'll arrest them.
What?
What's wrong, Reiko?
Doesn't that Gigi Ranger Green look like someone?
The Gigi Rangers of the Underworld
It's Ryo-Ryotsu!
This is enough.
Who's that? You're so noisy.
It's me.
R-Ryotsu!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Ryo-Ryotsu, you've been misled!
You're going to invite your friends to the local police station and do something stupid!
What?
I'm the Gigi Ranger who wants to go to the underground town!
You want to go to the underground town?
Gigi Ranger?
What's going on?
Do you still plan to kill me?
Wait a minute!
I really don't know anything!
You don't know even if you see this?
I don't dress like this!
Really?
You've been charged with the house arrest.
I'm not kidding!
I didn't leave Ryo when I was on the house arrest!
I made this!
All of this?
Yes!
Do you think you have time to go out and do such a stupid thing?
Chief...
Oh...
I'll prove my innocence!
I'll catch the Ikari-Squad with my own hands!
All right!
If you say so, then catch me!
Yes!
The Gigi Ranger of the Ikari-Squad appeared in Asakusa, Chushu.
It's about 3 kilometers in radius.
Master Ryo, we should patrol thoroughly within that range, right?
That's right!
Listen!
Those who do not follow social rules must be marked thoroughly!
Yes!
It was forbidden by the law to track even non- Mccapers!
If you understand, go away!
Yes...
Yes...!
It...
Me!
Master Ryo!
You have finally managed to escape!
Where am I?
We are at the shrine!
We speak of the fallen hoping!
Okay, I'm on my way.
Nagagawa, can you hear me?
The Hikari team is in the shrine's vicinity.
Stop it!
You think you can stop me?
Young man, you're going to be a scapegoat before the Kamenari Park.
Stop right there!
Don't move!
I can't run anymore!
You're in my way!
It's Momosu's Natsuki!
Oh no!
Maria, follow White!
I'll follow Green!
Yes, sir!
Damn it!
Hey, wait!
What?
He's hiding somewhere.
Yo, Kankichi. What are you doing?
You're a policeman, but you're peeking into other people's houses?
Hey, Mr. Tatami.
You're still alive, aren't you?
I'm working hard like this.
I'm doing my best.
That's good.
By the way, Mr. Gen.
Have you seen a weirdo in green tights?
I don't know.
I just finished work and came out.
I see.
Did something happen?
Well, there's a group of young people who don't follow social rules.
That's not true.
That used to happen a lot in the past.
By the way, I used to be beaten by Mr. Gen often.
That's because you guys did something wrong.
No, I didn't do anything wrong.
I was beaten even if it wasn't bad.
When I was scolded for picking up persimmons from Mr. Gen's house,
he said, "If you want to eat persimmons, come here."
So I did what he said.
After all, I was beaten.
Is that so?
Hey, I don't have time to talk about such a useless thing.
See you later.
Hey, how was it?
I was caught up in the empty space in the castle.
I got into a pit.
Me, too.
I thought I was caught up in the empty street.
But the old man who was there was an old man from the shop.
I let him go.
Old man?
I met an old man when I lost sight of him.
By the way, I met your grandfather, too.
Ryo, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
I'm sorry to have helped you today.
I'll do it by myself from tomorrow.
See you.
Hey, Senpai.
Where're you going?
I'm going to your hotel.
Oh, that's fine.
I've been waiting there for a while.
Get back here!
I 'll check it out.
Yes, please move it.
Don't'me take it easy.
I'm going to take a walk with my friends.
They won't listen.
I'll do one.
Okay.
Genza, hang in there.
He's got a heart attack and has a pacemaker.
Hurry up and get your phone!
Are you okay, Genza?
Somehow...
You're good, old folks.
30 minutes left.
I guess I can use it.
There are still people who can't keep up with their manners.
What should we do, Kanbei?
There's no other way.
Let's use that thing.
Hello? Hello?
He hung up.
Why is he out of the country?
He's using a machine to turn his cell phone out of the country.
What a scary old man.
The old man is there.
There's no doubt.
Even if I tell the numbers, there's no doubt it's them.
But I want proof that they won't move.
There they are!
Is that true?
Okay.
There's no doubt about it.
There must be a skull on the body.
It's him.
I saw the skull.
The old men are getting more and more frivolous.
I knew it.
Wait!
What are you guys?
You heard me right. We are...
T-Ranger Green!
T-Ranger Blue!
T-Ranger Yellow!
T-Ranger White!
T-Ranger Blue!
T-Ranger Red!
All five of you!
Sabachii Karantai T-Ranger!
You're in the way. Get out of the way!
I can't do that.
A week ago, I was in the subway station's garage.
I was trying to get a call from you.
What?
I don't know.
Don't lie.
What do you think?
This face looks familiar, right?
You are...
It's the Genzo who was with Ume who was kicked down the stairs.
Wait, old man!
Hey, old man.
You made me feel embarrassed on the train.
Stop it.
You're the one who's wrong.
Shut up.
You're a jerk.
Ume!
Are you alright?
Get a grip.
Ume can't play the game because of the injury at that time.
I see.
That's because the old man fell down the stairs.
Are you going to get better?
What do you mean?
I'm going to replace you with the Katsushikaku Kameari Park Exhibition.
What?
What's wrong with you?
I don't know what you're saying.
Alright, alright, alright.
Get out of here!
Or I'll beat you up in the street!
Wait!
Huh?
Old ranger, Black, on duty!
What?
Disgusting.
What are you doing on your own?
What?
If you underestimate me, this is what will happen!
Did he just say "Jijiranger Black"?
I don't know.
Don't worry about that, just do it!
Let's go, Hewako Ichido!
There you are!
Taking an exit before Kamey почかめやり公園, you're quarreling!
And what are you thinking!?
Your state isn't like this, Omino!
All of you just give him a big punch!
I can't stop laughing!
Stop it, stop!
Justice always wins.
We will win!
Let's go, Jijiranger!
Thank you, Jijiranger Black.
You saved me.
No, by the way, Black.
Who are you?
You're already awake.
Kankichi...
Come on, you're getting old.
Don't overdo it, Kanbei.
What?
It means you saw through everything.
What are you doing?
If Kankichi is going to get arrested, I'm going to kill him.
Now, put it on the table.
I don't know anything.
I just killed an idiotic young man.
Kankichi...
I, Jiranger Black, will be leaving today!
See you!
I see.
But I can't use my power like that.
I can't.
Chief, that's right.
About the old men...
I won't ask you about that.
Chief...
Enough.
Here, drink.
Okay.
Here.
In the old days, there were adults who scolded young people for their bad behavior.
Since when did the adults in Japan...
forget to scold young people?
That's why I'm so happy.
Because there's a chief who always scolds me.
Idiot!
Hey, chief!
Don't you get it, Ryotsu?
Don't get it wrong.
Your goldfish is not yet melted.
Please forgive me, chief!
Please drink, Mr. Naizawa!
Someone is calling me.
Who's calling you?
Don't you get it?
No one is calling me.
I don't even know how to say my name!
I can't hear you.
You know what it is...
I know it?
This is why I'm going to the farms.
All right.
Thank you.
Everyone was a child once, but everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn around and see that corner
Everyone can see everyone
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
There is a wall there
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
There's a bicycle hat shop
A butcher next door
Is there this shop that cut my hair without taking money?
Where to go?
What's that little mouthy ganko dad, Is arrived at Hikarajima?
That's okay
What's that?
The next time we'll spread the world
Baseline w
See ya
Let's go!!
There's a wall over there
Oh, there's definitely a wall
Everyone, come to our town
Thanks!!!