"The One-Eyed Girl"
I look up at the sunset floating in the river
I kick a pebble and I fly to the shoes
I wonder if I'll go to the gym I used to do the savings
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
There is only a single wail
The cityscape is strangely kind
"The One-Eyed Girl"
From the fountain of the Tungari Boshi
To the sea of sea urchins
The sunset falls
Tomorrow will end with a burp
"Katsushika, Shibamata, I'm so happy"
I lost it and realized
I'm such an idiot
"I'm such an idiot"
In the evening
Biosan Ninjyo
New release
"Animal Crossing".
Suddenly.
I want to show my cute face
"Parkard"
Thank you for waiting.
I'm needs due change
"Cabrero"
is a baby doll
"St致Cabrero"
"Cabrero"
" realise"
"fansfear"
That hurt...
Ryo-san got his third day's food!
"The
Please tell me how much you want!
That's great!
If it's 500 yen, I can buy a McNochie lunch.
Then, 50...
50,000 yen?
Huh?
If it's 50,000 yen, I'll pay you right away!
50,000 yen?
That doll is so valuable!
I didn't know that I was a doll enthusiast from the beginning of G.I. Joe.
Oh, that's great!
Now we have all the types of Ponytail in the early birdie.
I'm so happy!
You're a bad guy.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm like this.
Doll critic?
Is there such a profession?
If you have a valuable doll, I'll take it anytime, so please visit me.
Well, I'll go home and clean it up.
Okay.
I didn't know that a doll would be so valuable.
I still have to eat.
Ryo got 50,000 yen.
I'm so hungry that I can't eat that much.
Even a gorilla can't eat this much.
Shut up!
You didn't lend me a single penny when I was in trouble.
Well, Ryo asked me to lend you a small amount of money.
I got an order from the chief.
If you get an order from the chief, will you do anything?
I'm sorry, Ryo, but I'll use it as soon as I get paid.
What are you talking about?
Oh, good morning, chief.
Good morning.
Ryo!
You bastard!
You should have been paid three days ago, but what's with that luxurious meal?
Did you rob?
Or did you buy?
What?
No, no, no, no.
Please calm down.
Ryo, tea, tea.
I thought I was going to die.
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
I'm a good cop.
I'm not stealing or stealing anything.
Seriously.
But I don't know how to pay 50,000 yen for such a cheap doll.
There are some otaku, or rather, maniacs.
"Nantoka Kanteidan" or "Otakara Hakkutsu" are popular on TV shows.
Thank you for the meal.
Nakagawa, let's go paddling.
What?
What's wrong?
All of a sudden?
Is it wrong for a cop to go paddling?
No, no, it's not wrong.
Then don't say anything and get in the car.
Yes, sir.
Well, then.
Ryo, tea, tea, chief.
I'm going to go paddling.
Oh, yeah.
Ryo is going to go paddling by himself.
I wonder if it's going to snow today.
I wonder if it's going to rain.
Of course there's no need to go paddling.
What?
I'm going to meet the president of a doll company in Oiba.
Are you saying that's all about money?
Just think about it.
Dolls are money.
But it's quiet.
I used to hear the sound of machines even when I was a kilo away.
Wait!
We're out of money.
Everyone's eating the fish.
What are you doing, boss?
Ryo.
The doll we made last year was still out of business.
We're going to be in debt, and we won't be able to pay the wages,
so we're leaving the company.
It's a total disaster.
I'm sorry, boss.
Then what about the stock of the dolls we made last year?
They all went to the debtors.
What a mess.
What kind of doll did you make with your luck?
This one.
What's this doll?
It's a doll made by Puffy, who's popular now.
It's real, and it swings its hips like a jellyfish,
but it's old, so it bends its hips like this.
Who's going to buy such a thing?
If we make such a thing, of course the company will collapse!
I thought it would sell.
If we keep this up, we'll lose both the land and the building,
and the family will be lost in the street.
Don't cry. I'll do something about it.
Don't take a break.
The debt is 50 million yen.
Ryo doesn't have that kind of money.
Who said I'd make money?
What?
I'll think of a doll that will sell.
Even if you're a senior, you're still an amateur.
You shouldn't accept cheap things.
Don't worry!
Even if you're an amateur, leave the money-making know-how to me.
I see.
First, let's start with the recent situation of the doll industry
and research on the trend of sales.
Excuse me!
Hi, welcome.
I have something to talk to you about.
Here you are.
Did you collect all of this?
Of course.
There are so many GI Joe and Combat Joe series.
Amazing!
This is the GI Joe.
It's said to be one of the most mysterious of the World's Soldiers Series.
It's a Japanese soldier.
The GI Joe Japanese soldier is not sold in Japan.
Oh, is it the GI nurse?
The mania seems to be drooling.
Oh, it seems that there is a lot of knowledge about GI Joe.
Yes.
There are also a lot of birdie series.
Thanks to the buy from Ryo last night,
all the birdie series have been assembled.
Which doll did you buy from me?
This one.
Oh, the new one is the same.
It's been properly maintained.
Oh, I see.
Aren't these four the same?
It looks so.
I don't think the amateur can tell.
Well, if you look closely,
the expression and finish of the face is a little different.
I didn't know this difference.
I have the ability to become a birdie mania.
Oh, you sometimes change your personality.
So, what do you want to talk to me about?
Oh, the man here is the president of the Tateishi Gang.
Oh, it's the company that issued the Baba fee last year.
Do you know about it?
Of course.
I bought it.
I'm a Mania, so I can't believe I bought such a useless doll.
By the way, Kiwamono is also collecting.
But, that kind of thing is also a bad thing among Mania.
I knew it.
The company is going to collapse thanks to making such a doll.
So, I want to get advice from Yano and make a doll that sells well.
I understand.
Please let me cooperate.
Oh, thank you.
First of all, I would like to know your opinion.
I think that the doll that sells well is an action figure.
Oh, action figure?
Action!
No!
It's not a figure of skating.
An action figure is a doll that can move each part of the body.
It's a doll that can do all the movement.
Oh, you are so amateur.
By the way, there were 21 moving parts in G.I. Joe.
That's right.
If that is, you can make a good statue and oil like Japanese.
You are right.
That's not interesting at all.
I agree.
If you increase the number of moving parts, you will have more fun.
That's right.
From now on...
I will increase the number of moving parts.
You are so slow.
Ryo-chan, it is impossible to make a doll that sells well at night.
Who said that?
Ryo-chan...
Senpai!
Don't bullshit me.
Ryo is not the only one.
Oh, that is...
You made one?
Are you surprised?
The ultimate figure I made is...
this one!
Th-This is...
W-Wonderful!
Ryo-san got a ticket to success.
Ah...
Did, did you make your own doll?
I named it "President Ryo-san."
But isn't it cute?
I wanted to make it look like me, but...
I have to make it look like Tamagotchi, and make it look like a middle school girl.
That's right.
The celebrity's hair is the life, and the doll's face is the life.
It's too early to be surprised.
This doll still has a great function.
Y-You can make a constellation?
Not just a constellation.
Agura too.
Just like this.
Amazing!
The king of the figure skating world...
Even the G.I. Joe, who keeps on being the king, can't do this kind of action.
Of course!
The G.I. Joe can only move 21 places, but this "President Ryo-san" can move 40 places.
40 places?
"G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe"
I put a joint on the knee hinge, so I can bend it this far.
In addition, I increased the moving part by 3 places, and I was able to respond to all directions, so it's Agura.
I put a joint on the slowly moving part and it is Agura.
This is how you carry the ball on your back.
There are so many moves, but this one isn't a G.I. Joe, so it's Agura.
The hair is long, but this is Agura.
The "G.I. Joe's G.I. " "G.
I. Joe's G.I. Joe" "G.
I. Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. G.I.
Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe's G.I. Joe style Hat aunque si se
ni enfrune osi hirata, ginza kimi
no muna me niyoti This model is the
The index finger is also independent, so you can put it in the nose hole.
Oh!
You can also recreate the hand of this Domo Domo.
It's amazing! This will definitely sell!
Let's use the Internet to send information to the puppet maniacs!
I'll do it!
That's good!
All right, sir! Please produce this!
Wait, Ryo-san!
I want to make a lot of things, but I don't have any money to start with.
Don't worry!
You don't mind if your boss's family gets lost in the street?
You don't have any blood or tears?
I-I understand.
Let's talk to the bank from our company.
Boss! I've got the money!
Oh, yeah! Then let's...
Let's decide the amount.
Yeah.
How about this for each of my tickets?
What? This much?
If you don't like it, you can just say that you didn't talk about it before.
No way...
Senpai, you have a lot of money.
Yeah.
You're right.
Hmm...
June grooming shop
Excuse me, a ticket here please.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Ryo-san Dolls are a huge hit!
The second and third editions have been sold out.
Today's "Ozaku Haiken" is brought to you by the very popular "Jun-Sacho Ryo-san"
made by Tateishi Gang, in front of the Tateishi CEO's parking lot.
CEO, you have a wonderful house!
This is all thanks to "Jun-Sacho Ryo-san".
Amazing.
You can build a self-driving car with the money you've made.
I didn't think it would be this big of a hit.
Everyone has a "Jun-Sacho Ryo-san" doll.
I can't wait to see it.
Ryo-chan, how much did you make?
I made a lot of money.
One hundred million...
No, I think I made one hundred million.
What?
Who paid you to assemble it?
The groom.
The one who was hired to hand out the lottery...
I'm Sato the shepherd.
And you are the new bride of this time.
What?
Don't tell me...
What...?
Why...
Ryo-san...
How dare you...
That's a disgusting way of dressing!
Hmm...
I hope you don't want me to call you out, Chief.
What?
The police decided to stop today.
And from now on...
Yes, sir.
Please, have a meal.
Vice President...
Project Manager...
Chief?
Well, that's what it is.
You should call me Vice President Ryo-tsu or Ryo-tsu-sama.
You, you!
What the hell is this money?
I'm the one who's been in your care.
I'm thinking of giving you a gift for your overseas trip.
That's enough.
If you have so much money,
why don't you return the money you made for the lottery?
That's right, you have 1 billion yen.
This is why the commoners are in trouble.
I'm going to make a fortune of 1 billion or 2 billion.
I'm not a man.
I'm going to invest all my profits in the next project.
I'm going to make a fortune of 10 times or even 100 times that.
What is this?
This is the next new project that I've invested all my profits in.
It's the world's first action figure of the Toshin generation.
It's amazing.
It's eerie.
You look different.
It's impossible to scale it by one-sixth,
but it's possible by one-first.
But unlike the figure of one-sixth,
it's too eerie.
It's not.
It's one-first, so you can wear real clothes.
That's true, but...
If you don't sell this at a fairly high price,
you can't get a profit, right?
That's right.
The lowest price is 300,000 yen.
300,000 yen?
That's too expensive.
Nobody buys at that price.
Don't say that.
I won't say anything bad.
But please don't.
I'll tell the police what to do
and make sure they do what they're supposed to do.
Stop!
This is what amateurs are.
The figure is immortal.
I will become the Phil Gates of the doll world.
The world's first action figure in full scale.
President Jun is here with us!
Today, it's being released worldwide.
Thank you.
A figure in full scale has been released.
Oh?
Yes!
The figure didn't sell at all.
We have to carry the mountain of stock and pass it through!
Ryo-san, please do something!
Hmm...
Alright, leave it to me!
What's this?
This should be sold for sure!
Really?
It's not nice to have a hug with Ryo-chan!
If the business is good, anything is fine!
Huh?
There's a line in that shoe shop too.
Oh, that one!
That's my Shibuya version!
Shibuya version?
It's a very popular premium sneaker,
and I can't believe I can buy it.
It's like a popular hero's snack with a fork.
Hahaha!
Now we have zero stock!
Let's get the president to Ginza!
If you're going to do that,
you should drink the Ginza tea at Akasaka!
Yeah!
Hahaha!
Here it comes!
Here, Reiko-san, you too!
I wonder if it's okay to be told like this...
I'll do what you told me to do,
but I don't think it's going to work this time.
Yes, this is Nakagawa.
Huh?
A transformation unit?
What?
Chief, where's the transformation unit?
That's it! That's it!
Whoa!
That's my figure!
What's going on?
Chief, we got a testimony from the witness.
A customer who bought a set of dolls and a pair of sneakers
was throwing away a male doll after taking only a female doll and a pair of sneakers.
What did you say?
Everyone's goal is to get a Reiko doll and a pair of sneakers for a pair of sneakers.
Hey, look!
The dolls are coming in!
Ahhhhhhh!
We can't sell the figures anymore...
I want to sell only a small piece of figure...
Wh-What became of it?
I'll have you pay for the cost of collecting the doll.
You can't say that!
The company has been bankrupt, and I don't have any money left.
It's no use crying. You're not a police man anymore.
No, that's a joke.
I don't know.
This doll will cost money if you don't clean it up today, so please get rid of it.
That's ridiculous!
I'm in trouble!
Ridiculous!
The End
Chief! I'm going to go on a trip to the Kazushika Shrine next time!
Why do you doubt me?
Why don't you borrow a super rich cruiser and enjoy a meal with a luxurious band?
Next time, "Gekiryu Yagata-bune Panic!"
See you!
I've heard that I'm a woman who can't fall in love
But I have a lot of things I want to do
I want to ride a motorcycle through the vast desert
I want to be free more than a bird
The speed of the Oyakas
Changes the lady's dream
My love, I'm sorry, wait
The dazzling future of the panorama
You know, right?
I'm sorry, wait
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.