Translation by:
TheLegendaryKizuna
Translated by: TheLegendaryKizuna
Translation by: TheLegendaryKizuna
♪ It's a big shock! Hmm... The sunset is falling ♩
♪ ♪
♪ Still, I don't care if you're happy ♩
♪ Because I'm a fool who got lost ♩
♪ Yeah-♪
Cycle sacrificing operation
"Camping"
There are so many bicycles!
Are you going to take all of them, Kanchi?
Hey, if we leave them, they'll get in the way of the passage.
Leave them in the bicycle storage for a while.
If no one comes to pick them up, they'll be disposed of.
Are there people who don't come to pick them up?
Every year, about 2 million bicycles are disposed of.
But half of the people who come to pick them up are disposed of.
Really?
What a waste of money.
Hey, wait!
What?
You want a bicycle, don't you?
You said you wanted to see the bicycle disposal work today.
I'll go with you.
Now that you mention it, I've been interested in bicycles lately.
No doubt about it.
Lemon, do you want a bicycle?
What are you talking about? Bicycles are expensive.
Hey, what do you mean you want one?
You really want one, don't you?
I'll make it for you.
Really, Kankichi?
Yeah, leave it to me.
Hey, are you sure you're going to pay cheaply?
Don't worry.
There are 1 million bicycles disposed of every year.
If you take the parts from the bicycle that's out of warranty, you can make any kind of bicycle.
It's done, Lemon.
Wow!
Oh, this is a new one.
It has your name on it.
It stops right away.
I'm going to change the gear.
The gear process is also changed automatically.
When you speed up, the weight moves to change the gear.
The frame is made of carbon and aluminum.
It's light, so it doesn't rust.
The wheel is made of 14-inch magnesium.
The rear wheel is a 2.5-inch German Netszler.
Wow.
It looks so cool.
This one is really great.
What a surprise.
There's even a wallet behind the saddle.
There are always 30,000 yen in my bicycle.
Why?
You know, sometimes you need money while you're out.
Like buying a horse.
You're the only one.
Huh? Try it.
Y-Yeah!
Huh?
Alright! Good!
It's comfortable!
Thanks, Kankichi!
No problem.
Huh?
Lemon, you're going to kindergarten on that bike?
I used to go from Ochanomizu to Surugadai to play.
But I thought I'd leave home soon.
You were going to kindergarten in Ichibancho?
You're good at climbing the Kudanzaka.
When the market goes up, the gear fee changes.
Kanda has many slopes.
And she can climb up with the strength of a lemon.
It's high-tech for a kid.
Thanks to that, my favorite lemon in the house became out-door.
I'll come to this station by bicycle.
No way, Ryo-chan.
It takes hours to climb the Kameari from Kanda.
That's true.
We're here to play, Kankichi!
Huh?
You came here by bicycle from Kanda?
Of course not!
Huh?
Geppardo!
From there.
Huh?
You came here by bicycle?
I'm going to run around here!
Don't go far away!
Then I'll go with you.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You have something to do.
What is it?
I wanted you to make a bicycle.
A bicycle?
You're not going to ride it?
I'm a high school girl.
I used to run along the Sumida River a lot.
It's gone!
I can't imagine it!
Anyway,
The bicycle is for the shop.
Super Kanda sushi?
The young man stole it when he went to the shop.
I want a replacement.
Make it right away.
Why do I have to make it?
I just have to buy it.
I don't want to waste money.
I refuse. I'm busy.
You refuse?
How many days until the next payday?
What?
Recently, you have been coming to eat at home when you run out of money before your payday.
If I say a word, I can ban you from going out.
You come to a painful place.
You will make it, right?
I got it. I can make it.
I will definitely steal it.
I'm asking you not to steal it.
I made it.
Which one?
Ta-da.
A bicycle that will never be stolen.
It's an ordinary bicycle.
However, this saddle is a kind of landing.
If you carry a saddle, you can't get away.
Furthermore, the handle, the pedals, and the tires.
If you walk all the way here, you will not be able to step on the gate.
It's broken.
There are more.
There are two bicycles that will never be stolen.
You can also put a battery on the bicycle.
If you want to take it, it will be electrocuted.
It's extreme.
The disadvantage is that the rain can be used.
It's going to be electrocuted.
It's dangerous.
There are more.
Number 3
5.
The simple and easy way to protect yourself is this.
Hold the black paint in the saddle like this.
It's a cheap and simple guerrilla-like method.
It's really simple, though.
Listen, don't forget that you were wearing it when you were out.
You're late, Lemon.
What? You still haven't gone back?
You're a little worried, aren't you?
Okay, I'll go look for you.
Then I'll...
What an idiot.
Oh, Lemon.
I'm glad you're okay.
The bicycle...
I see. You got stolen while you were in the bathroom.
Damn it. I should have taken precautions against Lemon's bicycle.
I'm sorry, Kanki-chan.
Lemon doesn't forgive anyone.
His bad 1 is that he stole it.
That's right, I'll definitely get it back.
Kanki-chan, be good.
It's a noticeable bicycle.
Someone might have seen it.
Let's ask around.
OMG!
That's terrible!
I should be quick!
I should go check that bicycle.
Hmm, there's no clue here either.
What should we do, Kankichi?
Huh?
Ah! My bike is gone!
I hid 30,000 yen in that bike!
Damn it!
It's either Lemon's bike or my bike was stolen!
Huh?
It seems like there are no other bikes.
Come to think of it...
Oh, Kankichi! There!
Huh?
Ah!
It was a fake bicycle and it was removed!
Wait! My bike!
Damn it!
Hey! What the hell is going on here?
Huh?
What is it, Genshin?
Don't play dumb!
Hey, Kankichi!
I was using it for work!
I hid 30,000 yen right after I returned it!
W-Wait, what are you talking about?
My bike was removed with another fake bicycle!
Huh?
That's...
When?
Just now! At the shopping street!
Oh! That's strange!
What's so strange?
I saw it with my own eyes, the bike was removed and was taken away.
But I don't plan to remove the bike today.
What!
What?
Sen...Senpai...
Ah! Honda!
Not a man...
Not a man!
Oh!
Hey, Honda! What happened?
The...the fake bicycle...
The fake bicycle?
Ex...Except...
I had a short break in Kanamachi and the fake bicycle was removed, so I walked home.
What!?
The fake bicycle was removed?
You can't be serious!
This is an accident!
Ryo!
Someone tried to take the bike, and stole it.
There must be someone who is stealing bikes and bicycles!
What?
Both my bike, Honda's bike, and Lemon's bike were stolen by them!
I can't forgive you!
I will definitely catch you!
The places where there are a lot of bicycle-worn places are usually painted red.
I contacted my friends while patrolling and gathered information, but the place where a lot of bicycles have been lost today is here.
Here.
I was hit here.
I was here.
Well, then, the next target is...
It's here, right?
That's right, Lemon.
Are you going to wait and catch the culprit?
No, they're the ones who do such a big thing.
There must be a hideout somewhere. We will find it.
Huh?
Oh?
The primitive man is saying something reasonable.
It's like a police officer.
Hankichi is a top-notch police officer.
Huh?
Oh, that's right.
Is there a good way?
Hey, leave it to me!
Senpai, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
You're monitoring this place, aren't you?
Yeah, I can see it.
Don't lose sight of it.
Yes, sir.
Here it comes.
Oh, no!
Hey, hurry up!
All right.
Ouch!
Ugh, ahh, it hurts.
Crap, you should've handled it more carefully.
Tch.
Hey.
It's the police. Let's go.
Ahh! W-what's wrong?!
Ahh! The truck's going away!
What?!
Ah!
Crap.
Naoko! Are you okay?!
I'm okay. But I can't continue. I'll leave the rest to you.
I got it. Leave it to me.
The culprit is over there.
It seems they're heading to the highway.
It seems like it's working.
Alright, I'm going to catch up with the high speed entrance!
There it is!
Ababa, here it comes again!
How many times do I have to do the same thing?!
Oh no!
Damn it!
I'm going to have to go a long way from here.
I guess I'm going to have to go a long way from here.
Damn it! I fell down!
Hey, wait! I'm falling!
Damn it, did you not notice?
I'm going to lose sight of you!
D-damn it! I ran out of gas!
Hello!
Huh?
It's a regular man-tod!
Oh, I-I spoke!
Hurry up!
Okay!
Send me the waiver to the Katsushika Office!
Huh?
If we don't catch up ASAP...
There he is!
What's wrong, old man?
I'm asking, what's wrong? Hurry up!
I crumpled my legs.
It can't be helped. Where's my house?
It's right there.
Right there?
I got it. Take me there. I'll send you there.
I got you!
Old man!
Old man, what was that?
You sent me there. Thank you, thank you.
Get out of the way!
I'll show you the way!
I'm the number one of this pass!
No, I'm number one!
What?
The monkey pulled me.
It's a nightmare.
That monkey even
I've finally caught up with it.
Looks like this is the hideout.
Honda, can you hear me?
Damn it! Honda! Honda!
What's going on?
Senior! Please respond to me, senior!
Senpai!
Did something happen to Kankitsu?
It's okay. I'm sure the transmitter broke down.
That's fine, but...
He's not that easy to get into.
Yes.
I know where he is. I'll see him soon.
What is this?
They stole so much.
What did they steal?
They stole the bicycle of the chief inspector.
I thought they had a big bike.
What? They already dropped it?
Lemon's bicycle...
There it is.
My bicycle is...
Boss!
So he's the boss.
Hmm. That's a lot of people.
Japanese are weird.
When a bicycle is removed, they think they're bad and don't even pay for it.
I'll sell it to the best of my ability.
Damn, what a guy.
I'll melt the oil in the back of the tank.
Don't leave any chocolate.
Yes!
Boss, this won't be sold, right?
Ah, my bicycle!
Oh, a police bicycle.
This is unusual.
It won't be sold, but I'll put it in my collection with the white motorcycle.
Don't be kidding. My 30,000 yen is in it.
Boss, how about this?
Idiot!
That's not going to be sold.
But it looks pretty expensive.
That's an order-made.
I only have one, so I'll be in trouble soon.
I see.
Melt it later.
First, the rice.
That's a good one!
Hey!
I'll play with Leman's bicycle at night.
Honda! Honda!
It's not good as I thought.
I have to call for backup.
Hey, didn't you hear anything from the warehouse?
It's the sky eaves. I'm tired.
I guess so. It's the sky eaves.
Haa.
But I'll look at it just in case.
Let's take a look.
Who's there?
It's Toa Mas!
Toa Mas is here!
This is bad!
Where's my bicycle?
What?
What? There's a face on the bike!
I'll arrest you!
The bike spoke!
Let's get out of here!
My bicycle!
Get out of here!
Damn it! My 30,000 yen!
What?
That's Lemon's bicycle!
We'll be in trouble if we don't do something.
Get out of here!
Damn it!
I put a cover on it to protect me from the crime.
My bicycle!
Where are you going?
If I keep going, both of them will be killed!
Damn it!
Wait for me!
I'll get you.
Let's go!
My bicycle!
Where are you going?
No!
Well, you forced me here!
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
Here you go.
Thank you, Kankichi. I won't lose you again.
Huh? I think I forgot something important.
Kankichi? Is that yours?
My bicycle! 30,000 yen!
30,000 yen!
Don't stop me!
Give it back to me!
30,000 yen!
35,000 yen!
If you keep going like this I'll be on your side.
I love you so much!
I love you too, Kankichi!
5, 4, 1!
Do you like the signs?
Is rising the sun too much too heavy?
Ready to go!
I'm going to see you all.
Turn around and look at that corner.
I'll see you all.
There's a turtle there.
There's definitely a turtle there.
Come on, everyone. Let's go to our town.
Let's go!
There's a turtle there.
There's definitely a turtle there.
Come on, everyone. Let's go to our town.
Thank you!
I did it! There's no noisy leader today.
That means I'll be the most important person in the headquarters.
Okay, I'll do whatever I want.
Why are Matoi, Komachi, and Naoko here?
Next time, we'll go to a women's sewage station.
See you there!
There's a turtle there.
There's definitely a turtle there.
Come on, everyone. Let's go to our town.
Thank you!