"When you watch TV, make the room bright and look away!"
"When you kick a stone, fly to the shoe."
"I wonder if I'm going to the gym that I used to work out."
"I laughed at the fact that I was still a baby."
"Even if I try to cheer up, I only have a fever and a cold."
"I have a cold."
"It's drawn silence at night."
"I have a cold. But it stays at night."
"Would you like something to eat?"
"You've been drinking too much, Kenji."
I realized I lost happiness again
Because I'm such an idiot
Oh, Reiko-chan!
Oh, good morning, Grandpa!
Good morning, Grandpa!
You look cute today, Reiko-chan.
Especially that mini-clothes.
It suits you, doesn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you, Grandpa.
See you later!
That's nice.
Reiko-chan.
You're always trying to impress me, aren't you?
Every time I see that thigh, I feel like I get younger little by little.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Oh, is that so?
Then I'll give you a hug.
Oh, how many? How many?
Three, two, one.
Run! Reiko's Great Whip
Me and Gaisten
Ryo-san, look at that.
Hmm, if ya waste it, it'll fall apart.
You gotta do something about it, Ryo-san.
Yup.
It might reach you in just a solid gear.
I might be able to get there by car.
Reiko, get in the back.
Why would I get in the back?
Because you're lighter.
No, Ryo-chan, you get in the back.
You're the one who's in the back.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm heavy.
Hey, Ryo-chan.
Don't mess up my hair.
I've done my hair for a long time.
Sorry, sorry.
Then, give it to me.
It's not going up at all.
Wait a minute.
It's going up a little.
Ouch, my hair is stuck.
You're a noisy person.
Good luck, Reiko.
It's for the children.
It's really heavy.
Hey, stop it.
What?
Don't push your chest against my legs.
I'm giving you too much service.
sufficiently
I'm sorry.
Ryo-chan, are you okay?
I thought your ribs would break.
What can I do?
I'll take a ride.
I told you to do so at first.
Be careful.
Don't raise your head too much.
My skirt will get up.
Minnie is wearing something.
Ryo, a little further.
A little more to the right.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You're too close to the ground.
I got it, Ryo-chan!
Yay!
I got it!
Ryo-chan?
Yay!
Thank you!
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Hang in there.
It's Ryo-chan!
Are you trying to kill me?
You just got too strong.
It's a neck breaker.
If you were 10 seconds late, you'd have died.
I told you I'm sorry.
No, I almost died.
You should keep your legs long.
You shouldn't wear a mini skirt.
No, I'm wearing it because it's easy to move.
How is it?
Senpai, Reiko-san is a great athlete.
I'm wearing a mini skirt because it's easy to move.
Don't be ridiculous.
A short skirt is useless if you make a man feel bad.
What?
I don't want to hear that from a Ryo-chan who doesn't know fashion.
I'm not a little girl.
If you're not polite, be polite.
This is bad, Senpai.
Yes, Reiko-san was really angry.
What?
Shut up.
Good morning.
Oh, Reiko-san isn't here.
Reiko?
I don't know.
What's wrong, Ryo-san?
Well...
Good morning.
Reiko, did you quit mini?
Yes, because an old man from somewhere said it's not good for mini.
Maria, I got this from someone.
You got it?
I'm glad.
What's that?
I was asked for shampoo.
It doesn't fit me well.
I use it in a salon in Paris.
Did you get it from Paris even though it's shampoo?
I always use soap.
Hair is the life of a woman.
Don't be so naughty.
Don't you dare say such things.
By the way, I have something for you, Ryo-chan.
I can do it if it's shampoo.
Who gives you shampoo?
Look inside.
What's this?
I don't go to the salon every year.
So I got it from the office.
I don't need it.
I was told to dress like a rich man.
I have to dress like a rich man for Ryo-chan.
I'm fine with this.
Why are you fine with it?
No cap.
Wrapped in sleeves.
Toilet sandals.
Which is the rich man?
Shut up.
This is my trademark.
Because of this, everyone knows me.
For example?
It's a trap!
Run!
Hurry up!
Wait!
Oh no! Ryo-chan is in a coma!
I can't win.
Run away!
I thought I could escape!
Thank you, Mr. Ryo-chan.
You're fine now.
But,
If I try to dress like a rich man,
The criminal will know I'm the one.
It's a trap!
Run!
Hurry up!
Wait!
I'm not running.
Just a warning?
Shoot him.
Yes.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't need this.
This is a trick.
You can wear it even if you don't want to.
What the hell is this scary atmosphere?
Stop!
Stop, Reiko!
I can't beat Reiko, even with a tank.
But, it's fine to be a police officer.
Right, Maria?
Yes, I'm very happy.
That's right.
Senpai, you're cool.
Right?
You're saying whatever you want.
Good morning.
I'm sorry, I think I got the wrong exit.
Kameari Park exit.
I think I got it right.
John, stop your stupid jokes.
Oh, it's you, Ryo!
I thought you were someone else.
I see.
It's a shame that Reiko died in a miniskirt.
Anyway, I'm glad you're here.
You're dressed like a police officer.
You've been a policeman for 30 years.
I'm so happy for you, Daijirou Ohara.
You don't have to cry.
Shut up!
Do you know how I feel about you being my subordinate?
Anyway, here.
What's this?
You haven't written a single letter since last month.
Oh, well...
Write a two-month letter today.
Sure.
I'll write you a letter.
Here.
"I, Kankichi Ryotsu, will write a death letter."
Good.
Well then, Ryotsu.
If you write a death letter, I'll bring it to you.
I'm going back soon.
Well then, Ryosama, good luck.
I'm going on patrol.
Senpai, Reiko, take care.
Have a good trip.
Oh, dear.
I can't walk with my shoes on.
Hey, Reiko.
Give me some tea.
If you want some tea, you can drink it yourself.
What?
It's fine if you give it to me.
I can't get used to this skirt, so it's hard to move.
I wish I had a mini skirt.
So, I'll be doing my own thing from today.
Then don't wear that skirt.
What are you talking about?
Ryo-chan told me not to wear a mini skirt.
I know.
I'll do it myself.
Hey, Reiko.
Where's the bathroom?
It's over there, right?
Yeah.
Oh, it's there.
Where's the tea pot?
You're so annoying.
I'm in the living room.
I said I'd do it myself, so don't ask me.
I know.
I'm the one who's annoying.
Oh, dear.
This is so annoying.
Sorry, I'm all answered.
It's okay.
You don't have to worry.
We're sure you'll be fine.
Listen up, ah?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
You're in a bad place right now.
It's not me who I've been doing this for.
Don't worry.
I'll do it, Ryo.
What's wrong with you?
What the hell?
It's over!
It took me all day to rewrite the draft.
This uniform and hat are a little too big.
Reiko, you brought a bigger size than me on purpose.
Why do I have to wear this?
It's hard to move because of this uniform.
I can't do this.
Are you giving up already?
Shut up! I was just resting.
You're more difficult to walk than me.
It's not like that. I like it because I can walk well.
How long will you keep this uniform?
Oh, I'll keep it like this from now on.
I wonder how long you'll keep that uniform.
I like it too.
It makes my spine feel tight and tight.
I see. That's good.
See you.
You can't keep your feelings tight.
Huh?
I forgot to tell you.
What? You still have something to complain about?
The chief said to bring the draft to the office as soon as possible.
I told you properly.
Yeah, I got it.
It's time to get out of the office.
Taito, you're so hard to walk.
Oh, hi, grandpa.
What's wrong, Reiko?
You're in such a long skirt.
I was looking forward to seeing your thighs.
Oh, come on, grandpa.
Yeah, right.
That's right.
When I see those fat thighs that don't get ripped,
I get the feeling that they're alive.
Everyone in our old age group is a fan of Reiko's thighs.
No way.
If you make a skirt out of that,
there may be an old man who will be shocked and get a cramp.
That's too much.
No, it's not too much.
We can't take away the lives of the old people.
We should return them to Minnie.
That's a good idea.
Why are you following us?
It's the closest to the library, so we have no choice.
Keiko, are you the newbie?
Huh?
What are you looking at, old man?
It's me, Ryo-tsu.
It's really you, Ryo-san.
What happened to this outfit?
I'm wearing shoes too.
Are you going to a cosplay contest?
Shut up!
Why are you going to a cosplay contest
when the police is wearing police uniforms?
I'm going to arrest you!
Don't push yourself, Ryo-chan.
Why don't you wear your usual outfit?
Hmph.
Thank you very much.
It's the principal!
Huh?
Reiko!
Yes!
Stop!
Oh no, it's the police!
I can't run well in this skirt.
Damn it.
My legs hurt so I can't run.
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
You're going to run away!
You're the one who's running!
That was dangerous!
You're not the one who's running!
Huh? Ryo-san?
I'm borrowing a bike.
This is the only thing I can do.
It's my problem!
Hey, Ryo-san!
You're still on the way out!
I'm sorry!
Ouch!
I thought I could run away from you, Ryo-tsu.
My shoes...
I was told I was a steel man,
but now my shoes are like shoes.
Damn it.
Ugh!
And the handle...
I can't see forward!
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
Where's the culprit?
Over there...
You're a loser!
Damn it!
Look at this!
Do you know what you're doing?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Huh?
Oh, this is the police!
Agency have forgotten all this.
Anyhow, I have to fight them with this!
Wait up!
I'm still going to follow you!
What a fast woman!
Oh, no!
What?
I can't afford to get lost in a place like that!
Reiko!
Ouch!
I won't let you get away!
Okay, me too!
I-I'm sorry...
Idiot! Where are you looking at and running?!
Because you came down from the sky!
Shut up!
I lost sight of you because of the ghost!
Hello?
Ryo-chan?
Yeah, Reiko!
Contact the police immediately!
I'll keep following you and let you know where you are!
Keep your phone on!
Okay! I'll contact you!
You be careful too!
Yeah!
This is Ryochi from Kameari Park!
I'm currently at a convenience store outside Shosen.
I'm chasing a gang of robbers who attacked a convenience store outside Shosen!
Please give me support!
Roger!
Please tell me where you are!
Damn it! They're still following me!
What? They're women!
I-If this is the case, they should follow me!
I'm going up from the ceiling!
I can't climb with this skirt on!
I don't care anymore!
Don't worry, I'll handle it!
How can you be so bl 충분ing?
Aren't you going to let us go?
I can't believe you! I'll go up!
What are you doing! Hurry up and follow them!!!!
Ryo-chan!
The ring processing bank is running away to the south direction!
I'm running away!
Okay, the south side of the bridge.
Hey, turn left at the next corner!
Yes sir!
She's still following me!
What a woman!
It's a woman!
I'm saying goodbye to Fukuya-san here!
You're no match for her!
Those two jumped down!
They're wearing skirts, but...
I don't care anymore!
Ouch!
My legs are so sore today!
From that height...
Amazing!
Now, to the east side!
Running away from the things women are not good at...
That's the worst!
I won't lose!
I will never forgive...
...a man like that!
Argh!
I really got the chance to try and dive for an hour an...
Where's the other one?
Wait!
No wonder, Dekiru.
That thing like...
Where does that gross-looking body have all that power?
You were caught, Goto-san!
Now, get a hold of yourself and get arrested!
You...
I thought you were a woman, so I'll lick you!
Too bad, Mr. Innocent.
I thought something like this would happen, so I split you in two.
It's painful...
Hey, how long are you going to sleep?
I heard you, sister Nakano Girl.
Let me give you a lot of thanks.
What?
Ryo!
You did a good job!
Reiko, are you okay?
Yeah, I think I got in a little trouble.
Hey, get in the car now!
Shut up!
Damn it! If Mr. Innocent wasn't here...
You did it, Reiko! It's a good deed!
Here, a towel!
Thanks!
Ryo-chan was a nice follower!
Huh?
Hey, Reiko, you!
Look at your clothes!
My clothes?
Aren't they the same as your previous clothes?
Oh, but...
Ryo-chan is like that, too.
Huh? What's this?
What the hell?
I guess Reiko looks better in mini clothes.
Ryo-chan, you don't have to wear that kind of outfit.
I don't know what you're talking about!
I'm gonna go change my clothes.
Oh, Reiko-chan!
Good morning, old man!
You're back in the same uniform as before!
I knew it! You look really nice in one of these mini skirts.
True. You're a tough chilly guy.
He sure is, old man.
Goodbye then!
Hey!
Yo! Reiko-chan is the best in Japan!
Reiko-chan is the best in Japan!
♪ ♪
Senpai, what are you doing in the bathroom?
Why are you using a candle to light a candle?
In your room,
there are full of newspapers, matches,
soy oil, gas, dynamite,
and missiles!
Next time on "Wateru Seken ni Kagi Genki",
stop writing!