It has been a while since my last video, and I made two videos on the same topic, so I
hope you are still happy with my new video In this video, I talk about the
When I kicked the tree, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I should go to the gym that I used to go to
I was laughed at for being a baby
Even if I try to cheer up, there is only a punishment
There is only a punishment, and my yawns are the same
The cityscape is strangely kind
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
The sun sets to the Taishakuten
Tomorrow, I will wake up
and go to the gym
It's over
If I win, I will be happy again
I lost it and realized
I'm such an idiot
That day, Senpai and I were asked by Senpai's mother
to repair the floor of Senpai's family
Ouch!
Are you okay, Senpai?
Hey, Honda!
Light the hand properly!
Yes, sir!
The sand is heavy!
Senpai, what is this place?
Well...
It's a pot!
Oh, it's just like in the movies
The pot looks like our mom's
Oh my goodness!
Well, you know...
That's what you think
*gulp*
*splat*
*panting*
Hey, hold on!
*splat*
The pot...
Hey!
*splat*
The pot?
Huh?
That pot was hidden by my ancestors somewhere.
The pot 400 years ago...
It really was there.
So what's in it?
I haven't heard about it.
But it's a pot that the fallen warrior brought with him to save his life.
Well, it's a treasure.
I'll go and buy it.
A treasure?
Is that all?
Yeah.
Alright, let's take it out, Honda!
Yes!
Hurry up and find it before your father finds it!
Why?
It's about your father. He's going to demand a share.
I see.
Alright, we're done taking it out.
That's right.
Oh, that's...
*splat*
What is this?
Let's take it back.
*splat*
Senpai! I think there's another pot in there!
Bring it here!
*splat*
What's this? It's pretty big.
One, two, three!
*splat*
How many are there?
That's too much.
You've dug up a lot.
What if there's another pot?
What's the point of being scared of something so unrealistic?
Rather, look at the reality in front of you.
The pots are all mine, Honda!
*splat*
One pot is 100,000 yen.
That's 1 pot, 1000 pieces.
That's 50 pots.
1, 10, 100, 1000...
5, 5 billion!
5 billion, Honda!
If you have 5 billion, you can have anything.
Give Otohime Nanan a high-end motorcycle.
You're so nice, Honda!
I'm glad you're alive.
What are you going to do, Honda?
I'm going to...
*splat*
I'm going to follow you.
Good!
I'm going to check the treasure.
Hold this.
*splat*
Ouch!
It's a bird!
Someone help me!
You hit yourself!
It's a bad bird!
Otohime!
Help me!
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
You're a coward, aren't you?
You're an old lady.
What happened?
I put the microwave and the cooler together,
and the breaker fell off.
I thought so.
Alright.
What?
*splat*
Touch it carefully.
That's what I'm going to do.
Hold on...
Hold on, Honda.
Senpai, aren't you going to stop?
I don't want to.
I want to.
I'm going to...
If you want it,
hold it down!
Yes!
You can't hear me, Senpai?
It's the voice of the fallen ghost!
Hey, Gyal!
No! I'm going to get possessed!
Look closely. This is the voice.
Saori!
What's wrong, Sakonji?
I finally got to the place where I can confess to Saori.
But the data disappeared in the power outage.
I hope you understand, Honda.
Yes.
I'll give it to you next time.
Okay.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-chida!
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
Please don't hit me! Please!
What's this?
Let's stop it! There's no human head in here!
There's a falling ghost and a hit!
Shut up! You'll understand when you see it!
I'll show you!
I have a full-on head.
A-a-a-a-a-a-a...
Damn... It's hard to get it.
Ugh, it's no good...
Let's stop this...
Shut up, for God's sake!
Take this!
Oh no! It's blood! Blood, blood, blood!
Blood! Blood! Blood!
This...
Blood, blood, blood.
It's blood, blood.
It's blood.
What the hell...
Blood, blood, blood.
It's blood! Blood!
Honda, look closely! It's just a plum blossom!
What?
Plum blossom?
It was just a plum blossom?
That's great. It's a plum blossom.
Not good!
But why are there umeboshi in the pot?
I see. This is probably a dummy to distract the enemy.
The real thing is another pot.
This is also a dummy.
Damn it! It's all dummies!
All umeboshi.
The five billion of the star.
Five billion.
Senpai, there was a wooden box with us, right?
That's right! There was something in it that was cheap!
Is it just a piece of paper?
No, wait. All the pots are dummies.
It must be written on this paper that there is a real treasure.
I see.
Well, one day, a fallen warrior fell in front of my house.
The warrior carried it and opened the lid of the pot.
And...
Huh?
Umeboshi.
So this is all umeboshi.
That's right.
All of this is a pot of umeboshi.
Please, take it.
Huh?
Hey! Hey!
I am Shinzaemon Adachi.
I wanted to leave this umeboshi which is passed down from generation to generation to my descendants.
But I am not strong enough for such a thing.
Instead, please eat it.
Please.
Oh, that's fine.
Really?
I put it into my pot.
I guarantee the taste.
Please eat it without leaving a single grain.
Oh, I understand.
Please.
Oh...
I said that, but I am not good at umeboshi.
I have no choice.
I will bury it with this guy.
I will make a grave and bury the umeboshi and the pot.
I will live as a king for five years.
I will take the umeboshi.
What?
So, it was umeboshi after all.
5 billion...
My 5 billion!
Gakun...
So, what are you going to do with this umeboshi?
Would you like to eat it?
I can't eat the umeboshi that was 400 years ago.
Please let me do it.
Me?
I am not good at eating bugs.
I will beat you with it.
All right.
I will beat you.
Sorry about that, Mr. Sh Isaimon Adachi.
You umeboshi will be carried to the garbage collectors from 20th century.
Don't you throw it away.
Don't throw it away.
Don't give up your job.
No, no!
It's out! It's out! It's out!
Oh no!
It's a ghost from the Armored Carrier.
That's right. It's definitely a ghost.
I can see it with my own eyes.
Then, you were filming a movie, weren't you?
I'm sleepy. Come out quickly.
It stinks.
I see. It's a movie.
Well, there should be ghosts.
There should be ghosts.
This is...
Don't throw away the stick!
You're still living!
Useless!
I'm really sad!
Don't say that!
I don't think you'll dare to touch it.
Oh, please!
Ah!
I'm not Adachi Shinzaemon.
No!
You brought a pot, didn't you?
A pot!
Ufufufufu...
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
What's so frustrating, Shinzaemon-san?
That plum was made with my own effort.
I grabbed it and buried it in the ground without even a single bite.
It's frustrating that you didn't eat the plum.
I'll cut you to pieces and beat you to a pulp.
By the way, who are you beating?
Of course, the human of Ryotsuke!
Alright, I completely believe you.
Ah!
Ufufufufu...
What a cruel villain.
In order to put him to sleep, I'll take this one-and-a-half-dollar card.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad I'm not beaten.
Are you not a human of Ryotsuke?
Yes, I'm a human of the Honda family.
No way...
Ah!
Um, I'm sorry to bother you, but...
Can you teach me a way to eat your plum?
My senior says he doesn't believe in pale
and I wanted to tell him about it, but...
You should have a plum!
So...
If a human of Ryotsuke eats all the plum,
that will be all the pale and no more of your foetal virgins.
You're kidding!
Can I eat a plum from 400 years ago?
But it doesn't rot.
You said it'll last for a long time.
Then, do it.
-You eat it! -No, I'm not from the Ryotsu family.
Hmm...
Wait a minute!
Look! I've sent you the report of the foster care unit in the district office.
From today you are my son, Ryotsu Hayato.
Now you are also a member of the Ryotsu family.
Therefore, this pot is...
...your turn.
Are you telling me to eat everything, senpai?
Not senpai! Call me Papa.
Papa?
Alright.
No, I mean don't force me into this...
Shut up!
I am a lioness who will take my child down to the valley of the ancestors.
It's the virtue of love that I want you to raise him to be a strong human being.
Understand?
No way, senpai...
Call me Papa.
Papa...
If you can't eat it all,
I'll give you 4.
I'm the member of the family, so I'll also give you 4.
Don't forget that!
I'll leave it at that.
Please.
How mean!
I'll leave it at that!
But is it really edible?
No, it's not.
It's 400 years old!
It's sour!
But it's just a normal plum.
I can eat a lot of rice with this.
But I don't need any plum.
Let's eat!
It's so sour!
It's so good!
Sir, what's this?
It's a bento.
Is it good?
It's good.
Let's eat!
Is it good?
It's good!
Today,
today,
today.
Thank you, sir!
Thank you!
This is nothing.
Thank you, sir!
Gochisousama!
I'm so full.
Now, let's eat some dessert.
What? You're not eating only umeboshi?
Give me some.
Mizumi!
What's this?
Umeboshi cake and 100% umeboshi juice.
If you don't eat it, I'll eat it.
It's so sweet and delicious.
I'll eat it with you.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
How was your trip to Kyoto?
I had a good time.
I bought something rare.
It's probably something like Shikasenbei.
That's Nara.
I'm not going to fight with people who say that.
What is it, chief?
Don't be surprised.
How is it?
Umeboshi?
That's right. I bought it at a old store in Kyoto.
I'm not kidding.
You can buy umeboshi in Tokyo.
What are you thinking?
You don't know anything.
The longer you keep umeboshi in the fridge, the more flavor it has and the better it tastes.
What?
By the way, I've been sleeping on this for 30 years.
It costs 3,000 yen per grain.
What?
3,000 yen in 30 years?
That means you're not going to buy it, right?
What?
If you found umeboshi 400 years ago, how much would it cost?
400 years ago?
I don't think that's really possible.
I think it was sold for 10,000 yen in 100 years.
50,000 yen per grain.
No, it might be 100,000 yen.
What?
100,000 yen per grain?
I think that's 400,000 yen.
What do you mean by 400,000 yen?
I think that's 500,000 yen.
100,000!
400,000 yen?
It's a lot.
It's only about 400,000 yen.
That's about 1 million yen.
400,000.
500,000...
500,000?
500,000.
*punch*
Senpai...
I ate all the plums!
Who are you?
I've been in the business of driving for 35 years.
I'm the 7th class of the traffic safety leader, Tetsuo Ishizu!
I'm here!
You're the one who saw the car, right?
Yes, I did!
I was putting the garbage in my stomach, so I was careful.
You!
You're the one who broke the speed limit and broke the rules!
I won't forgive you!
So...
I'll give you a punishment!
When he realized, the armadillo and the empty plums were gone.
Maybe he came to thank me for eating all the plums.
Hey, stop it!
The garbage in the middle of the night is cash!
Return everything to the owner!
Hey, why do I have to do this?
And you've even taken the empty plums!
Shut up!
Yes, I'm sorry!
Damn it! Why do I have to wear armor?
Nagagawa is the king of the underworld?
Don't make me laugh!
The one who's hiding in the center is the king of the underworld!
He's not in town!
If you're upset, take that blackmail,
and go around and look around!
Next time: "Is Nagagawa the child of the town?"
Come on, go around and look around!
Translation by Arale
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Wow!
Surprisingly
No!
"I'm not going to be a coward!"
"I'm not going to make a fool out of myself!"
"Then who am I to think? They were always waiting for me!"
"The only ones who want to know how I feel!"
Thank you for watching!