*Under the beech tree*
♪ I somewhat see today ♪
♪ Right in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I dig a Mid-northern rock ♪
♪ And keep flying ♪
♪ To my seeming feet ♪
I wonder if I'll go if I do
He laughed at me saying that I was just crying
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I can't help but cough
I can't change a single grumble
The cityscape is strangely gentle
From the fountain of the Tungari-boshi
to the Taishakuten
the sun sets
Tomorrow will end already
Katsushika and Shibamata
will be happy again
I'm tired of it
I'm a fool
Katsushika and Shibamata
will be happy again
Saori
Ta-chan
I'm so happy.
Sakonji!
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
What's he saying?
It's a waste to run away in this situation.
Right, Saori?
Huh?
One push!
Before that...
Ryotsu! We beat Sakonji!
Oh, he's happy with the man's heart.
Th-This is a practice match, but we lost five times.
What happened to Sakonji?
Ryotsu, do you have any idea?
That idiot was thinking about Saori's Doki-Memo during the match.
Doki-Memo? What's that?
Could it be the Doki-Doki Memorial of the love simulation game?
Huh?
You're still playing?
CD, poster, fancy goods, and all kinds of Doki-Memo goods.
And a lot of bones, too.
Sakonji is no longer a fighter.
He's a super Doki-Doki Memorare now.
I'm not kidding.
Next month is the national tournament.
Everyone is expecting to win.
Why are you so into such a game?
Don't hit me.
I can't help it if I get stuck.
Well, I'll give up this time.
Let's hope for the next tournament.
I'll be too tired to play Doki-Doki Memo by then.
Well, you taught me.
Ryotsu, immediately separate Doki-Doki Memo and Sakonji,
and concentrate on Judo.
What?
If Sakonji can't win, you won't get a bonus or a bonus.
Why would that happen?
Because it's your responsibility.
No way.
W-Wait!
Hey, shut up!
I'm getting a bonus and a bonus.
Stop!
I'm going to die!
Sorry.
I'm trying to take my Saori, so I can't help it.
My Saori?
I'm pretty sure you said you were into Doki-Doki Memo.
I see.
You always forget about it when your brother comes to play.
You're a troublemaker.
I see.
Then your brother must be in trouble, too.
I'll pay you back.
Wait!
Do you want to be charged with murder?
S-Sorry.
Anyway, I'll keep this in my office.
Tell your brother to come get it.
No way.
What should I do, Saori?
Your...
Your life without you...
I can't think about it!
Huh?
Boshi...
Hey, wait!
That's...
That's the last Saori I'll ever have!
Saori!
Gaki!
Whoa!
That was close.
Although, that wasn't really funny.
I think it's Sakonji's.
Weird.
There's something about this.
Hey, you.
Huh?
You're not going to swear?
Oh!
Ah! Help me!
Ah!
Saori.
Where are you, Saori?
What?
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious!
I'm serious.
Saori, Saori.
You're a patient with no symptoms.
You're so lucky to have won the game.
But...
If it's true...
Sakonji can't win.
And I'll give him a bonus.
I'm sorry!
Honda, show me the way!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
If I let you go, I won't leave you alone.
No way.
Look, Senpai.
Huh?
Sakonji.
Look! What's wrong with you?
You're always so cold.
No, that's not the way I look.
But look at that face.
Huh?
Right?
S橋
What's wrong, Senpai?
What's making you so bad?
This is the theme for the opening of Doki Memo.
But I don't think you bought it after breaking my ceremony.
Pikori!
Sakonji!
You brat!
I'm Pikori!
Ah!
In 1988, on April 9th, change was announced into the school year.
"If I wait here, I can see Saori."
*crying*
Senpai, what's going on?
There's nothing on the screen, but you're...
It's the forbidden symptom.
Ehhh...
Huh?
It's no use.
If other characters appear,
Saori won't be able to appear, right?
Eh?
N-No, Sakonji!
We're not characters from the game!
Please be a little more creative!
S-S-Sorry...
So, the forbidden symptom is still there?
Yeah. I want my body to be healed for the sake of the bonus and the bonus.
But it's not for Sakonji.
Of course.
But he's just a senior.
If it's a game, his body will remember it.
See?
You have to be more creative, right?
Saori!
Saori? Where are you?
Where are you?
You have to be more creative!
But, Mama...
Saori...
Are you okay, teacher?
Sakonji, teacher!
She doesn't remember it perfectly.
No, I'm not joking.
Come here, Sakonji!
What?
Are you going to let Saori do it?
I'll do the opposite.
I'll train in the mountains far away from humans and make her forget about Saori.
No!
What?
Do you remember it?
Stop worrying!
Saori! Don't forget about Saori!
I don't want to die!
Did you see her?
No.
Damn it. Where is she?
She's here!
She went inside!
Wait, where is that store?
No!
She's here!
Saori!
I think one-sixth of Saori is here today.
What?
You're a bad boy.
I'll beat you up!
Give me...
Give me Saori!
I'll beat you!
Let go, you wretch!
What are you talking about, Ryosuke?
Don't be ridiculous!
You were trying to buy Saori!
Saori?
Oh, that's right. You're going to cut the silk.
Then why did you join the art school?
I-I mean, I'm the head of the school, right?
I thought I'd try making it for you, Kibun.
Yes, sir.
You're lucky. This is the last one...
Hey!
I'll take this as well!
Y-Yes.
Zagonji, are you really interested in plums?
Of course.
Even though it looks like it, I made them a lot when I was a kid.
I see...
It seems like you're back to the Zagonji you're used to.
I hope so.
Here.
All of them cost 85,350 yen.
What?!
They're all exclusive, so you can't take them.
K-Kan! Wrap it for me!
Now then...
Saori is finally back!
There. I'll wrap it for you!
Whoa!
What?!
What's this?!
Uh...
Saori...
Saori!
I don't know what's inside the figure, so I'm going to do it.
Which one do you want?
Wait...
When I saw the figure at the plumber's, it was back to normal, wasn't it?
I think I can use this one...
Saori!
Wait...
I thought, why are you doing this to my company?
Ohara!
Yeah!
Today's practice match looks good, right?
Do you suppose Sakonji will lose by one to six?
Well, I did give him the liquid endgame, but you think Ryotsu is running away from Sakonji, just like that?
Saori...
Sakonji!
Ryo-Ryotsu...
What's wrong? You look very upset.
It's nothing.
Go over there.
I see.
I brought some presents.
What's this?
Sakonji!
Calm down!
I'll let you touch it.
Hold it!
Just a little.
Don't do it too much.
I know.
Ouch!
It hurts!
How are you feeling?
I feel better.
Alright, Sakonji.
Let's make a deal.
If you win this match,
I'll give you this figure.
Hold it!
If you win this match,
I'll give you this figure.
you'll be mine.
You'll be mine.
Japan!
It's the final!
I hope it goes well.
Ouch!
It hurts!
He threw me.
What are you saying, Reiko?
You can't throw a kid seriously.
But he threw me so beautifully.
I'm teaching you the technique.
Damn it.
Hey, Sakonji.
Sorry.
Oh no, it's a dangerous symptom.
If the chief finds out, it'll be a disaster.
Okay, that's all for today.
What?
Hey, Sakonji.
It's me, Saori.
Try to do it as you always do.
Come on.
Oh, Saori.
Ouch!
Okay, okay.
It doesn't work!
What?
Hey, idiot.
Try touching it more.
Come on.
It's no good.
Huh?
What?
Did I lose my motivation just by the same figure?
Saori's figure?
It's here.
Really?
The one that just joined the school today...
It's Saori's 1/3 figure.
His length is over 50cm.
Okay, I won!
Idiot.
Don't make a loud voice.
Are you okay, Ryotsu?
Are you okay?
I'm okay, so hurry up.
Put your hands down!
Do you have to do all these things?
It's not like you can't do them, Saori.
One, two...
Three...
Four...
Nine...
Ten...
The last one is mine.
inomini...
Here, take him.
You can't just put him on the stage with me, Saori.
One, two...
One, two, three...
Five...
Seven...
And one...
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Oh, you're almost done! You touched it too much!
The figure of Gensundai will be sold.
Really?
There's no place to put it in a regular store, so it's only for mail.
What should we do?
Of course! Order it now!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ahoy!
Wait, it'll be here soon.
Hey, Yotsu, here's your delivery.
Oh, here it is. It's really big.
Ahoy!
Be happy, Sakonji. I've already painted it, so you'll be able to touch it right away when you open it.
There we go.
Hey, I only ordered one.
That's fine. If you contact the manufacturer, there are ten types in total.
T-ten types?
What should we do?
I'll have Daikin return it to Sakonji later, so it's fine.
Yoku, hurry up and buy this!
Got it!
Okay!
Bye!
Oh! Saori!
I'll make it, y'know?
Saori...
Chon! Chon! Chon! Chon! Chon! Chon! Chon! Chon!
A-ah!
Ah!
channels!
테
Then I'll go practice.
I'll do it! I'll win the national tournament!
Well, if I have this much money, I'll be able to hold the tournament.
Ryosu, is Ryosu here?
What is it, chief?
It's not what it is.
Sakonji has been skipping practice lately.
What?
The judo game is tomorrow, right?
Sen...Senpai!
I don't know!
Ryosu!
You're not taking my advice and taking my money, are you?
I'm not doing that!
I'm getting paid and bonuses, too!
I see.
Sakonji, you're not listening anymore?
Sakonji!
Hello, Ryosu.
Welcome.
What are you doing?
What about practice?
The tournament is tomorrow.
Practice?
The tournament?
What is it?
It's not about anything.
It's judo.
Judo.
Judo?
Oh, that.
Not that.
Drink it first.
Is it a high-tech game?
And it's all in one!
You're a loser!
You're wearing pants.
It's not that kind of problem!
Now, hurry up and go to the dojo.
Chief Ohara is waiting.
I don't want to.
What?
I'm staying in this room all the time.
I'm going to live with Saori and the others.
Oh, no.
Because of the sudden stimulus,
I'm back to being a former Saori addict.
No, I'm more unlucky than before.
The chief is suspecting us.
If we find the figure,
we'll all be taken away.
Taken away?
Yes.
Saori will disappear from this room.
I don't want to be separated from Saori anymore!
So hide it right away.
Yes.
We'll put it in the closet.
It's hard to put the futon out even if I put it out.
I have no choice.
I'll hide the rest in my room.
No, no.
Don't put it out of this room.
You've changed too much.
I understand.
Don't cry.
I'll hide it somehow.
First, I'll hide one under the stream.
My smile is creepy.
Sorry, Saori.
Now, four more.
You're hiding the whole thing in the fridge.
What?
I get it.
I'll think of another way.
It's only in the sandbag.
That's terrible.
Next, we'll put the statue over there.
Are you hiding it?
I won't tell you how luxurious it is.
Two more.
What?
I'm Ohara.
Sakonji, can I help you?
What's going on, Ryo?
I don't know.
I didn't even hear the chief coming.
Put one in the closet.
One more?
He's not here?
Excuse me, Ryo.
Chief, are you visiting me?
Are you injured?
It's just a cold.
Cold?
The tournament is tomorrow.
Are you okay, Sakonji?
Yes, well...
Saori is my chikumi!
He seems to be in a fever.
But he's much better than yesterday.
Really?
Ryo.
Yes?
You're not getting any better, are you?
You can't get a cold in a cold room like this.
You should put a stove on.
Okay.
Okay, chief.
Leave the rest to me.
Well, then.
Make sure you get better, Sakonji.
Yes, sir.
Sakonji,
you're done.
You're such a pain in the ass.
Get up.
Get some fresh air and cool your head.
Here.
Finally, you're awake.
I'm calling.
Saori...
Saori and his friends are calling.
Saori!
Saori, Saori.
and my bonus and fee too...
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
One!
Until then!
He won!
He's the winner!
As expected, in the real game, he's showing off his strength.
Well done, Ryotsu!
Well, if I had said so, you would have known it would turn out like this.
Thanks to you, my bonus and my paid salary were saved.
Then why don't you be even more happy?
Look! He's crying so much in excitement.
This victory made him so happy.
Yeah.
I don't know what will happen after this.
I don't know.
Now that the tournament is over, I can't even think about where I will be angry next.
Saori!
Give me Saori!
You're here again, Shiratori Reiji!
But what is that camping car?
You don't know the fun of camping at all!
Alright!
I'll teach you the real thing!
Next time on "Burning Camp Spirit"
In short, "Cantama"!
See you then!
"Burning Camp Spirit"
♪ It's said that a woman who can't fall in love is a woman ♪
♪ But I have a lot of things I want to do ♪
♪ I have a lot of things I want to do ♪
♪ I want to run through the vast desert on a motorcycle ♪
♪ I want to be freer than a bird ♪
♪ A lady's dream that changes with the speed of a firefly ♪
♪ My love, I'm sorry ♪
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♪
♪ The future of the panorama ♪
♪ The dazzling light that dives into it ♪
♪ You get it, right? ♪
♪ I'm sorry, wait for me ♪
♪ Make me smile more ♪