Engsub by Kay Salmon
It's time to watch TV
Keep your head up and keep an eye on yourself
On a hot sun,boarding on a river
When I kicked the stone, it flew to my shoes
I wonder if I'm going to go to the gym that I used to play
I laughed at the fact that I was still a child
Even if I try to cheer up somewhere
I'm always a shy little turtle
Even my yawns don't change
The cityscape is strangely kind
From the fountain of a pointed hat
The sun sets to the sea
Tomorrow
It's over like this
I lost my happiness
I realized
I'm such a fool
Good morning
I see. Today is the day
We have to clean your house
That's right
I saw she's coming
She went somewhere
Just what a trifle
If you come home, you'll be in a bad situation
Hey, let's start cleaning
I'll help you
Okay
Are you OK, Terai-san
I'm fine.
This is...
It looks like an old photo.
This is the history of the exit in front of the park.
This is a photo of the police officers who worked here.
This is the photo of the first time I came here.
Young man! The chief had such an era.
Of course. I can't suddenly become the chief.
By the way, this is the chief Iwata who was in charge of this place at that time.
He was a kind and honest man. He was like a police officer's mirror.
Oh!
I think there's only one person who does such stupid things.
Is it Ryo?
He came to this exit because he was a graduate.
Actually, I met Ryo-tsu the day before the deployment.
Really?
He was drunk in the Han River.
There was a report that the police were in a big trouble.
Hey! Be quiet!
The police are scared, so they can't drink.
What?
Cool your head down for a night!
That was Ryo-tsu.
What?
The chief knew that he was a police officer who was assigned to the exit in front of the park,
so he made me go to pick him up.
Oh, thank you for coming!
What's the big story?
Well, well, calm down.
It's an old story.
Besides, I was supposed to be an educator for Ryo-tsu, but when I went on patrol with him...
Hmm? Oh!
He'll be gone for sure.
Hehehe, a lot, a lot.
Hey, Ryo-tsu!
Or...
Ron!
I did it!
Hey, Ryo-tsu!
Or...
All right!
3-5! 3-5! Go! Go!
Hey, Ryo-tsu!
Ugh!
I was supposed to be fired, of course.
But Chief Iwata...
He's still young.
Those who educate people shouldn't get up so soon.
Oh...
Come on, come on!
Huh?
I went on patrol with him to keep him from running away.
Ouch!
I'm not used to wearing shoes, so it hurts.
Hmm...
Thank you very much.
I bought him sandals with my money.
The sandals he's wearing now are from that time.
Since long ago?
He's so young!
Senpai has always been a senpai.
He's a senpai, I see.
Hey!
Hey, Ryo-san!
You're not dressed up!
That's unusual.
Oh, this is a photograph Ryo-tsu took when he was assigned to the police department.
The police department?
Senpai, were you a cop?
Yeah.
It's been a while.
Wow, I've never heard of it.
He has his own memories he can't say in words, too.
I have two.
It's decided.
Ryotsu, what have you been doing?
Eh? Senpai, haven't you been watching "Yuuhi ni Hoyoro"?
I only watch TV news and historical dramas.
It's such an interesting program, but it's a waste.
Senpai, how can I become a detective?
Eh?
I want to become a detective since I joined the police.
Are you a detective?
You can't be a detective if you don't work for the police.
I'm not good at working for the police.
I don't do anything big, and I have to wear a cool uniform.
It's better that you don't do anything big.
That's right.
If I catch ten people,
I'll be a detective.
I might get a call from the police.
Well, I don't think I can.
I see.
Wait!
You thief!
Damn it, let me go!
I'll let you go even if you die!
One down!
I'll arrest you!
Huh?
You're going to be a detective?
I'm certain the chief prosecutor will.
But he's short of time, short of speed, and short of cells.
And he's pretty strong, if you think about it.
That's what he said.
We're going to have a blast in the name of him.
What a jerk.
So this is my battlefield from today.
Boss, I'm coming in!
What are you?
I'm Ryo-tsu. Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
I've become a detective since today.
Ryo-tsu?
You're right.
Hey, everyone.
I'm Ryo-tsu, the one who's been assigned to this department.
Please call me "Jeans."
What's wrong with you?
Are you a half?
That's my nickname.
Normally, a detective would call me by my nickname.
No, that's not what I meant.
Oh, then please do that from now on.
By the way, I'm going to wear jeans every day from now on.
So, "Jeans Decker!"
The jeans are...
Hey, someone lend me your pants.
What's wrong with you?
What's with that "dabu dabu"?
These pants are too big.
You don't have to laugh so much.
Just call me Ryo-tsu.
Don't get so angry.
Nanbu.
Yes.
I'll leave the rest to you.
I'm Nanbu, who will be your partner.
Nice to meet you, Deca-pan-Deka.
I'm Ryo-tsu.
"Ryo-tsu"
"Mam tombu"
What the hell?
In addition, you're a detective on a vitality test.
And I'll call you "Ryo-tsu,"
that's all.
No, it's not that.
You're not qualified to do so.
Anyway, why didn't you tell me I could get you a " Assembly? " No,
You did great! The last part of the G-Pan was amazing!
What's this?!
Shh!
What are you doing, Nanbu-san?
Look at that.
Huh?
A kiss?
Both.
Let's go.
Yes!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Oh no!
Ryosu, go that way!
Run away!
You!
Ryosu!
Give it back! Give it back! Give it back! Give it back!
Alright, Ryosu. It's over.
Yes!
Hey, hey. What's with the way you're running?
Huh? I'm running properly.
Huh?
Hey, Ohara-kun. You did great.
Ryosu.
What are you doing here?
I was just following the investigation.
Oh!
Hey, hey. Did you know?
I was the one who caught Kaito.
It seems so.
The day I became a detective, you arrested the culprit.
It means I was really looking for a detective.
Well, Ohara-kun.
You'll be our detective's hand and foot.
Work for me.
Now, let's get out of here.
That idiot is really getting in my way.
What's going on?
Well, ohara-kun.
I'm sorry, Ryosu.
Hey, Ryosu.
I'm listening.
Again?
Let's do a investigation once in a while.
What if we catch the culprit we're following?
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
Mr. Namu, there's no more criminals around here.
It's no use doing this for days.
But what if we give up and the criminal shows up?
But...
If it's a criminal drama, we'll find a clue soon.
Is that so?
Yes, yes.
I understand.
Then...
What's wrong?
It seems that the planet we were chasing was caught in Kyushu.
What?
Then everything we've done...
It's all in vain.
Don't be so angry.
It happens often.
Anyway, it's time for the next job.
Cheer up.
Yes.
Mr. Namu.
How long have you been dressed like this?
Until I understand the movements of the Otaguro group.
Recently, the movement of the gang has become active.
There may be some kind of big deal.
But if there's nothing...
In that case, it's a good thing.
Hmm...
I don't want to be seen by a friend who knows me like this.
What?
A friend?
He's a senior at the station.
Grandpa, are you here for the sunbathing again today?
Yes, this is Mr. Omawari.
The weather is good today.
Yes, it is.
Ryotsu, Japan is said to be a country with few crimes.
Do you know why?
Huh?
Hmm...
I don't know.
That's because there are police stations all over the city.
That's why the police patrols.
Oh...
What?
What happened?
It's a bigger mountain than I expected.
Huh?
The leader of the Otaguro group, who was on the run abroad, has returned.
He was sentenced to death for gambling and murder.
What?
Let's go.
We're on the back door.
Yes.
Finally, it's becoming like a detective.
I'm counting on you, Ryotsu.
Leave it to me.
Who are you?
You're still there.
Mr. Omawari, this way.
Don't run away, Otaguro.
Hey, Otaguro!
Mr. Omawari!
Yes!
Stop right there!
Ouch!
Ryotsu?
Huh?
As I thought, it's him.
Yeah, it's true.
What's with that thing?
Didn't you become a policeman?
You became a policeman?
Ah, Otaguro!
Oh no!
Idiot!
You let the criminal escape because you were a junior high school classmate?
How could you make such an excuse?
But, but...
You!
Nanbu, stop it.
Tch! Nanbu, you don't have to hit me.
Ryotsu, you know what Otaguro did, right?
Yeah.
Uh, he killed Tobacco, right?
What Otaguro killed was Nanbu's fiancée.
What?
But, Nanbu, you didn't say a word about that!
I thought I'd give you extra pressure if I told you.
Nanbu, you're so bright.
I didn't know you had such a past.
That's what a detective is.
Nanbu.
Yeah?
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry!
Huh?
I didn't understand how you felt, and I was just looking at myself.
I... I...
I'm a bad guy!
Don't be like that, Ryotsu.
Huh?
I cut myself too, so I'm sorry for hitting you.
What? No way!
All right, get a grip.
This time we'll arrest Otaguro together!
Yes, sir!
Nanbu, I bought it!
Oh, thanks.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's been a week.
I think Otaguro went overseas.
Maybe.
Then, it's no use staying here.
But we'll hide his money.
Before we go abroad, we might come and get it.
Just wait a little longer.
But I want to eat decent food sometimes.
Don't be so naggy.
I'll take you to a drink once this mountain is solved.
Really?
Oh, you're still a minor.
I'll be 20 on March 3rd.
Okay, I promise.
Let's drink until the morning on the third day.
Yay!
It's his car.
Ryotsu, call for support immediately.
Yes!
Ugh...
Ah, shit! I don't have the 10 Yen coin!
Hey, you! Give me the money!
Just give me the money now!
Mr. Omawari! Mr. Omawari!
Come on, hurry! Hurry!
Give me the money!
Hey, Ryotsu! What are you doing?
Senpai, there's a criminal over there.
We have to get the criminal.
But we don't have the 10 Yen coin.
If we don't hurry, he'll run away.
What?
You idiot!
You can call for support even if you don't have the 10 Yen coin!
Oh, really?
I'll contact the police.
You go back to the scene.
Y-Yes, sir!
Shit...
He's already out.
Did he see us?
Hey, hurry up.
Otaguro!
Yes?
We're not gonna let you get away!
Don't touch that!
Otaguro!
We're gonna arrest you for fraud and murder!
Mr. Nam!
Ryotsu!
Don't let anyone else get away!
What the hell is this?
You bastard!
Namu!
Hurry up!
Stay still!
I don't care.
Just follow him.
But...
But the blood is...
If you let him escape,
you'll never catch him again.
But...
You're a detective, too!
We have to catch him.
No matter what.
Let's go!
Otaguro!
Get him!
Yes, sir!
Ouch!
Get him!
Damn it!
You bastard!
You killed Namu!
Damn it!
Senior!
Yotsu!
Where is Namu?
No way!
If only I had called for help earlier...
Is that drama funny?
Cheer up!
Let's drink till morning on the third day.
You're a detective, too!
Namu!
It's been a while since then.
Oh, good morning!
Ryo-tsu, why are you here?
I didn't know anything.
Please let me work here again.
Ryo-tsu...
That's why he came back here.
Although, he returned to his usual Ryo-tsu soon.
Ryo-chan also had a hard time.
Then, maybe today...
I see.
It was like this that day, too, Namu.
I'm better than him.
You're still a fool.
There is no such thing as Mr. Namu.
Today, I'll treat you to something.
Let's drink!
"The Power of Power"
I'm sorry.