Vacation is intense!
Ryo, I know what you're saying.
Come out!
It's been six months since you stopped helping.
I'll have you pay today.
I'll close this deal and pay you 55,000 yen.
Pay the three bills!
You think it's okay for the police to pay the debt?
Open it, Ryo Kankichi!
I have to go home before they pay today.
Hurry up and come out!
I know you're hiding, Ryo!
Come out!
30 seconds left.
This way is no good.
I see.
Five seconds left.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Stop!
You're done, Ryo.
Let's play again.
How much is the debt?
It's nothing.
It's about 180,000 yen.
It's the same as my salary.
I'll pay you back!
I'm confused.
Hokkaido is good, isn't it?
The autumn leaves are already starting.
Okinawa is hard to throw away.
We can play scuba diving.
Hokkaido is great.
Okinawa is good.
Hokkaido?
Okinawa!
Hokkaido!
Well, well, you two...
What's wrong?
Actually, I was talking about the trip to Yan at the exhaust.
Where are you going?
That is...
Ryo!
Hokkaido is good, isn't it?
You can eat anything you want in the fall.
I knew it!
It's Okinawa, isn't it?
It's a great place to go on a trip!
Hokkaido and Okinawa, huh?
It's a great place.
I think it's better to go abroad.
You can enjoy the feeling of the South China Sea with Hawaii or the Gulf.
That's impossible.
The budget is not enough.
How much is it?
48,000 yen per person.
After the previous trip, I decided to go to the university.
I paid 2000 yen a month for two years.
I worked hard for two years.
By the way, Ryo,
you've been saving up for three months.
Shut up!
I'm happy with that.
Leave it to me.
I'll let you go on a trip abroad.
What?
I'll make good use of the travel expenses and pay off my debt.
I'm so smart.
A travel agency for the first time.
Travel agency for the first time.
I hate this name.
I think it's the place where the fake real estate is located.
Well, whatever.
I don't have a contract with him yet.
I'll have to do something with the debt, or I'll be in trouble.
I'll ask him!
Why are you here again?
Cheers!
Welcome!
A travel agency for the first time for the first time for real!
It's been a long time.
You're a fraud!
You're a fraud, you know.
Why are you the one who's the travel agent?
Well, the real estate industry is in a bad shape.
So I've switched to the overseas travel agent.
It's about you anyway. You're still doing frauds.
N- no way.
I'll start a new life from now on.
I'll be honest!
I'll be devoted to my job!
You'll be honest, huh?
Y- yes.
Actually, I want to go on a trip to Iyan with my wife.
Y- yes, you do.
Which way are you going?
I want to go to the South Island, like Guam or Saipan, in 3 nights and 4 days.
Sir, you're lucky.
Just now, I got the information about the super-cheap Guam tour.
Oh.
How about this?
60,000 yen in 3 nights and 4 days.
The hotel is super-class, so it's super-profitable.
So, why are you going?
I'm going!
That's a good idea for an airplane.
I'm so excited.
What's written in this small font?
I'll ask!
The meeting place, Guam Airport?
That means the airport is different.
What?
You, where did you get your heart?
This is the same as the old days, isn't it?
Huh?
I'm so sorry.
Night-night.
This is a super-cheap tour.
It includes the flight fee, so it's 60,000 yen in 3 nights and 4 days.
So, what's the hotel like?
It's a pretty good hotel, even though it's a super-cheap hotel.
Super-cheap hotel, huh?
What's this sign?
It says, "Super-cheap Hotel."
I think I heard it wrong.
Can you tell me another hotel?
Super-cheap hotel.
Can you point at me?
Um, this one?
It's a kind of unnatural way of pointing at me.
Giku-giku.
What the hell is this?
This "super-cheap" hotel behind this fancy hotel is called Super-cheap Hotel, right?
Well, that's...
I'm sorry.
I can see through your way of doing things.
Hey, you!
Why are you doing such a serious tour?
It doesn't matter if it's a southern island.
I don't care where you are, but you have to make sure that you have a proper hotel and proper food.
And of course, you have to take the plane.
Is that clear?
Yes, I understand.
I'll prepare it.
I see.
That's good.
And about the price.
Since it's a 5-person group trip, we'll charge 30,000 yen per person.
30,000 yen?
Yes, 30,000 yen.
You're so ridiculous.
It's impossible to pay 30,000 yen in the country at this time.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
So, everyone who is passing by,
this is a fake business.
Everyone, please be careful not to get caught.
I got it. I got it.
So please stop.
Let's get 4 tickets.
Everyone who is passing by,
this is a fake business.
I got it. I got it.
I'll do it for 30,000 yen somehow.
What?
You should have said that from the beginning.
Hey, keep this trip's cost of 30,000 yen a secret from everyone.
Why?
I got it.
Y-Yes.
If you get caught, I'm sure you know what will happen.
Yes, I do.
If you pay 18,000 yen per person,
that's 90,000 yen for 5 people.
The cost is 180,000 yen, so it's half.
What?
Are you going on a trip without a ticket?
How about it?
But I have to go to Shirobaetai next month.
What's wrong with you?
You've been in hot springs for a long time.
Our trip is amazing.
It's a luxurious trip of 3 nights and 4 days to the south island.
Is it overseas?
It's amazing.
Yes, the south island is good.
If you get on a jet bike,
you'll be popular with a blonde lady in a bikini.
Oh.
I'm so excited!
You're an exciting boy!
I can't tell you how excited he is.
He's excited for his new friend.
Thank you, sir.
Excuse me.
There's a man in the back.
It's a man!
What's wrong?
I didn't know?
It's a man!
$12,000 plus the actual cost of $30,000 plus my savings of $6,000 in three months.
In short, it's $126,000!
$126,000? That's a bit...
I see. It's a shame.
You and I are friends, so I called out to you alone.
No jet bikes, no gold hair!
I understand! I'll buy the equipment and prepare it!
I see! Great! I'll pay the debt with this!
Is he really okay?
He was in such a bad mood the other day.
That's right!
It's okay! It's okay!
Really?
He said he was tired of traveling with you the other day.
It's a shame.
He complained that he could travel to the southern island with that money with my help.
I think he should be more grateful.
That's right, chief.
That's right. I'm sorry, Ryotsu.
Well, I hope you understand.
What?
What are you doing here?
Well, let's continue our journey.
That's right.
Hey, manager!
I'm counting on you!
Yes, sir!
Everyone, please come this way.
Welcome!
Thank you!
That's it!
Why?
We will be in a separate seat from now on.
Separate seat?
Yes, sir!
By the way, I heard only you two were in a separate seat from now on.
You guys are in first class!
No, you are not.
That gentleman is...
Here we are again!
Well done, sir!
Hehehehe!
Uh, we're here to check out that plane service.
Oh, that flight, huh?
It's wonderful!
Please move completely.
Please be careful when you walk, okay?
Stop right there!
What's going on?
Since only five people were allowed to enter the inn,
the guests will be taken outside.
What? What do you mean outside?
You can catch them at the place you like, whether it's a beach or a beauty salon.
What?
Then you'll be taken outside, right?
We're guests, guests!
Even if you say that, what do you want?
Three!
You idiot!
Hey, Ryotsu, what are you mumbling about?
We're about to leave.
I'm not mumbling!
If you don't hurry, you'll be late for the ride!
What?
Hey!
Don't fly!
Idiot!
What's that?
Who, you've got no później?
I was an old Japanese soldier that must've traveled the Zero Line.
Oh...
But I'm happy to see such a beautiful, Japanese guest,
so I'll have to give you a little gift.
Huh? A gift?
Don't you wonder what I look like in the old days?
What?
Hooray!
We're going home!
masukan kono
Damage Stuck!
Let's turn the card into cans!
Oh!
Ah! Senpai is down!
Oh, come on! He can hold out.
He'll follow you in a bit.
Good work. This is the destination, Otto Dokkoi Island.
Do you want to share the room first, or do you want to have a meal?
Meal! Meal!
The hotel is buying your job.
Why me again?
Because the staff is too much.
Is the hotel over there?
No, it's over there.
I don't understand.
It's a wonderful hotel.
We have arrived.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm sorry to be the last one to go to the bimboku.
I'll go to the restaurant first.
The viking is at this garden restaurant.
What?
Here it is.
Me, too!
I'm sorry, but this place is full of staff.
You like this place?
We have prepared the customers' portion over there.
What?
It's delicious.
It's wonderful.
The food is delicious.
There's nothing to say.
We have to thank the senior.
That's right.
By the way, where is he?
He is...
Why me again?
This is the place where you will stay.
Aren't you staying at that hotel?
The budget is too expensive.
But the inside is like a hotel, so don't worry.
Well, the room is divided into two.
The wife will stay alone and one will stay in the cottage.
And the other two will stay alone.
Wait, wait, there's one left.
I'm staying, too, so there are two left.
Wait! What are you going to do with those two?
They are prepared at Hanarekojima over there.
It's an optional Robinson Crusoe tour.
Oh.
Well, one is fine with both.
Why me?
The life in Hanarekojima is perfect for you who are separated from humans.
Yeah, yeah.
But what about the other one?
Hey, I'm not going yet.
Hey, the manager, do something.
Even if you tell me to do something, this is the most I can do.
Anyway, 30,000 yen for one person...
Idiot!
30,000 yen?
Ryochi, what do you mean by 30,000 yen?
The total amount is 48,000 yen, but...
You've already raised it to 30,000 yen.
You were going to do it, weren't you?
Senpai, you are so mean.
I can't even get 126,000 yen.
In total, 186,000 yen.
You were going to do it, weren't you?
Oh, that 18,000 yen is the amount of your debt.
6,000 yen is the amount of travel expenses for Ryo-chan.
Hmm...
Don't you know that I'll pay for it.
Why?
Don't you know that I'll pay for it?
Why do you want me to pay for it?
Because I have the highest cost of the expenses.
Don't you get it?
Because you lost in the 'Janken' game.
.
Will you really let me stay at this island?
Um...
Yes.
Use this, please.
What?
Isn't it a hammock?
Then I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
Hey, what about the rice?
Please look for it properly.
It's an island with nothing.
That's right.
Then, let's sleep comfortably.
Senpai, please wake up.
Senpai, Senpai, wake up!
Senpai, it's terrible.
What the hell is this?
Why are you in the sea?
I'm sure it's a man-tongue.
I see.
That's why you gave me a hammock.
You bastard.
Uh-oh.
I'm saved.
But Senpai, you can't move your body.
What's wrong?
You have a strange feeling?
Senpai!
I'm saved.
HONDA!
Do something!
I'm saved.
But what are we going to do now?
That's our luggage.
Lucky!
Ready...
Go!
HONDA, be gentler.
Yes.
No, not there.
Not there.
Cheers!
Thanks!
Here we are, Phuket.
7 nights, 8 days.
Your wife must be happy about it.
Yes, she is.
It's been a fun vacation trip.
It's because I made Ryotsu an island.
But poor thing.
Are Ryo and his friends doing well?
Yes.
Oh?
That island, I'm sure, was...
...a bit bigger in the daytime.
When it's full of fish, it sinks more than half.
What?
Are the seniors all right?
That person is all right, I suppose.
I don't think they've told us anything.
Oh?
Did I forget to tell them?
Hmph.
That's a big excuse for threatening me.
I'll have to suffer a little.
That's bad.
What?
I'm sure they'll turn us upside down and do something.
Giggle.
Oh, there!
There!
It's a curse.
Buchi...
Koro.
Ro..
Su.
hallucinating...?
That really is bad.
A-A-A-A-A-A-A...
.
Damn it!
Attack! I'll tear down the entire cottage!
Yes sir!
The enemy is still sleeping. Let's go.
Yes sir.
It's a banana!
A goat!
You're following me, aren't you, senior?
Yes!
It's corn!
Attack!
You're following me, aren't you, senior?
Yes!
It's a lobster!
Attack!
Hey, Honda, isn't that strange?
Look!
It's moving away from the cottage.
It's true!
This is a trap.
A trap?
It's a trick the chief is thinking of.
It won't work!
Let's go, Honda!
It's a 100-yen coin!
A 100-yen coin!
Huh?
There are a lot of coins here and there!
I'm so lucky!
Senior, money is more like a trap!
I don't care about the trap!
It's a motorcycle handle!
It's a fork and a tank!
I'm so lucky!
It's a 10,000 yen machine!
I'm a genius!
You seriously got caught, Ryosuke!
Chief!
I didn't know you'd get caught in such a simple trap.
Hey, why haven't you changed?
Get out of there!
Silence!
You're company assigned to Cojima!
We'll certainly catch you four!
I want you to remember that!
What a poor thing.
But I feel sorry for him.
Well, if you cool your head a little,
I'll call you back for dinner.
What are you going to do next time you make something like this?
If this happens, it's war.
I'll definitely take the cottage apart!
I'll take the cottage apart!
It's looking good.
Ryouchi, something to deliver.
What's that? It's Omu.
What's this?
Hey, can you hear me?
It's the chief's voice.
It's a wire phone.
I can hear you.
Please.
Ryouchi, did you reflect on yourself?
Then, I'll cook you an afternoon meal with a barbecue.
It's your call.
It's okay.
Stop being so obstinate.
If you stop here tonight,
we can do it all over by rock-paper-scissors.
Please.
Thank you.
If you stand in front of me
and apologize for a painful incident,
I can think it over, but please.
What did you say?
Stop being so obnoxious!
What are you doing?
He's such a child.
It's such a hard day's work.
I'll be fine as long as I enjoy myself here.
Forget about him!
Damn you! You monte of a Chief!
Wanna attack us?
No, I'll just put up a guerrilla front!
Let's just protect Negura for now!
*de jazz music*
There is a perfect hole for digging.
*footsteps*
Ah it's so ... cold.....
What is this?
*footsteps*
Is it some kind of military factory or something?
Oh?
What's that?
It's a gold coin!
Yahoo!
"O-Hara"
Mr. Ohara! Mr. Ohara!
Hm?
A fax for you has arrived at the hotel.
It's from the director.
Mr. Ohara, you are not allowed to go on holiday.
"Actually, I found a fake coin today..."
"I found a fake coin..."
"and I was selling it at a store in the city of Gokubo..."
"I managed to arrest the criminal group."
"In the news of the murder, the fake coin factory..."
"is at the little island where you are going..."
"and the gold coin is floating on the lake."
What?
It's the island where Ryo is staying.
"The special mission officer, Dolphin Deka..."
"is going to arrive at the same place at 3:00."
"So, let's meet and find the factory..."
"and find the fake coin of the evidence building."
Right.
"Dolphin Deka?
A dolphin? I have a bad feeling about this.
There was a time when they said it was a sea turtle.
Could it be a dolphin?
It's possible.
The sea here is far. Why do they come here?
Isn't it an airplane like us?
But I can't feel any sign at all.
Oh, what?
It's a submarine.
Could it be that it's in such a place?
It looks like a small ship.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Oh, my.
"I love the sea and protect justice. Who called it? Who called it? Poseidon."
"I'll put it in my tank. I'll put it in my tank."
"I'm the captain of the Marine Police Force, Umino Dozaemon."
"The big and strong cut is trademarked. Dolphin, big and strong."
Chief, what's that?
"The big and strong cut is trademarked, Dolphin, big and strong."
Oh, you know the big and strong cut?
"The land is a great big one,"
"The sky is a moon big one,"
"And the sea is this Dolphin big one."
"This is the best three big ones in Japan."
Is he really a detective?
"I'm sorry to hear this, but you should see this."
"You are a warrior."
I'm sorry for that.
"I am a lawyer."
It's an illusion that starts only on hot days like today when crime increases.
Shouldn't it be an illusion as it is?
Hmm...
What is the water police force?
Good question.
It's not just one person, but five other people.
What? Five people?
I don't want to imagine it.
Hmm...
The Dolphin Squad, start!
It's a dolphin!
This is before I woke up.
I was a former dolphin teacher,
a glass craftsman, and a manga artist, and grew up.
Let's go home.
Kwa!
Even a spring can be made.
999,900 yen.
100,000,000 yen.
1, 999,969,999,
100,000,000!
Wow! There are 100,000,000 pieces too!
10,000,000 yen per piece x 100,000,000,
1, 10,100,000,000,
1, 100,000,000,000,
10,100,000,000,
10,000,000,000,
1,000,000,000 yen.
But, senior.
Senpai, what are you going to do with this gold coin?
Of course, I'm going to take it!
That's a crime, isn't it?
It's worse to leave it here.
But we're police officers.
I'm not going to be a cop.
I'm not going to quit.
I won't be able to ride on the white horse.
That's too bad.
With this much money,
you can buy a hundred motorcycles.
Eh?
I'll follow you, senpai!
I see!
Alright!
I'll buy this gold coin and make a Harlem!
Yes!
Eh?
Huh?
Who is it?
What is it?
Is it a chimpanzee?
But it seems like it's angry.
It seems like it's going to leave this place as its own.
It seems like it's asking me to get out of here.
You're so cheeky, even though you're a chimpanzee!
This gold coin is mine!
I'm going to get out!
Ouch!
You bastard!
There's a gold and silver factory on that island, huh?
Yes.
Probably.
Good!
Let's claim the gold with the
It's a little...
Good!
Could you wait a little longer?
Why?
Actually, a fool who said farewell to a fight...
No, a subordinate of mine is hiding in that island.
Then leave it to me.
Masukaho!
I-I'll try to persuade him somehow, so please wait until then.
All right.
Please wait a little longer.
Masukaho!
Ryotsu!
What are you doing here, sir?
Ryotsu, I'm sorry.
You can give me a piece of cotton.
I can do anything with my bare hands, so please come home.
You're quite different from what you are now.
Maybe...
I've already found out about the gold.
You don't need to do anything else.
The chief's naked body is also disgusting, so it's fine.
Look, Ryotsu.
If you leave that island, I'll give you 10,000 yen.
How about that?
I don't need that kind of money.
It's strange that you're giving me 10,000 yen.
I think you've already found the gold.
I'm sure I have.
It's a big trouble.
Ryotsu, that gold...
Gold?
You knew about it, didn't you?
I don't have any gold.
You're not going to give me any gold!
You do it, too!
Yes, sir!
I won't give you any gold, or I'll become the chief!
Got it!
I'm going to prepare for their counterattack.
Yes, sir!
They're so pitiful.
No one's here.
Now it's my turn.
Hurry up!
We have to protect the gold!
I'm ready!
I'm the opponent this time!
Yeah, you're here already.
Huh?
What? There's no one here.
That's strange.
Huh?
Whoa!
It's a submarine!
Oh.
It's pretty small.
It's a Plamo, right?
You're the one who called me a "lion"?
That's right! Who are you to call me that?
I love you and protect justice.
Who called you?
Who called you, Poseidon?
I'm going to put you in my tank!
I'm the captain of the Marine Corps, Umino Dozaemon.
The small one is the trademark of a Dolphin!
The factory's too long.
The proud one...
No, no, no...
You have to stand...
You have to...
I will protect you!
You won't get away with this!
Dolphin time!
What a dolphin!
It's no real dolphin.
Wow!
Yow-yow-yow...
No, that's not what I meant!
Yes sir!
What kind of game are you going to show us this time?
It's a grenade!
No!
It's no use running away!
It's a missile!
If it's a dolphin, then it's a chimpanzee!
It's strange.
Why is it exploding?
Pull it! Pull it more!
Go!
Run!
The enemy is also a missile!
Retreat!
No!
Ginga, you can't be hit!
What kind of enemy is there?
Ryo-chan and Mr. Honda are just two.
That's impossible.
I saw 50, no, 100 people.
No way.
It's not a coincidence.
Ryo-chan...
No.
Enough!
We won't leave without you!
Then let's ask for support.
Support?
!
6 years later
We're in a big trouble.
What's the matter?
Is something up here?
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
While you are attacking, I will land and conquer the island.
Very well.
I don't know if it's a drift or a dolphin, but it's not a big deal.
But someone else is attacking us.
Don't worry. Don't worry. Leave it to me.
It's the American Harrier.
The American Harrier
Are you going to fight the army this time?
You bastard!
Alright! Not yet!
Now, Honda!
Not yet!
I won't let you get away with this!
If you steal this, you'll get this.
I've made the plumber, but how can I control it?
You bastard!
Take this!
I won't let you get away with this!
Look at my skills that I've trained at the game center yesterday!
Tenshi!
This is bad.
Captain!
What's going on?
I've figured out a lot of tricks.
I've found the enemy aircraft carrier!
It's not easy to splash two planes in a blink of an eye.
Captain! The Harrier that was taken by the enemy is coming!
Ready for Arafx and C Sparrow!
Fire!
Come on! The round's about to hit the coast!
Did you see that?
Don't get close!
communion!
It's too..
What is it?
Berserker!
The mission went to failure.
Where is the escape device?
Where is it?
It's here.
What?!
I'm coming.
Alright, I'm landing.
You're stuck in a swamp, you idiot!
That's right, you're an idiot!
You're going to get a free bucket!
You're going to get my bucket!
I'm going to get your bucket!
Ouch!
Damn you!
Oh!
A small object is approaching in the abyss.
Achoo!
What is it, a roundabout!!
I'll attack immediately, but first you should pass through here, give me a hand!
If you're going to resist that much, then...
Just give it up!
This gap!
Look, it's more of a fire than that.
What?
Press the ignition button.
This?
Yes.
What did you press?
As you said, the ignition.
It's the fishing button.
You've never even hit me, have you?
Sorry, sorry.
It's flooded.
It's too much.
Ugen, speed up.
It's the fishing rod.
What?
This is...
Splendid.
It's a great shot.
We're in danger!
We've sunk the aircraft carrier.
This is terrible.
The US Navy won't keep quiet about this.
Exit 182
We're a big way on the front of the ship!
What are your thoughts?
It's all right.
Let's hear from him.
I'm stuck again!
Senpai!
That's a good book! Give it to me!
That's not all! Look at that!
Huh?
What's with that big gun?
The Island
The origin of the island is gone.
Ryo-chan must have fallen on the southern island.
Ryo-chan...
Oh, look at that!
Oh! Mr. Honda and Dolphin Deka!
Amazing! They're alive!
Where's Ryo-chan?
Ryo-chan? Ryo-chan is alive too!
What?
If you disappear, you'll be a burden to the world.
I'm sorry.
Ryo-chan,
they're asking you to pay for the fighter that was blown up by the sinking aircraft carrier.
What did you say?
You'll have to pay for the hotel's cost.
I don't know.
You're also responsible for asking the Navy for support.
No way.
I know.
You just have to pay.
Pay?
You're going to pay?
Where did you get that money?
There's a gold coin worth 1 billion yen here.
I'll pay you with this.
This coin is fake.
You're making fun of me again.
I'm not lying. This is real.
If you compare it, you'll see.
Oh! The Queen Elizabeth is red-faced!
I can't help it.
I'll take care of it myself.
Yeah.
I haven't gotten tired.
I couldn't sleep well.
I became a flying giant.
Ryo-chan and Honda-san,
I wonder when they'll be able to come home.
Stop it.
My head starts to hurt.
Damn it.
Why do I have to do this when I'm abroad?
Mr. Ryotsu,
we need to motivate him.
Like that guy.
Wolf,
Luffy!
Next up is a big jump!
Hey, Ryotsu-san, I don't think we can pay the debt back anytime soon.
I know!
Done!
What am I doing?
I hate traveling abroad!
♫ On sleepless nights ♫
♫ Invited by the wind ♫
♫ The rose is blooming ♫
♫ The moon I look up at ♫
♫ Somehow resembles her ♫
♫ People say that I'm a woman who can't fall in love ♫
♫ But ♫
♫ I want to do it ♫
♫ I have so many things to do ♫
♫ I want to ♫
♫ Ride through the vast desert on a motorcycle ♫
♫ I want to be freer than a bird ♫
♫ With the speed of a telescope ♫
♫ I change into a lady's dream ♫
♫ The heart of a loved one ♫
♫ "I'm sorry" ♫
♫ Wait for me to tell you ♫
♫ The future of Panorama ♫
♫ Rises in brightness ♫
♫ I know that ♫
♫ "I'm sorry" ♫
♫ Wait for me to tell you ♫
♫ "Wait for me to tell you ♪"
Thanks for watching!!
I'll be waiting for you!