Mamma Mia!
When you watch TV take a bright room and look away.
Come to me if you're penniless.
I'm not either but I'm worried.
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen to them
Come to me, you jobless man
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red clouds are burning
The red clouds are burning
I wonder what will happen to them
You know it, don't you?
If you know it, then keep quiet and follow me!
Rakugaku!
KASUKE!
Right!
TOT LOL
Hit Subscribe!
Hm?
This stain...
Looks like something?
What is it?
Wait...
Eh...
You put it here.
Here...
Called...
This...
You put it here...
Called...
It became like this
Nyanygyonyonyonyonyonyonyonyonyonyony...
Nyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyany...
Nyanyanyanyanyanyan...
Nyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyanyany...
And this, and this...
and this...
Ah! It's Chief Ohara's little beard!
You noisy old man!
You've been making fun of me in front of the subordinates all this time!
Geez, you're just like any other child!
Ryo-tsu!
Why don't you act with a sense of responsibility and awareness in the position of the chief of the police?
You can't get married in that situation!
Damn it! I'm getting dizzy just thinking about it!
I'll do it like this!
Oh! You've been playing a prank on me!
Hehehe! You're so annoying!
No, Ryo-chan! What are you drawing?
Huh?
Ah!
Oh, no! What am I doing?!
Ryo-chan, you have to erase it properly!
Eh?
Ehhh...
Now that I think about it, I drew it with oil-based magic!
I'm sure there was an oil-based cleaner somewhere.
Thanks.
Be careful!
Ah! Finally, this day has come!
Be quiet! Why are you getting excited by yourself?
Ryo-chan!
That person was the 9,999th person I guided on my way!
Huh?
Actually...
The first job I did when I came to this police station was a guide!
That's why I took the number of people I guided every day to the corner of the road!
See!
Huh?
Did you draw this letter?
I've been wondering what it was for a long time, but now the mystery has been solved!
Oh, that's not it!
Hey, Ryo-chan! Listen to me until the end!
The person I drew just now was the 9,999th person!
That means...
It's magic number one, Ryo-san!
Magic number one?
That means I've reached 10,000 today!
Look at this, Ryo-san!
What's that?
It's a mini-sand ball I made myself.
I made it last night at night...
I'll have the 10,000th person draw this.
This is a souvenir for my heart.
Are you a junior high school student?
Then lend it to me!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
I'll pull it for you.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Let me break it!
I'll have the 10,000th person draw it!
Lend me your hand!
*Sneeze*
Stop it, Ryo-san!
If you don't break it, I'll tickle you more!
*Sneeze*
Stop it! Stop it!
What are you doing?
*Sneeze*
Ryo-san, help me! Help me!
You're a big guy.
*Sneeze*
I'm sorry for making a crumpled shoe.
Ryo-san!
If someone comes to the street,
I'll be the guide!
If it's a gas station,
it's located at the second signal.
Thank you!
*Scream*
Ouch!
*Sneeze*
My 10,000th person is gone.
What's that?
It's cute, isn't it?
*Scream*
Stop it, Reiko-san!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Anyway, I'll be the next guide.
And don't try to break my mini-caterpillar!
That's all!
Don't be so angry over that.
*Sneeze*
Huh? What was I trying to do just now?
Be quiet, will you?
*Sneeze*
*Meow*
Oh, no!
I've never heard of a cat's death.
*Meow*
I wonder when he was out.
I didn't notice at all.
Poor thing.
He's so fat.
I think he's hungry.
He's too fat.
He should go on a diet.
He had some milk, didn't he?
*Kiss*
I don't think Reiko is going to buy anything here.
If you're feeling better, you should find a buyer.
Ryo-chan!
*Sneeze*
Did you call me?
You're so manly!
Of course!
Don't you deny my gender!
You haven't folded your bed sheet yet!
This isn't your room!
*Sneeze*
Poor thing.
You're suffering.
*Sneeze*
I'm sorry.
Once you're done, clean up the trash.
You should separate the trash that burns from the trash that doesn't.
Okay?
I know.
I'll give you some milk now.
*Sneeze*
Who do you think I am?
If you separate the trash, what will come out of me?
*Sneeze*
You're so hungry.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
I'll be back in a minute.
Chief?
What?
Ouch!
What's wrong, Chief?
Chief Ohara is having a stomachache.
What?
Oh, no!
*Sneeze*
I forgot to erase the drawing!
Oh, no!
Don't scare me, Ryo-chan!
What's wrong?
I'll tell you.
That cat looks strange.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to give you milk.
*Sneeze*
What a mess!
What?
What's going on?
This is Kameari Park Expo!
*Sneeze*
Oh, my, my, my.
Hey, Kien, is that you?
Hm?
A prayer room?
Okay.
*Sneeze*
Oh, no.
No, it's not going to stick anymore. What should I do?
- It's not my phone. - No, it's not.
I see. Nakagawa, can you lower the chair a little?
Yes.
Thank you.
Why did you get so surprised, Chief?
Oh, yesterday...
I was just trying to find a way to put the bonsai in the garden.
And I was so surprised.
It wasn't a heavy pot, you know.
Are you okay?
That must be a lot of things.
Yes.
Nakagawa, can I have a cup of tea?
I can't just sit here like this forever.
Oh, right.
Chief, why don't you take a break in the back room?
Right? Let's do that.
Oh, right.
Here. Take your time.
Oh, no! It looks like she's pregnant!
What?
Excuse me. My hand slipped.
Would you like some tea?
Please.
Pregnant? Whose child is that?
Well, that's...
You don't know?
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch.
Chief, it's not Reiko who's pregnant.
It's a cat. A cat.
A cat?
That cat?
She was lying down in front of the exit.
Oh, poor thing.
That's why I want to let her give birth in this room at least.
I see. Ryozu, please lower the chair.
Huh? But, Chief...
No, today I have only one day break for boys.
Lower the chairs, Ryozu.
Uh... Okay...
Thank you, Chief.
I'm sorry.
There's something I'd like you to look at.
Um, which one was it?
Um...
It looks like someone is here.
That's it. Don't worry about us.
Hey, you with your hands free!
Yes?
Yes, sir!
What's wrong?
Is there a problem with this file?
That's the biggest problem.
The second corner is on the left.
The next corner is on the right.
You'll find out soon.
Thank you very much.
My number 10,000!
The cat will be surprised, so be quiet!
I'm sorry.
Please, sir.
Thank you.
What's the number 10,000?
It's the number of people I've guided since I worked here.
Amazing!
Did you guide the 10,000 citizens?
Only one of us is 10,000.
As long as there's a serious officer like you,
Katsushika's safety is safe.
I'm sorry I didn't know.
He's doing it on his own.
There's no need to apologize.
That's right.
I'm just thinking on my own.
Next time, I'll let you know.
Thank you.
Ryotsu, you're always looking at the bookshelf.
I'll have you show me this file again.
Is that so?
Then, how about this?
Thank you.
My black eye can't help you.
I thought I'd never borrow your help.
I don't want to, sir.
Please say anything.
It's so wet.
There it is.
Please let me stay here for a while until I get a call.
I'll wait here to get a call as soon as possible.
Please rest assured, sir.
Really?
Oh, I see.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
What am I supposed to do?
Summoning Katsushika
Kuromatsu.
You seem to be well chosen, sir.
Well...
Can you tell?
I know my father.
He's the president of the bonsai association.
There is a person who works as a board member of the forestry association.
I've heard of his hard work in growing vegetables.
It is not easy to raise such a branch.
Yes. It took me 10 years to raise it all the way here.
10 years? Ryo-san, the picture of the bonsai that the chief grew.
Oh, what a good branch.
You don't know what a branch is.
You're thinking that bonsai is something that old people do when they have free time.
I usually say it here, but I'm a little weak here.
I'm going to do it carefully.
I'm not even going to do it.
Since I saw the bonsai at the chief's house, I've been thinking that I want to make bonsai my hobby.
I see.
Senpai is good at small work, and he may be good at it.
Yesterday.
If only I could fix the short part of the tree.
Shut up!
Actually, I ordered this for the bonsai auction today.
Is that so?
My wife went to the venue on my behalf.
As soon as I get the result, I'll contact you.
Then the phone the chief is waiting for is from his wife.
From his wife?
Yeah.
I'm kind of nervous.
Come to think of it, these 10 years have been a battle against myself.
This bonsai is a work like my own statue.
When I think that the statue is now being evaluated by others,
whether I stand or not,
Ouch!
Are you all right?
Chief.
You always say, "Kaho, sleep."
If you can't go to the venue, you should just sleep at home.
If it's a phone call, it's the same no matter where you answer it.
It's hard to wait at home alone.
I understand how you feel.
You feel like you're back to the entrance exam students, don't you?
That's right.
It's a bad thing.
If I'm here, I'll be confused about something.
When the chief sits here as it is,
I have to do something about the graffiti on the wall.
But I can't do anything on my own.
I need backup.
I can't be a monk.
I can't be a wild snake and be found out by the chief.
Then I have no choice but to hug Nakagawa.
What is it, senpai?
What's wrong?
Yeah.
There's a cardboard box on the locker.
Take that out.
Cleaning detergent?
Are you going to clean it?
Senpai!
What are you writing?
I'll tell you more about this later.
I want to erase this so that the chief won't notice.
Please help me.
That's impossible.
Just take the box on the locker.
Please.
I'll just take it.
What are you doing?
While waiting for the wife to contact me,
I'll ask the chief if there's anything you can do to keep me from getting bored.
Ryotsu.
You...
Now!
Y... Y...
Hey, Ttaki!
Z... Zoot!
Ahhhhh!
Why the...
Why the bat!
No, we don't have much time!
We will keep our eyes on them until the conclusion.
What?
Zoot!
T... T... Zoot!
Hm, hm.
I apologize for the mess.
This is what a monk should do.
But it's too late to regret now.
That's right.
This is it.
Ah!
Chief! I have a good thing.
Let's do a show of martial arts.
But you're working, aren't you?
There are monks and Nakagawa.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's not like I'm going anywhere.
Isn't it good to do it once in a while?
Let's do it, Chief.
I see.
I'm not sure about this.
Let's do it.
I'll go first.
Ah.
I see.
It's your turn, Ryotsu.
Before I come here,
Before I knew it, I had the actress shake hands with Sayuri Yoshikawa.
So I don't want to touch anyone else today.
What's up with you all of a sudden?
Is that why you've been acting suspicious?
But it's Sayuri Yoshikawa.
I don't see her very often.
I wanted to see her too.
I was shooting near the Katsushika library.
I've been a fan of yours for a long time, so I had you shake hands with me.
You're a junior high school student, huh?
I've never been told by you.
I'm kind of relieved to hear what Nakagawa-kun has to say.
That's right.
Nakagawa, who seems to be completely innocent, has a personality like everyone else.
Please don't tease me.
Hey, everyone.
What?
I was born.
Oh, I see.
You're so tiny.
You're so cute.
Good job.
No, I'm nothing.
It was all done by my mother cat alone.
I was just watching by her side.
This skin...
The oil-based cleaner...
This one, huh?
It's too light.
Excuse me!
Um, Michio...
Terai, you have a guest!
Huh?
The 10,000th one!
You've finally reached your goal, Terai-san.
What's that?
It's really a huge trip!
This is a big trip.
Uh...
What?
What a great trip.
I've been here for over a year and a half, but it's all for nothing!
You said it had aENCe!
It's just a 5-minute trip!
Or even one and a half have a 10,000th one?
It's a real one!
You're only worth it.
Oh, come on!
Your 10,000th one is now 10,000th one!
Can you tell me what it's worth with this trip?
What do you need?
Shall we take a walk here at Ijimaki?
I'll take a walk around Ijimaki-tee!
Let's walk!
There's only one left.
Let's just send the complicated case and wait for the next one.
That's right.
Hey, Terai!
What is it, Ryo-san?
Where is the nearest convenience store around here?
If that's the case, it's near the new Colomart that opened last week.
It's about 200 meters from here, and to the left...
Thank you!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
I just wanted you to be honest with me from the beginning.
I don't want to be the first person to get 10,000!
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Please wait a moment.
It's me, your wife.
I see.
Hello? It's me.
Yes.
I see.
I understand.
What's the result, Chief?
It seems she was in second place.
She's the runner-up!
Isn't that amazing, Chief?
Congratulations!
What are you talking about?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
I won't let you shake hands with me today.
No, Chief.
Congratulations.
You're giving an indirect hand shake with Sayuri Yoshikawa, aren't you?
OK. I'll show you what's done today.
Is there something wrong with Sayuri Yoshikawa?
She's seen you again, Ryo-san.
Oh, no.
I don't want to, you'll be embarrassed, Chief.
I can't show that anymore.
You were perfect for me today, and you did a great job.
Thank you.
Hey, Chief, what's wrong?
You're not like a Chief, please stop.
I've never felt as strongly about your presence as today.
Thank you.
You're the only one who can draw something like this!
I thought you were stuck up all night today, so I hid this.
No, Ryo-chan, you didn't turn off the alarm this morning, did you?
Chief, there are many reasons for this!
You idiot!
What happened to Gikkuri-goshi, Chief?
Fourth
Thank you, Chief.
After the rain, I looked back at someone calling me, and I was walking.
I knew.
It was my parents, who were killed in that rain while I was walking.
I'm sure it's the same being important that...
I walked only to a far place
Everyone was a child once
But everyone has forgotten
A politician with a great face
And a blue old lady above
Turn around and look at that corner
I'll see you all
Let's go!
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
Speaking of Grandma's Harajuku, it's Sugamo
But Grandpa has nothing
There is nothing there
I thought
I'll make Kameari Grandma's Harajuku
And make a town
It's a great plan
Next time, Ryotsu Town renovation plan
Please look forward to it
There is a wall
There must be a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!