"Summer is here again this year!"
Nagisa-de
Puri puri puri puri puri puri puri puri
Minami Kaze ni Horiu
Nagisa-de
Purupuru
Purupuri
A Newcomer From the Sky
It's a nice day.
Something good is going to happen on a day like this.
It's quiet.
It's too quiet.
That means...
You're late again!
Ryo- Ryo- Ryo-tsu is working!
He's been like this since two hours before he came to work.
We were just talking about it, thinking it might rain.
I'm very moved right now.
I've been a policeman for 30 years, and I've never been this happy!
Sir, you don't have to be so moved.
Ryo-tsu finally woke up to work.
The hardships he's gone through have been rewarded.
All right!
You're great, Ryo-tsu!
I knew you'd do it someday!
By the way, what documents were you writing?
What do you mean, I don't want to!
Did you forget, sir?
Didn't you say it yesterday?
You said you'd submit the remaining death certificate.
Death certificate?
I wrote it all down.
My hands are frozen.
You idiot!
Ryo-tsu!
You're a...
Sir, are you all right?
I'm sorry. I need to go to the bathroom.
Yes, sir.
You drank too much, sir.
You're old enough. You need to take it easy.
It's dangerous.
What? It's all your fault!
Sir, calm down.
If you get too angry, you'll get a broken heart.
Huh!
I can't believe I had such a bad subordinate.
I have no choice but to give up.
I remembered it as a subordinate.
Is Nakagawa still here?
Mr. Nakagawa?
He's a new employee who's coming to this station today.
What kind of person is he?
Oh, he's pretty handsome.
He stayed in New York until he was 16.
I see.
So he has a job in the same place as Riko.
Yes.
He has a driver's license, a boat and an airplane license.
And he's a sports and a language expert.
He's a great shooter.
Who is this Nakagawa?
He's the head of the Nakagawa family.
The Nakagawa family?
Is that the Nakagawa family that has five fingers in the world?
Is that Nakagawa's fortune?
Yes.
What's that Nakagawa something?
It's a fortune-telling shop.
It's not a fortune-telling shop.
It's a conch.
What's that? A conch shop?
Oh.
No, it's not.
Riko.
Yes?
Don't talk to that idiot.
He'll hurt his stomach like me.
Yes.
Hmm.
You're such a hard-working police officer.
You don't have a job.
I'll say goodbye to you soon.
Then, Ryotsu.
So don't do that.
You must instruct Nakagawa.
Now, now.
How about that?
Isn't it great?
The combat rescue type of the American Black Hawk.
Is it?
I'm so tired.
So that's what you were doing yesterday, skipping work?
Well, well, if you find out, you'll be in big trouble.
Well...
Hm?
That's strange.
What's with that slouch?
What's with that locker?
Oh, right! I remember!
When did you get that?
What's with that?
You didn't know?
He's completely turned the exhaust into a private one.
Good, good.
There!
Good boy!
Anyway, you sure made a lot of stuff.
I wish I could use this passion for work at least a little bit.
You're always using it, aren't you?
Yeah!
Sorry, sorry.
Jo-chan!
Ryo?
What's going on?
Are you all right, Ryo?
I thought you were going to die.
Oh, by the way, where's Ellie?
Ellie?
She flew out.
Wow!
Oh, we got three hundred thousand yen!
I'll pay her when we lose the money.
I'm not kidding.
The bad thing is you, right?
Shit, I'm so screwed...
Wow, it's Ellie.
It's the best셨!
She brought her friends over!
I'm out of breath!
Give me that gun!
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Wh- what's going on?
The train is coming this way!
Wh- what?
What's that?
Shiro, what the hell is that?
It's a bomb!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-...
Ya-ho!
Everyone, I'm late.
I've been working at the power station from today.
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa.
Nice to meet you.
You!
You broke my helicopter!
Huh?
It's a Walther MPL submachine gun!
You know what? I'm so happy.
By the way, this is the gun.
Oh! It's the same gun as the Dirty Harry!
That movie was awesome!
Oh, if you don't mind, can I apologize for breaking the helicopter?
Really? That's boring!
No, we still have a lot of them.
Do you want to come see them next time?
Yeah, I'm coming!
You idiot!
What are you thinking about?
I'm calling for help!
So, you can't take this either?
Of course not.
Tellai, go get it.
Yes, sir!
I'm getting a little too excited.
I'm going to the office, so you can take care of it, Eiko.
You sure have a good eye.
My name is Ryo. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryo.
Oh, you're the super famous Ryochi from the senior department.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so happy to have two of you.
You're the one that's happy.
Hehehe.
Huh?
That helicopter is for the next world?
Hmm...
You're rich, despite being a konnyaku shop.
A konnyaku shop?
Hehehe.
Anyway, why did you become a police officer, Nakagawa-san?
Well...
I've lived in New York for many years, where crime is common.
I've always been a police officer who fights for the people's lives.
Anyway, you're wearing a fancy uniform.
Huh?
I see.
I think it's more of a problem than a gun.
Really?
Japanese police uniforms are not that good.
I was an order maid in Germany.
I see.
I think it was about 1 million yen.
Wow!
1 million yen!
I don't think I can afford such a cheap uniform!
I don't think you can afford such a cheap uniform!
Don't you agree?
Yes.
But, you know...
I haven't been to the police station recently, but I've been told to forgive such a uniform.
Well, I was told I shouldn't wear it.
But I changed my clothes in the helicopter.
I'll do it to you.
I'm sure you must be upset.
I'm gonna go check on the patrol.
Ryo, tell Nakagawa-san about this.
Have a nice trip!
So, what should I do?
I'll teach you.
Ryo, you are the instructor, right?
I'm going to patrol too!
Damn it...
Well, I...
Well, you can just stand there and guide the way.
Yes sir!
Oh, are you the man?
Yes, I am.
Oh, I see. I'd like to ask you about the way.
Yes, I'd love to.
Senpai, wake up.
What's wrong? I slept well.
I was asked about the way, but I don't know much about this area.
Huh?
What?
Show me the map and let me look for it.
That's the old man who came back to Japan after 50 years and he said he doesn't know where this place is.
I can't help it.
So, where do you want to go?
The cafeteria.
What?
I forgot the name of the place, but I have a clue.
Huh?
It's this kind of place.
Oh.
That's a bad drawing. Did you draw it?
When I was a student. It's been over 50 years.
What? 50 years?
So, where is the place?
It's under Tokyo.
That's all?
Yes.
No, no.
It's a big city. You won't understand.
Give up.
That's not good.
It's my first job.
Do whatever you want.
If I had looked for it, I would have thanked you.
Why didn't you say that first?
Let's talk about the details later.
Hey, Nakagawa.
Order coffee and cake at the cafe.
What?
Go now.
Yes.
I see.
I went to the cafe a few times when I was a student of art school.
Art school?
Yes. It's Tokyo Art University.
It was a lunch break, so it was always crowded.
So, you are next to the art university.
Yes. I thought it was about 15 minutes walk.
The art university is the upper neighborhood.
Hmm.
Hmm?
If you like, you can have this.
Sorry.
Okay.
Let's look for it around YANAKA NEZU.
Um.
Yes?
I wonder if we can find it in 2 hours.
It's about 20 to 30 minutes by car.
It will be fine.
Actually, it's Narita's first flight at 1 o'clock.
I have to go back to Paris.
Hmm.
It's about an hour by express.
It will be fine.
Narita, get a taxi.
Then, I'll call you with my car.
Yes, it's me.
Please bring your car to the exit immediately.
Hmm.
Um.
How about mine?
No, thanks.
Here it is.
Oh!
Ferrari F40!
Here you are.
Thank you for waiting.
But this is for two people.
It has been modified for four people.
It's okay.
Please get in.
Hmm.
Reiko.
You came back to a good place.
Ryo-chan.
Help me.
I'm begging you.
Huh?
See you.
Ah!
I think I saw someone now...
Hmm.
Phew.
I wish I had more time.
Hey,中川!
Turn there.
I can't.
The exit is a single lane.
You undermine the company.
I don't want to make the wish of an old man.
Gosh!
I'm going back.
It will be fine.
No.
I got it.
Senpai,
I'm going back.
I got it.
What are you talking about?
It's not that far from here!
What?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Our...
Don't fool me!
You don't know, don't you?
Ah! Ryotsu Kankichi!
He's going to pass at one stroke!
How nice. He got on that super-bubbly car like...
He's not the time to observe!
It's the time to arrest!
What?
Stop the Ferrari in front!
What should we do, Senpai?
When the fight is in its midst, come on!
Show them the power of the Ferrari!
Yes, sir!
That was too fast!
That's no use, Kanchi!
If anything happens, I'll make sure to get you out of there!
That's right!
Right corner, to the right!
The next street, to the left!
But I can see why the alley is so crowded.
I've been playing around here since I was a kid.
It's like a garden.
No matter how close we are, we can't go any further.
Idiot! It's your first job, right?
A police officer is one who is always ready to do anything,
no matter what happens.
Senpai...
I was wrong.
All right!
Hey, hey, hey!
It's getting faster and faster!
Don't worry!
I can get through!
I've been here before, too.
With a bicycle.
Come on!
You're the best, Senpai!
This place...
Can you stop it for a second?
I miss it.
I've lived in Paris for decades,
but I often think of Japan.
That was when I was a student at an art school.
I was surrounded by good friends,
drawing all day long.
Ueno is a forest of art.
I used to walk to and from art museums every day
and exchange art theories with my friends.
At that time, I fell in love with the daughter of the cafeteria
who took me with my friends.
It was really my first love.
That's the cafeteria in that picture, isn't it?
When was that?
I think it was near graduation.
It was when I fell asleep in the cold.
She came to the cafeteria,
and she took care of me.
I was in a good mood,
and I thought I should thank her.
At that time, I was poor,
and I didn't have the money to give her a nice present.
I thought about it,
and I drew her portrait.
And I gave her the painting.
I think it was the best.
The happy face of that daughter at that time
is still burning in my eyes.
And what about that daughter?
At the same time as graduation,
I went to Paris to study.
I didn't say I liked her.
It's a long time ago.
Grandpa!
You shouldn't get into trouble.
You have one hour left.
Let's find the cafeteria.
Yeah.
I have one hour left.
Do you remember the scenery around here?
Hmm?
It's 50 years ago,
so it's a lot different.
I have one hour left.
I'm not going to let you go.
I can't take it anymore.
Memories are memories.
I'll take them home.
I have 10 minutes left.
I won't give up!
I can't give up!
I can't find one or two things.
I have to be a policeman!
Damn it!
I've been thinking about this for 50 years.
First love.
I wanted to see you.
It's okay.
This is also fate.
That tree...
I got it!
Look at this shop.
It's still in the picture.
It's changed a lot.
Let's go see the first love.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong, old man?
That woman is married and has a family.
It's a sudden visit.
What are you talking about?
Get in.
But...
If you don't open it, I'll open it.
Come on.
Open it.
Hurry up and open it, old man!
Ms. Misumi.
Mr. Taki.
It's Mr. Taki, right?
Yes.
Long time no see.
Oh, really.
Mr. Taki.
That picture is still in the shop.
What?
You took good care of it.
This picture is my treasure.
Thank you, Ms. Misumi.
Senior, look.
That happy face.
Yes.
Our police officers are working hard for the people's smiles.
Police officers have a wonderful job.
By the way, how much will you give me as a reward?
Senior.
Thanks to you, I have a good memory.
Please accept this as a reward.
Thank you.
Well, I'll take care of it.
Be careful.
Goodbye.
Let's go home.
What?
Are you going to go again?
I'm not happy and there is nothing.
I don't want a picture like this.
Hey, you.
What?
I'll do this picture.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Come on.
Taki, Jotaro.
Is it just a Ferrari that's broken?
It's nothing.
I still have a car that's rotting.
Are you that rich?
Well, the asset is about 400 trillion yen.
400 trillion yen?
Nakagawa, let's get along.
Ryo, it's hard.
There was an old man on the Ferrari, right?
Yes, that old man.
That's ridiculous.
He was a world-famous painter.
Is he that famous?
A picture costs at least 100 million yen.
100 million yen?
I won!
Hey, Ryo!
I'll ask you a lot of questions.
My 100 million yen!
Hey, Ryo!
I'll ask you a lot of questions.
I'm there, too!
...
Good.
You can't go.
Then go.
Good luck.
Bye.
"Let's smile anytime"
Let's smile anytime
Even if something terrible happens
Please smile cutely
It's okay to go out with a face that doesn't matter
Hey, please smile
You're not bad
You're in the same mood as before
Smile anytime
A woman who is too serious is not beautiful
You should smile right away
If you're not a child