Let's Go Home
♪ When you're watching TV, ♪
♪ light your room and try to see three different sides. ♪
♪ I look at the sunlight, floating in the middle ♪
I was looking for a good day to sleep
When I kicked the love stone, it flew into my shoes
I wonder if it's a joke
I was laughed at as it was
Even if I try to cheer up, I have a bad luck
I have a bad luck
The city is so gentle
From the water tank of the Tungari-boshi
To the taishakuten
The sun goes down
Tomorrow will end like this
I lost my happiness again
I realized it
Because I'm an idiot
This is Komachi
Inside
Right here
I'm sorry
Come on
My heart is about to burst
Go out
Come on
Come out
Jump
Oh, Komachi.
So that's why you're with the tough village farmer.
What?
I forgot!
He was with us, too!
You guys...
You're not that bad...
Huh?
What are you talking about, Dad?
Ryotsu-san, I'm a good daughter, but...
Please take care of Suenaga.
What?
That's a misunderstanding!
If everyone sees this photo,
my credit will drop so much!
W-What should I do?
Hey, look, everyone!
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
Look at this!
It's a two-shot of Komachi and Nakagawa-san!
What?
No way!
They're helping each other!
Wow!
Right?
Komachi, what's going on?
I took a picture of them when I went back home for the summer vacation.
What?
With Nakagawa-san?
Don't tell me...
Just the two of us?
Hmm...
Wow!
That's amazing!
There are so many two-shot photos with Nakagawa-san!
Komachi, normally when you go to your boyfriend's house,
it's a pretty good time, right?
What do you think?
Tell me!
It's not like that!
I heard that there was a meeting at your house.
So I wanted to ask Nakagawa-san to go.
Then did you summon him as your boyfriend?
No!
I'm so shocked!
That's what I'm saying!
It's so hard to be a girlfriend!
I'm so jealous!
I want to kill him!
It's so hard!
Well, I guess...
I'm calling the traffic police.
Hello, this is the traffic police.
Oh, Mom.
Yes, me.
What?
Are you going to Tokyo?
Oh, on Sunday, the day after tomorrow.
And then,
did you get along with that boyfriend?
That boyfriend?
Nakagawa-san?
Yes, that's right.
It's about Ryotsu-san.
Mom, don't misunderstand!
This is bad.
Everyone thinks it's about Nakagawa-san.
I can't even say the name of the city governor.
I talked to my dad about it.
He's a manly man and a good guy.
That's why you're not that close with him.
He's a man?
This is...
I'm sorry.
Now I'm sorry.
I said it's a bad ring.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy today.
I don't know.
I've only heard it by myself.
Is it good to be close with them?
I should go to sleep.
It's late.
I'm a good-for-nothing, so...
Wait! I'm here!
What are you doing, you primitive?
Sh-sh-sh...
I'm a stray dog!
Dogs are much better.
The number one thing you hate!
The number one thing you don't want to marry!
The number one thing you don't want to be in a relationship!
The number one thing you don't want to date!
The number one thing you don't want to be in a picture!
The number one thing you don't want to be in a relationship!
What did you come here for?
You're all playing with each other.
I came here to complain about this!
Don't do anything unnecessary!
I think that's...
When I went to Komachi's countryside...
What is it? What is it?
I see.
You're playing with a panorama.
Everything I see is clearly cut out.
If I'm not there, it looks like a trip between lovers.
Right?
I can't believe I'm with you now.
It has nothing to do with me.
There's no one who can help me with that newspaper article!
You're asking me to do something about it, aren't you?
Right?
It's a bad thing!
What?
I'm telling you that you can't do anything about it.
What's worse, you'll lose, and...
I'll erase this article and put a apology on it.
I'll put a apology on it and put a apology on it.
What?
If you don't like it, it's okay.
But my mouth is very light.
I understand. I understand.
I understand.
We'll be right there.
I said we understood, didn't I?
Then...
It's a secret.
You're so naive.
What?
A picture from the summer vacation in Komachi's countryside?
I have one.
You've seen one before, right, Senpai?
Yeah, I was going to cook some yakimashi for myself.
I was going to cook some yakimashi for myself.
You said you didn't need it at the time.
Here.
Hey, you changed your mind.
Oh, this is it.
Let's borrow it.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Did you make a mistake in the list of the hateful ones announced this month?
In first place, Sakonji Tatsunosuke will be the winner.
Why?
How could I?
I thought I could be at ease as long as Ryotsu was around.
Damn it! What's wrong with that woman?
I'm going to prepare for the upcoming Budō tournament and go to the mountains!
What's wrong with that woman? What's wrong with that woman?
I have Saori.
Saori.
Hey, Komachi, what's up?
That's right, that's right, there's no mistake in the list.
The original person was No. 1 straight away.
Huh? Really?
But it's fine.
If you're always together, there's no freshness.
But...
Hey, Komachi.
Why are you here? Again?
Shut up. I have something to do with you.
Hey, Komachi, you forgot your wallet.
Could you lend me about 30,000 yen?
What did you say?
You're so annoying! Go home! Go home!
I said you forgot your wallet.
Oh, right.
You said you were in love with Nakagawa.
What?
You went to your country with him alone,
and you introduced him to your parents, right?
With just the two of you.
Oh, my.
Oh, no.
Reiko got it from him.
I-I see.
30,000 yen is fine, right?
You're so smart.
I'm going home, then.
What? You said you could return it anytime?
I see. I'm sorry.
Hey!
What's going on?
You're not like Komachi.
I'm serious.
N-Nothing.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, Kenji.
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh, Ryo.
The minipato has taken over the parking space,
and the pato car can't be stopped.
It's a problem.
If you go to the lecture, you'll be beaten back.
Especially Komachi.
They're so violent.
I'm not afraid of that.
You're saying Ryo is all right?
Yeah.
Leave it all to me.
I can't do anything.
Oh, God of Rescue!
Please, Ryo!
Tell Tsuke and the others to stop the minipato.
Is that all?
Anything else you want to say to them?
We're finished with all the organizing.
Here we go.
N-No way!
Good, good, good.
This way.
What?
If I go to the public place,
is everyone free?
Yes.
I respect that, Ryo.
You said that you wanted to go along with it.
Well, maybe not.
I don't care.
Let me explain.
Oh, you're not that strong, are you, Komachi?
You're in love with Nakagawa, aren't you?
What are you talking about? It has nothing to do with you!
I wonder, Komachi.
I get it. I'll admit it.
Komachi, what are you talking about?
You have to be like that.
And you have to make sure the entire school is closed.
And you have to make sure Valentine's chocolate is fair.
Isn't that great?
That's great.
Huh?
You really understand, don't you, Komachi?
I think you'll do a good job from now on.
I'll be in your care.
Oh, my. The floor is dirty.
Hey, Komachi.
Oh, come on. Let's blow it clean.
Yeah, yeah. You're so thoughtful.
He's always getting in my way.
I'm going to be sick and tired of him from now on.
If this goes on, the primitive will be in trouble.
I have to do something about it.
What? Ryo said that?
That's really awful.
As soon as he heard it was a secret, he turned into a devil.
You can do whatever you want if you want to.
I'm in trouble. What should I do?
In other words, it would be really nice if you and K-chan had a two-shot picture.
But if Nakagawa finds out about this ...
It's okay.
I'll talk to K-chan and take a two-shot picture of you.
Really? Eiko?
That's great.
Leave it to me.
Even so, you didn't say you'd come with us.
K-chan has a friend from France.
I asked K-chan to show me around.
I told him that he should make a plan in his room.
I see. I thought about it.
That flower watch is very beautiful.
Let's take a picture.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Did you think you could fool me with such a little craft?
Reiko's strategy is very good.
Hmm. Would you like to stick together a little longer?
That would be better.
Really?
Something like this.
Then let's go.
Yes, cheese.
Oh?
I wonder if I just saw something.
Then let's take it in front of the dinosaurs.
Komachi-chan, a little more to the right.
Yes.
Then I'll take it.
Yes, cheese.
Is that Ryo-chan?
No way.
This is a haunted house.
It's Ryo-chan.
Komachi-chan, come here for a moment.
This is bad.
Ryo-chan is in the way.
Even in the pictures taken so far, Ryo-chan is reflected in them.
No way.
Is something wrong?
Did something happen?
Not at all.
No, it's nothing.
I'm wondering where we should go next.
In the past, Ryo-chan was the one who got in the way.
Let's go on the gondola, okay?
That sounds good.
Okay?
Okay, then.
Come on, Kei.
Hurry, hurry.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You're aware of it.
That's it.
You're going to be there now, too.
Why are you still running?
Is he staying there?
He's not going anywhere.
Just wait for it.
The kappa did it! Over there!
Reiko-san, it's the kappa!
Y-Yeah...
Ryo-chan's doing it.
If this happens...
What are you both in such a hurry for?
If this happens, it's a jet course!
I won't let you get in the way!
Don't think you can escape from me!
Hey, Reiko-san!
Oh, my...
Ow, ow, ow!
Damn it!
Looks like he's exhausted.
He'll be fine if you start running now.
Oh, no! Did I start already?
There's no way to get in the way!
Huh?
There!
Now that you've come this far, you're safe!
Just a little more.
Now!
Hey!
A-A senior is falling from the sky!
Oh, no!
Ryo-chan, don't get in the way!
I can't do that! Give me the camera!
No!
Give it to me, you idiot!
I won't!
I did it!
Now, look at me!
Ryo-chan!
Ow!
Shh!
Ryo-chan's gone!
Stay here!
Reiko, what's the matter?
I don't have to worry!
I...
Now, open!
Here, cheese!
Whoa!
Senior!
You scared me!
This is historia of your little smile!
Now, open!
I won't!
Ugh!
What about here?
Here, cheese!
So sweet!
Oh, I'm so annoyed!
Ah, a Puri-Kura!
I don't think Ryou-chan will get caught here.
I'll keep an eye on her, so hurry up!
Okay!
It's okay.
I can't see Ryou-chan.
Yay!
We finally got her.
What is this?
What's going on?
*Ryuu-chan is still there*
It's all Ryou-chan.
No way!
What do you think?
I thought it would be like that, so I made a plan in advance.
Oh, no!
What's going on?
Banji is a good kid.
Wait.
Maybe that hand...
If it turns out like this, it's a win or a loss.
*A
Ah, no!
The 500-yen coin...
What?
Where is it?
Wait!
Now!
Ken-chan!
Komachi-chan!
*K wobbling*
I did it.
Too bad. I won, Ryo-chan.
Now you're not going to be the one to complain about it!
Damn it! All the hard work I've put in!
Then, I'll take this.
No, it's fine. You can do it tomorrow morning.
I'll do it right away.
My dictionary doesn't have the word "lose" on it.
I'll take this.
Oh, oh, oh. This is it.
If there's a match, there's no way I can win.
You just came here, but where are you taking me?
Don't worry. Just follow me, Mom.
You're really good at misunderstanding.
I'll prove it to you.
Yes, it's done.
Now, Mom. If you look at this, you'll see for yourself.
See? You got it, right? My boyfriend is this guy.
If he's this guy, he's definitely Ryo-chan.
That's right. My boyfriend is Ryo-chan.
Mom, where are you looking?
There.
There, there.
Hey, Ryo-chan!
There he is!
Hey, he's here.
Hey, I'm Ryo-chan.
Hey, Ryo-chan!
Hey, you!
You!
Ah!
That's enough!
Kyo-chan switched the part where Kei-chan was reflected on the computer with herself.
I don't know why, but did you have to go that far?
Well, there are many things.
Please help me, mom!
You say that the more you fight, the closer you get.
It's not like that!
I won't forgive you!
If you say you won't forgive me, I will never forgive you!
Help me!
I won't!
You two are really good friends.
Oh, yeah.
You! You! You! You!
You're the only one I can see.
Oh, my mouth! My mouth!
I'm a plum blossom with my whole life!
I've been buried in the ground without eating a single bite.
I will go to Matsudai top and
the next episode, I will go to the cursed plum blossom!
Surprised and screaming
Hullo!
We're going to fight, and we're going to solve the problem.
We're going to get rid of it quickly.
I'm scared.
We're going to decide, and we're going to spark.
We're going to hit, and we're going to put it all together.
We're going to take action, and we're going to fly.
Power is the best thing.
If we all come together here,
It's like a dream.
The last energy.
Look at tomorrow.
Believe in yesterday.
If you draw the universe and stand on the ground,
The planet of the turtle will turn into a circle.
This is good, right?
There's no reason to be good.
Hey, don't do this!
I don't want to die.
This is the end of today's story.
Thank you for watching!