I'm so happy you're here.
Wait up, Reika!
Goodbye, Shunta.
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
Hoshi!
I've always liked you.
Ever since you were born.
You're so touching.
Mr. Honda, you're a big fan of girl manga, right?
She's the girl manga artist, Nana-chan, the sound girl.
Oh, by the way, you were in the same week as Sapphire, right?
Yeah, it's been three years since I started.
Wow, that's a long time.
Yeah, I remember.
I have a manuscript for next week.
Here it is.
What?
I always send it by fax, so I can keep the manuscript.
But you can't throw it away.
What? I don't have a manga of you.
I thought you quit.
What? I'm sending you a manuscript every week.
I'm sending you a manuscript every week.
I've never gotten it.
Oh, here it is.
What? A reading space?
The same treatment as an amateur.
Damn it.
By the way, I used to be four pieces of a 12-page work.
Are you meeting the director properly?
No, not for the past few years.
The contents and pages are free.
There's no such serial.
How much is the manuscript?
Hmm, I don't remember getting it recently.
Ah, by the way,
I've sent a pendant from the editorial department.
Senpai, here's the thing.
A present for everyone?
It's like a simple reader who likes to post.
I don't think he's a serial writer.
Ryusenshi, if you meet him next time, you'll get paid for free.
Hello.
Oh, Nana-chan.
Honda-san, did you wait?
Not at all.
I was listening to Senpai's interesting story.
Then we're going on a date.
What?
I'm just wasting my time.
Well, everyone.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Let's go!
Honda-san and Nana-chan are a perfect couple.
I'm so jealous that they're so close.
Honda and Otohime are the best couples that everyone envies.
But if something terrible happens to these two,
Otohime will be the one to blame.
In the end, no one knew how to stop him.
When you watch TV,
light the room to make it brighter,
and try to look out the window.
The next day
It's the same morning.
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
You know, right? You know, you know!
If you know, then quietly follow me!
The Great Collapse of Love
It looks like you've been caught red-handed!
He's still chasing after us!
No way!
Stop!
You monster!
I'm telling you to stop!
Do you think you can get away from this Honda of the future?
What? Honda of the future?
That legendary racer, Mr. Honda?
Sorry!
Did you catch him?
Yeah, perfect.
That legendary racer, Mr. Honda?
Today's super video is a scoop of the moment when the evil gang was arrested.
Please watch the powerful video.
This police officer is the number one driver of a car off-road.
He's the Honda Hayato of the Katsushika Prefecture.
Oh!
It's Honda!
You saw it on TV.
It was very cool.
No, I was embarrassed.
He's the one and only guy of the time.
What?!
Hey, never mind.
Let's do this.
I want you to take a picture with me.
Me first?
I'd like to.
I'd like to go first.
You two are popular.
Let's take a picture!
Let's do this.
"Katsushika-San"
Senpai, look at this!
What is this?
Everyone's sending letters and fax to Honda-san.
It seems that there are already a lot of emails to the "Katsushika-San" office.
The "Katsushika-San" office is also sending a sign to the "Katsushika-San" office.
You are a modern hero.
I'm not a hero.
This is Honda-kun's bike.
Is Honda-kun here?
I want to catch him.
I want to ride behind Honda-kun.
I want to ride too.
Honda-kun!
It's Honda-kun.
What should we do, Senpai?
If we go out now, we'll be in a panic.
What? I'm fine.
Why?
That's right. The power of the current female high school students is amazing.
I'm fine.
So why?
Think about it. The world only knows the face when Honda rides a motorcycle.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
G...
What?
You don't have the same image as me, do you?
Yes!
So you should go out of the way.
Look.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
It's Honda-kun!
The version of when he wasn't on a motorcycle.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Senpai, help me!
Damn it.
Did you break your usual face, too?
Help me, Senpai!
It's been a while since I've been working.
What?
I'm going to work, too.
Help me, please!
What's wrong, Honda?
Sen... Senpai...
It's dark.
Is something wrong?
Senpai!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Sen... Senpai, I can't do it anymore!
I don't know if you were crying.
Try to explain it properly.
Here, Honda-san, a handkerchief.
Thank you very much.
You're very kind, too.
It's not like this, is it?
You're saying thank you, but how do you explain it to me?
Do you think I can do it,
even if I can't do it?
I'm sure I can, but...
I will be using some people's words.
It's not easy in such a way.
Sir.
Oh, Intimidation!
Never do that!
No matter which word you use,
Ryo-chan!
So that's how you fought with Otohime.
That's right. I don't like the details, what should I do, senpai?
That's it.
That's it, Ryo-chan?
That's right, senpai.
Honda suddenly became popular, so it's burning.
The boom will be gone in no time.
If you can endure it, you'll be like the old Sayan.
I can't endure it.
Nana-chan won't come to my cell phone, and she won't reply to my mail.
I'm no good.
You're overreacting. You don't know even if you cry.
Now, go home.
Senpai, that's not true.
Shut up!
You can solve your own problems by yourself.
Yes.
Are you really okay?
Ryo-san.
At times like this, time will solve everything.
Just leave it.
I'm the master of love, so there's no doubt about it.
Eh? Ryo-san was the master of love?
I've never heard of it.
Anyway, he's the master of love.
That's right.
Shut up!
Ah!
Damn it, look!
Honda is in a hurry?
Yes, it's been like this since the day before yesterday.
It's serious.
Senpai, are you really okay?
Just leave it like this.
It's fine.
Such trials make love stronger than love.
What you're saying is the most important thing.
Hello?
Ah, Ryusenshi!
Hey, you're treating my manga with dignity!
What? An emergency?
Otohime's manuscript hasn't been published yet?
I see.
I was in a hurry last time, so I was late.
It's dangerous this time, too.
Hmm. Are you influenced by Honda?
Yes.
I'm consulting with them.
I want Ryotsu-san to get along with them well.
In other words, you want them to get along?
My manga is the sign of my life, so there are many more emergencies.
If you can help me, I can think about Ryotsu-san's serial.
It's not okay to think about it.
Please do.
Please.
Then write 50 pages of the Kanto-color and put it on.
That's a little...
Oh, I see.
I see.
I'll write 50 pages of the Kanto-color and put it on.
All right. I have an idea.
Well, leave it to me.
Yes.
I'll write it.
Oh, it's a key.
There's one key and it's very interesting.
Do you know what this check is?
Let me know.
I know.
Mom, why are you crying?
I mean, don't cry.
Because it's time.
Well, you couldn't stop.
I have to cry, too.
It's time.
Mr. Hayato!
And the person who saw that was...
"I can't beat you for being so strong in love."
That's how it went.
It won't work out that well.
Yeah.
Leave it to me.
No matter what you say, I'm the master of love.
But what are you going to do with the other person?
I'm the chief. The chief.
Get up, Honda!
Get up!
It's not time for you to sleep. Get up!
I don't want to!
It's okay. Get up.
Please leave me alone!
Women are not only princesses.
No! I don't want to be Nana-chan!
Believe in me, the master of love!
I can only believe in three things about you!
Forget about being a princess!
Live a strong life!
No!
The meeting that the chief recommends
is one of my past spirits.
If you don't believe me, I won't let you go.
It won't work out.
Honda, sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello, chief.
Come in.
Yes.
What a beautiful lady!
I'm Noriko Asakusa.
"Noriko Asakusa"
See you later, Honda.
Senpai!
Your eyes are really cute.
What? My eyes?
I recall a lot of people who have that kind of look.
Everyone. You have this photo with you.
Really?
All of my photos were filmed on that TV,
I've also put it on the TV and filmed it.
But it's more wonderful to see the real thing than to see it on TV or in pictures.
H-Hi...
H-H-Haha...
You're the type like me.
What do you think?
Huh?
Hey...
T-That's pretty.
Not that.
Do you like it or not?
Hey, which one?
W-Which one?
I'm positive.
I love food.
Huh? I forgot something.
What is it?
I can't help it.
I'll go get it.
You can go home first.
See you.
It looks delicious.
Come on. Let's eat a lot and cheer up.
Okay.
Hey, Dara.
Yes?
You're so cute.
If you can't help it...
I guess this is where Ryu and Princess Oto are.
Well.
Yes, we are here.
Vadivac is here...
With this Razi-con mouse.
Go.
A-An-A mouse!
That's not good for a mouse!
No! You're not my opponent!
Move!
Mr. Ryu...
Nana...
Nana!
What's so funny?
Oh, Nana...
How's it? It's perfect, right?
It's a little different from what I planned, though.
You made it, huh?
Mr. Ryu!
You promised me something different!
Oh, really?
That's terrible, Senpai!
You completely hated Nana!
I'd rather die than do this!
No, I was at the meeting the other day.
The leader liked Honda very much.
He said he wanted to go out with me as a marriage proposal.
Hmm...
I'll tell him tomorrow.
Hey, Ryotsu.
Can you find us a date?
Yes, yes.
Well then, I'm counting on you.
It's the first couple in my name.
What are you going to do, Ryo-chan?
That's right, Senpai.
But there's a little mistake.
I'll leave it to you.
If you do that, the two of you will be in trouble.
Hmm...
What's the point of being a master of love?
It's your responsibility.
I know.
But I have a good idea.
I can cry no matter how many times I watch this movie.
That's right, this is it!
In the extreme state,
match Honda and Otohime!
This is the only way!
Nana-chan, I don't care what happens.
You're going to live for me.
No, no.
I can't beat your love.
For my sake,
I want you two to be happy.
If you see your two loves tied together,
they'll give up.
Nakagawa!
Make my good attraction for the Nakagawa amusement park scene.
Let's do it with a special-purpose construction.
What?
*
Hurry up!
You have to finish it by tomorrow!
*
I'm done.
Senpai, I don't like people other than Nana-chan.
I don't like people other than Nana-chan.
It's the chief's order.
This way.
Senpai!
Come with me!
Ah, yes!
This way!
I don't feel like coming here.
It's okay, it's okay.
Just play with it and forget about the bad things.
That's right.
Ah, this is good.
But...
Wow, it looks fun!
Let's cheer up!
Yes.
Here.
It's here, isn't it?
You're Asakusa Norika, right?
Yes.
Mr. Honda seems to be a little late.
Until now, he had promised to be my partner.
Eh?
There's a tea room over there, so let's wait there.
Yes.
Well, let's start from here.
Eh?
You're not going on a date with Norika?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
This is ...
Everyone is a robot.
R-Robot?
Oh wow!
Look, look, that outfit is cute.
Nakagawa, are you a Nakagawa concert?
E-Well ...
I'm Nakagawa's magazine.
Everyone has them!
I-Is that so...
Senpai, that just now...
We've collided with the Hyozan! Everyone, please evacuate!
Hyozan?!
Alright, next it's just Honda and Otohime.
"Honda and Otohime"
Nana-chan!
Honda-san!
Hey, stop it!
What are you doing?
Stop talking!
Nana-chan...
Honda-san...
Nana-chan!
What is that the atomic bomb?
Are you serious?
They think the computer is not working.
Seriously...
Let me go.
It's not like that.
What the hell?
The ship is sinking.
Damn it...
Please...
Kogachi, catch me if you can!
This... this...
It's sinking!
You're not going to make a good thing if you're here!
Shut up!
Go over there!
You're not getting away!
I'm not!
Get out of my way!
Hey, by the way, this is just like the Titanic, right?
So after this, you're the only one who sinks in the water, right?
That's great!
You're so funny!
But, by the way, it's not funny at all.
What? What is this music?
Idiot! Why the shark?
The more we get in trouble, the stronger our hearts are bound.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
If you're bound, you'd better be eaten by a shark!
I'm the same!
You're going to be eaten!
You first!
You're the same! Fight me!
Shut up!
You're going to get caught in that bowl!
What the hell is this? What's going on?
This love for a gay man is no joke!
I'm not kidding with this little horse!
Don't touch it!
My head isaking!
Look, Ryo!
Komachi!
Reiko, where are Honda and Otohime?
That way!
Good grief!
Love may be born out of the blue!
Just as you said, you're the Master of Love.
But...
Grrrr!
In the name of the Master!
Pl sortie!
Pl sortie! Pl sortie! In the name of the Master!
In the name of the Master!
There are couples who don't know each other.
Help me, Senpai!
Mr. Nakagawa!
What's wrong, Mr. Nakagawa?
He says I'm better than Mr. Honda!
Wait! Mr. Keiichi!
Nana-chan!
Mr. Honda!
No! No! No!
What's wrong, Senpai?
I promised to read 50 pages of the book with Ryu-senshi.
But it's not on the page.
Maybe it's this.
It looks like a fingerprint, but when I look closely, it's a page.
It's on the page, so I wrote it on the page.
Ryo-chan, you got one.
Damn it, Ryu-senshi!
If I get it again, I'll pay for it!
Ryo-chan!
Yes, I kind of had a fantastic question.
If you're foreign, where do you live?
Do you live in Nagasaki?
I'm sure you don't know.
I don't know either.
If you go down the wrong path, the moon will run away
Because now is not everything
Don't worry too much
Even if you lie and cheat a little
Sometimes you are helping someone
Baby do you know me?
Head to tomorrow
Nice breath
Don't be sick
I'll do what I do
Cute breath
I want to show you
What is hard to understand
It's better than seeing it again
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
Everyone, come to our town!
Thank you!