The End
When you watch TV
Make sure your room is bright and keep your distance
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
You look back and walk
Put your hand on the gacha
The strange feeling I felt at that time
So I walked on the black tile of the arcade
Everyone is the best
I was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue aunt above my eyes
Turn around and see
That corner
Everyone can see everyone
There is a turtle
There must be a turtle
ok
It probably is a turtle
It must be
The prize is 200,000 yen cash.
The cash is the best prize.
If I have 200,000 yen...
I'll buy Saori's 1/1 scale Vivia, which has been on sale for a long time.
I have 200,000 yen.
I'll go see Joby, who's coming to practice in Guam.
I'm shocked. I've never played golf before.
You're sweet, Naoko.
What? Komachi, are you sure you can play golf?
Actually, I've been taking lessons for 3 months.
No way! Shut up! You're mean!
If you're going to get a high-grade boyfriend, golf is a must-learn thing.
If you go to the practice ground,
you'll find a man who's pretty good at it.
He'll teach you how to play golf, and invite you to a date.
Thanks to him, you'll get better at golf.
If you win the next competition, you'll have 200,000 yen cash.
The bag you've been wanting is mine.
200,000 yen is mine!
What are you talking about? I'll be the winner!
What did you say?
I don't think you three can win.
Nakagawa-san.
The winner is Ryo-chan, right?
What? Can that gorilla-guy play golf?
I've never heard of that.
I've played tag-golf with the president and the chief before.
But he said he scored better than the two of them.
He said he won by playing against a professional golf course.
Yeah, I can tell that he's got a great athletic ability.
I didn't know that.
When money gets in your way, you'll get even more power.
That's right! That's right!
Ryo, are you going to join the golf club?
Of course.
Stop it, stop it.
That course is really difficult.
The first to play must give up.
Does that mean you've played at that golf course before?
I've played it before.
I'm the one who's got the most experience.
I've played the game yesterday.
Ryo, you're getting better at it.
I'm the one who's got the most prize money.
It's time for us to face the odds.
We can't lose!
Let's see who wins.
The fourth group is the president and the chief.
Reiko Nakagawa.
And the last group are Komachi, Volvo, Sakonji, and me.
Do you have any questions?
Ryo, usually, the first group starts early in the morning, but they're pretty slow.
The golf course is close.
It's still in Tokyo.
Oh, the golf course in Kasenjiki.
No, it's not in Kasenjiki.
It's just around the corner.
Just around the corner?
Is there a golf course around here?
Well, it's not like there's a shopping street nearby.
Here we are.
Where on earth is the International Country Golf Course?
But it's written on the sign.
The International Country Golf Course is a private name, isn't it?
It's very fake.
Huh?
Hey, Ryo.
You didn't use the compensation money again, did you?
And you didn't bring me to such a strange place, did you?
I'm not kidding.
I'll know once I get in.
It's nice inside.
It really is.
I've been waiting for you.
This is Kokusai, the owner.
He makes his own golf course.
Do you play the video games of golf here?
Hey.
There's a proper course.
This is my golf course.
Oh, this place looks pretty spacious.
But this is a course from thirty years ago.
What?
Currently, it looks like this.
It's almost in the middle of the city.
This is the place!
That's right. This is the town.
30 years ago, there was a hill here.
We used the natural land to build a golf course.
To destroy the hill is to destroy nature.
The natural golf course is the best.
I see. There is a policy.
Soon the railroad will pass.
This is also natural flow.
Then, the station was built.
My land was also provided to the country.
While we were taking care of the natural flow,
we found a natural town in the golf course.
Where is the natural golf course?
Don't say hard things.
I've been here many times.
This golf course is interesting.
Hall 1, 200 yards.
Per 4.
90 yards to the front.
110 yards to the right.
Green.
It's almost a course through the alley.
I see.
It's a alley.
The fairway is very narrow.
It looks difficult.
Chashu-men!
It's OB.
As a rule,
there is no lost ball such as OB.
You can go around the entire course with one ball.
It's a waste of resources to lose many balls.
If you lose the ball, you will be disqualified immediately.
That's tough.
Don't be so hard.
Nice shot.
Kei-chan is good.
90 yards is perfect.
Okay, I'll continue.
Oh, no.
I'm in trouble.
Ah!
Oh, a good turn!
You got to a pretty good goal.
Yeah.
It's all right with the results.
It's my turn.
I won't score if I keep in line like you.
I'm aiming for one-on.
Boss, where's the green ball?
Between OB Curry
and the Ikepocha real estate.
That's a bad landmark.
A lead.
You got away!
That was a good shot.
I'll show you a good shot.
Everyone go to the green and watch.
That's a lot of room.
Let's go.
Well, then.
The target is under the sign.
All right.
The target is perfect.
It's a one-on-one.
What? One-on-one? Who is it?
You did it.
It's an eagle chance.
I don't know the course.
I'm still scared.
No wonder you're the champion.
What are you talking about?
It's just begun.
I'll never be the champion.
I can't lose.
I'll do it for Saori's sake.
I thought I was around here.
It's in here.
What?
Oh, here we are.
This is terrible! It's been three days since we had a meal!
S-Sorry.
Sir, if you want to shoot, it's a sandwich. What do you want?
I can't shoot with this.
I'll give up because it's an OB.
Eat something more nutritious with this.
Thank you very much!
Ah! My ball!
Unfortunately, you're disqualified.
I'm disappointed.
You're on the road.
I have no choice but to shoot a high ball.
Nice shot!
Oh, it's a good shot!
Sir, you're disqualified if you don't chase after the ball.
I can't do it.
I'll give up because it's an OB.
Ah! Don't look around!
I don't want to do this anymore!
I'm going to die!
Everyone who has no commitment to money is falling behind.
I've become more and more advantageous.
Hehehehe.
This is the safest to attack like this.
I'm the safest.
You're really smart when you're getting paid.
Caddy, where's my ball?
Under that car.
A little more.
No, I can't get it out.
Hey, Borobo! You're finally giving up?
Don't worry about that.
What are you going to do?
Everyone, this is dangerous. Get out of the way!
You idiot!
That's no good.
It's out!
Good. I got a par with the fourth hit.
This isn't golf anymore.
Don't shoot at dangerous spots. Get out of the way!
Hey!
Who the hell are you to throw a punch at me?
Come out!
It's you!
No, it's not!
Hmm.
Are you going to shoot there too?
If you don't shoot, you're out.
It seems like you've come this far, Komachi.
What? I'm not joking. Wait a minute.
Komachi!
What are you going to do, Komachi?
What's this?
It's a golf ball.
What?
What's that?
Wow!
What was that?
I don't know.
Are you okay, Komachi?
I've managed to escape.
You're a girl, but you've come this far.
Komachi might be your biggest enemy.
I'm behind you there.
Komachi.
Komachi's back.
And he's a man!
Damn it!
What a shame.
Alright, I'll shoot straight.
Oh no!
This time, I'll shoot like a woman.
I'll shoot deliberately.
Hmm, Borubo is weak to a woman's nudity.
That's it.
I'm not happy because I'm just an old man.
Oh, I should have shot like a woman!
I'm just an old man anyway.
Jody!
Oh no!
But I can't stop for Jody's sake.
It seems that there was a young customer.
I'm a little envious.
Ryo Chikankichi, this is your second time.
Yes!
Oh, lucky!
This is how you attack a straight long hole.
Alright!
That's it!
Now, it's a straight line to the green.
Oh, what a bad guy.
If this goes on, the gap will open.
Naoko, wait a minute.
Hmm?
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
I got it.
If you win, treat me.
Oh, damn it!
I didn't expect to stop so soon.
Oh, lucky again!
What?
Hey, stop!
Now, Ryo Chikankichi is done.
Huh?
He's a persistent man.
What about this?
Oh, damn it!
It bent again!
I'm going to win!
Hey, wait up!
Huh?
Naoko!
No way!
You grabbed my dirty hand!
Hey!
Huh?
No matter what you do, I'm the one who owes you $2,000!
If you're the one who's going to do it,
let me give you a share of my dirty hands, too!
Hey, taxi!
Huh?
Ah!
Ryo Chikankichi, you're so cold.
W-w-w-w-what are you doing?!
Hey, Sakonji. You're lucky to have shot Saori's room.
If you shoot, you'll hurt Saori.
Winning is the only way to win!
I can't... I can't hurt Saori.
You're going to fall off alone.
Wh-what is this hall?!
Hall 9.
The final stage is 350 yards per fall using the garden of the animal lover.
Most players will be in danger in Hall 9.
The remaining players are just seniors.
Okay, I'm the owner.
Damn, I wanted to say that I spent my savings in that hall.
Anyway, this is a great place.
We have to fly far away and avoid encountering the other beasts.
Nice shot!
Amazing! It's over 300 yards!
You're giving up now, aren't you?
No, not yet!
Not yet!
You're going to fly the helicopter?
What a great obsession.
You won't be able to stop her if you don't try.
Yeah, you're freaking out, aren't you?
Yeah.
A fox doesn't do great.
Let's see.
That'll be the end of the line.
freshman #6
That's right, what's your mistake?
Think to yourself!
Shosshi!
You've got a good chance.
Don't wake up.
You're not playing golf, you're hunting beasts.
You've got a good chance.
Yeah.
What a birdie chance!
Don't come near me!
You're gonna get burned!
Let's fight!
This is where you really shine, senpai!
Come on, if you're gonna beat those beasts,
come to Ikepo-Chan!
I've won twice in this round,
I'm gonna beat you right here!
What?
Ryo!
I'm gonna beat you!
Oh yeah!
What kind of trouble is this?
Out of the way!
What?!
He's one-overced, and he's gonna make a hole-out!
Dammit!
I'm gonna pay you back for that!
Damn, ¥200,000 is mine!
And Ryo's turn is the fourth,
so he'll win at this point.
Ryo's a real royal.
He won't be able to get his chip in without you two.
No way.
He doesn't need to know about all this,
you can just try to be a friend with him.
That's the only place I can aim for.
Fire!
Flag!
You're a professional golfer, Saruke!
Did I get in?
You did!
Yay! It's the playoffs!
Well, I don't know about that.
What's that?
Yay! We won!
N-no way!
I didn't know you could do that.
I'll pay you back in 200,000 yen!
Help!
You didn't do that?
You must have paid for it.
Hey! I'll pay you back in 200,000 yen!
Take that!
Don't you dare!
You didn't do that!
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm not going to do it!
Get the hell out of here!
Don't come near me!
You'll regret this!
I'll get you!
Yeah!
♪ Awaken, clock, kick it off, my little finger hurts, ta-ta-ta ♩
♪ For now, I'll draw my eyebrows and then I'll go to the station, dash, dash, dash ♩
♪ On the main train, I'll sleep on my father's back ♩
♪ This week, I'll do my best, and I'll do my best, even if it's more than 5 times ♩
♪ I'm doing my best with my bucket in one hand, but my body is so warm ♩
♪ Even the annoyance that continues today will be solved with annoyance and comfort ♩
♪ No problem every day, if you cross the hot shower ♩
♪ No problem every day, I'll recover my health with a sleeping pillow ♩
♪ No problem every day, I love myself like this ♩
♪ No problem every day, my heart is flying every Monday ♩
What? You want to make your life a waste? Don't make me laugh.
You're just using cards and you've never seen cash before.
What can you do?
Alright! I'll tell you what my real life is like!
Next time, "Henshin! Shominha Nakagawa-kun!"
Please watch!
Translated by 方 Hou.