"The End"
When you watch TV
Make the room bright and try to get away
It's like someone is calling
After the rain
Walking while looking back
Put your hands on your mother
I felt it at that time
A strange feeling
So I tried walking on the black tile of the Akegogai
I tried walking
Everyone was a child once
But everyone forgets
Politicians with a great face
And a blue aunt above their eyes
Turn around and look at that corner
You can meet everyone
There is a wall there
It's a wall
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
"The End"
Did you see her?
You should be proud of yourself
"The End"
This is the girl I met when I was delivering the newspaper.
Delivering the newspaper?
Ryo-chan?
Yeah.
Really?
I can't believe it.
Why?
Because Senpai is the type to make money easily.
Delivering the newspaper early in the morning and delivering it one by one, right?
Not delivering it one by one.
Yeah, sorry about that.
What's the reason?
My best friend was doing it.
I was scouted by him while I was doing it.
Really?
Yeah.
What was her name again?
Tsuyoshi.
Yeah, Tsuyoshi.
Hey, Kankichi!
It's you again!
Stand in the corridor!
Yes, sir.
When I'm in the corridor,
I'll make sure to meet the girl.
Wait.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Why?
The girl's purpose was to hide,
It was really dangerous.
But she didn't hide anything, right?
Who is it?
He's Kankichi!
I know.
What kind of boy do you think he is?
I'm Tekano.
I've been seeing this girl for many years.
At least just for a while, yeah?
I mean-
You bastard!
Well, I sometimes lose.
Tsuyoshi's family lost their father last year due to illness.
Tsuyoshi, his younger brother and sister, and his mother went to work.
So Tsuyoshi was also delivering newspapers to help his family.
What's this? Why are you so noisy?
It's Kankichi. He's going to deliver newspapers from today.
He can't wake up early.
I'm going!
Before delivering newspapers, it's our job to put the ads in between the newspapers.
This is a lot of work.
See you!
Newspapers! Newspapers! Newspapers!
I'm in charge of about 60 newspapers.
If I forget to deliver them, I'll be fired, so I had to do it.
Thank you.
He eats well in the morning. This is his fifth meal.
It can't be helped. I've been working since morning.
I can't help it. I have to pay for food.
It's not home. The house where the young man lives will be popular in the neighborhood.
No.
With a proud son, both my father and mother are...
This kid is...
Who does he look like?
By the way, when I was passing by the shrine on the way to deliver,
I saw a lot of old newspapers being thrown away.
I picked them up, packed them in between the newspapers, and brought them home.
My heart was beating so fast.
Are you okay?
I'm seriously injured.
The police car comes and the ambulance comes, so it's a big mess.
However, here, they say that if a newspaper is found, they will be pardoned, so they are hiding a newspaper that is desperately scattered.
You. Hurry up and get on the ambulance.
I'm fine. I have a job, so I'm fine with this.
Because you're bleeding from your head.
Oh, is this it?
This was out from before. I have a lot of bloodshot hair, so it came out immediately.
It's a mental accident, isn't it? But the victim?
I'm fine, look! As you see, nothing happened.
Let's go for a drive.
That boy is amazing.
The truck was 70 km away.
The L-Horn was not found out, but it was cracked by the right hand bone.
My father was angry because I broke the bicycle.
He was about to die because the temperature was 40 degrees.
But he still gave me a good feeling.
He is a professional.
He also gave me a job.
It's difficult to find a house without a lot of people and to use the L-Horn.
However, my collection rate was 100%.
It's amazing when money gets involved.
I was stuck until I collected money.
It's like a detective.
Thanks to him, I was able to get a job in a difficult district.
There was a guy who saved a lot of money and moved for a year.
Of course, he will follow me.
But he is a elementary school student, so he is completely despised.
He is not willing to pay at all.
So please pay a year's salary.
Shut up, kid!
I will pay! I will pay now!
I had a friend who looked scared.
Thank you.
As expected of Ryo.
At that time, the big sister of a university student at another delivery company was a hot topic among everyone.
I talked to her yesterday.
Really?
Yes.
What did you talk about?
I said "hello" and she said "hello" and I said "goodbye" and she said "goodbye".
That's all?
Yes.
Idiot! I talked about it.
Don't talk about it.
Exactly.
I'm so jealous.
One day.
I was in a hurry and I fell asleep.
Oh!
I became friends with a famous lady.
Hello.
You always slip away.
Yes.
Are you a elementary school student?
I'm in the fifth grade.
You always fly at a great speed.
I have a wide range of things to receive.
You are doing your best every day.
No, not really.
Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
I love chocolate.
It's a little bitter for adults.
It's hard to stop raining.
Yes.
I was in a hurry and I fell asleep.
I was like that when I felt like it didn't matter if it rained.
It's ready.
That's good.
Yes.
You have my regards.
Bye.
See you.
As expected, chocolate was a little bitter.
You have good memories.
After that, I started drinking it.
She's a new person in March of next year.
I don't know if she graduated and went back to the country or got a job.
You do meet people.
But Ryo, what happened to that blonde girl?
Oh, right.
There's a rich house in the area where I deliver.
The End
Okay, who's going to answer this question?
Hey, Kankichi!
Stand in the corridor!
What?
P-chan!
What's wrong?
Ka-chan!
Tsuyoshi's mother has fallen.
He's in a lot of pain.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't push yourself too hard.
Please rest for the time being.
Okay.
See you.
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
Uncle...
Thank you.
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
I talked to your mother.
You don't know what's going to happen if you don't tell her.
Okay.
So, why don't you just leave the house?
You don't have to hold back.
I want to see you both.
Tsuyoshi.
I want a piece of the food.
Oh, it's going to be okay.
He has gone.
He's not going to say anything.
He'll just stop the eating.
Oh, let's leave him be.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
See you.
This is the first time I've run this much.
Me too.
Thank you for saving me.
My name is Flora.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tsuyoshi.
I'm Kankichi.
By the way, why are you being chased?
Who are they?
That's...
A bodyguard?
I was in the house all the time without being allowed to go outside.
Every day?
Yes.
So that's why you ran away.
But the people in the house are worried.
My parents are not at work.
I'm always alone at home.
If that's the case, leave it to us.
Right, Tsuyoshi?
Yes, that's right.
We'll go with you today.
Really?
Yes.
I don't need your support.
Thank you, Kankichi, Tsuyoshi.
Then you live in the inn where Doberman lives.
What's wrong with your house?
I'm a newspaper delivery guy.
You always fly at a high speed.
Do you know that?
But the other day, I was too fast, I was hit by a dump truck, and I got a lot of eros.
Eros?
Don't say such strange things.
I'm a big fan of you.
You're my favorite.
And you're making me fall!
You idiot!
Idiot!
Why are you so quiet?
Don't laugh.
Neusal
Did you enjoy your time here?
Awesome.
I want to stay here like this.
You three can escape far away.
Ugh.
Really?
Tsuyoshi...
Ah, just kidding.
Just kidding.
What the...
My lady, where did you go? I'm so worried.
It's all right. We're safe.
By the way, who are you?
I was helped by these people who were lost on the road.
They gave me a meal and sent me here.
Thank you, my lady.
Thank you for your help.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's right.
I'll invite you to the next Wednesday's garden party for this.
That's good, right?
That's already...
If you say so...
Oh...
If you say party, will there be a great feast?
Isn't that so?
Idiot!
Sorry.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Where's the guy who's playing around in the middle of the money?
If you do this, I don't think you'll understand even if you think you're a rich man.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, um, I have something to talk to you.
Oh, you're going back to the country.
Yes.
You've got a lot of trouble, too.
Well, you can do it over there.
Yes.
Then I'll make up for what I've done so far.
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
Is the party going to be a dance after all?
I wonder.
I don't know what to do.
I don't dance.
Hey, Tsuyoshi.
Shut up.
Party, party, party.
I can't go to such a strange place.
What?
A party is a gorgeous place.
It doesn't suit me.
But if you don't go, Flora will...
Then you can go by yourself.
I'm not going.
Tsuyoshi, what's wrong with you all of a sudden?
Shut up.
What?
You're just like a fool from a while ago.
It's embarrassing.
What?
Can I step on Flora's feelings?
I'm just trying to date a rich girl.
I don't want you to go to someone like you.
So I'm telling you not to go.
I'm telling you.
It's been this long since I've done something for you.
I'm totally in for it with you.
As you wish.
See ya.
What?
You stupid Tsuyoshi.
Come to me with a bang.
You fool.
From the next day, Tsuyoshi has not appeared in the delivery room.
Did he say he quitted?
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's going back to Japan.
Next Wednesday, 4 a.m. Ueno-hatsu.
You can pick him up if you want to go.
Garden party?
I'm starting to laugh.
Mom, this shirt is so hard to wear.
What are you saying?
If you dress up like that, you'll be in trouble.
Right, dad?
Well, yeah.
But you're a big shot with a girl friend with blue eyes, Kankichi.
You've become internationally known for your beauty.
You'll get married soon.
What are you talking about?
You're too quick-witted.
I'm just saying.
But you did something bad, didn't you?
You said you were moving today.
It's okay, that guy.
He's mean.
He tells me to go to the party alone.
And he doesn't tell me to move.
That guy has nothing to do with it.
That's not right, Kankichi.
I'm sorry to say goodbye to you.
I know I should have said that.
But he…
You know what?
If you knew he was moving, you wouldn't go to the party with Ugiki.
But I'm not going to you.
If you don't go to the party, you won't be able to meet that girl.
That's why I didn't tell you to move.
I told you on purpose.
Why don't you make me cry?
I understand, Kankichi.
Let's have a party for Tsuyoshi.
If a girl cries, I'll have to pay for it.
Thank you for inviting me today.
Oh, thank you, Gankichi.
What a beautiful flower.
What happened to Tsuyoshi?
He's been out of business for some reason.
I'm sorry about that.
Let's go, Tsuyoshi.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you for having me here.
Gankichi, could you dance with me?
Oh, please!
Sorry, Flora.
Kankichi!
Ryukan, let's go home!
Hey, Kankichi!
"I miss you so much that I want to give you up."
"You're so far away from me."
"You're so faint."
"I feel you."
"You laugh at me."
How long will it take?
About 30 minutes.
Maybe a little longer.
"You're so strong."
Kankichi!
Tsuyoshi!
Take care, Tsuyoshi!
You too, Kankichi!
Kankichi!
Tsuyoshi!
Flora!
The best memory in Japan was being friends with two boys.
They were both kind, nice, and small gentlemen.
I will never forget them.
Kankichi, Tsuyoshi. Thank you.
Well, that's it.
What a wonderful memory.
Is that so? Is this girl Flora-hime?
She was a beautiful girl. She could have been an actress.
I've seen her a few times.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, I remember.
I saw a picture of her with her.
What?
Look. Flora-hime is next to me.
This is her?
No way.
No, that's not true.
No, it's not.
No, it's her.
I admit it.
You've grown up.
You're kind and lovely.
You're getting old.
No, it's not.
It's her.
Shall we call her and check?
No, it's not.
Even if she admits it, I will never, never, never admit it.
Then, I'll call her back.
I really should have done it sooner if not now.
What?
A rat too weak?
Go, go, White Bear.
I'm about to burst into tears.
♪ I'm holding a bucket in one hand, but ♪
♪ it's so warm and cloudy ♪
♪ I'm still irritated by the constant work ♪
♪ I'm irritated, irritated, and I want to get rid of this ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ When the hot shower goes blue ♪
♪ I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine ♪
♪ No problem every day ♪
♪ I love myself like this ♪
♪ My heart is beating ♪
♪ Monday ♪
♪ No problem, no problem, no problem ♪
It's a crow! It's crow's work!
Damn! It's crow's work, but why do I have to doubt it?
Wait, even if I did the opposite, it's all crow's fault!
Next time, a big fight! Ryo-tsu vs. Crow!
See you later!
♪ There's a crow over there ♪
♪ Ah, there must be a crow ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
The End