Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
♪ Looking at the sunset ♪
♪ Floating in the middle of the sea ♪
♪ I kicked a pebble ♪
♪ How far did I fly? ♪
♪ I wonder if I'm going ♪
♪ To the place where I jodged ♪
♪ I was laughed at ♪
♪ For being a bad boy ♪
♪ Even if I'm a bad boy ♪
♪ I'm just a bad boy ♪
♪ The cityscape is the same ♪
♪ It's so gentle ♪
♪ The crows are crying ♪
♪ The moose is shaking ♪
♪ Are you looking at the roasted chicken? ♪
♪ From the water tower of Tongari-boshi ♪
♪ To Taishakuten ♪
♪ The sunset falls ♪
♪ It's over tomorrow too ♪
♪ But I'm happy again ♪
♪ I lost it ♪
♪ I realized ♪
♪ I'm an idiot ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Welcome, Honda.
Hello.
What do you want, Honda?
Well, I went to a bookstore earlier
I said I bought you because I was going to spare you on "Weekly Sapphire".
What do you think? Let me see.
Let me see. What is my Chief of Robodeca?
Have you still been practicing, Ryo?
Of course, I have.
My Chief of Robodeca is set up for "Canban Manga".
What?
I don't have my Robodeca Pancho.
No!
It's not on anywhere!
Don't tell me you forgot to give it back?
That's not true.
I sent it the week before.
Ahh!
Senpai!
Look here!
Hmm?
What?
Ryo Churyu: Manga Jyuku
*Drum roll*
You're a Ryu-senshi, you bastard!
You just randomly cut my manga out!
I'll never forgive you!
Get out of here, Honda!
*Drum roll*
Yo, Ryu-senshi!
What the hell is going on here?!
H-hello, Patricia Kanco-sensei.
Let me ask you a question.
Y-yes.
What are you doing here?
I'm going to the royal office.
Yeah. So?
First of all...
*Drum roll*
Take a look at this.
What?
This is...
The results of the last week's readers' survey.
Wow! Nana-chan's "Medhead" is the first place!
Yay!
My "Robodeca" is...
Huh?
It's resumed!
Wait, it hasn't even been one second.
B-but...
Even if it was resumed once...
No, it's not just once.
This is a 100-page survey.
Is that okay?
Yes, it is.
Please take a closer look at the results.
*Drum roll*
Huh?
This is crazy.
I can't believe it's resumed.
*Drum roll*
As you can see,
The "Robodeca" is the 100th place in a row.
B-but...
Well, it's fine if it's not popular.
*Drum roll*
An odd-looking thing...
B-but I don't know if you're all right.
It's the fact that you're now in the middle of a bright new ro-
Oh, do you have a book you want to sell?
So have that book.
*Drum roll*
Awww, that's--
The "Robodeca" is still a little big.
Listen, I heard it.
Oh.
What's the matter?
You not have one?
It's all in here...
What?
Actually, I thought the boss of this place was a complete mess.
At this time, let's stop it quickly.
Is that so? I'm glad you understand.
Instead, let's start a new series.
New series!
Finished.
Fast! Write it in 5 minutes!
Try reading it.
What kind of manga is it?
This time, Robodeca is going to change the style of the work and spread the Minato Yokohama stage.
It's a drama, hard-boiled gag action.
Hajiki is calling me.
Hard-boiled drama gag.
The work is James Ryotsu.
This is the amount.
Let's buy it for 1 billion yen.
We're both bad.
The boss has a problem.
That's right, Kintaro Ikano.
Jari.
What?
That's right.
This is the drug-faced Tondobayashi Joe.
Call me Joe with two guns.
It's not Dandy of Pyokkori Pyotanjima.
Boss, this is a big deal.
Guys, kill Joe.
Take a shot of Joe's green.
This is the weekly Sapphire?
It's fun and my jaw will come off.
Especially the last is the best.
Last?
If you don't wear a vest, you'll be fooled.
I don't care.
Tondobayashi, this is not a drug, but a udon.
What?
Gabin.
That's why I said it's wrong.
I just bought a udon at 1 billion yen.
Oh, Tondobayashi, what's going on?
Excuse me.
Sui, sui, sui, da da da da, sui, kan.
How about a unexpected Don Dengaishi?
It's a house that even a top writer can't come up with.
But why do people who aren't criminals have a machine gun?
That's a lie.
No, that's a coincidence.
A machine gun fell in the harbor warehouse.
When I picked it up, the main character appeared.
The main character is killing the other person.
No, that's right.
The other person was wearing a bulletproof vest by chance.
So it's a weapon.
Everyone is shot in the head.
So I'm wearing a bulletproof wig.
It's unnatural to buy a simple udon at such a high price.
Yeah, yeah.
Why would you go to the harbor and do this?
And why do you think it's a bad idea to buy udon?
It's noisy every day.
It's a gag manga, so leave the details alone.
Either way, it's not a manga for Weekly Sapphire.
This manga cannot be published.
I'll somehow get it out of the way.
No, you can't.
Anyway, Ryo-chan's manga will never be on Weekly Sapphire.
This is the final decision at the editorial meeting.
Damn it, Ryusenshi!
It seems like a bad thing is a bad thing, so you give up so easily.
What are you talking about?
It's that easy?
Huh?
Stop it, Honda!
What's wrong, Ryo-chan's husband?
Look, there.
Oh, you've thrown away a lot of books.
This is the head of Sekine Shippan.
It's my father's.
Why are there so many books?
They're still new.
They're not thrown away.
What's wrong, father?
This is a book that has been returned.
All of them?
Not just the outside.
There are so many of them.
That's a lot.
Because it's not published yet.
What kind of book did you make?
The world's pen tip?
The world of the wonderful Bolt and Nat?
There's no way a book like this will sell!
Is that so?
It will never sell!
I guarantee it.
I knew it.
I have to make a book that will sell here.
If I don't do it, I'll be a father.
Hmm, a book that will sell, a book that will sell...
Hm? Then it's a manga!
Manga?
That's right, you can make a manga magazine.
You're small, but you're the president of a publishing company!
Among these published books, the only thing that sells is manga!
Manga is read widely by young people, from children to adults.
And it's cheap, you can read it anytime, anywhere, and the contents are interesting!
If you publish a manga magazine, you can overcome your father's crisis!
I see!
But it's impossible.
Huh?
I don't have a know-how for manga magazines, and I don't know any manga artists either.
If that's the case, don't worry! Leave everything to me!
Huh?
The popular manga artist's serialization is just about to end, and my hands are empty!
Ah!
Senpai, are you going to serialize your own manga?
Of course!
I knew it.
Yes! I'm done!
F-faster! This time it's 4 minutes!
This is my masterpiece!
How is it, Honda?
This is...
"Robo-Deka Bancho R"!
R?
It's a sequel to "Robo-Deka Bancho", which ended in a huge hit!
Speaking of "Robo-Deka Bancho", it's also a TV anime and is extremely famous.
It's a waste to let it end like that, so I decided to re-release it in a new magazine!
Huh...
But, Senpai, what about other manga artists other than you?
What should I do?
You should ask the publisher!
Hello?
Is this the weekly step editorial department?
Who is the most popular manga artist in your area?
Hoshi Hikaru?
Yes!
Tell me his phone number!
Reason?
Of course, to have it written in my magazine!
Huh?
Damn it!
You cut it suddenly!
You're rude!
I'm the rude one!
You're the rude one, Senpai!
What?
For the publisher, a popular manga artist is a property.
The information of a manga artist is a top secret.
Damn it!
Ryo-san, it's impossible after all...
Don't give up!
You have to re-release the manga magazine no matter what!
But how?
There should be something.
Something?
Huh?
Right!
If you can make a manga artist who is as good as a famous writer,
why not Replicas?
Huh?
Hey, Ryo-san.
Isn't it bad if a manga artist is as good as a famous writer?
There should be something called Replicas in manga, right?
It should be good even if it's a manga.
I feel that manga is something different from manga in manga...
Besides, what if a professional manga artist complains about it?
Don't worry.
That's what I'm good at.
I'm confident that the person who complains about it will say that he copied it.
I have the confidence to tell you that I have it.
But how do you get good people to draw?
I have an idea.
Is it a manga school?
Students are asked to write a manuscript as a task and publish it in a magazine.
That doesn't cost any money.
If you convert the tuition fee and teaching expenses of the school into a manuscript printing fee, you can make a free book.
I see. That's great.
This is the magic business method.
But are the students going to get together?
That's okay.
We have a special instructor.
What?
Mr. Jacky Ponchi, Mr. Kazuyoshi Horori, and Nana-chan.
No, no.
Take a good look.
What?
Mr. Nomiko Nobunaga's ex-boyfriend...
What? Are you talking about me?
Ping pong!
I'm not joking!
I can't draw a manga.
Besides, we're still dating.
We're not old friends!
Don't worry about that.
Then maybe it's someone else, too...
Mr. Jacky Ponchi's ex-husband, Mr. Horori Kazuyoshi's ex-fiance.
Aino Sensei's main character...
is here...
The teacher is here!
I wonder if Aino Sensei will come!
I want my autograph!
You've gathered well, Ryo-san!
The special instructor has come, right?
Now, we will perform the special instructor's lecture.
I've been waiting!
It's Aino Sensei!
He's here!
What's this?
Is Aino Sensei a man?
Well...
Aino Miko Sensei's main character is Nana-chan, the sound princess.
And this is...
a picture we took together.
a picture of the time we went on a touring.
He's a different man than before.
He really is.
That's all.
What is it?
What did you want to say?
In other words,
Aino Sensei's main character is Nana, the sound princess.
And she's dating two men, right?
I'm glad you thought that.
You're doing great.
Leave the rest to me!
Hello, everyone!
I'm a special instructor, John Ryo-tsu.
Nice to meet you!
Um...
If you enter this school, you'll be able to become a professional.
It's okay!
If I do what I say,
I can debut 100% as a professional.
Really?
That's great.
That's the right idea.
Because I'm here,
You guys should be in a big room.
Then, let's start the class.
First, prepare the paper.
I brought it.
Me too.
What?
No, not this paper!
Use the paper that is designated for the school properly!
If you want to be a professional, use good paper!
Otherwise, don't write good manga!
Understood?
I got it!
500 yen per sheet.
It's like a 10 yen paper.
458!
Then, everyone should buy a textbook.
It's absolutely necessary to be a professional.
It's expensive.
80,000 yen.
One pencil is 1,000 yen.
Will you use a pen?
And a driver.
I chose only wonderful things.
100 yen for a screen tone.
Teacher, you can buy a cheap tone.
That's right.
It's a student's tone.
It's a special point.
Then, please give me 10 sheets of No. 61.
Me too.
20 sheets for this one.
Yes, 10 sheets.
Is it so small?
Paste it on a small part.
It's like a cut.
I prepared the necessary materials as a professional.
Be sure to buy it.
It's expensive.
It costs 200,000 yen to draw one work.
Manga artists must have drawing power.
So, I'll give you drawing dolls from now on.
I'll give you a drawing doll.
Drawing Doll No. 1.
It's like a cursed straw doll.
It has a wire inside and it can move freely.
Next, it's a drawing doll for girls.
It doesn't change at all.
There is also a horse drawing doll.
It's like a big stick.
Then, I'll teach you the basics of making a story.
Teacher.
Yes?
I brought the work I drew.
Would you like to see it?
Okay.
I'll hold it.
I thought I was going to make an artistic work on the theme of human love.
What do you think?
Hmm?
Are you kidding me?
The theme is art?
You don't want that?
That's my own desire.
I'm satisfied with myself.
What you want to read is an interesting manga.
You don't understand that?
Yes, I'm sorry.
What is an interesting manga?
I'll tell you the secret from now on.
Got it?
It's a boy manga!
The main character of a boy manga is a little naughty.
And next to him is a beautiful heroine.
And the main character's story.
And the main character always needs an enemy.
The stronger the enemy, the stronger the desire.
The more the main character is happy when he defeats him.
And finally, the battle with the enemy.
It's a battle.
The main character and the enemy always have a battle.
Even if you make a mistake, the main character must not defeat the enemy.
You must not be defeated by the enemy once.
And the main character realizes his own helplessness.
He shed a tear of regret.
And then he exercises.
Exercise?
In a situation like this, the main character is buried in a mountain and hit by a waterfall.
And after the exercise,
the boss is
trained by the enemy himself.
And the enemy is a trick to become a very strong enemy.
And the enemy does not run away from the mountain.
It's even better if you cut off one of the chịples yourself.
And then it will be a ground fight against the enemies again.
But here's just a little bit of excitement here.
Finally defeat the enemy.
And the enemy is SK of the heroine.
Becoming a partner of the heroine.
But at that time, a black shadow that was already hiding from them
There is a new enemy
More than that
Enemy appearance, confrontation, defeat, special training, confrontation, victory, reconciliation, enemy appearance
If you repeat this, you can continue the boy manga no matter how many times
Oh, is that so?
Um, teacher
What?
I want to draw a girl manga
Girl manga, good
Girl manga is love
The main character likes a transfer student boy
The main character is a little bit of a girl to get the reader's sympathy
And the main character is troubled by the appearance of a rival in love
It's going to stick, it won't stick
Ah, don't be frustrated
If you like it, say it quickly
I'm just trying to make the reader feel
Confession
Then
The transfer student also liked the main character from the beginning
What a ridiculous development
It can be said to be the standard of most girls manga
Let the main character hide his glasses
It was actually beautiful to take off his glasses
If you do something like that, the reader will be even happier
I see
Then the next is a boy manga
The main character is left alone by a man who can't stand it
Suddenly a cute girl comes and lives with him
Like this
If you talk about something that makes a man's selfish desire come true, the reader will definitely eat it
Girls wear glasses and dress up as a maid to make them even happier
Next is a fantasy manga
It's a world of anything
If you say something like superpower or age, the reader will be convinced that it is
But if there is too much of anything and the story becomes incomprehensible, you should keep it in the first part
The theory manga is a basic trick
Before the culprit gets involved in such a complicated thing
Talk to the sad side of the culprit
Don't forget about the forceful trick
I feel like I can draw something
Me too
Then, based on the above
Let's actually ask you to draw a manga
Even if I say
Because you are an amateur, you will not get ideas so easily
I will draw a wonderful original work
Thank you
Do useless employees get along with the president?
Does a submarine declare an independent nation?
Does a hero with a simple face play an active role?
Does the school slip to the future?
Does a frog stick to the shirt on the fallen cover?
Do robots fight?
Do you push and push instead of the moon?
Then, each of you will draw a manga in that original work
This is today's task
Draw
The characters all have the same face
You can only change the hairstyle
I can not draw the background well
Make a lot of screen tone and deceive
It is difficult to draw each mecha
Copy and turn it over
Somehow it seems to work well
That's right
As expected of Wagyo
I did it
Me too
I also
Put the original work on the desk and go home
OK
That's all for the original
All you have to do is print this
Then I'll print this immediately
Ten thousand
Is it too many?
Idiot
I'm saying it's too little
It is said that the selling manga magazine is more than one million copies
One million pages
This magazine also has my most popular manga, Robodeca Banjo R.
Three million... No, I mean 5 million copies will sell.
5 million copies!
Stop being so picky!
I'm going to sell all the manga magazines I've made and smash you up!
So this is the comic Ryotsu Senpai made?
Yes, Robodeca Banjo R is in Kanto.
It's still a great picture.
It's even better when it's colored.
There's no way a manga like this would sell in Kanto.
Besides, the manga inside is all things I've seen somewhere, so no one buys such magazines.
Reiko-san was right.
The comic Ryotsu that has made 5 million copies is not selling at all.
It was this one that was crushed, not the weekly Sapphire.
There are too many people who don't care about the world.
No matter how you think about it...
It's obvious that it won't sell.
Ryo-san!
The father of Sekine Publishing!
Sensei!
You guys!
Ryo-san!
We finally have a father because of Ryo-san!
How are you going to pay for this!
Hey, no, you can't say that!
Sensei, what do you mean by the manga school is closed?
We paid for the class fee for a year. How are you going to pay for this!
And what kind of magazine is this?
You can't just put your manga on a magazine and...
It's a scam!
So, this is...
Why are you giving it to me, Ryo-san!
Sensei!
Ryo-san!
The magazine is already full!
I don't want to do it! I don't want to do it!
Why do I have to do something I don't want to do and do something I don't have to do?
If you tell me that I don't have to do something I don't have to do, I might want to do it!
Next time on I Don't Want to Do It!
Please watch the other one!
♪ There's a turtle over there! ♪
♪ Ah, there's definitely a turtle! ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town! ♪
Thank you!