Watch with the power of Tamiya on all TVs!
When watching TV, be sure to turn on the light in the room!
Those who don't have money, come to mine!
I don't have it either, but I'm worried
Look at the blue sky and the white clouds
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
Come to me, you who have no job
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
I wonder what will happen in the meantime
I know, I know, I know
If you know, keep quiet and follow me
I know, I know, I know, I know
If the world ends, you and I will meet again
The future of the prayers of the gods will be set in your hands
What's wrong?
What the hell is this?!
Oh, you got that catalog too?
It's too cruel! You're fooling my colleague!
What's wrong, Tegai?
Did something happen to Ryo-chan?
Listen, Reiko-san, Nakagawa-kun.
Three days ago, Ryo-san was asked to buy the latest version of the 200,000-yen computer,
because it would cost half the price if it was a direct purchase.
If the latest version is half the price, that's a good thing.
But when I looked at the catalog of this delivery that was distributed at the station today,
it was actually 70,000 yen.
So Ryo-chan spent 30,000 yen?
Hey, don't say bad things about people.
Look at this carefully.
I can buy it cheaply because I have more than five customers.
It's not strange that I paid 30,000 yen for that effort.
I see.
Wait a minute.
What?
If you pay 30,000 yen for five people,
you can get 150,000 yen from your colleague.
I see.
It's a fraud to make 150,000 yen just by collecting people who buy it.
Don't be silly!
Think about it carefully, Tegai.
It's a profit for the company to sell five of the stock computers,
and it's a profit for you to buy a 200,000-yen computer for half the price.
I'll make 30,000 yen for each one.
There's no one who's making a profit and losing money.
I see.
Then it's okay to keep the four ways.
If you say so.
Mr. Tegai, don't be fooled.
It's unnecessary for Ryo-chan to make a profit.
That's right.
If Tegai collects the four people who want to buy the computer,
he can buy it for 70,000 yen.
I see.
Hey, don't blow in the unnecessary wisdom.
Anyway, I spent a lot of money on the computer yesterday,
so I'm already late.
No way.
What?
What are you talking about?
Oh, sir.
Good morning.
Sir, please listen to me.
Ryo-san is...
I'm sorry.
I'm on patrol...
Stop it, Ryo-chan.
Well, sir, that's...
Actually, I have something to ask you.
Huh?
Hey, Itaike-kun.
Come in.
Oh, yes.
Um, nice to meet you.
Boss, what's with you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
What's with you?
It's I, Itaike-kun, a patrol officer who became a member of my office.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Akimoto Reiko.
Oh, nice to meet you, too.
You have a pretty body shape.
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa.
Oh, my God.
Wow, you're cool.
This office is like a model club.
I'm Terada Ryo.
I'm the best!
But you're not.
Ah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Ryotsu, as you can see, Itaike-kun is a little weak.
The director asked me to fix him.
No way! I'm that role?
You're good at guessing.
Anyway, train him well.
Itaike-kun.
Yes?
This Ryotsu chief will guide you.
Thank you, Ryotsu-senpai.
Hey, can you walk faster, Itaike?
Yes.
Senpai is faster.
I'm the standard speed of Japanese.
Thank you.
No!
What?
Scary!
No!
You're in my way!
Go away!
Hello.
Please.
Thank you.
You know what?
Police officers should always be proud.
Don't say that you're a police officer loved by the citizens.
Senpai!
What are you doing?
I can't see.
Please help me.
I did it.
I was saved.
Why don't you refuse?
I was going to refuse, but I felt bad if I didn't get it.
You idiot!
You're working part-time there.
And you're a fool to go with me.
I'm sorry.
Don't leave me!
Yes.
Hey, Senpai.
Me?
This is the latest computer-compatible all-automatic sewing machine.
This is supposed to be 150,000 yen, but this time...
It's only 80,000 yen!
Ah, that's cheap.
Right?
See?
It's like this.
You can sew anything with just a cloth.
It looks convenient.
Right?
How about one?
But I don't use a sewing machine.
Oh, no.
You're not good enough, sir.
You're good at gambling.
Let's add another 10,000 yen and make a deal with 70,000 yen.
But...
No, I can't win against you.
I can't win against you, sir.
Then I'll add this sewing machine set as a service.
Here's 70,000 yen.
What?
70,000 yen.
I'm weak.
I have 70,000 yen...
I have it!
That idiot is gone again.
Senpai!
Senpai...
What's that?
It's a sewing machine.
Don't you shop while patrolling?
No, I didn't.
I was bought when I noticed it.
What?
I've never used a sewing machine.
I see.
Your personality is the problem.
All right, follow me.
Yes, sir.
Well, well, ladies.
Have a look.
What is it?
I'll give it back.
What?
I bought it by mistake.
I'll cancel it.
No way.
It's a problem.
I sold it once.
I'll tell you again.
I'll cancel it!
Yes, immediately.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to you, I got 70,000 yen back.
You can refuse it yourself.
But I thought it would be bad if I refused.
It's not bad.
Just look at the other person's face and say, "I don't need it."
It's about my daily life.
Do you understand that?
Yes, I do.
If you don't voice your opinion, you won't be able to live in a good city.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Welcome.
Well, um...
Here's the menu.
Phew, I'm screwed.
I don't want to be cheated on again.
I see.
Just like Senpai said, I'll look into the eyes of the other person...
Excuse me!
How about 10 sets of new hamburgers?
Okay, then I'll...
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
How about freshly fried potatoes?
How about a set of fries?
Please...
Where did Itai-ke go?
Itai-ke!
You got robbed again?
I can't eat 10 hamburgers!
I'll help you.
Sorry.
It's lunch time.
Where's your drink?
Don't go.
You'll get robbed again.
Then,
why don't you come to my room?
I have some juice.
You live in a mansion like this?
It's 3 minutes away from the station.
Isn't the rent pretty high?
It's 200,000 yen.
200,000 yen?
I couldn't refuse it because it was recommended by a real estate agency.
Hey, hey, hey!
Is there such a person who can save up so much newspaper?
Oh, this is all today's money.
I couldn't refuse it because you gave me some money.
Here you go.
What's this room?
I bought some things from the market and catch sales,
so I ended up like this.
What?
You don't need a fire extinguisher like this.
But the lady who came to sell it was so unfortunate.
Actually, I'm going to the hospital.
My parents are in the hospital due to a car accident.
I have to buy this or I'll be in trouble.
I understand.
Then, one, please.
One, please.
Just one?
What?
If it's just one, I'll be in trouble.
I understand. I'll buy it.
I'll buy everything.
Thank you very much.
That's a lie.
What's this?
I'm sorry.
A video of English conversation?
Are you going to be an English teacher?
I'm sorry.
It's not just English.
I've been bought all the foreign language tapes in the world.
That's right.
French, Norwegian, and Vietnamese.
What do you think is the correct Edo dialect?
I was just bought.
Is this a demolition stone?
Yes.
Why is this in the room?
I was passing by the jewelry store.
It's a big bargain that goes four years in a row.
It's not like the Olympics.
I'm sorry.
Did you buy a demolition stone and have a grave?
I was also evicted for ten years.
Senior!
Then, what is this simple toilet?
There must be a toilet and a bath in this room.
That's ...
This is the toilet?
There's a bath in the back, but there are a lot of bookstores, art and literature museums, and so on.
The library will open.
Do you want to see the bedroom?
No, I'm fine.
I'm not going to get angry anymore.
There are a lot of things everywhere.
Itai, sit down.
I can't sit down.
You bought most of the things in this room by mail, right?
Yes, I don't think you can see it with the piano, but there is a water bed and a tropical fish set in the back.
You didn't sell it to the seller, but why did you buy so much?
There's a direct mail from the mail every day.
I think it's around here.
There it is.
It comes like this.
In a day?
Yes.
There's a postcard for the transformation in it.
I think it's here.
If you put this out, the goods will arrive.
Of course. It's an application postcard.
But it says, "Put it out within a few days."
I feel bad if I don't put it out.
It's okay not to put it out.
If you do that, the room will be full of things.
I'm sorry.
What if your throat is dry?
Oh, by the way, it was juice, right?
Here you go.
It was probably this refrigerator.
Oh.
I found it.
Here.
Oh.
By the way, it hurts.
Yes.
Why are there three refrigerators?
The other day, I was walking around the store and I was robbed.
You have a lot of money.
Most of them are loans.
Even if you say it's a loan, if you buy this much, the monthly payment will be difficult.
That's right.
Please look at this.
Oh, it's a cotton candy.
It's nostalgic.
No, it's a credit card.
What?
You have so much?
It's been so long and I never pay the annual fee.
There are about a thousand in a hurry.
How can I live from now on?
Anyway, which products have you delivered within 8 days?
Well, World Art Training Week, Athletic Equipment, CDMD Compo and ...
Put it on the list. Everyone can return.
Huh?
There's a system called "cooling off".
Most people can cancel a contract if they don't understand it.
Can you do that too?
You don't even read the contract.
It's always written in any contract.
On the corner.
I didn't know.
I'll take care of the card company.
Thank you very much.
Well.
I've cleaned up a little, but there's still a lot.
All I can do is force it with a strong blow.
Ah...
What?
Are you paying back?
All of this?
Yeah.
It's all unprocessed.
But...
Call the manager.
Yes.
Um...
Leave it to me.
I'm good at talking.
Great.
I'm really going to get all the candy.
However, the troublesome thing is the candy that was bought in this town.
Ah, I'm sorry.
You should go to a place where catch-sales are well used.
Yes.
I often do it on Sunday.
It's a catch-sales gold.
I'm sure you're the same group.
There should be a monster over there.
You're also a joke...
Ah!
No one's here!
Oh no!
They already caught me!
Where are you?
Hey, Taikei!
When you become a member,
all the travel, hotels, and movies will be special fees.
That's amazing.
Most young people are joining the club.
Really?
Then,
it means you're joining us...
Ah, senpai!
Hey, Taikei!
Don't say you don't need to!
But, there's no admission fee or fee,
so you can join for free.
That's right!
Hey!
You're not going to get paid for staying a member!
What?
Well, it's just a little.
It's about 20,000 yen a month.
It'll cost you 240,000 yen a year!
Huh?
I didn't even say that!
Look, there's nothing more expensive than this!
Then, I'll take this...
Hey, wait!
You don't have any teaching materials for language, right?
Oh, if that's the case...
Here.
The correct Edoben.
Can I use it?
Wait a minute!
Huh?
It's a paper that was bought at your house.
Cancel it!
Huh?
Oh, that's impossible.
Look, it's the 125th edition of the application form...
Oh!
I-If I read it well, there's an exception!
Let's cancel it!
Cancel it!
One teaching material video is over.
Okay, next.
Hey, Taikei!
Wait!
Hey, what are you selling?
It's a fashion ring.
There's no return list.
Ouch!
Let's go!
Um...
The high-end jewelry is very cheap right now.
No!
Wow, he ran away with a single word.
That's why I said I don't need a single word.
Um, do you have a survey?
I'm busy, so I can't.
Give me something else!
Excuse me!
The survey is fine, isn't it?
I was a beautiful woman.
That's why you're no good!
Look at this!
Huh?
Look, a young man like you is already caught.
It's true!
Oh, I'm going to the cafe.
Look closely.
It's from now on.
At first, it's like a date.
Oh, I'm on the phone.
Someone's here!
I changed with a man!
Try being persuaded by two men for two hours.
Most of them will fall.
That woman is a food.
Oh, I met the same man.
In my case, I signed it in three minutes.
Don't be stubborn, idiot!
I'm sorry.
And you won.
A woman called me and called me.
It's like that.
Oh, that too.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Hmm.
The other things I bought here are
a hundred-year-old set of art books,
a body-building set, and a grand piano.
All right!
What are you going to do?
Oh, my God!
I want an art book!
I want to buy a body-building set!
I want to go on a trip abroad cheaply!
I'm not sure how to spend the money!
Senior!
Huh? Huh?
I have an art book!
If you have a body-building set,
I'd like to go on a trip abroad!
Now's the chance!
Among these, where are you handling the grand piano?
Yes!
That's just me!
I can't return the loan, so I'll return the piano.
What?
It says here that it may be used as an used one.
Well, that's possible.
What?
Huh?
Then,
you can have it.
Y-Yes.
Don't run away!
I'm always scared of the grand piano.
What?
So you took it all out?
I sold the things I couldn't find to the used one.
Thanks to that, there's nothing left in Itaike's room.
But, there's a problem with Itaike-san, who can buy anything easily.
Yeah.
That's the problem.
I think Itaike-san's personality won't be fixed for the rest of his life.
Don't worry.
My idea made it so that no one would buy anything from me.
Huh? How did you do that?
Senpai, help me!
Huh?
R-Ryo-chan is with two people?
I'm Itaike.
Mr. Itaike!
He asked a toy company I know to make a mask that looks like me.
Ah, so Senpai's face means that no one from Catch Sales is coming.
Exactly.
But, Itaike-san, what's going on?
I'm sure Catch Sales is not coming anymore, but if I try to go shopping around here...
As long as you don't pay me, I won't sell anything to you!
Don't you dare to come to my store until you bring me a large amount of ramen!
Don't show your face until I pay you!
Go home now!
I'll show you what I can do!
T-that was quite a blow.
Senpai is a very bad debtor.
I can't take this anymore.
Ryo-san!
Huh?
This is bad, Ryo-san!
What is it, Terai?
Look at this!
Hm?
Is the evil media company a project bankruptcy?
The company name is the same as the company in the catalog!
What?!
Hm?
Huh?
The number you called is not available right now.
What?! I'm screwed! I spent 350,000 yen on it!
Ryo! If you can't get the computer, give me back my 100,000 yen.
Okay, Terai. But I've already used up all the money I've made.
Oh, right!
Itai-ke.
Yes.
Would you like to buy this card?
This card is all premium cards.
There's a special card that costs 50,000 yen each, and if you're a fan, you'll cry and be happy.
It's worth 1 million yen in total.
I'll lose 500,000 yen today, so please buy it for me!
But I'm not interested in card games.
300,000 yen is fine!
But...
No, Itai-ke. You have to refuse here.
Shut up!
Itai-ke.
I'm begging you. I thought you were helping me.
Itai-ke, I refuse!
Itai-ke.
Look at the other person's face and say, "I don't need it!"
Hey, Itai-ke, say, "I don't need it!"
That's why I said, "I don't need it!"
I... I... I don't need it!
I was rejected for the first time.
You're great, Itai-ke.
If you do it, you can do it, right?
Yes, thank you.
Itai-ke.
Then how about this helicopter?
500,000 yen is fine for 100,000 yen.
I don't need it!
Itai-ke.
I don't need it! I don't need it! I don't need it!
Yahoo!
I'm going to be completely rejected!
Itai-ke, you've finally overcome your weakness.
Why are you always rejected when I'm around?
What are you talking about?
Ryo-chan taught you, didn't she?
No way!
Ryo-san.
Giku.
Give me back 100,000 yen.
Uuuh!
Itai-ke, wait for me!
Once again!
Say "yes" one more time!
I don't need it!
Itai-ke.
Uuuh!
Everyone was a child once, but everyone forgets
A politician with a great face and a blue aunt above his eyes
Turn and see that corner
Everyone can meet everyone
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!
I did it!
Viking is free to eat at only 500 yen!
If you look closely, it's a woman's limited!
Damn it! I was also born a woman!
If this happens, true men and women will be sick!
I will fight for my rights!
Next time, I'm an actress, Ryoko Kameari!
Nice to meet you!
There is a turtle over there
There must be a turtle
Everyone come to our town
Thank you!