A
When you watch TV,
make your room bright and
please watch it from a distance!
Meow Meow
Those who don't have money,
come to me!
I don't have any,
but I'm worried.
I'm worried.
Look!
The blue sky,
the white clouds,
they'll be all right
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Those who don't have work,
come to me!
Come here!
I don't have any,
but I'm worried.
Look!
The red clouds are burning
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
They'll be all right.
I know, right?
I know, I know!
If you know, just stay quiet and come with me!
Just stay quiet and come with me!
UwU
You don't have to worry!
I know, I know!
That's all for today.
I hope you enjoyed it.
The young boys' crime is in the low age category.
As a child, it's not a person's business.
You're in the way.
Can you move out of the bed?
Ah, yes, yes.
Even so, we moved in a long time ago.
Why are you in a corner?
No, it's too big.
I can't calm down without a wall behind me.
It's a poor thing.
By the way, what are the children doing?
I was playing games until a while ago, but I think I'm already asleep.
I see.
You're sleeping well.
Well, it's okay for my child.
I was playing games at home.
It's summer vacation, so I want you to take me somewhere to play.
Shinji went to Hawaii with his father and everyone.
I want to go somewhere, too.
Yoshiko went to a mountain in the countryside.
He wanted to go fishing.
I want to catch a cicada or a beetle.
What happened to your face?
Haruo went to the sea and went fishing and made fireworks.
Because I love the sea, I want to go fishing there.
I want to go fishing.
Haruo, who became a monk in the sea.
What's going on?
He's making a wasp face.
Yes.
Mr. Mokuzu is enjoying cruising with his family on weekends.
Well, it's best to meet nature that you don't get to see in the city.
The beauty of the stars seen in the sea is so moving.
I don't think the kids will worry about flying.
I'm glad I bought a cruiser.
It's fun to stay on a ship.
Dad is amazing! I caught such a big fish the other day!
This is it!
Dad is a young captain!
What? You bought a ship?
You don't have to be so surprised.
What's wrong, Terai? Are you finally desperate for life?
No, don't make a fuss.
I'm not making a fuss.
What's wrong?
You have a life that suits you.
That's right, Terai.
That's the point. I was wondering what my life was like until now.
I was busy at work and didn't have time to spend time with the kids.
I didn't have anything that I could call my hobby.
I think I'll buy a ship and spend time with nature for the sake of the children's education.
I think I'll get the job, too.
Are you suddenly talking about cruisers?
You, who have never been in a life of life.
I'm going to give you a home steal because you're only two outs behind the nine-point lead.
You, shut up!
Terai is thinking of you.
Maybe, Terai.
Haa...
By the way, I had a lot of fun when I first rode my father's cruiser.
I have a lot of fun.
That's right.
Well, your dad's back looks bigger and stronger than usual.
That's right. I want to ride a cruiser like a father and a man like Yuzo Kayama.
What's a young captain? You're the most unsuitable cruiser in Japan.
It's not like that. Yuzo Kayama is impossible, but if it's a young captain like Kunie Tanaka...
We can't keep up with you because you talk too much.
Really?
Do you know how much a cruiser costs? It's as expensive as a ball of cotton flying out.
That's because there's something you can dig out. It's this.
It's perfect for a father who's a working man. It's a cruiser for a family.
Wow, Ryo-san, it's a cruiser! A cruiser!
Yeah, I know. But is this something you can get with a working man's salary?
Welcome!
All of our cruisers are the best.
Hey, you!
What?
You're a fake real estate agent and a fake travel agent!
What are you talking about?
Are you looking for a cruiser?
Yeah, but it looks expensive.
Don't worry about it. This cruiser is delivered with confidence by us.
It costs 80 million yen, and it's 40 million yen.
80 million yen is 40 million yen?
It's half the price!
Are you going to buy it?
I-I can't...
We've got something even more expensive for you.
Here it is.
It's 80 million yen, and it's 100 million yen.
100 million yen? That's a lot of money, Ryo-san.
And now we've got a hanging health machine and some tea mushrooms.
It's getting more and more expensive.
Yes! Then, make a contract for 100 million yen right away.
100 million yen?
Hmm, it might be possible if we make a contract.
Wait a minute, Ryan, you should look it up more carefully.
N-No, it's not like that.
Now is the time to read the contract.
If you miss this, the cruiser will belong to someone else.
I see. You're a fast winner.
That's right, sir.
Now, hurry up and sign here.
Well, wait a minute.
It might be a 1/1 kit plastic model.
Take it!
Well, it's a 1/1 kit plastic model.
Plastic model?
It's a water-cooled motor.
Are you going to use batteries to move it?
It's a 1/1 kit plastic model, and it's 30 cm long.
Are you going to sell such a bad plastic model for 10 million yen?
This is a joke.
The real one is here.
This is the real one.
This is also 10 million yen.
Wow, it's big and beautiful.
No, no, I don't know yet.
That might be the bottom.
Now, hurry up and sign here.
If you keep moving it, you can sell it.
Yeah.
Look closely.
There's a mark that connects with another ship here.
I thought it was strange.
The outside is well deceived, but the bottom has a subtle change in color.
No, this is a two-tone color that is popular now.
Don't be silly.
The accident was a waste of money.
I'm sure you could connect the two.
I understand.
I'll make it cheap.
5 million yen.
It's expensive.
3 million yen.
Not yet.
2 million yen.
It's 1 million yen.
I won't give you a better one.
1 million yen.
It's okay.
Yes.
Okay, fix this for 1 million yen.
Okay, sign here.
Really?
It's okay.
Yes.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
I did it.
Now the cruiser is mine.
It's all thanks to me.
When you first open it, invite me to cruising for free.
Thank you, Ryo.
I didn't think I'd get it for 1 million yen.
I'm glad we got the boat license and the marina.
Really?
Yes.
I can see Terai and his children enjoying it.
When it comes to cruising, I have a lot of fun memories.
Let's go, Ryo.
Now you go.
Me too.
Let's go.
The End
Hey, you guys!
Imagine something more public.
At least...
The End
Something like this.
That's right.
Because the main character is Terai-san.
The End
Let's go!
Hey, wait a minute, Terai.
What?
Your name is not good.
Blue Max doesn't suit you at all.
What?
All right. This is fine.
Life-Sending Bant?
This is the perfect name for you.
No way.
We're in the water!
It's floating!
Of course!
Captain Eos!
I don't like it.
No...
When we go out to the sea,
the head of the ship is the most important.
Everyone!
You must listen to the captain!
Yes!
All the responsibility is on the captain.
All the responsibility is on me?
You're so tough.
All right.
Terai.
Show me the cabin before you go out.
Yeah.
Look. It's so big.
Here you go.
What?
It's big, isn't it?
It's twice the size of the previous house.
Damn it.
I was beaten.
I slept in a sleeping bag in the tent at night.
I made it with a sleeping bag at night.
It's really crazy.
It's the same as a camping site.
That's why it was that price.
But Terai thinks this is the real thing.
Let's keep quiet.
Yes.
There are many ships.
This is the only place near and cheap.
Oh?
It looks like we'll be hit on the left.
Dad, this side is also hit.
Don't return with the locker of the car.
It's a hard job to hit a human ship.
It's a right-right.
Terai, you are pretty good.
It's the first time.
But I found the line very good.
I-Is that so?
All right!
T-Tenai!
It's dangerous if you go too fast!
The sea also has obstacles!
Don't drive recklessly despite the selfishness of Mark!
This piercing feeling...
I'm the captain!
I'm the man of the sea!
T-Tenai!
Whoa! It's on!
Calm down!
Raise the rod and wind the reel!
Phew...
Me too!
Calm down and don't rush!
Yay!
I did it!
Amazing!
Whoa!
All right!
Then I'll grab the best sushi with this one!
Hmm...
I'll have this sushi with tempura and the horse mackerel with tataki!
I'll leave it to you, Ryo-chan!
Yeah!
Wow, it's delicious!
The freshness is different, isn't it?
Right?
This is a taste you can't taste unless you go to the sea!
I didn't catch any...
But it was because I had my cruiser!
Well, that's true!
But there are a lot of cruisers and yachts out there!
And they're all very expensive!
Hello!
Oh, hello!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Sushi is a combination of freshly caught fish!
Well...
I see.
I don't have to leave this alone.
What?
You're going to deliver it with this cruiser?
What do you mean, Ryo-chan?
With this "Life Delivery Band"
You can go around the cruisers
And you can make sushi with freshly caught fish
Or you can make sashimi with it!
And you can deliver seafood and vegetables
Depending on your order
So it's called a "ocean convenience store"
But why would you do that?
Well...
It's to help the cruiser's "lone hell"
To help the cruiser's "lone hell"
Right, "lone hell"?
Ryo-chan...
Ufufu...
Every time we call you
For the cruisers and yachts who enjoy fishing and diving
Freshly caught fish
We'll make fresh sashimi and sushi
On the spot
Please feel free to call us
And other stuff like
Jet-ski, aqualung, goldfish bait
And mobile phone
A freshly caught fresh sashimi?
Sounds good
Hey!
Over here, please!
Yes, sir!
Hey, terai!
Get in between that cruiser and that cruiser!
Y-Yes!
Ah! You idiot! Over there!
Now!
Ah, we somehow got away.
Ah, my life is on the line!
Don't worry! Business is a crime!
No way!
He's like a demon.
You...
Here you are!
Do you want sashimi? Or sushi?
I guess sashimi is the best.
I'll take this.
Here you are!
Can I have some sushi?
Get ready to eat!
Don't just sit there.
Help your wife and children!
What?
It's for your daily wage!
I-I see.
Give me the money!
What? The money?
How nice.
I'll have some sashimi.
Here you are!
Marmaid, sashimi!
Ah, Nakagawa!
I don't have money!
Make me work in Hokkaido!
Reiko!
Ten cakes, still on?
Ah, wife, smile a little more lovingly.
Terai!
You're in the way!
Oh...
51, 52...
Terai!
I'm going to distribute sales!
Huh?
But I've made a lot of money.
Well, then I'll give you 5% of your income.
Thank you.
No matter how much you do, 5% is too much, senpai.
That's right. Why do you take 95% of it?
I came up with the idea.
I made sashimi, I grabbed sushi, plus there's a management fee.
That's terrible.
The ship belongs to you, so you have to make it at least 5%!
Ryo, at least you can get a repair fee.
I got it.
What's this, a repair fee?
Thank you.
Hey, poor people!
Shiratori Reiji!
Why are you wearing a coat in the middle of the summer?
It's hot and painful.
Aromani's jacket and coat.
The tie is made of plastic.
The shoes are made of leather.
The whole body is 10 million yen.
Even in the middle of the summer, good things are good.
More importantly, you seem to be talking about small money.
Take this!
I don't understand!
What is this?
It's not a child's bank account again.
My body just reacted.
Please, please, please!
By the way, I have a question.
What's that duck's foot boat floating in the lake?
Terrible! My cruiser!
Cruiser?
Hahaha!
Cruiser is the one that I'm riding, the super rich guy!
Kuhuhu!
It's true that the other side is many times bigger.
It's cool.
It doesn't look like it!
Both men and cruisers!
Oh, do you mean I can beat my life's money log?
Uh...
You...
Dad...
It can't be helped.
You see, that's not all there is to it.
That's the only way to win this battle.
What do you think?
Wow...
That dice...
That's ridiculous.
That's bad.
I'm not going to lose, man!
But I've put it to my body.
I'm going to win!
So it's all on you!
I'll lose!
I have to win tonight!
That's right, I can't catch it!
Alright!
Ahh!
It seems to have been used up.
What kind of guy is it when it comes to driving a car?
That's right, I should have been careful with the Super-Karemochi!
Hey, get off!
Alright!
Good boy!
Wait for me, Reiko-san!
Bam!
Hooray!
It's finally starting to run!
Damn it, it won't collapse!
It's catching up!
It's coming, Terai!
Get it to stop more!
Ahahaha!
Here we go!
Damn it, Terai!
It's slowly getting worse!
Up the speed a little!
I got it!
Oh dear...
What's wrong, Terai?
I'm drunk!
Are you alright, Mr. Terai?
No...
You...
You, you...
Alright, you two, I'm counting on you!
Ryo-san, can you drive?
What? This is just like a car, right?
Just a little bit here.
There you go. Let's go!
It's fast!
Go, go, go, go!
Alright, I can see it!
You've finally caught up!
Alright, speed up even more!
Wait up, you bastard!
That's it!
Take this!
How's that?
Damn, I can't keep up with speed!
You're not going anywhere!
Alright, let's have a little race!
Ryo!
Go, go, go, go!
Alright!
I'm out!
Go!
Alright!
I'm out of here!
Take this!
Senpai!
In front!
Hm?
Huh?
Ryo!
Hey, are you alright?
Yeah, we're fine!
What the hell?
Aaaaaaah!
A
I'm saved!
Can't get through!
Aah!
This sweet potato might make me super-poor again.
"Groans"
"My life's sending card"
"It became two and sank into the sea"
"Groans"
"You, be careful!"
"Today, Papa's cruiser became two and sank into the sea."
"Papa was fainted."
"The end."
"The End"
"Like someone is calling me, I walked after the rain"
"I looked back and walked"
"My mother was holding my hand"
"At that time, I felt"
"A strange feeling"
"So"
"I walked on the black tile of the arcade"
"Everyone was a child once"
"But everyone forgot"
"The politician with a proud face"
"The president's mother's affection"
"I Bang"
"A girl of the year."
" electrifying"
Thank you!