When you watch TV,
Make the room brighter and try to look away.
I look at the sunset floating on the river.
I throw a stone, and it flies to the shoe.
I wonder if it's a joke.
I was laughed at as it was.
Even as a little boy, a child with no age
The cityscape of a cat purring won't change.
It's so kind.
From the floodgates of the cat's hat
To Kaishakuten
The sunset falls.
Falling
Tomorrow will end like this
But I realized that I lost happiness again
Because I'm stupid
Kanrui! The first sight of the Terai
It's about noon.
Do you want to have some katsudon?
Ryo-san, please have mine too.
What is it, Terai?
Isn't today lunch?
Then you have some katsudon too.
No, it's Morisoba.
What? Morisoba?
You just got paid.
The loan is too tight.
I can only get 5,000 yen a month.
It's a good idea to get married.
Mr. Omawari!
What's wrong?
I forgot my wallet.
I'm in a hurry, Mr. Omawari.
Can you lend me 5,000 yen?
5,000 yen?
Please.
Kanada!
I'll pay it back.
I'll be in a hurry.
I beg you!
I'm sorry!
I'll get it back.
I don't have time.
That's right.
We can have a katsudon and a morisoba at the branch.
Ryo-san, tanma!
Can you take out my morisoba?
What?
Didn't you ask for 5,000 yen?
You didn't even ask for a name or address?
Yeah, it's not someone around here.
I didn't see him.
You're an idiot.
Then he must have spent 5000 yen on something.
He won't come back for sure.
I wonder.
Come on.
In this harsh world,
if you see people, you think they're thieves.
That's the way modern people are.
I can't help it.
If you can't help it, you don't need the police.
I'm telling you, I won't let you do my job.
Okay.
Hey!
Hey.
Oh, this is Mr. Terai and Mr. Ryo.
Good work on the patrol.
You're on a diet and you don't have a job?
You're taking a dog walk?
You're so nice.
I'm not on a diet.
I'm on a job.
Oh, really?
I always see you at the pachinko place.
Don't worry.
I'm the same when I don't have a job.
Right, Pochi?
What?
I'm John.
Right, John?
You're so annoying, John.
I'm so attached to Mr. Terai.
Dogs and cats are popular with Terai.
Hey, Grandpa, Grandma, how are you?
Hi, Matsui.
Hi, Kiyohara.
How's your back?
Oh, Mr. Terai.
Oh, Mr. Takahashi.
Did you find the missing number?
Yes.
I found it.
Oh, I see.
Bye.
Hey, do you know the address of that old woman?
Well, yeah.
Communication with local residents is important.
It's for when the time comes.
When the time comes?
What kind of when the time comes can you find the address?
Oh, there's a dog barking right ahead of here.
Let's go from here.
That dog has been in the hospital for a day because of the cold.
Yeah.
Grandma, watch out!
I'll do it for you.
Oh, Mr. Terai, I'm sorry.
Hey, Mr. Terai, we're patrolling.
I think it's better than a pachinko.
What do you think, Grandma?
After your grandpa died,
you're all alone and lonely, aren't you?
That's not true.
Recently, Genjiro, the third-born, has made a tea-octopus friend.
He's going to karaoke.
Right, Grandma?
I don't want to, Mr. Terai.
I know everything.
Speaking of the third-born,
you know Mr. Kawata, the tofu shop's owner, right?
Oh, the one with the big, big belly?
Oh, dear.
I'm tired of it.
It took me three hours just to go around there.
Mr. Terai is a local-based guy.
He always calls people who come to him.
It's like he has to do a sent-out banter
whenever there's a runner in baseball.
He always does a sent-out banter.
He's a life-saving guy.
But that's important for a police officer.
Yeah, I don't know what's so funny about it
that I became a police officer.
The police officer's charm is
when he's caught a criminal.
When he's caught a criminal.
By the way,
have you ever been caught by a police officer?
I don't remember that.
I don't remember that either.
I don't know, either.
Perhaps he's never been caught
by a police officer since he was found out.
Perhaps he's never been caught by a police officer since he was found out.
Action!
Did I catch a cold?
Hey, that's cheating!
What's with the later?
You should've done it earlier.
I don't care.
I don't care!
Ouch!
Please be quiet!
Huh?
A game where you become a detective and catch a criminal?
Yeah.
It's pretty difficult.
I see.
So there's a criminal in here.
Everyone's got a scary face.
By the way,
your dad was a police officer, too, right?
Yeah, by the way.
By the way?
I've been a police officer since you were born.
So, Dad,
you've caught a thief, right?
Yeah, I've caught a thief, right?
What do you feel when you catch a criminal?
Huh?
A criminal?
Yeah.
Even if you say that,
I've never had any experience.
What?
Not even once?
I can't play games or watch a crime drama.
Well, if I have a chance.
Sure, sure.
However,
so if you can't play video games,
then I'll have to teach you a lesson.
deze is a story from the time
you haven't played a game.
Is the entertainment related to a game?
Yes, it is.
Oh, I see.
Well,
then you go and play video games,
and learn how to play a game.
I'll be there right away.
Really?
Yes, please.
We're going to arrest the culprit.
Reiko and Nakagawa, head south, Ryotsu and Terai, head north.
Yes, sir!
Hey, chief!
What is it, Ryotsu?
If you arrest the culprit, will you get a reward?
A reward?
If you do a home run, you get a home run prize.
If you play double, you get a double play prize.
Idiot! This isn't a game!
Oh, I don't want to!
I'm just yelling at you, so I don't feel motivated.
If you arrest the culprit, I'll treat you to a drink.
Right, chief?
All right.
If you arrest the culprit, I'll treat you to a drink.
No, chief! I like it!
Let's go, Terai!
Let's start with the basic rules of the investigation, Ryo.
This is...
Ryo, you're going to hit me one by one?
The chief often advises us to pile up small things.
That's like sending a bandit without a runner.
There should be a faster way.
This is the Chirigami Port, as usual.
First, from that block.
That's it!
What?
This is the Kouenbai Post Office, as usual.
Yes, sir.
We ask for your cooperation.
All residents please show your faces.
This is how you'll investigate, Ryo?
Shut up. Leave it to me.
Those who don't show their faces will be considered guilty as the culprit
and be arrested.
Huh?
What's going on?
Is there anyone here, Terai?
Well...
Oh, are you there?
Saito-san from the 4th floor has retired.
What?
No, that's not it. We're looking for the culprit.
The culprit isn't here.
I'm so glad.
You're so glad, aren't you?
I have a good idea.
What?
How about this?
Call the people there to arrest them all.
The culprit must be the one who runs away in a hurry.
Will it work?
I'll throw a sword ball at them.
Is there anyone around?
You're a suspicious man!
Hey, don't arrest me!
Ryo-san, you ran away!
I'm going to arrest you right now!
I'm going to arrest you!
Wait!
This way is the shortcut!
Motoki-san's precious flower!
This is good.
What?
Ryo-san?
I'm in trouble!
You're in trouble!
Get a hold of yourself!
Take care!
Tsu-no 0075!
We're going to make a witness!
All right!
I got you!
Ryo-san, I'll take charge!
Seori!
Hey!
Come out!
Sorry, it didn't hurt.
Why? You're a fool!
You idiot! Why did you run away?
No, I thought if I found Saori's figure,
I would be told something again.
You're such a troublemaker.
Let's go, Terai.
Ryo, where are you going?
That naughty dog is in the hospital because of the cold.
Ryo! Ryo! Ryo!
The police is here!
You idiot! Hurry up and say that!
In this case, we'll have to arrest him first and then find out who the culprit is.
Is it really okay to do something like this, Ryo?
It's okay. The police officer's job is to arrest the culprit.
We'll have to do it a little forcefully.
I-I guess so...
Let's go!
We're going to arrest him!
What's going on, Ryo? Is the culprit here?
Um...um...
He's not here, Ryo.
Okay, next!
Why are we the ones being arrested?
That's too much.
Let's ask him about it, Ryo.
That old lady knows a lot about people around here.
I'll go ask her.
Yeah, hey!
Terai!
This is getting a little annoying.
Hm?
Is this a new store today?
We've got to go.
Ryo! Ryo!
I heard something nice!
What?
Where did he go?
I've been trying to get information about people who moved here lately.
I can hear his heart beating.
He's got a sweet taste.
Why is the police here?
I don't know.
That's not good, isn't it?
What?
No good.
I knew it.
This line is more...
No, that's it.
No good.
I-I'm in a bad mood right now.
I'm in a bad mood...
Hey, wait!
Huh?
There's still some bullets left.
What?
No...
I went to the bathroom...
Hey, you!
It's time for the 0075!
Get outta here!
Hey, wait!
You're going to die!
Ugh!
Where did Ryo-san go?
Hm?
What the...?
Wait!
I'm not waiting!
Get him!
What are you doing?!
Wait!
Damn it! You got away!
It was only a little while ago.
But now...
It's all because you're so slow.
That's why you can't catch the culprit.
What do you feel when you catch the culprit?
Even if you say that, I don't have any experience.
What? You don't have any experience?
I don't think I can do it.
I can't...
What?!
Ryo, look at this!
What? What's wrong with the 10-yen coin?
This 10-yen coin was dropped by the culprit.
This 10-yen coin with the scratches is...
Hey, old lady.
I wonder if anyone has moved here recently.
Recently?
Oh, there's a turtle over there.
Two of them.
Over there...
Three of them in Okatsushika.
And two in Okirasou in Nichome.
You're really knowledgeable.
I wonder if you know anything else about them.
I wonder...
Oh, right.
There's a new person who moved to Okirasou.
I think his name is Tsuruta.
He has a 10-yen coin with the old horror and Giza-giza.
He has a 10-yen coin with Giza-giza written on it.
He likes saving it as his hobby.
When he gets the continuation, he said...
No way!
What are you thinking about?
Go away morons!
That's the 007!
This is it.
Great, you go around you.
You!
Tsuruta-san, this is your delivery.
Here, I'll open it now.
You're the one!
The one from before!
Arrest him!
I told you, Terai!
I-I'll arrest him!
Tsuruta!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Wait!
Wait for the chief!
What?
Give me the alcohol!
What is this?
Wait!
I told you to wait!
I can't do this.
Damn it, did you lose sight of me?
I'm slow and I'm not good at fighting.
I'm not good at fighting either.
I'm not good at arresting criminals.
Oh...
That's why you can't arrest a criminal!
You better hold on.
I'm not going to let you down!
That's right!
Oh...
"I'm not going to let you down"
I'm not going to let you down!
Look at this one.
This guy is...
It hurts!
Terai, arrest him!
I-I'm not going to let the one from before!
I'm arresting him!
I'm not going to let you down!
Even if you're dead...
I'm not giving you away!
All right.
I'm going to kill you!
Calm down, Terai!
What are you talking about, Maruka?
It's the first time I've ever arrested a criminal.
I'll do it, I'll do it!
I'm going to run away! I'm going to run away!
Calm down, Terai.
You're not a chicken.
Don't tighten your neck like that.
Put your hands on your head.
Hands...
Don't put your hands on your neck!
I see.
It's the first time.
Hurry up! You're going to die!
The serial killer of the year!
The national police station!
The prison cell 007!
We're arresting you!
This feeling is a free feeling as a policeman.
I feel like I'll never have another chance.
I want to feel this excitement again.
The serial killer of the year!
The national police station!
The prison cell 007!
We're arresting you!
The serial killer of the year!
The national police station!
The prison cell 007!
This refreshing feeling that permeates deep into my heart.
Terai Yoichi, this is the biggest feeling in my life.
Okay, I'm going to burn this feeling in my heart for 10 more times.
Stop it!
That's enough!
Anyway, I'll go to the station.
I'll go to the station.
I did it, Terai!
Ryo-san...
Yeah.
This is the captain's treat for today.
Wait, Ryo-san.
What?
Since we're here...
Huh?
It's done, Ryo-san!
You're already feeling it?
Okay, then.
Oh, by the way...
Please sign this to commemorate your arrest.
What?
What is this?
One...
Two...
Four...
Seven...
Eight...
Ten...
Four...
Seven...
Eight...
Nine...
Fif...
Ten...
Eleven...
Twelve...
Three...
Four...
I was able to arrest the culprit because of the patrol.
I want to be watched closely by some of you.
Well, well, Chief.
It's a happy day today.
Let's go as promised.
With the chief's permission.
I'm sorry.
Oh, the last time.
Thank you for the other day.
No...
Here.
Please eat this with the 5,000 yen you borrowed.
What do you mean?
I didn't know you were really coming to return it.
I see.
I'm glad I could help you.
Please come anytime if you have any trouble.
No, I was in a hurry because of my wife.
I was really helped.
So, you were born safely?
Thanks to you, I have a healthy boy.
And he is a twin.
That's great.
And what's your name?
My name is...
What do you live in?
I live in Koji and Kenji.
The address is the next corner of the second intersection.
It's the house on the corner to the left.
It's good to arrest three people.
After all, that kind of figure suits the temple priest the best.
Really?
Well, sometimes it's a farewell or a final destination.
But I'm going to go with the life of a manly home run.
You have more three-dimensional.
Oh, oh, oh.
I'm from Kobe.
Beef is delicious.
Did something good happen to you?
No, nothing.
Come on, let's eat.
Yes.
Here, have a meal.
I'm hungry.
Oh, I have dinner too.
We did.
It's a become-lady.
See ya, baby.
Hello, Oh.
You didn't believe it, did you?
Yes, what's the matter, boss?
What's your name?
It's Umi.
I want to make friends with you
I want to be loved by you
The more we say it, the more we feel like we're melting
I want to break up with you
For some reason, love is cowardly
Don't hide all the strong things