"When you watch TV, make your room bright and try to look away!"
"I'm a little worried about my mom..."
"Come to me, you poor thing!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried about you."
"Look at the blue sky and the white clouds!"
"It'll be all right eventually!"
"I have no job!"
"Come to me!"
"I'm not here, but I'm worried about you."
"Look at the burning red clouds!"
"It'll all be all right eventually!"
"Do you get it?"
"I get it! I get it!"
"If you do, just come to me!"
"Come and follow me!"
The End
Lemon, what's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Oh, Kankichi.
When I came with my family,
they said that the summer vacation was coming to an end,
so they brought me somewhere.
What? Is that so?
It's not like that. Look at this.
Oh, it's a picture diary.
I was drawn to it when I was a kid.
It's nostalgic.
Which one?
Huh? I went to the pool.
It was fun.
I took a walk with Mikan.
It was hot.
I went to the pool. It was fun.
And the rest is the same.
Hahaha.
There's only one different one.
What's this?
My relative Kankichi came to help the store.
He was drunk and
danced naked with the customer.
It was embarrassing.
Don't write such a thing!
It can't be helped.
He didn't take me anywhere for the summer vacation.
Geppardo, take him.
Well, that's right.
Kankichi, take him somewhere.
Me?
I'm counting on you, Kankichi.
I can't take him anywhere.
But he's the one who comes first.
You don't have a good friend,
but you have a good friend.
Then I can't go.
It's better to work part-time here.
Grandpa.
I got it.
I'll pay for my part-time job and transportation.
Remon, I'll work for you.
Okay, okay.
You're not as cute as you are.
So, where are you off to?
A mountain or a beach?
It is.
Remon's into the love of the people.
The love of the people?
A female ninja of the new princess.
Oh, the old کےのお銀 .
Well, I'm a strong ninja and
I'm pretty cool.
Hey, Kankichi, I wanna see the real ninja.
The real ninja...
Yeah, then we have a friend.
Really, Kankichi?
Yeah.
Grandpa Borubo is running a library in Kagoshima that has a ninja mansion.
Sounds fun.
I want to go there too.
Kyushu...
There are nice hot springs there, so I want to go there too.
Let's go, let's go.
The more you travel, the more fun it is.
Lemon will become a ninja.
The End
It's like a historical drama.
There's no transition.
There must be a ninja in this place, Kankichi.
Yeah, we'll be able to meet a real ninja soon.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Hmm, I'm a little worried if you expect too much.
Well, whatever.
Oh, it's a ninja-like house.
Yeah!
Hmm, this is pretty serious.
Stop it, Gesbro!
Hm?
What is it, Kankichi?
You hear me? This is, in fact, a house for ninja.
Look carefully.
Ah~!
It 테ke about the trap to prevent intruders from the outside.
I won't set such a dangerous trap!
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch...
If you miss one step, you'll hurt Lemon to hell.
I'm just set it up.
I'm not!
Kankichi, how do you get in the house?
Hmm? Ah...
Well, I think...
Oh, I know, I know.
Here we go.
Hmm?
Hmm...
Huh?
Wow!
Amazing! It's a real deal!
It's so nice!
Old Man Goldbeard, are you there?
Are you free?
Well, I've informed you that you're coming.
I'll wait for you up there.
Hmm?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
Oh.
Hey, Kankichi! It's Shuriken!
Well, it's a ninja mansion after all.
Amazing!
Huh? What is it? You're here.
What's wrong?
You look like you're asleep.
It's not a big deal that the guests are coming all the way here, but they don't notice.
Well, it can't be helped.
All right.
Hmm?
Oh, I'm not sleeping!
Oh, wait, wait, it's 3:00, I should have just woke you up already.
I still have half an hour.
Oh, it's Ryotsu.
What are you doing?
Flash mode?
Huh?
Hey, hey.
This Otsugi wants to meet with a ninja.
A fire flower?
A lemon?
I'll buy the fire flower.
Huh?
Oh, sure.
Mmm...
Do you eat or talk?
I don't know which one to talk about.
I thought you were a little shy.
You're a naughty kid.
I've been watching a lot of historical dramas.
That's why I'm talking like this.
I'm interested in the people who like historical dramas at that age.
Let's all do ninja training together.
Yeah! I want to be a ninja!
You look good, Lemon.
You're cute.
Is that so?
That's strange, Debalt.
Shut up! I'm going to calm down.
I don't want to get in the way of your movement.
Why am I the only one in this costume?
That's the special version of Kunoichi.
Big ears to find enemies.
Chain shoulders to protect yourself.
Can you wink?
Like this?
The way you look when you confuse enemies is exactly what Kunoichi looks like.
I see.
That's not strange at all.
Wow, that's great.
That's a new kind of ninja style.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
This old man can't use that kind of ninja style.
What? Is he wearing a mask?
And he's got a good kick.
I guess you should stop.
Where's Kogane-maru?
He's sleeping over there.
He's more like a ninja than Kogane-maru.
Master...
I'm gonna...
Don't make such a rough sound in front of me, you idiot!
Master, I'm terribly sorry.
Thank you for your help, but I have to go out of here today.
What? You're going to go out of here too?
Go ahead!
There's no one here, and my apprentice won't let me go.
This is the end of the line.
This is all because of the Ninja Land we built next door.
Ninja Land?
What's that?
That's the Ninja Land.
There are so many buses and cars!
And I'm gonna go home, I think.
Isn't that a theme park?
Right, it is.
The theme park was recently abolished due to lack of pay for my apprentices' expenses.
I think you should have run away.
If I do, I'll become like an offender, too.
Can I somehow bring another tourist back over here, Lyotsu?
I don't know!
I'm not interested in you.
Let's go!
Wait, Kankichi!
What?
You're watching people in trouble,
and you're leaving without doing anything.
Are you a man?
Lemon.
Lemon, you shouldn't be involved in this.
Grandma, I'll definitely save you if you're a police officer.
That's a TV story.
Even if everyone goes home, Lemon will save this old man.
Lemon?
As expected of you, Princess Lemon.
Princess Lemon?
For seven years of labor...
So cute!
Princess Lemon, I'll risk my life to protect you.
Hey! We're talking about something else!
Don't use the child as a tool!
You're kidding, right?
That's a very good trick.
What?
It's a trick to replace the child.
Damn it, I'm a little frustrated.
I can't help it.
Let's take a break for Lemon.
Hey, stop it!
You're mean!
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm going out to kill you.
Extremely annoying.
I still haven't llegaed to my needs at all.
Just let me go.
Do you need help?
What you're doing is not fair.
I'm worried you'll get sick.
I'd better not.
Is there ever going to be a time when you're a fairy like this?
I'm leaving!
Now, what are you looking at?
I just want to see that beautiful complex.
Amazing!
Ugh...
There are so many people here.
No matter how you think about it, you won't win.
Ryo-tsu, don't say it so easily.
It can't be helped, it's the truth.
Hankichi!
Huh?
It can't be helped.
How about a sandwich and juice?
Huh?
Please give me one.
Yes.
Aha!
Hey, don't be so serious!
That's why I'm a man.
How about tea and lunch?
One Ninja lunch.
Hey, hey.
Hmm.
I just saw this, but I knew it wouldn't be possible at a ninja house.
I wonder if Sanada-style ninja land is something that can't be helped.
Ryo-tsu, Hime.
Hmm.
Huh?
Ah!
Who are you?
Ryo-tsu, Hankichi!
Who is this flashy woman?
When I was looking for Tokugawa's hidden treasure at the spring party last year,
I found a female boss of a thief from Sanada Yukimura's descendants who was trying to take a side trip.
Give me the treasure!
Take this!
Oh yeah!
Huh?
What?
What's up with this girl?
She's the owner of Ninja Land.
What?
Huh?
I didn't think you were a friend with the owner of that crappy ninja house next door.
Shut up!
What are you doing here?
You were arrested along with your friends and sent to jail.
I'm a ninja.
If you're interested in me,
gonyogonyogonyo.
Ah?
Hey!
Hey! I'm sorry for the poor, messy, shabby ninja house!
I-I didn't mean to say that...
Well, I'm busy! Excuse me!
I have to make money to rebuild the house!
Wait, Meitsune!
Now that you know you're the president here, you're getting motivated!
That's right, Ryotsu!
Come on, let's have a game!
Huh? A game?
A game?
Who's stronger, my Saigo-ryu ninja or your Sanada-ryu ninja?
Let's have a match between the ninja!
Interesting!
I'll take it!
If I win,
I'll destroy this annoying ninja house right away!
Sounds good!
Then if I win, I'll have you leave right away!
Heh, that sounds good!
Sanada-ryu ninjutsu can't beat the local ninjutsu!
Right?
When's the match?
Tomorrow at 12:00.
The venue is here.
That's great!
Grandpa, you should be ready to move out today!
Ahahaha!
Grandpa, you're okay with that kind of promise?
That's right!
A ninja match...
No way!
What?
If you're a decent ninja, you'll be a good match for Ryotsu!
What?!
If you're a coward, no one can beat you!
Hahaha!
Right, that's right!
You're the same as me!
There's no way you can beat me here!
Let me do this for you.
Of all things, I'll definitely beat you!
Ok!
Off to the Great Manga!
Where's the national media?
What's going on here?
Kankichi, is that you?
I don't know.
Then who is it?
Huh?
Ah...
Hahahaha!
My phone's ringing!
It's a good opportunity to promote our Sanada-style ninja and Ninja Land.
That woman ninja is pretty good.
Damn, Houei-ken, did you have that plan?
The game is whether to make the opponent say "Maita" or "Kizetsu".
Also, if you fall on the ground, you lose.
Kunoichi has two of them, and Yoboyama has two of them.
There is a chance to win.
No, even if they are in love, they are the descendants of Sasuke Sarutobi and Saizo Kirigakure.
You shouldn't underestimate them.
Then, the first ninja to the center!
I won't stop you because you are a woman!
I hope so.
Matoi, do your best!
Fight!
Take the Naginata that the dog trained you!
Take it!
You're really good, Chii-chan!
Now it's my turn to attack.
Big Chou Kabo!
Kamagaeru!
I give up!
No!
You must endure it and somehow escape!
I will endure it, Matoi!
No way!
You are a bad girl. You can't escape!
Get up!
Matoi!
Oh, no!
Now, I'll give you a hard time!
Hey, Renma!
This is my last blow!
But, it's still not over, Matoi!
Take a blow!
No, you were right!
Don't feel sorry to accept her!
Oh!
Don't think that you can defeat me!
You are the worst!
No way!
How dare you!
Don't give up!
No, you don't!
Oh, no!
That was a good one, Matoi!
Now, it's the next match.
Kamako Yuri vs. Kankichi Ryo.
I'm counting on you, Kamako.
Alright, it's my turn.
That's wrong.
It's the last one, Kanemaru.
Is it alright to change it?
Oh, really?
I understand. Go ahead.
Is it alright?
Wait a minute.
You're the champion, aren't you?
You should beat the opponent and take the lead.
I thought the opponent was a woman.
You're a scumbag old man.
One of the Sanada Jyu-Yu-Shu.
Kamakosuke Yuri's grandchild's grandchild's grandchild's grandchild's grandchild's grandchild's grandchild's
Kamako Yuri.
Now, let's have a fair match!
Now, come at me from anywhere.
NINPO.
I'll give it to you!
Oh, no!
Damn it.
What a hopeless old man.
It can't be helped.
I'll go next.
Grandma, I'm counting on you.
If you don't beat me, I'll beat you to death.
Grandma, use that NINPO right now.
Put it on, Kanakichi.
Yes, ma'am.
What are you doing?
I'll treat you to a super Kanda sushi made by Kanda Myojin.
What's your favorite story?
T-Take it.
Here you are.
Wait a minute.
It's delicious.
Next, I'll give you octopus and kohada.
Here you are.
Yes, ma'am.
Next, I'll give you sea urchin and salmon.
Yes.
Eel and sea urchin and salmon.
Next, I'll give you hawthorn and squid.
One more time.
Wasabi.
Here you are.
You want to fight me?
Wasabi!
Water.
The team of Saigo and the team of Sarutobi and Sasuke is the winner!
We did it!
Grandma.
NINPO can't eat sushi!
I'm not eating!
Both of them!
I won't lose anymore! I can fight easily!
I can't give up on Ninja Land, which is so popular.
I'll win no matter what and take it to the draw!
Saito!
Take this!
Ha ha, what a shame!
It seems like my sword skills are better than that of a police officer!
Even without a sword, I can use Ninja Land!
Take this!
Wow, it's a full-fledged kill!
-I can't! -Now!
Kankichi, watch out!
That was close!
You used your dirty hands!
What's Ninja Land?
Ninja Land, the killer form!
Ah, full-fledged kill!
Damn, you tricked me!
I didn't trick you.
I told you, it's a form-fledged skill.
There's a real one inside.
What? Where? Where?
What about this?
Ninja Land, the killer form!
Take this!
What? I don't know which one is real!
Kankichi, it's a shadow!
The real one is in the shadow!
Shadow?
That's it!
Yeah!
Okay!
Kankichi, this is a real one!
-A real one! -We can't get to anybody else!
A…
The real one!
That's it!
Here.
Take this!
Okay!
That's it!
It's a ghost!
What happened?
It's a real one!
Everyone, arrest them for the purpose of exorcism!
Exorcism? Haruka, you!
Wait, you're not going to stop!
You bastard, where did you go?
Over there!
It's a shame.
Farewell!
They're...
Ryotsu, use this!
Stop!
Alright!
My mansion...
will be destroyed!
Ryotsu!
What's that?
Why don't you get it?
I'm the same as you, you!
Look at you, you!
Don't try to talk back!
You're so bad, you'll pay for it!
The water soon went out!
The lanterns may not be around anymore.
They're still there.
Spare me a while!
California, do you have a macchiari?
California, no macchiari.
This is not America.
I'm sorry, sir.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
Then, kushiage, kakiage, katsuage, whatever, age, age, what was it?
What do you recommend?
Be careful with only katsuage.
Huh? Is that a father joke?
Soon?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I have no idea.
Huh? Huh? Huh? What? What? What? Really?
Yes, please come in.
Yes, please.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Wow! I was surprised!
I thought it was someone else from elementary school
but it was Omaari Sensei!
He's still alive!
It's been decades but he hasn't changed at all!
Eh?
The secret to his youth is because he's in love?
Next time!
"The Sensei is a Hachamecha Grandpa!"
Please watch!
Next time!
"The Sensei is a Hachamecha Grandpa!"
Please watch!
Thank you!