"If you want to watch TV, keep your room bright and watch it from afar!"
"Come to me, you moneyless fool!"
"Even though I'm not here, I worry."
Look at the blue sky, the white clouds
I'm sure it'll be all right eventually
Come to me, you jobless one
I'm not here, but don't worry
Look, the red cloud is burning
I'm sure it'll be all right eventually
I know, I know, I know
If you know, just keep quiet and follow me
The Modification Project
The mayor is a wind?
That's right. So, I have a consultation with Mr. Ryo.
With me?
I wonder what it is.
Why don't you come and see?
Yeah, I'd like to.
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Here it is.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Mr. Ryo.
It's the wind.
Let me get up.
What?
You want to talk to me?
Hey, Mr. Ryo.
You're here.
Come on, just sleep.
Actually, it's about the festival at the town council.
Oh, the festival.
That's right. It's almost there.
Mr. Ryo is good at organizing festivals, right?
Will you take care of it for me?
What?
Leave it to me.
I'll do a festival that everyone will be happy with.
I was saved.
Actually, only half of the donation money for the festival has been collected yet.
What? Half?
Please do something, Mr. Ryo.
Only Mr. Ryo can organize this southern area, even if it's Hiroshi Kameari.
So, do you want me to help you?
It's the perfect job for you, a life-saving bandist.
Oh, here's the first thing.
I'll help you.
Sorry to bother you.
You're welcome.
Oh, what's up with Grandma today?
She's going to a festival with the neighbors.
Oh, is it her Harajuku?
Oh, is it a gift for the festival?
Yes, please.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
I'll give you 100,000 yen for ten of them.
It's a very good deal.
All right.
So, I'll start from where the money's coming in.
What?
Hey, Mr. Ryo.
What are you going to do?
Are you the mayor of this town?
Yes.
I'm here, President Daiko.
Okay.
I'm tired.
I'll help you.
Mr. Ryo!
Kiyo-san!
I'm the branch manager. What can I do for you?
I'm here to ask for a donation for the festival.
I-I'm fine with just a little bit.
A donation?
Then, here you are.
Huh? What is this?
What do you mean, a donation?
It's only 10,000 yen!
Everyone, listen up!
A bank like this only costs 10,000 yen!
I-I was wrong! It was 20,000 yen!
Wait a minute!
The festival is a great opportunity to meet local residents.
Or is what's written on this poster different from what it really is?
It's ridiculous! That's the motto of my bank!
Then, I'll give you 50,000 yen.
I'll give you a lot!
A donation of 1 million yen!
1 million yen! That's ridiculous!
Kiyo-san, I can't believe it's 1 million yen.
Terai, do you have a bank account in this bank?
Eh? I-I do.
Then, go back to another bank today.
Okay?
That's...
Everyone, stop thinking about banks that don't understand this kind of thing.
And transfer your bank accounts to the bank next door!
I'll pay! I'll pay!
1 million yen!
Really? You're overreacting, aren't you?
It's just a sign that you want to show your gratitude to the locals.
Please let me pay with pleasure!
Please!
You have to do that.
Huh? The Zakuro Bank is donating 5 million yen?
But...
Ryo-san, it's not 5 million yen.
Hmm?
It's good that you're happy!
It's a bank that everyone can meet.
Let's happily pay it out!
I'm just watching you cry.
Just that.
You know, your bank accounts are doing a good job.
Everyone, just think that you want to transfer your bank accounts to the bank next door.
Okay, what do you wanna do?
Let's pay it out!
That's a goal!
Let's come back at 5 million yen for sure!
It'll be awesome!
What?
What did you say?
Ryosu is collecting a lot of donations?
He said he collected 7 million yen for the festival.
My senior forced me into an apartment in the town, so I got 500,000 yen.
500,000 yen?
I'm a member of the Kameyari Town Council.
He's so crazy.
He's going to make the shrine a gorgeous speciality.
What's he thinking?
Amazing.
Just look at the seating.
People are all glittering.
He wants to make it look greedy, so he's just taking the risk.
He's got a new nahi.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
The Tamagotamatsuri!
These guys are like a fish in water.
They drink from the roots.
He loves festivals.
Alright, let's go!
But festivals are nice.
The more people, the more fun it is.
Well, well.
Cheers!
Thank you, Ryo. It was a great success.
As expected of Ryo.
The more people gather in this way, the more I appreciate the shopping district.
Would you like to think of something else that will make you want to come back?
Make me want to come back?
Yes! We will plan a festival from now to the next.
That's good! A festival from now to the next!
A festival throughout the year?
It's going to be a hot topic!
Alright! Then, let's see what comes next!
A donation?
There's another festival?
The one from last year.
The Tanabota Festival.
The one from this year.
The Kameari Neboke Festival.
No way! We just started the festival.
From now on, we're going to have festivals every week!
The next week is the Don Taku Festival.
Then, the Samba Carnival.
Then, the Hada Ka Yaro.
This year, we're going to have the Special Thanks Festival!
Every week?
As expected, every week is a lot of money.
Even if it's only 300 yen per month, it's nothing.
Alright! Let's get the tax!
Tax?
Are you serious, Senpai?
I'm serious about it!
There's national tax and national tax.
It doesn't matter if there's a tax on the government.
There's something we can't pay if it's the government's tax.
I'll make them pay it as a tax!
But, we can't raise the price.
I've thought about that too.
How do we get the government's tax?
We can bet on anything.
But, will everyone pay it honestly?
That's why the currency is not a coin.
It's a hectopascal.
100 hectopascal is 10,000 tons, so it's 112.5 yen.
This is cheap.
It's a pain in the ass to calculate.
Everyone pays for it because they don't know what it is.
How cunning!
First, we'll get the tax from the small house in the town.
It's a tax of 1,000 hectopascal per year.
100 hectopascal is 10,112.5 yen, so it's 11,125 yen.
It's a bit expensive.
We'll get the house as well.
1,000 hectopascal.
Plus, we'll get the tax for pets.
500 per month for the lottery.
100 per month for the magazine.
How's that?
It's cheap, isn't it?
We'll get the tax from the children too.
It's 100 hectopascal for the game.
Plus, we'll get the tax from the bus and the patrol car.
The tax-man.
That's still too much.
That's right.
Nakagawa, you're a good man.
The highest tax is 3,000 hectopascal.
A good man?
Good men have a lot of benefits in the world.
So, we have to pay a lot of taxes.
I see.
Plus, the model body tax is 180 cm or more.
Plus, the playboy tax is 9,800 hectopascal.
That's too much.
Reiko!
Reiko has 3,000 beautiful tax.
Plus, the model body tax, breast milk tax, seduction tax,
and breast milk tax.
That's too much!
We'll get the tax from the children too.
Are you kidding?
I don't live in this town.
If you step into this town,
you'll have to abide by this law.
Do I have to pay the tax?
You don't have to.
It's in the basic construction.
I guess I'll get the tax from the children.
What are you talking about?
Chief.
Chief! Congratulations!
What's the matter?
The chief is in a bad situation.
The tax is coming back.
The tax is coming back?
I'm so glad.
The annual tax is 2,000 hectopascal.
I'll pay the tax more and more.
You guys are so hardworking.
Here's the tax.
95 hectopascal.
The tax?
It's for the city.
Is that possible?
It's to make the next Kameyari.
Get it out of here.
You guys are so hardworking.
I'll take the 68 hectopascal for the breast milk tax.
What?
What are you talking about?
Here's the 111 hectopascal for the cell phone tax.
Don't mess with me.
The tax for the mouthwash tax and the tobacco tax.
Pay it now.
I'll pay the tax.
Okay.
Stop!
I'll get the breast milk tax from now on.
But we live over there.
This is the station.
If you take the dog, you'll get the pet tax.
This is enough for the next sleepwalking festival.
No, not yet.
We don't have enough money for the construction of the new building.
The new building?
Weren't you waiting for me at the festival?
The time is already the 21st century.
Can you build a 21st century town in a place like Nagaya that looks like this?
For the 21st century, you need a suitable building for the 21st century.
That's the new building.
The festival is after that.
Is that so?
I'll collect the tax.
It's nice to have a place to look down on people.
I'll decide the production at this height.
Ryo, come down here.
Do you think you can build a building like this with 50 million yen?
Who are you talking to, chief?
I'm the temporary chairman of the council, who has been appointed to the full power.
I want you to keep your mouth shut on everything I do.
But you're doing too much.
That's not enough.
I'm going to change Japan from a turtle.
Senior!
Ryo!
Building a new building was bad.
The lecture call was all over the place.
What?
The tax is too high.
More and more people are leaving the town.
There are no more people in the shopping street.
It's becoming a ghost town.
The Hekto Pascal of the shopping street is in a big trouble.
What?
Look at the sky.
What is a ghost town?
There are so many people.
It's a ghost town!
That's the people who treat you like a senior.
What?
Ryo!
Now, you can have fun here.
And the chief and the baton are not here.
No, they're not.
What are you doing?
Ryo!
The chief got hurt?
I know.
He was fixing the roof then slipped from the responsibility ladder.
Because he's not used to it.
Ryo, did you visit him?
Really?
Excuse me.
Huh?
Hey, Ryo-san.
You got hurt, huh? I'll take care of it.
Hey, how's it going?
You're back at the super-unit again!
No, I'm not. That was a bad news, right?
I'm just a visitor. I fell off the ladder.
I see. You're very sharp when you think about the super-unit.
Give it to me.
What about the super-unit?
I want to find something unique about this super-unit.
A city with UFOs, dinosaurs, and a city with an iron fence.
I see. So you want to gather people and create a city like that.
Okay, leave it to me.
Wait, Ryo-san!
I'm not good at making money like I was before!
I know, but there's no way to do it right.
But it's a city with a lot of old people.
Where's grandma?
Huh?
I don't know.
I'm going to visit the old people and the old people.
Oh, so you're going to visit grandma's old city.
The young people are going to visit the old city, the old people are going to visit the old city, and the old people are going to visit the old city.
Ryo-san, wait!
I left everything to you the other day!
That's right! We're going to make the Kamihari your old city!
Leave it to me!
Hey, Ryo-san!
Ryo-san, what are you going to do next?
Well, look at this.
What?
Grandpa's Harajuku?
Now, the old people have no place to play with money.
I'll gather old people from all over the country here.
How?
For example, in the front.
The tiles are all made of iron.
And the wall is a paradise.
There's a karaoke room in the public hall.
The front is the world's most destroyed city, Daimihon-ichi.
Blood pressure is measured everywhere in the shopping street.
We hold a handmade diabetes medicine class.
In addition, the park is the hero of the old people's world, the statue of Mito Komon.
With this much, there's no doubt that the old people will leave and come to visit.
Why?
I don't know.
Why are you here?
I don't know at all!
The gap between the old man Ryo-chan and the real old man seems to be too big.
Isn't it best to ask the elderly, old people?
Hmm...
Oh, that old friend...
Ah...
I have an unpleasant face.
I just thought of something.
What's that face?
Is it real?
Oh, it's Ryo-chan's grandfather.
Ryo-chan is a good-for-nothing.
He's a good-for-nothing, but he's a good-for-nothing.
That's perfect.
Why don't you ask your grandfather?
That's right, Ryo-chan.
He says he's older than a turtle.
Is it really going well?
Israel is a failure.
It's for the sake of cute grandchildren.
I'm worried about that lightness.
I haven't lived for 104 years.
I have the know-how to meet the needs of my grandparents.
My employee's average age is 88 years old.
What?
He's a designer of beautiful girl characters.
His name is Adam.
He's 92 years old.
He was also at Mr. Shigeru Sugiura's place.
The gap between characters is amazing.
He's 87 years old.
He's in charge of robot mecha design.
Robots are also like now.
Now, he's developing a fighting game for the elderly.
Fighting game?
Does your grandfather play fighting games?
In games, even my grandfather can be a superman.
He's a great guy who can beat up young people instead of himself.
Lord Butsumi X 3
All the players have a strong and powerful mind.
What's better than your grandfather?
I'm thinking about getting him to stand on that major stage.
That is the most difficult question.
Is it OK?
Your grandfather has a strong mind, that's why.
You have a strong mind?
Yes.
Is that a match?
A match?
Don't you think it's a game?
I would be fine.
You're looking for a match.
That's right. Leave it to me.
First, the battle is...
Bandai has young and beautiful women.
They wear a big TV with a swimsuit instead of a mask.
At the public hall, they have a concert with the old men in a band.
At the square in front of the station, there is a para-para classroom.
At the shopping street, there is a silver plicke.
You can also take a two-shot with Harase Tsuko and Beatrix.
And there is a beam center for old men.
Go away, old woman.
At the movie theater, they have a high blood pressure ojingerion, a super-large SF movie.
Damn it, young man.
High blood pressure beam.
Next, Ojingerion.
They also have a convenience store for old men.
This is great.
If they are all together, they will be able to push the old man away.
Wow, they are amazing.
They are all old men, whether they look to the right or left.
The Kameari Ojingerion project is a great success.
Ryo, this time it is a great success.
Sales have increased by 50%.
Our shop has also increased by 35%.
We are also growing.
Let's do this.
The Kameari is the most popular one in Japan now.
The most popular one in Japan...
We are the best, right?
Great!
Next, this one.
Senior!
What's this?
You are doing the old man's woodstock?
You know what?
We will gather old men all over the world and hold a big event in Kameari.
That's great.
Use the internet to call the old men all over the world.
I see.
Hurry up!
Make an airport in the river in Arakawa,
and take the old man from the world by direct flight!
The old man is back on his feet again,
and he's started something?
Yes, it's an international airport for the old man.
He's going to gather the old man from the world in Kameari.
And he's going to make a new hotel,
for the old man.
I don't know where to stay,
that idiot.
Let's go to Kameari!
Kameari is over there!
Kameari!
It's Kameari!
Kameari is here, Kankichi!
I did it!
It was a big success!
Too many idiots gathered.
Did we get too close?
Ryo, do something!
With this, the
The old man is overflowing and the shopping street will be broken!
But, that's true...
Here it comes again!
I'm not dead!
Everyone, to the death of the half-dead!
-Nyaaah! -Nyaaah!
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Then, the rest is up to the veteran chairman...
Again, that hand!
-Nyaaah! -Nyaaah!
Damn it!
Nyaaah!
-Nyaaah! -Nyaaah!
Whoa! I'm being swallowed by the old man's waves!
Nyaaah!
The chairman is the second chairman?
That's right.
There were many things that hurt my stomach and my stomach.
Ryo, why don't you go visit him?
Hmm...
That's right.
That's what I'll do.
I'll visit him, huh?
Huh?
You don't have to come!
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
♪ The politicians with the faces down and the blue ladies with the eyes up ♪
♪ Turn around and look at that corner ♪
♪ You'll see everyone, everyone ♪
♪ Go! Go! Go! ♪
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ Ah, there's definitely a wall ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!
This is the machine that checks the ratings!
Is that true, Hojo?
Wait a minute!
The TV staff should want the number even if it's 1%.
If I could control all of this machine,
I might even become a god!
Next time, "The Man Who Stole the Ratings!"
Don't miss it!
♪ There's a wall over there ♪
♪ Ah, there's definitely a wall ♪
♪ Everyone, come to our town ♪
Thank you!