Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Ohara family's secret recipe!
Hey, hey, are you sure this road is safe?
Yes, I think it's a road that's been made recently.
If it's not on the map...
I haven't seen a single car in this area.
How about you, Honda?
There's no doubt that it's an old road.
It's always a one-way road.
But, chief, are you really commuting from here?
Yes.
It takes 20 minutes from JR to the train station and the bus.
It will take at least two and a half hours.
Five hours?
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind.
By the way, Ryo-chan.
What did you buy for the chief's birthday present?
This.
It's a secret until it arrives.
What is it?
We all gave each other money, so it's okay to tell me.
Don't worry.
It's something I specially chose.
There's no doubt about it.
That's not what I meant.
I'm just saying that it's strange that the people who give the presents don't know what they're giving away.
That's right.
I'll just say that it's the best.
Chief, if you see this, you'll surely be impressed and lose your mind.
Huh?
We're already in the residential area.
It should be about time.
But this looks like a dangerous scene.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing all of a sudden, senior?
Huh?
Sen-senior?
Um, I'd like to ask you something.
Yes?
Do you know the otaku named Ohara?
Oh, if that's the case, it's about a kilometer away.
Is that so?
If you don't mind, please get in the car and show me the way.
I'll take you there.
But it's a one-way street.
There's no need to get lost.
Well, well, without saying it, it's called a road trip, isn't it?
When I see a beautiful woman, it's this right away.
Get off, Honda.
This person will get on.
Huh?
Then what should I do?
Well, it's right away.
Then you don't have to show me the way.
Um, I don't have to get on forcibly.
I'm sorry. Please wait a minute.
Oh, it's me.
Senpai, this car can fit five people.
Shut up, Nakagawa.
I don't like small cars.
Ryo-chan, I feel sorry for Mr. Honda.
Reiko, sit in front of me.
Honda!
Do you think it's bad to let the lady wait?
No, no.
Shino, don't go.
Get off quickly.
Come on, come on.
Oh, my God.
Why is it like this?
Oh, why is it like this?
Well, let's celebrate your boss's birthday.
That's right.
This is also the last day of the week.
It's hard.
It's been a long day off.
I didn't have to go into the mountains.
Yeah, you're right.
I built a house in a place that looks like a raccoon.
Excuse me.
Do you live around here, too?
Yes.
Well, even so,
I can't believe you're celebrating my birthday.
You must be very fond of your subordinate.
It's ridiculous.
I don't listen to what you say.
What about Ibaru?
What will happen?
It's suspicious.
It's not easy to be loved.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I have to work under such a person.
Well, sometimes you have to take care of yourself.
In the case of Senpai,
I'm bothering you with a lot of things.
I'm being bothered.
Oh, over there.
I see.
This is the chief's house.
A small veranda.
A garden that I made forcibly.
But what is it?
To build this small house,
I spent half my life sweating and crying.
That's right.
You have to send it to Otaku.
It's okay.
I'm here, too.
What?
Because this is my house.
I mean, maybe...
That's right.
My feet stink.
And I'm Hirobi, the daughter of a boss who doesn't listen to numbers.
Welcome, everyone.
Oh, you're...
The chief's?
Yes.
Well, I've been noticing you for a while.
I've heard a lot about you from my father.
No, I've always respected you.
You're really like a mirror to the police.
Yes.
It's okay.
Don't overdo it.
Because my father is really like that.
That's right.
Senior!
I'm here, too.
I'm home.
Hey, father.
We have a guest.
Yeah.
Who is it?
Oh!
Hello.
You guys.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean, what are you doing here?
Your cute subordinates came all the way here, didn't they?
It's cute.
Wait a minute.
I hate you a thousand times.
Oh, welcome, everyone.
I'm sorry.
I was suddenly pushed by a crowd.
Thank you.
Well, get up.
Thank you for your time.
Here you go.
Chief, you're a great man.
The construction of this house is well organized.
The chieftain has a good personality.
Yes.
In addition, the taste of this turtle god.
I'm not going to give this tension to the guests.
You don't have to get up.
What are you talking about, father?
You came all the way here.
Come on, Ryozu, get up.
I didn't know the chieftain had such a cute daughter.
Should I say that the chieftain gave birth to her?
Hey, Ryozu.
I'll tell you a little bit, but don't get angry.
I don't think Hiromi will have an interest in an overbearing man like you.
I'm an overbearing man anyway.
I'll lose to the chieftain.
What?
Father, stop it.
This is not a workplace.
Oh, sorry.
But again.
What's wrong?
Why are you suddenly pushing me?
Oh, are you really not interested?
Father, happy birthday.
Birthday?
Chieftain, congratulations.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, chieftain.
Yes, father.
Chieftain, do you have anything to say?
Oh, thank you, everyone.
Congratulations.
Then you guys.
To celebrate my birthday.
Chieftain, are you crying?
Idiot.
I'm not crying.
Yes, father.
This is from my mother and me.
Thank you.
Oh, leather shoes.
I'll use it carefully.
Chieftain.
This is a small gift from us.
What is it?
It's pretty big.
After all, what did you buy?
What is this?
What do you think, chieftain?
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
I'm doing a nostalgic candy fair in the department store.
Look.
Gindama and menko.
Gindama and pachinko.
Sconbu and sauce senbei.
There is also a squid suzuke.
And this Bakuchiku.
It used to be 2B.
It was a bigger one.
Chieftain, are you going to use all the money you collected?
Of course.
If you have 20,000 yen, you can buy a lot.
Didn't you know?
Yes.
Senpai didn't ask me to choose the gift myself.
After all, it was a mistake to leave it to Ryo-chan.
Hey, hey.
What is this?
What?
You don't know menko either?
Alright.
Look.
This is how you do it.
You can get it if you turn it over.
Wow.
It's interesting.
Menko is like this.
You put your hips in like this.
And you do it.
What?
Are you going to lose to me?
You did it.
How was it?
Gentlemen.
Thank you very much for today.
I'm very happy that everyone celebrated my birthday,
regardless of whether it was a gift or not.
Regardless of whether it was a gift or not.
You were playing with it.
That's why.
I want to treat everyone to tea as a sign of gratitude.
Tea?
What is this room?
There's nothing here.
This is a tea room.
It's a place to drink tea.
Tea room?
Oh, my.
Even though it's a small house,
did you make this room just by drinking tea?
Ryo-chan.
You have to sit here.
Is that so?
What is this?
Oh.
Please.
Thank you.
Thank you for being so careful.
Then, I'll be able to...
Ouch.
You can't touch it right away.
Wait until the manager comes.
I'm not a fool.
Then, please wait a while.
Hey, Ryo-chan.
Do you know?
When you drink tea,
you can drink it slowly like this.
What?
I know that much.
You have to turn it three times like this.
You're an idiot.
If you turn it vertically, the tea will spill.
What a waste.
It's already started.
Next day
Mr. Honbo,
is something wrong?
I got a slipped foot.
Oh, I was waiting for you.
Oh, I finally got a bite.
Well then, I'll take it.
Hey, you pervert!
You know nothing about the heart of tea!
You don't have to do anything, so just sit there quietly!
Huh? I understand.
Hmph.
Anyway, you pervert.
I'd like you to taste it with my prideful tea bowl.
Tea bowl?
This is the most precious thing I have right now.
Oh, my.
I found it when I traveled to Kyoto, and I really wanted it.
I thought I'd use it for the rest of my life, so I bought it.
It's a black javanese tea bowl.
It looks like it's pretty good.
I wonder if it's made by Koetsu.
Oh, you know what I mean?
The black koutaku is wonderful.
I'll make tea for everyone with this tea bowl.
You're an otaku, aren't you?
You're just a black javanese tea bowl.
R-Ryotsu!
Hey, stop it!
I said stop it!
Let me see it!
Ryotsu!
Oh!
Ah!
Hey, chief, that was close.
That was a nice catch.
You idiot!
Be careful.
This tea bowl is worth 400,000 yen.
Huh? 400,000 yen?
That cheap tea bowl!
There are things in the world that you can't understand.
Ah...
That was a good catch.
Yeah.
You're so slow.
That was a very good catch.
Uh, it was very delicious.
You don't need to know the recipe, you just need to taste it properly.
Now then,
I'm not going to tell everyone that I can't make only Ryotsu.
Yeah, chief.
I'm better at making tea than making tea.
Yeah, that might be more suitable for you.
But,
I'm not going to tell anyone that I can't make only Ryotsu.
I'm preparing the meal right now, so just wait a little longer.
Dad?
There's a phone call.
I see.
Then Ryotsu,
wait for me.
Don't touch the tea bowl again and again.
Got it?
I know.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
Ah, man.
What the hell is 400,000 yen worth of tea bowl?
If you're going to be so generous,
just put it on your bedside table.
But,
I was very nervous to drink tea with 400,000 yen worth of tea bowl.
The tools of tea look simple,
and they're all things that can help you sleep.
I see.
Oh, this is just right for ear cleaning.
Senior,
it's not good for you to do that.
That's right.
I don't care.
Well,
this time I'll make your tea and pay you.
I'll just write down the real method,
like a washing machine.
Ah, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle...
Hey, don't do that.
Ah, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle...
Hey, Ryou-chan,
stop it.
...gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle...
Ah, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle, gurgle!
Senior!
Ah...
Ow, ow, ow...
I think I got carried away.
Ah...
Huh?
R-Ryou-chan...
Senior...
Huh?
W-Why?
Ah!
W-W-What?
I-It's finally...
...broken.
I-It's so easy to break...
...the chief must have been fooled.
Run!
No, sorry to keep you waiting.
Hm?
Ryou-chan, what are you doing?
Ahem...
No...
But, Chief, you're really a beautiful young man, aren't you?
Hmph.
Do you know what's good about you?
Of course I do!
I feel like I don't want to let go of this wonderful thing.
Really?
Then I'll make you some tea, so hurry up and give it back to me.
N-No, no...
Please let me sit here for a while longer.
No, no!
It's no use letting you keep it.
Now, hurry up and give it back to me.
N-No, just a little bit more...
No!
Just a little bit more...
Hey, Ryou-chan, that's enough!
Huh?
Ah, what's that?
Gah...
Hey, wait, Ryou-chan!
Don't you want to wait?
Is the tea party over?
I'm preparing for the barbecue right now, but...
That's...
Barbecue?
It'll be ready soon.
Oh, thank you.
Where are you, Ryou-chan?
There you are.
Here, hurry up and give it back to me.
Hey, Ryou-chan!
Hey, Chief, when you look at it in nature,
it's even more beautiful, isn't it?
That's enough.
Hurry up and give it back to me.
What's wrong with you?
N-No...
You?
You're being rude to our guest.
Here, Ryou-chan.
Please eat up.
I'm sorry.
I'll forgive you if you give it back now.
Here, hurry up and give it back to me.
You're right.
If you give it back now, you'll forgive me, right?
Yeah, men don't have a second thought.
What should I do?
Please, give it back to me.
Raku-chan is easy to break.
What should I do if something happens to him?
I'll have to take it back.
You!
Why are you acting like a child?
Ryouchi-san can't eat meat, can he?
That's enough, Dad.
If you give that tea bowl to Ryouchi-san for a while...
I-I'm not going to do that, you idiot!
It's terrible to call your daughter an idiot.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
Then it's fine.
Mr. Honda, over there, it's burnt.
Then, I'll eat it.
Ryou-chan, why aren't you eating it?
You're such a good boy.
That's right.
Hurry up and eat it.
Reiko, let me eat it.
I refuse.
Hey, Ryouchi.
Here, drink it for the time being.
No, I won't.
That's not for drinking beer.
Here, drink it.
No, it's not for drinking beer.
Here.
That's not for a senior like you.
It's fine.
Here.
Honey, the meat is burnt.
What was that?
What?
It was my imagination.
I felt like I saw two tea bowls.
You're drunk already, aren't you?
There's no way that would happen.
Ryouchi, show me the tea bowl.
That's...
Ryouchi!
What did you do to that tea bowl?
I can't take it anymore for someone like you to make an important tea bowl into a toy.
Hey, give it back!
Wait, Ryouchi.
I can't take it anymore for someone like you to make an important tea bowl into a toy.
Hey, Ryouchi.
My tea bowl...
It broke because of the chief.
It was my...
It was my only treasure.
What should I live for tomorrow?
Hey, Dad.
Don't be so depressed.
Why don't you buy a new one?
Okay?
It's so good.
Ryouchi!
What?
Hurry up and eat it.
I'll eat it all by myself.
Ryouchi, apologize to him.
I feel sorry for the chief.
Chief, things that have shape will eventually break.
That's the truth of all things.
Anyway, let's eat meat. It's delicious.
I don't need it. You eat it.
Then I won't have to.
Ryouchi!
Chief, actually...
Hey, idiot! Stop it!
That's what happened.
What?
Chief, I didn't mean to be mean.
Ryouchi...
I won't forgive you!
Chief...
Hey, chief!
I don't like barbecue!
Stop it!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're self-sufficient, Ryouchi.
It's been a long time, Hiromi.
But it looks like you're having fun, father.
Ryouchi's charcoal barbecue.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
This is the best present for me.
Please forgive me.
Nakagawa, Reiko, Honda, Hiromi, please help me!
The End
Height 167 cm. Weight 71 kg.
Both of them have 2.0kg.
Chief, are you going to challenge this perfect body?
Fine.
If you have to fight, start from anywhere.
Next episode, cockroach race.
Thank you for watching!
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
Wave your hand
Say goodbye to unpleasant things
Oh yeah
Let's live the way we want
There's a good thing
Outside the door, the sun is calling