Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
It can't be! Ryotsu and Reiko!
So this is the latest model?
Yes.
It's lighter and more compact than steel.
How do you use it?
Can I borrow your hand?
Sure.
If you touch the inside of the handle like this...
...it locks automatically.
Really?
You can unlock the key with this electronic lock key.
That was quick!
Now we don't need to arrest the culprit.
Finally, the guys from the exchange school are here.
Today was a tough day.
You look sleepy, Ryo-chan.
I'm not sleepy at all.
I went to the beach five days ago...
...and drank and sang every night.
After that, I played Tetsumon for 70 hours.
Then I went straight to bed.
I haven't slept for 120 hours.
That's a lot.
I'll sleep for 100 hours if I go home today.
I'm tired.
You have to change your lifestyle.
I can't afford it.
What's that?
Is it this?
It's a new model.
It locks in 0.2 seconds.
That's interesting.
Just touching it is enough?
That's convenient.
I'll unlock it with this key.
That's cool.
That's interesting.
That was quick.
You looked so sleepy just now.
You don't have eyes for fun.
Let's go home.
I want more.
If you're tired, you should go home and sleep.
Like a child.
What did you say?
I'll break your bones.
I'll arrest you!
What?
The key!
I ate it!
Hey!
Damn it!
It ran away!
What are you going to do?
I don't know!
Do something, Nakagawa!
It wasn't me.
Terai borrowed it from the head office.
I'll ask him.
There should be a spare key.
Yes, that's right.
That dog ran away because you yelled.
You should have caught it.
You're the cause of the key.
Really?
It's hard.
The person in charge went on a vacation.
What?
When will you come back?
It seems to be tomorrow.
Are you going to stay with Reiko for 48 hours?
That's my line.
Wait.
Is it Saturday today?
That's right.
It's not a joke!
It's the day of peace!
I don't have time to do this.
I have to do something.
It's the latest style.
I don't get hurt.
I had a bad feeling when I was playing with my hands.
I'm sorry, but I have something to do.
I'll go home first.
What?
Wait!
Ryo-chan will work with me.
What?
Wait a minute.
I haven't slept for 120 hours.
Are you going to let me work for 8 hours?
It can't be helped.
Today is a day off.
Why do you work?
It's okay.
You can do whatever you want.
Of course.
I'm going to sleep.
That's great.
It doesn't take a second.
You can sleep anywhere.
It's the same as animals.
This is the Kamewari Park.
I'm here.
Reiko, the head office is calling.
Me?
Ouch!
My eyes are cold.
Come here.
Hey!
I'm back.
Yes.
I'm going to the office.
Right now?
Yes.
I understand.
My head is burning!
Hey!
Come here!
What are you doing?
I'm going to the office.
No!
I don't want to!
I'm not going!
What are you doing?
Hey, you!
I'm in a hurry.
Hey!
I'm going.
Wait!
Hey!
Reiko!
Why do I have to run?
It can't be helped.
It's forbidden to ride with two people.
I'm going to fly.
Do your best.
Stop it!
That's enough.
What?
That's a new record.
Do your best.
It'll be embarrassing if you get caught.
They are a bold couple.
They are beautiful.
Stop it.
What?
This way.
I want to pee.
You can't go there with me.
I'm not going.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to get caught.
I'm in trouble.
I know.
What if I do it in the back garden?
Do you want me to stand in the back of the office?
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Hurry up.
I don't want to.
Why do I have to do this?
Reiko!
What are you doing there?
I'm going to take a bath.
You don't look like Reiko.
Let's play volleyball together.
No.
It's too early.
I told you it's too early.
They treated me like a pervert.
That's enough.
Excuse me.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ryo-chan.
You're done with your work.
Let's go home.
Well...
What?
Toilet?
If I go in with you,
you'll become a real pervert.
Go outside like me.
I'll close my eyes.
You can't do that.
Then wait until we get home.
Be patient.
There's only one way.
How?
Like this.
I don't want to live like this anymore.
Even I'm treated like a pervert.
I'm tired.
My left hand hurts.
I'm tired, too.
I've been running around
without enough sleep.
I'm sweating.
Let's take a bath.
A bath?
No, it's okay.
I won't look at you.
What's with your eyes?
Do I look like a pervert?
Ryo-chan.
But just in case.
Damn it.
I made you faint again.
Don't hit me on the way to the toilet.
You're getting more and more resistant.
You're getting faster.
You look like a cockroach.
Do you want to take a bath?
Let me in, too.
Wait.
I'll be right out.
No, right now.
Don't be naked in a place like this.
If you want to go in, go ahead.
Don't be ridiculous.
Damn it.
But how did you change your clothes
with your hands tied up?
Huh?
It's a little hot.
I feel refreshed.
I don't feel refreshed at all.
I'm going to take a bath in my clothes.
I told you to go in.
Who is it now?
Ms. Akimoto.
She's the manager's aunt.
She's famous for her talk.
I don't know what rumors will spread
if I find her in a place like this.
You don't have to tell me anything.
I'm not going.
Ms. Akimoto.
Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Did you take a bath?
Your luggage is here.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Do you know the girl in room 8?
I don't really like rumors.
Well, that girl takes a different man
into her room every day.
I don't want to see her crying.
Is that so?
Compared to that, you are rare now.
Weird men don't flutter.
This is tough.
The next day
Let's go to bed.
Let's get changed.
Huh?
You fell asleep without doing anything.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep in a place like this.
It's not that hard.
You've been awake for 135 hours.
Yes.
It's me, Pappa.
It's me, Pum Pum Maru.
What's wrong, Pappa?
I'm on my way.
To Tokyo?
What's going on?
What?
I didn't hear you.
That's strange.
Anyway,
tomorrow at 1 o'clock,
I'm going to see Tengamaru Shoji.
Even if you say that suddenly,
I'm not going to get married yet.
Do you have someone you like?
It's not like that.
I didn't do it.
Reiko, what was that man's voice?
No, Pappa.
It's the sound of the TV.
Ryo-chan.
It's the TV.
Stop it, Reiko.
Stop it.
It's Reiko now.
It's the TV.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
I'm in trouble.
If I take Ryo-chan away like this,
it'll be a big trouble.
Pappa might be shocked and fall asleep.
I think it's about time,
but I'm sorry.
No,
I don't mind being a little late.
If it's for Reiko, I'll wait for hours.
Right, Pappa?
That's right.
Excuse me.
Is it Reiko?
Hello.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry.
I got caught up in traffic.
I'll leave it here for a moment.
It's cute, isn't it?
You like it, don't you?
You're always with me wherever I go.
Ryo-chan has been sleeping since yesterday.
If you keep sleeping like this,
everything will be over.
Reiko-san, you're so cute.
I like that.
Thank you.
As you know,
I'm Tengamaru Daisuke.
I'm Tengamaru Shoji's uncle.
I'm glad to be able to get close to
Reiko-san.
Nice to meet you.
What's your hobby?
I spend money.
It's hard to spend money
because I have too much money.
That's another good hobby.
What's your hobby, Reiko-san?
It's just my imagination.
Ouch.
Poor thing.
Did you get up?
I said I wanted to see you.
Is that so?
Excuse me.
That's why.
So that's why I'm wearing
a raccoon doll like this.
Ryo-chan, please.
Please don't find out
until the meeting is over.
Do you like
a guy who does stupid things?
No.
It's an important
transaction between my partner and my father.
If it goes well, I'll buy you
a radio-controlled helicopter that Ryo-chan wanted.
What? Radio-controlled?
Okay, I got it.
Leave it to me.
The lady seems to be
calculating everything.
Even though it's on the radio,
it's hard to stay still.
It looks delicious.
There's sake, too.
By the way, I haven't eaten anything since last night.
Okay,
watch it.
Anyway,
my father-in-law is
Himiko's mother's sister.
Ryo-chan.
That's enough.
Reiko-san.
Yes.
If you were to get married,
would you go to Asia or
Dengen?
I'd go anywhere.
Really? I'd go anywhere
except Shita-machi.
What?
I can't stand it.
Shita-machi is old
and has a bad pattern.
I don't like it.
I don't like Shita-machi.
I hate it
because it's a fake.
What do you think?
It's delicious.
Water!
Give me water!
Captain!
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Would you like to talk?
That's good.
Young people are young people.
Right, Tenkamaru-san?
That's right.
Reiko-san.
Yes.
We're finally alone.
Reiko-san.
Ever since I first saw you...
Um...
Reiko-san.
We're doing a Dragon King show over there!
What?
Dragon King?
I think Tanuki was running.
Dragon Kick!
It's good to do this once in a while.
Yes.
It was a good chance.
Good job, Dragon King.
Dragon King!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's strange.
Calm down.
Dragon Kick!
The moon!
This is Tanuki from Kachikachi!
Reiko-chan, run!
Help me!
It's really shallow.
But it's good.
Half of my face is fine.
Damn.
But I'm in trouble.
Reiko-san!
What should we do?
We'll be found!
Reiko-san! Reiko-san!
Why are you so slow?
What?
It's your turn.
Hurry up.
What?
You're a good Devil General.
But who is this girl?
Dragon King.
I'm a huge fan.
It's a big Devil Devil.
Take this!
You're a big Devil Devil.
Reiko, you do it too.
What?
He's serious.
If he wants to do it, let's do it.
Yeah.
It can't be helped.
Take this.
Good. Everyone, follow them.
Go, Sora!
Reiko-san!
Where did he go?
Reiko-san, you're so wonderful.
Reiko-san!
What are you doing?
What?
I don't think it's appropriate
for Tenkamaru to do that.
Reiko-san!
The rest was a mess.
But I'm relieved
that I finally got a job.
I'm so glad
that I got a job like this.
Maybe you're still lucky.
The person in charge
is going out for a month from today.
A month?
That's great.
By the way, where's Reiko-san's match?
Of course, she rejected it from the other side.
This?
Yes, the one we promised.
I did it!
So, did the match go well?
No.
She doesn't want to get married.
She rejected it
because of her father,
but she was wondering
how to reject it.
That's what I thought.
This is useful.
Ryotsu!
Good morning!
You're playing with
something like that again?
No, I'm always
busy with work.
This is not a toy.
It's the latest model.
Isn't it great?
I see.
Take it off.
This key...
What's wrong?
You can't take it off for a month?
You bastard!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to die if I play with you for a month!
Forget it!
He's really stubborn.
This is Kameyari Park.
I'm busy right now.
What?
There's an elephant in the shopping street?
I can't touch it because it's dangerous.
Wait a minute!
Why do I have to go?
Next time,
let's play with an elephant!
Hey, you!
What's wrong?
It's dangerous!
Come on!
Hey, you!
Let's go!
Let's play!
Hey, you!
Come on!
Sayonara sa Oh Yeah
Suki na you ni ikite mi yo
Ii koto aru sa
Doa no soto de ohishitama ga yonderu yo