Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Everybody can do!
I don't want to say it even if it sticks out a little.
Don't worry about making a fuss.
Strong and high-pitched voice.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Gyozutsuki Test Special Report
Wow, this is great!
TXR-002 Robojack.
40,000 yen.
I can't buy it even if it stands upside down.
I can't buy it.
This tiger is also a short-tempered person in front of his payday.
Oh, no!
Stop!
Wait!
Good job, Junpei!
You're having a hard time again.
Are you going to study?
You have a test tomorrow, right?
That's right, but even if I do it now, my head won't get better all of a sudden.
That's right.
Ryo-san.
Gigu.
What's the good thing about an adult who is so old with a child?
It's a masterpiece of a full action robot equipped with a radio channel.
Those who understand it will understand it.
Those who don't understand it won't understand it.
Is that so?
If Junpei gets at least 80 points on the test, I'll buy it no matter how much it costs.
Really?
Will you buy it no matter how much it costs?
It's an example.
You can't get 80 points, right?
Ryo-san.
I'll buy it no matter how much it costs.
What?
Look at the Nagashima Titans this year.
They beat the 11.5 game difference in the first half and won the Miraculous League.
If you have the will to do it, you can do anything.
If Junpei gets 80 points, he'll really buy the radio channel.
Well, that's true.
Alright, it's decided.
Let's go, Junpei.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Ryo-san, wait for me.
Nene.
What are you going to do, Ryo-san?
What are you going to do?
Leave it to me.
In return, if you get the radio channel, I'll buy it for free.
Alright.
I'll do it.
I'll definitely do it.
Huh?
A home teacher?
What happened to a home teacher?
Why is Senpai here again?
You can do it.
Ryo-chan is a home teacher.
What?
Don't make fun of me.
What are you going to do if you don't know how to study in elementary school?
Alright, let's get started.
Get started?
The test is tomorrow, right?
That's why.
From now on, don't sleep for 24 hours and study.
What?
That's too much.
It's not too much.
When I was in high school, I studied without sleeping for three days and passed the test.
You didn't sleep at all?
Why are you saying that again?
If you sleep, you'll forget everything you've learned.
It's too much.
But normally, people's concentration doesn't last that long, right?
Yes.
They say that it's better to take a break at work.
That's a commoner's story.
In my case, my concentration is different.
Ordinary common sense doesn't work.
It's right to say that there is no common sense.
Listen carefully.
Normally, the pace goes up and then it falls.
But in my case, it starts from the peak.
And then it rushes into the test day.
That's a lot of concentration.
I can't believe it.
I'll tell you why.
Even if a commoner is focused, it's still a lot.
In my case, my whole body is focused on the test from my brain to my fingertips.
I have 100% common sense.
But if I don't pay attention to one thing, I'll fall to zero.
I see.
It's like a human airplane.
It's like Ryo-chan.
I'm so happy.
That's why I'm going to teach you how I do it.
Where did they go?
Wow, that's amazing.
Oh, no.
I knew it.
I hid my plan.
Wait a minute.
Stop it.
Don't touch it.
Ryo-chan, are you really going to study?
I understand your concentration, but it's a different problem from your academic ability.
Where are you going to study?
How are you going to become a teacher?
I don't know.
How long are you going to play?
Are you really going to study?
Of course.
If it's for the radio, it's in the fire and in the water.
Come on, give me the problem sheet.
What's the test range?
All right, let's start with the language problem.
Well, what's this?
Answer the meaning of the next word.
50 steps, 100 steps.
It's easy.
That's you.
You said 50 steps, 100 steps.
This is the starting line.
All right, Junpei.
Walk 100 steps from here.
All right.
One, two, three, four.
Is that so?
Oh, Ryo-chan.
It's dangerous to play on the road.
Grandma, this is studying.
Oh, my God.
100 steps, 100 steps.
Good job, Ryo-san.
All right.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Ryo-chan, what are you going to do?
I don't know.
46, 47, 48, 49, 50.
Exactly.
In other words, 50 steps, 100 steps.
It means that even if you walk 100 steps with your feet,
you can walk 50 steps when you become an adult.
Yes, I got it.
I see.
That's the interpretation.
That's not true.
Sleeping pills from the second floor?
Hey, Ryo-san.
What do you mean?
Well, you should try it.
Let's go, Ryo-san.
All right, let's go.
Aim well.
Are you really going to take sleeping pills from the second floor?
We did it!
What do you think, Ryo-san?
Did you get it?
I'm getting dizzy.
Sleeping pills from the second floor
makes me feel so good.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Yes?
That's a completely different explanation.
Sleeping pills from the second floor
are useless because they are too round.
50 steps, 100 steps,
is a saying that came from China.
People who ran 50 steps on the battlefield
can't help but laugh at people who ran 100 steps.
It means that there is no difference between them.
Oh, no.
I'm going to lose my job.
Yes, hello?
Shut up, Reiko!
You can't be so logical.
What did you say?
Excuse me.
The neighbors are calling.
They want you to go with them
to pick up a car that is being parked illegally.
Yes.
Listen, Ryo-chan.
I'll be right back,
so don't tell them anything weird.
All right, all right.
I'm going to work now.
You can take your time.
Oh, no.
Now, the noisy one is gone.
If you have any questions,
feel free to ask me.
Yes, Ryo-san.
What?
What is Tsurukame-zan?
Tsurukame-zan?
This.
Well, what is it?
Is there a crane and a turtle?
If you count the number of heads,
there are a total of 20.
If you count the number of legs,
there are 62.
What is Tsuru?
How many turtles are there?
Tsuru has two legs
and four turtles.
So...
It's a radio turtle.
Come on, come on.
Come on, help me.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Did you catch the turtle?
You're annoying.
Hey, how about the turtle?
There it is.
Alright.
It's about time.
Don't be angry.
The turtle is in your place.
Hey, there's a turtle too.
Alright, now it's finally Tsurukame-zan.
Oh, no.
Hey, hey.
If you hold your legs,
you won't understand.
Stop it.
Oh, no.
Tsurukame-zan is good.
It's Rika.
Rika, Rika.
This is a very important lesson.
Is this Rika?
That's right.
The principle of the pet bottle rocket
is to use the law of left and right.
The law of left and right means
that the person who uses force
can only receive this much force.
If you send a lot of air into the water
and spray it at once...
...the compressed air will blow out the water
and the pet bottle will fly away
with the same amount of force.
This is the same as the principle
of the real space rocket.
Hey, hey, Ryo-san.
Can you make a bigger one?
A bigger one?
Alright.
It's a big problem.
Alright, it's done.
Drum rocket Ryo-tsugo.
Let's launch it quickly.
Alright, let's go.
Ryo-san, please take care of it later.
Please take care of it.
Hey, you coward!
Ryo-san, are you alright?
Are you alright?
Alright, let's go to the social club next.
Turn right and there is a dance shop.
I didn't think there was such a map with a symbol.
The release site is a punishment mark.
Your acting is bad.
My acting is bad.
Maru is better.
Maru is a district office or a district office.
Oh, it's a ninja mark.
Oh, this is the mark of Manji Shuriken.
There are other Shurikens,
Roppou Shuriken,
and Happou Shuriken.
You know a lot, Ryo-san.
Of course.
By the way,
Shuriken can be made with origami.
Really?
Here you are.
Cool!
I used to make this and play ninja.
Tell me!
Alright.
First, fold the origami.
Keiichi Nakagawa.
I'm back.
Reiko Akimoto.
Thank you for your hard work.
How is the teacher doing?
He seems to be doing it quietly.
How is it, Ryo-chan?
Are you moving forward?
Damn it!
How can Fuma Ryo-tsu hit such a bad Shuriken?
What?
Fuma Ryo-tsu!
Just as I thought.
I was surprised.
It's the same as when I was a child.
Fuma Ninja Art!
Hey, Ryo-chan!
Ryo-chan!
Oh, you're back.
Well, this is...
Damn it!
I'm done for.
I thought so, but I'm done for.
History is simple.
If you do Maruan-Ki, you can get points for sure.
Yeah.
Well, how many years has Taika been?
What?
Taika Katsushin?
No.
It's Kaishin.
Taika Kaishin.
It's been 645 years.
The way to remember it is Muji-ko no Yozukuri, Taika no Kaishin.
What?
I see.
By the way, there's also the way to get drunk in the crowd.
That's the way to remember Heihou-kon.
Sui-hei, Ri-bei, my ship.
That's the Gensokigo.
There's also Nakuyo, Uguisu, Heian-kyo, Iyoku-ni Moeru, Kolombusu.
There's something like that.
Yeah, that's it!
Iyoku-ni Moeru, Kolombusu.
Suikin, Chikamoku, Dotten, Kaimei, Kyojin, Taiho, Tamagoyaki.
Oh, Kaneda, Hirooka.
What?
What the hell is that?
What are you going to teach your child?
I learned it when I was a child.
If you have any questions, tell me.
Hey, hey.
You're the only one who's not excited.
Tell me.
Sorry, sorry.
I remember that 645 was the peak of Taika.
Yeah.
Next is Ono no Imoko.
Oh, I know that.
Ono no Imoko is famous for eating sweet potatoes.
It's a nostalgic name.
You ate sweet potatoes and became a swordsman?
Swordsman?
Wasn't Ono no Imoko just a person who ate sweet potatoes and got angry?
Why does the name remain in history?
Because it was the first time in Japan that someone ate sweet potatoes and got angry.
I don't like it anymore.
I don't have any expectations.
There was also a swordsman, right?
There is.
It will be about 20 years later than swordsman.
There must have been a swordsman ship.
Yes.
It's a ship that was used to go to China.
Didn't that ship look like this?
Did you see it?
It's a ship with a lot of people.
It's amazing.
I think it must have been like that.
You remember it well.
I'm starting to remember it.
I remember that U-Boat was fishing at Gento Shisen.
I remember drawing a picture in the textbook.
It's cool.
But you remember the small parts of the ship well.
I imitated the ship and drew it many times.
I'll also draw Kanrinmaru.
Kanrinmaru is a small wooden ship with a length of about 50 meters made in the Netherlands.
I think it was used as a training ship for the Bakufu Navy.
It has five cannons.
You know a lot.
Someone rode this and went to America.
Who was it?
It's not Katsushin.
It's Kaishu Katsu, right?
Yes, that person.
I don't have any knowledge of history, but I only remember the picture of the textbook.
I'll also draw characters.
How about Ferry?
Ferry?
I think it was like this.
Please look at it.
Amazing.
Yes.
I think it's similar.
Why did you draw it so quickly?
I was on the textbook.
I always drew like this in class.
There was also Sugita Genpak.
It looks like this when you draw it like a picture.
How is it? It's good.
This hand's head is the most difficult to draw.
I was happy at that time.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Can you draw Yoritomo Minamoto?
How about Hideyoshi?
Yes, of course.
I can draw it.
I can draw Ieyasu, Nobunaga, Francis and Xavier.
Senpai, do you know what kind of person Sugita Genpak is?
That's you.
It's decided by Rakuoka.
It's a famous person who drew a new chapter.
I thought it was Rakuoka from the beginning.
Was it a person who drew the Yajikita Road?
That's Juppenschaick.
I think I learned a lot.
I don't know.
No matter what the test is.
Don't draw it.
You're good at drawing.
Ryo-chan will teach you something boring.
I'm impressed, too.
That's all for today's lesson.
Hey, what are you going to do with the radio?
I can't help it.
It's a joke.
Ryo-chan, bring it back.
Me?
It's a lesson to teach you not to do this kind of thing.
What?
Where did they go?
Are they...
What is this?
Ryo-san, are you okay?
Shut up!
Hey, I found it!
Ryo-san!
Are you guys going to stop?
You guys are really good at this.
I'm sorry.
Ryo-san, look!
Are you going to use that hand?
Look, it's the same as your brother's drawing.
What's that?
Hey, isn't that Magushiro Tatsu?
I knew it.
He changed his clothes.
Hey!
Wait!
I won't let you get away!
Ryo-san, punch!
Magushiro Tatsu, arrest!
How did you know?
It's a piece of cake.
I was just trying to teach them how fun it is to play pranks.
You're in a good mood.
Now that the test is complete, there's nothing to say.
Idiot, it's already done.
Who do you think taught you?
Ryo-san!
Look, look!
You did it, 80 points!
You're the best, 50 points.
What? I didn't get 30 points, why?
Because you helped the culprit arrest him.
The police officer bought you.
That's good.
Yeah!
There's nothing like studying on a desk in the world.
My practical way of studying is the true way of studying.
Yeah!
For example, my boss came here with only one study.
That's why he's so stubborn.
He doesn't even smile when he sees a variety show on TV.
He gets angry.
Wait, Senpai.
But it's true.
You can't have a subordinate with such a stubborn head.
He's just a stubborn old man.
Good for you!
B-Boss!
You did a good job yesterday.
You helped the citizens and arrested the culprit.
You're a good police officer.
I'd appreciate it if you could erase your practical way of studying.
You're joking again, boss.
They did it on their own.
Don't say that.
Erase it now!
Yeah!
Why am I the only one who gets to see this?
Kyoro-san!
I heard you were busy.
Yeah!
Hey, you guys help too!
Ryo-san!
We're going to the park to play.
Come when you're done!
Come!
Damn them!
Idiots!
How can they do this?
It's fun to clean up.
Ryo-kun.
Did you forget what you said earlier?
I'm going to ask you to pay for the broken show window.
What?
I don't need that, boss!
Bonus! Bonus! I'm so happy!
What?
Pay me back!
No!
I'm the one who made the money!
I won't give it to anyone!
Next time on Bonus Consulting Battle!
Thanks for watching!
The End