Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Wake Up! Civilian Police!
The fire in the sky in Atlanta is about to go out.
See you next year at Shidori.
The Olympics are almost over.
Hmm.
But it's not enough.
Not enough?
The amount of medals?
No.
When it comes to the Olympics, there must be something.
The Olympics?
Minami Haru from the Tokyo Olympics was good, wasn't she?
No.
There must be something more impactful.
Yeah.
The one where a woman puts powder on her face.
That's compact.
Hmm.
I can't remember.
Huh?
That's right.
It's a cicada.
It has something to do with cicadas.
A cicada?
The one that's crying right now is an oil cicada, right?
It's not an oil cicada.
Then is it a cicada?
Huh?
It's getting closer.
Is there anything else?
Yeah.
The one that's crying right now.
Huh?
Is it a cicada that can't cry?
No, it's not.
It's a sunflower.
Huh?
A sunflower?
I see.
I forgot about it.
It's not impossible.
It's the same as the Olympics.
It's only once every four years.
It's already been four years since then.
What are you talking about?
There's someone called Higurashi working here.
Huh?
I don't know such a person.
Me neither.
I don't know that you've started working here recently.
I guess so.
I think the last time he came here was four years ago.
It was the year of the Barcelona Olympics.
Does that mean he's been working here for four years?
Higurashi is a very naughty man.
He's been resting since he was a kid.
He only came here for three days a month.
As time went by,
he only came here once every four years.
Once every four years?
Yeah.
That's why he's called the Olympic man.
I can't believe it.
There's a man who's more naughty than Ryo-chan.
He's not good with his head.
Higurashi has a special ability.
A special ability?
You'll see when you bring him here.
What?
I won't do it.
You're the only one who knows about Higurashi.
Get out of here!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes, sir.
What?
Senpai, you just woke me up.
Why do you need such heavy equipment?
You'll know when you hear it.
Did Higurashi live in the same dormitory as Senpai?
I think it was this room.
Senpai, it's a storage room.
This isn't a storage room.
It's where people live.
It's here.
It's so rusty.
Nakagawa, open the door.
Yes, sir.
Get out of the way, Nakagawa!
Hey, Higurashi!
Are you there?
Yes, sir.
It's not a place where people live.
It's been abandoned for four years.
But you can't see anything in the dark.
Nakagawa, open the window.
Yes, sir.
Ouch!
There's something stuck in my face!
Is it a spider?
What are you doing?
The spider is scary.
Can't you see anything?
There's a bunch of spiderwebs.
It's so bright.
Give me my sunglasses.
You're so annoying.
Give them to me.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Every time I wake him up, he reacts like Dracula.
Is that voice Ryo-tsu?
That's right.
I'm here to pick you up.
What?
It's still summer in Heisei.
No, I slept a little, so isn't it autumn?
It's been a long time.
It's been eight years in Heisei this year.
You're stupid.
Then what happened to the Japanese Shinto that was booming?
It's gone a long time ago.
What?
What about the Japanese Shinto that was booming?
Some of them went out and made another tower.
So the prime minister is not Miyazawa?
Miyazawa?
By the way, it was like that four years ago.
While you were asleep, you changed to Hosokawa, Hada, and Murayama.
Now you're Hashimoto.
Did I change that much?
Even the governor is in Aoshima.
You shouldn't think of me like that.
You're going to say that the governor of Osaka will knock on Yokoyama.
You got it right.
Really?
Then what about Wakahana and Takahana?
Then I changed to Wakano Hana and Takano Hana.
Onii-chan is in Ozeki, and my brother is in Yokozuna.
Did the world change that much?
It's like Urasima Taro.
Ryotsu, who is that young man?
Nakagawa, who has become the head of the police station since this year.
More importantly, don't sleep forever and wake up!
Don't make such a big noise.
It will sound loud.
First, I'm hungry.
No, I can't do it.
Please help me.
This refrigerator is broken.
I bought it when I was sleeping.
I can't eat rice balls and bread.
Yes, it's a mess.
What about milk?
It's no good.
It's heavy.
What?
It's cheese.
Lucky.
I can do this.
How about you?
It's okay.
He's a shy guy.
Then I'll watch TV until I finish eating.
What?
It's good to watch while sleeping.
Next, I need to take a bath.
Ryotsu, I'm sorry, but can you take me to the home bath?
Where is there a bath in this room?
Is the washing machine a bath?
Please put on the sheets and pillowcases.
I'll wash them with you.
Please turn the water tank upside down.
It's the best way to turn the water tank upside down.
It feels so good.
It's the best place.
Change into this.
I'm sorry, but please spread it out.
He's a troublesome guy.
Are you okay?
I'm sleepy because I'm tired.
You're sleeping too much.
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
When did you build a staircase here?
It's been here for a long time.
Did you forget it?
It feels like it fell four years ago.
It fell eight years ago and twelve years ago.
It's decided.
What?
Didn't you come in a car?
I walked for 15 minutes.
Let's go.
It's boring. Let's go in my car.
Did you have a car?
It's a new car.
I bought it 20 years ago.
It's a new car because I've only driven it twice.
Two times in 20 years?
Isn't it better to take a taxi?
It's a hassle to pick it up.
It's scary that the meter is only three kilometers away.
I've never been out of town.
Let's go.
The engine started.
What's next?
I'll step on the clutch and put the shift lever in.
That's right.
I'll put the clutch in.
It's amazing to drive a new car in three seconds.
It's amazing.
But I woke up.
Next Episode
I brought the chief.
Thank you.
I'm tired from walking for a long time.
I'm sleepy.
You're still the same old Guttala.
You're the same old Guttala.
You're a big help.
Get up.
It's daytime.
I'm awake.
Say hello to the chief.
Director, it's been a while.
Are you still the director?
Thank you for your help.
I'm Terai, who resigned three years ago.
Hi, I'm Higurashi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a fan of Risa Miyazawa.
I bought a very popular photo book called YONTAFE the other day.
Let's look at it together next time.
Okay.
There's no one who's going to talk about that kind of photo book.
Next is...
I'm home.
Hey, Reiko, let me introduce you.
Oh, this is the man from the rumor.
Hi, I'm Higurashi.
People call me that Higurashi.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Reiko Akimoto.
Oh, Higurashi has completely awakened.
You're weak against women.
I can feel it.
What's going on?
The case is calling me.
W-What's going on?
It's finally time for Higurashi to show his true colors.
Terai, bring me the second case file.
Y-Yes, sir!
First, an unknown man.
I can see him.
This man works at a construction site in Yamagata City in the northeast.
Terai, contact the head office immediately.
Y-Yes, sir!
This is Higurashi, the head of the Kameyari Park.
He has awakened.
The second case is a gem.
What's going on?
Higurashi has awakened.
The second case is a gem thief.
The criminal is hiding in a mansion in Sumida River, called Nakayama.
The Yamanawa family of the Oka family is heading to Fukagawa's apartment.
The next family is heading to Asakusa Kaminari-mon.
That's amazing.
It's his ability to invest.
Every time Higurashi wakes up, he solves unsolved cases like this.
Next!
Ah, I'm tired. I'm getting sleepy.
Idiot!
I haven't worked for four years yet!
Reiko, rub my shoulders.
What?
Good work.
Higurashi-san, you have amazing abilities.
Good.
Ryotsu, take the camera.
Okay.
I can see it. I can see it.
What are you doing?
I'm burning it.
Higurashi can show the case that will happen within 24 hours.
He can do that?
What is it?
What is it showing?
It's a underwear thief!
There are a lot of injuries in the ship recently.
But I don't know who the culprit is in this photo.
He looks very cool when he gets burnt and becomes a shadow.
Let's take a picture again.
Four in a row. That's amazing.
Every year, there's a new trick.
Huh? What's that? A dog?
It's a dog that's often seen in patrols.
Alright, let's go!
Yeah!
This house...
What's this?
It's the house that's often seen in patrols.
The owner of this house is a woman that Amura hates.
Amura? What's that?
What's that?
Amura is the fashion lover of the top idol, Amuro Nanae.
What?
Isn't the top idol Risa Miyazawa?
Risa-chan has lost weight and is charging now.
No way...
Don't get depressed, Higurashi.
Let's go.
Why is my Taku-chan the culprit?
You're the ones who can't arrest the culprit, so why are you so stubborn?
What?
W-What's this?
Higurashi also has the ability to move.
It's a hole.
It's a stolen underwear.
N-No way...
Higurashi-san, you did it.
I can feel it again.
Nakagawa, it's the camera.
Yes.
Is it a bank robbery this time?
I remember this bank.
It's the bank in front of the station.
Look, the watch is also on.
35 minutes ago...
There's only 10 minutes left.
Okay, Reiko.
I'll go straight to the bank.
I'll leave this to you.
Roger.
Hurry, Nakagawa.
Yes.
To be continued...
Everyone, raise your hands!
Be proud and give out the money!
Welcome!
It's a gorilla!
What gorilla?
You bastard!
Senpai!
Damn it, you're in my way.
I'll kill you!
W-What?
Now!
Damn it!
It's a handkerchief!
Hey, Higurashi!
Put your handkerchief on it!
You're sleeping, you bastard!
Everyone did a good job.
But Higurashi-san, you really have amazing abilities.
I understand why you can't do it.
What about you, Higurashi?
Huh?
I've been here before.
I'm tired.
I can't do it anymore.
If you can't do the whole race,
just the main race is fine.
Tell me how many you can do.
What are you doing, Ryotsu?
Let's go!
Chief!
I was just trying to get Higurashi to solve another case.
There are two cases?
Did you hear that?
Chief!
Oh, I can feel it.
I can feel it.
Where's the horse?
What number is it?
Idiot!
I knew it!
Huh?
Hey!
I-I'm being pulled by a truck!
Oh, this is Ryotsu.
It's an ominous picture.
Hey, Higurashi!
Why did you take a picture like this?
I don't know.
I just took a picture.
It's not a quick death.
You might be saved by a truck.
I'm not a follower.
I'm not going to be pulled by a truck.
Ryotsu, don't worry.
There's a mistake.
My abilities are perfect and I'm confident,
but I don't think I can get away with a hundred million.
Are you encouraging me?
Are you proud of me?
Which one is it?
I definitely don't believe it.
You have a straight face when you say that.
I'm not joking.
Senior!
As long as you look at the picture, it's outside.
It's safe if you don't go out for 24 hours.
Shut up!
I'm scared of the train.
Can the police do it?
I definitely don't believe it!
Senior!
Ryotsu, don't do it!
Shut up!
Don't worry about me!
I told you it's dangerous to go out!
Get out of here!
Senior!
Ryotsu!
Are you okay, Senior?
It hurts.
So this picture is the moment you hit the truck that was parked by you?
Hey, Higurashi!
You should be sleeping for a million years!
Don't wake up!
Idiot!
I'll do that.
Chief, before that...
Oh, it's the usual ceremony.
Reigo-kun,
10 servings of Tendon,
10 servings of Una-don,
20 servings of Yakiniku,
and 10 servings of Sushi.
Please order.
What?
10 servings of Tendon
Here it is.
Everyone, please bring it to the back room.
Okay.
The food is really good.
I've been sleeping for four years, so I've been eating a lot.
It looks like a bear before it's born.
See you later.
How can he gain so much weight?
He looks like a different person.
Well, I'll see you in four years.
Shut up!
Go home and sleep!
Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
When we meet next time, let's meet in 2000.
I can't wait for the next Olympics.
I'm not kidding!
Try to be like me when I go to wake you up.
You can say that.
Kachidoki Bridge
Everyone, do you know Kachidoki Bridge?
When a big ship comes, the bridge breaks in two
and goes up.
Unfortunately, it's not open now,
but this bridge is a nostalgic memory of my childhood.
Next time, open Kachidoki Bridge.
Thank you.
Let's smile anytime
No matter what happens
Smile cutely
You can go out with a face that doesn't matter
Hey, smile at me
You're not bad
You're still in good shape
Smile at me anytime
A woman with a dark skin is not beautiful
You should smile right away
If you're not a woman