Kachidoki Bridge, open!
That was a wonderful wedding ceremony.
Yeah.
Cheers!
Hey, you came to Ginza after all.
Look at the Kachidoki Bridge and go home.
But the direction is the opposite.
What are you complaining about?
Oh, I understand!
Well...
Ryo-chan...
Ryo-chan, it's the Kachidoki Bridge.
Ryo-chan, we're here.
Get up.
Come on, tell him to go by himself.
Kei-chan, stop!
What?
What is it?
There's a man on the bridge.
What?
He's not a ghost, is he?
Where are you, Reiko-san?
I'm sure he's on top of this steel frame.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure I saw him.
He looked like he was about to jump off.
That was a wonderful wedding ceremony.
Yeah.
In the morning, there was a teacup standing in the morning.
I feel really good.
Yes, is that so?
Thank you for your help.
It seems that there were no accidents or incidents near the Kachidoki Bridge.
Kachidoki Bridge?
But why was there a man there?
Good morning.
Senpai, good luck.
The chief is in a good mood this morning.
Lucky.
Good morning.
I drank too much.
Idiot!
What do you think you're doing?
Please don't yell at me.
My head is pounding.
Come here.
I'll squeeze you a lot.
I'm not a stray cat.
Hey, where are you in a good mood?
Let's get out of here.
What's wrong?
He was in such a good mood.
Idiot!
Kachidoki Bridge
It's illegal parking.
Good morning.
Oh, it's Sapporo No.
Yes.
It was illegal parking near Kachidoki Bridge since last night.
Kachidoki Bridge? Since last night?
Yes.
The neighbor saw a tall man in a white dress get off.
White dress?
Could it be from last night?
Hello.
Please introduce the owner of the car.
The number is Sapporo.
It doesn't seem to be illegal parking.
Is it an accident?
No.
It's not decided by the car of the man last night.
Yes.
Toyohirakku, Sapporo City.
Shiratori.
A pure white chicken and a pure white chicken.
It's Shiratori Jun.
Thank you very much.
Did something happen to Shiratori Jun?
Yes.
Ouch.
Do you know him, Byo-chan?
He's a friend from my junior high school days.
Well, it was only a short time ago.
He left his car near Kachidoki Bridge and disappeared somewhere.
Kachidoki Bridge?
Oh, that's right.
He came to see the bridge.
The bridge?
What do you mean, senpai?
Well, that was when I was a cute junior high school student.
Yo, Kankichi.
Yes.
Wow.
Big spin ball.
My head is spinning.
Kankichi, who told you to spin in the air?
It's a service.
Kankichi, you're amazing.
You're the best.
Jun, did you have fun?
Next time, I'll show you something more flashy.
Kankichi.
Yes.
Hey, Jun.
You went to Banpak, didn't you?
That's great.
But I couldn't see it very well because it was crowded.
I heard you went on the Shinkansen.
Have you ever ridden a Tonkichi?
I've only ridden the Toobu Line.
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
Please enjoy your meal.
Oh, it's a cake again.
I'm sorry all the time, auntie.
It's okay.
From now on, get along with Jun.
Yes.
Well, take your time.
When I go to the gym, I don't get bored at all when I look at Kanchan and the others.
Kankichi is the only one who is energetic.
Next time, I'll show you a bomb.
In return, show me again when you're testing.
I have 2.5 vision.
I can't do canning.
Anyway, it's a great book.
Did everyone read this book?
Roughly.
I'll lend it to you anytime.
We're not good at this kind of hot books.
Right, Tonkichi?
Yes.
Just the textbook is enough.
That's right.
I think this is interesting.
Japan's...
It's called Japan's Kado Bridge.
I like this kind of thing.
Isn't it Kachidoki Bridge?
It's true.
Yes, it's Kachidoki Bridge.
Do you know it?
I know much about bridges.
Shirahige, Kototoi, Azuma, Komagata, Umae, Kuramae, Ryogoku, Kiyosu, Eitae, Tsukuda, Kachidoki.
That's it.
It's a bridge on the Sumida River.
Wow.
I was reminded of it when I was in elementary school.
My favorite is Kachidoki Bridge.
It moves like this.
I want to see it once.
You haven't seen it?
I want to see it, but it's far away.
It's close.
It's just over the bank.
The car stops and the bridge opens slowly.
When you look at the bridge, the road is like a wall.
It's very powerful.
It's amazing.
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Let's go to Kachidoki Bridge.
It's about 20 minutes by bicycle.
Okay.
Let's go.
This is the way of justice.
We're almost there.
Look.
That bridge opens.
It's perfect from here.
I always buy bread and look at it while eating.
The boat is coming.
It opens.
It doesn't open.
It's strange.
It should open at noon.
What's wrong?
It doesn't open anymore?
It opened yesterday.
It doesn't open anymore.
It's time to transport land.
It's easier to transport water.
I didn't know that.
Kachidoki Bridge doesn't open anymore?
Once you decide, it won't open again.
It's always us who make people cry.
I'm so disappointed that I came to see it.
I was looking forward to seeing it.
Don't be upset, Jun.
Kondo.
Yes.
Shibayama.
Shiratori.
Shiratori is a dead end.
Sir, what's wrong with Jun?
He has a fever and is sleeping.
It seems that he was shocked when he saw Kachidoki Bridge.
Let's go back.
What?
The weather?
I moved to Hokkaido because of the good air.
I was able to get along with everyone.
Even if we go far away, we are friends.
Right?
Yes.
That's right.
However, the only regret is that I couldn't see the opening of Kachidoki Bridge.
I wanted to see it with everyone.
Jun, when are you going to Hokkaido?
Tomorrow.
That early?
Is that so?
It's a pity that Jun moved.
I can't eat such a delicious cake for the rest of my life.
I'll go back to zero again.
Jun was disappointed with Kachidoki Bridge.
I wanted to show you the opening.
That's right.
I'll show you the opening of the bridge.
What?
That's why it's impossible.
We'll open it.
We'll open the bridge and show it to Jun.
What?
Kan-cha
What's wrong?
Come here.
I'll show you the opening of Kachidoki Bridge.
What?
The opening of Kachidoki Bridge?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Wait.
I'll change my clothes now.
This way.
Jun, I'll be right back.
Yes.
This is the best view.
Jun, wait here.
Are you really going to open it?
Don't worry.
Leave it to us.
Let's go.
There are four towers on Kachidoki Bridge.
The only one with stairs is that tower.
That must be the driver's room.
I'll open the bridge.
You two stop the car.
Got it.
Just as I thought.
It's here.
The key is locked.
But it's useless.
I'm good at opening.
Stop.
Kachidoki Bridge.
It's useless.
I can't stop.
I can't stop either.
It's open.
There are so many switches.
I have to sell the electricity.
How can I move it?
Stop.
Please.
The bridge is open.
Stop.
I did it.
It stopped.
What are you doing?
What are you going to do by stopping the car?
Look.
Takishi.
We found Omawari.
Wait.
Takishi
Close the door.
Hey.
Open it.
What are you going to do?
It's useless.
The car won't stop.
The plan is too reckless.
Let's stop.
Idiot.
Jun is waiting.
Really?
Is it really going to open?
But how can we open it?
Let's give up.
Open it.
Hurry up.
What are you going to do, Kankichi?
I'll open the bridge.
I have no chance now.
Okay.
I'm done.
Don't turn on the power.
Don't touch it.
Turn on the power.
Okay.
Turn on all the lights.
Stop the car right now.
Oh, the bridge light is on.
That's ridiculous.
That bridge should be closed.
Move.
The bridge is going up.
Move! The bridge is going up!
Please move! I'll win!
Stop it!
Don't come here! Open the door!
I'll win!
Open it!
The bridge...
Open it! Open it!
Open it more and more!
The bridge...
It was real after all.
It's a battle car!
What's going on?
Idiot! Hurry up and get the bridge back!
Open it! Open it!
The bridge...
We did it! We won!
We did it!
The winning bridge opened up!
It's like they're saying good-bye!
The bridge opened up again!
The winning bridge has to be A!
That's the face of Sumida!
It's really amazing!
It's more than I imagined, Kan-chan.
We did it!
Did you see that, Jen?
Open it! Open it!
Get ready! I'll deal with you all!
No! We can't run away like this!
What should we do?
Come on!
What are you going to do?
Hey! Don't let the bridge open up and run away!
What a bunch of people!
Help me! Help me!
Run away!
Then they swam to Hamari-kyu.
They ran away and came back again.
They were watching the big fight at Kachidoki Bridge.
It's been exciting for a long time.
He must be happy, Jun-kun.
Jun-kun!
Of course!
I can't forget that excited smile.
But maybe that Jun-kun abandoned his car and climbed up to Kachidoki Bridge.
That's not true.
He was weak, but his heart was strong.
I'm sorry.
The car in front of me...
Jun!
Kan-chan?
Why are you here?
You look like a police officer.
Kan-chan is your uncle?
Don't laugh!
You're a law enforcement officer.
No, I was just thinking that the repairman would take me there.
Oh, right.
This is...
A university professor?
You're a good student, Jun.
It's all thanks to Kan-chan.
I can't forget the day he raised the bridge with all his might.
Now he's setting up the bridge.
So, what made you climb up to Kachidoki Bridge?
There was something I really wanted to investigate.
Kachidoki Bridge is amazing!
Oh, chief!
That's my friend, Professor Kougakuha.
I think everyone heard about him.
What? Did you hear about him?
Chief, you're acting strange.
Yeah.
When the bridge was raised,
there was a police officer with him.
That's right!
I just remembered that he was struggling with his legs
and tried his best.
But in the end, he fell into the river.
Do you remember the face of that police officer?
Of course!
His eyes were so big,
and his eyebrows were so thick,
and his nose was so long,
and his mouth looked like a hippo.
I can't forget it!
Ryo-chan!
The chief's face...
What's wrong with the chief's face?
A hippo's mouth, long nose, thin eyes, thick...
No way...
I'm that police officer!
I finally met the culprit of that conflict.
Please calm down, chief!
Hey, wait, Ryo-chan!
It was just an accident.