Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Honda, for the sake of love!
Hey, Nakagawa, are you hungry?
Do you want to eat gyoza today?
Chinese food? Sounds good.
Honda, you're in danger!
Don't be so angry, Ryotsu's boss.
Anyway, I'm going to buy some bento. I'll buy it with you.
It's okay, I'll buy it today.
Can I treat you?
Honda, why don't you say that first?
I'm a special Hirekatsu staff.
I'll give you a tonjiru after a long time.
You're a lively old man.
Nakagawa, how about you?
Can I join you?
Yes, you can.
Hey, Nakagawa, this is for you.
Make it cheaper.
Then, fried chicken bento.
Okay.
Well, Senpai Nakagawa, I'm going.
It's rare for a person to change his personality.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Oh, welcome.
Are you going to buy bento today?
This bento is the best and delicious.
I'm so happy.
What would you like to eat today?
Special Hirekatsu bento and fried chicken bento.
I'll have nori bento and two more tonjiru.
Okay.
Special Hirekatsu bento and fried chicken bento and nori bento.
What?
Did I make a mistake?
No, that's fine.
And tonjiru.
Oh, six tonjiru.
Oh, okay.
Captain, I'll have two special Hirekatsu bento and fried chicken bento and two tonjiru.
Okay.
Here you are.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm sorry that you have to do this for us.
No, I'm always in your care.
That kind of attitude is important.
It's a big difference from someone else.
That's what the chief says.
Someone else.
It's about you.
Is the food here a little dry?
That's right.
That's not true.
I'm using the best light.
The buttocks are a little short.
This is just right.
This bento is the best.
No matter what you say, it's full of love.
I read it.
What?
You made a lot of mistakes with the number of bento.
You're getting paid to advertise the bento shop.
That's not true.
I understand.
Honda-san, you like the girl from the bento shop, don't you?
No, that's not true.
I see.
That clerk is cute.
How do you know that?
If you look at her face, you'll know who she is.
You're annoying.
What does that clerk say?
She's Megumi-chan from Hoshino.
Don't say bad things about her.
Give up on her.
Why?
Ryo-chan, are you still friends with her?
Please help her.
Reiko, how many times do you think she's been in love?
Not once or twice.
100 times.
101 times.
That much?
Try to be her boyfriend.
But...
Reiko, stop it.
You can't be in love forever.
I won't listen to that.
Grandpa!
What is it?
You're being rude to me, a nice middle for a girl killer.
What?
A nice middle for a girl killer?
Stop joking around.
Come on!
If this is the case, I'll get her and Honda together.
Really?
Yes.
Leave it to me.
It's a big boat, right?
Anyway, I'll get Megumi-chan and you together.
I'm counting on you, Senpai.
Yeah.
Senpai, how was it?
No, no.
There's a man I like.
No way.
What kind of person is that man you like?
He said he's been longing for a white boy who passes by here at 9 a.m. every morning.
Don't thank him.
Megumi-chan, give up already.
I'm also a white boy.
I also pass by here at 9 a.m. every morning.
What did you just say?
Come on!
Honda!
Hey, Megumi-chan.
Yes?
Isn't that the white boy you were talking about?
Look.
He always comes to buy things.
Hello.
What do you think?
Doesn't he look like him?
No, he doesn't look like him at all.
I'm sorry.
He looks a little slim, but his face is tighter.
He's always wearing a scarf and a scarf.
He's really manly and cool.
It's me after all.
Look at me!
Senpai!
His face is different after all.
You may not believe it, but when this Honda rides a bike,
his face and personality become completely different.
You mean Mr. Honda?
This Honda is the number one in the current white boy unit.
That's right.
If you're the same white boy unit,
you know who passes by this store every morning, right?
No, that's not it.
Yes, it's okay.
Please leave it to me.
Huh?
Mr. Honda, please tell me if you know his name.
Okay.
You made an unnecessary promise.
I'm sorry.
I see.
It's getting complicated.
Mr. Megumi, you like the Honda when you ride a bike.
Does that mean you can't ride the Honda now?
Honda, there's only one way.
What should I do?
From now on, you can keep riding the bike in front of Megumi.
Huh?
That's impossible.
I know it's impossible.
If you ask for a date while riding a bike,
it's absolutely okay.
That may be true, but...
It's a bit forced.
Men and women are the first priority.
If you decide right away,
the rest will be fine.
Is that so?
I'm sure it's because a nice middle-aged woman who kills women says so.
I'll do it.
Mr. Honda.
I like her.
If I can go on a date with such a nice person,
I don't care what happens next.
Okay, it's settled.
All that's left is to attack.
Yes, senpai.
Good morning.
Mr. Honda told you, didn't he?
Well, yes.
I'm sorry. Nice to meet you.
I'm Megumi Hoshino.
What's your name?
I'm Honda.
Are you also Mr. Honda?
No, I'm Suzuki from Honda.
Are you Mr. Suzuki?
It's strange that I can't ride a bike.
Do you want to risk your life and feel the wind with me?
Yes, I'd love to.
I'll pick you up here at 9 a.m. on Sunday.
Okay.
See you.
I'll get the prize.
Thank you.
I did it.
I'm going on a date on Sunday.
Really? You did it.
Listen, don't get off the bike during the date.
Okay.
Suzuki-sen.
What is it?
I didn't think the wind was so nice.
Really?
That's good.
I was Suzuki.
Don't go that way!
Don't run around with me.
Who are you guys going after?
Mr. Honda!
I'm not Honda.
I'm Suzuki.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you were Mr. Honda.
Suzuki, you idiot!
Please forgive me, Suzuki-san.
I understand.
I'll forgive you for today.
But if you do that again, I won't forgive you!
Yes!
Are you okay?
Yes.
If you're with me, I won't be scared.
Okay.
Hold on tight.
That's strange.
I'm sure you're Mr. Honda.
Suzuki-san is really strong and manly.
I'm impressed.
Idiot.
Do you want to watch a movie?
Yes.
The seats are open.
I always watch like this.
Don't worry.
You've changed.
Suzuki-san, you really like bikes, don't you?
Yes.
I'm the best partner.
Bikes and I are the same.
The best partner, huh?
What's wrong?
Actually, my ex-boyfriend is going to the U.S. today.
He has a girlfriend?
He's going to the U.S.?
Megumi-san, will you go to the U.S. with me?
What?
No, it's nothing.
Two years is too short.
We'll see each other again.
Is that all you want to say?
You can go to the U.S. or anywhere else.
Goodbye.
Megumi-san.
But it's okay.
It's over.
I'm the one who wants to get rid of that man.
After all, a man has to be manly like Suzuki-san.
I see.
Let's go home.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Wait here.
All right, it's done.
It's leaking.
How was the date?
As you said, I've been riding my bike all the time.
It's perfect.
I see.
You have to do it.
Megumi-san.
Yamamoto-san.
Senpai, please don't bother me.
Who do you think you're dating?
Who is that man?
I don't know.
Actually, he's going to the U.S. today.
Hey, Honda.
Explain yourself.
Who are you?
Wait, you bastard.
I really want to tell you how I feel before I leave.
What?
Megumi-san.
I like you.
I want to marry you.
This is a ticket for your flight.
I want you to come with me if you can.
You suddenly said that.
That's right.
It's impossible.
I'm always like this.
Take care.
It was late.
Do you have a passport?
I'm asking if you have one.
Yes.
If you get drunk,
let's go touring to Narita next time.
Damn it.
You're a curse.
Next time, I'm going to the U.S.
I'm going to the U.S.
If you do that again, I'll shoot you.
Honda.
Why is it him?
I like you.
I like men.
Suzuki-san.
I can't believe I'm stuck in a place like this.
What time is the departure time of the aircraft?
It's seven o'clock.
Damn, I can't make it in time.
Hold on tight!
Ah!
Thank you very much, everyone.
Hey, hey, don't look like that.
Going to Los Angeles means that I'm on the departure course.
I'll be going now.
Do your best.
Yeah.
Take care!
Call me if you need me!
Do your best!
Mr. Megumi!
Go ahead.
I decided to go with you.
Take me with you.
Mr. Megumi...
How long are you going to hold on to me?
If you don't hurry, you'll get on too late.
Mr. Suzuki, how can I thank you?
You don't have to thank me.
Let's go.
Yes, thank you very much.
Mr. Honda, it's you.
Thank you, Mr. Honda!
Good-bye, Mr. Megumi.
He was such a good boy.
It's the second time I'm seeing him.
I know, so don't cry.
I'm sorry.
It's been six months since I last saw him.
It can't be helped.
But, Honda,
to play the role of Cupid in a woman's love,
you're too good.
You're stupid.
You're just like Ryo-san when he was young.
Just like you,
Ryo-san got drunk here every time he fell in love.
Dad, don't say that.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Hey, Mr. Honda,
falling in love a hundred times is too much.
Ryo-san is over 300 times.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm feeling better now.
Let's drink, Mr. Honda.
Come on.
We're going to be drunk for two days
and get hit by the boss again.
It's normal.
What?
Come on.
I'm sick of this.
I'm going to drink all the booze in the store.
Yes, Mr. Honda.
Next Episode
Thank you for coming.
Would you like some tea?
Our cute subordinates came all the way here.
Please treat us to something.
Next time,
we'll show you the secret of the Ohara family.
To be continued
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
Wave your hand
Say goodbye to the unpleasant things
Oh yeah
Let's live the way we want
There's something good
Outside the door,
the sun is calling