Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Everybody can do!
I don't want to say it even if it sticks out a little.
Don't worry about making a fuss.
A strong and high-pitched voice.
The Rockets
How is it? Look at it.
The results of the health checkup before.
Is there anything wrong with that?
The blood sugar level is high.
You should be careful of the blood sugar level.
Where are you looking?
Here.
You are only 35 years old.
35 years old.
You are young.
Is there any secret?
Actually,
I went to an athletic club about three months ago.
I started building my physical strength.
Athletic club?
That's right.
My friend invited me to go.
It's effective.
I'm still young.
I can't lose to Ryotsu.
By the way, Mr. President.
Your face looks good recently.
That's right.
My shoulders have been healed.
How is it, Terai?
You should go, too.
But I'm not good at sports.
I'm tired of going home.
Don't worry about that.
At first, you should check your physical strength on the computer.
You can start from the menu that suits you.
It's really well done.
Good morning, Mr. President.
What do you mean, good morning?
It seems that your life is not getting better.
Do you think you can work properly?
Don't worry about that.
I have confidence in my physical strength.
I'm still making plastic models.
I spend two nights.
The night before that, I play two new games.
The night before that, I drink with my friends.
Baka-mon!
It seems that your voice is more powerful than usual.
Is it because of the athletics?
Athletics?
Why, Mr. President?
Don't talk about athletics.
I haven't eaten yet.
You should train your head before you train your body.
It's not food, Senpai.
Athletic club is a place where you do sports for physical strength and health.
You can make physical strength with a fitness machine or a computer.
You know that, don't you?
You're stupid.
You don't have to spend money to exercise.
You don't understand, do you, Ryo-chan?
It's common sense to spend money on beauty and health.
In the United States, people who can't quit smoking and people who are dissatisfied with it are people who can't manage their own bodies.
That's right.
People who can't manage their own bodies should experience it once again.
That's why I have physical strength even if I don't go there.
Baka-mon!
I'm saying that you need a well-calculated exercise.
I'm sorry, but if I tell you, you're wasting money.
What did you say?
Okay, then let's see who has physical strength.
Let's have a match with athletics.
A match?
Stop it.
You're not mature.
Are you scared now?
Say it as many times as you want.
What's so interesting about using physical strength for nothing?
You're stupid.
You always talk a lot.
I can see the result.
I understand.
I'll accept your challenge.
You're motivated.
I don't care if you regret it.
My physical strength is here.
As you can see, I'm 35 years old.
But let me decide the place.
At Kamiyari Athletic Square from 2 a.m. tomorrow.
Fine.
Be prepared, Ryo-tsu.
What's wrong, Senpai?
You're suspicious.
No, it's nothing.
What's this?
Kamiyari Athletic Square Open Ceremony?
A million-yen consultation event.
So this is what you wanted.
I thought it was strange.
I understand, Yabu-chan.
I just happened to get a prize for athletics.
That's great.
You don't have to participate.
I don't want a million-yen.
I'll be the head of the family.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you all together?
Yes.
We're going to do it together.
You're a great person.
What's going on?
I don't know.
That voice!
Kamiyari Athletic Square!
You're here, too?
I can't believe we're here.
We're here.
We should go somewhere else.
You said what you wanted to say.
Ryo-san!
You're here.
Ramen, moke, sake.
Ryo-san!
Hurry up and pay.
Don't you have anything else to say?
We don't want to say anything.
If you don't want to, give it back.
I'll give it back to you when I get the prize.
What prize?
Nothing.
Welcome, everyone.
We're going to have a 1-million-yen survival race.
What's going on?
Ryo-san, what's going on?
I don't know.
You're using me?
You're going to use me to make money?
Chief, there's no change in the game.
Do you want to admit defeat without fighting?
No, I won't lose to you.
Please enter.
Please change into this.
What's this?
It's a cockroach.
Please move to this side.
Why do we have to dress like this?
I don't like it.
Wow!
It's a huge kitchen.
What's this?
Are we going to be cockroaches?
Welcome to the cockroach aesthetic.
We're going to go through a lot of obstacles.
It's like a cockroach experiment.
How did they make this?
If you're going to stop, do it now.
What? Who said I'm going to stop?
It's a game.
The goal is to win the first place in 30 minutes.
The first person to arrive in 30 minutes is the winner.
There are three courses on the floor.
You can choose which course you want to take.
Choose the course you like.
It's the closest road from the front.
No, there are too many gaps.
There seems to be some kind of trick.
Let's go through the stream.
Let's start the game.
Ready...
Start!
This is the first place!
I'll do my best to win!
You're good at this.
Let's leave Ryo-chan to the cockroach tube.
It's hard to climb.
I'm going to break through the front.
There's another one.
The cockroach-resistant power supply is on the floor.
What? What is this?
The electricity is not flowing.
I can't see well because it's dark.
My tongue is sticky.
Where is it?
Ouch!
What is this?
No!
Is this a cockroach-resistant power supply?
My tongue is panicking.
The flow rate is correct.
1 million yen is mine!
Help me!
Ryo-san, please help me!
I'll help you if you give me the power supply.
That's terrible.
Then it's okay.
Wait!
I understand, so please help me!
Hold on to me!
I was late.
I'll give you the power supply.
Damn it!
It seems to disappear in about a minute.
When does it disappear?
In a minute.
I can't wait a minute.
I can't believe it.
It's not a human.
It's okay because it's a cockroach-resistant power supply.
Chief!
The culprit of the cockroach-resistant power supply is over there!
What?
Where is it?
You can't get through the night just with your physical strength.
You have to use your head, too.
Okay.
You're stubborn.
Then I'll go ahead.
You dirty hand!
The culprit of the cockroach-resistant power supply is over there!
Chief!
There is no idiot who is caught in the same hand!
There is a 10,000 yen coin over there!
What? 10,000 yen?
What a simple guy.
How is it, Ryotsu?
Try to do something with your proud head.
Damn it!
I'm still going to lose!
Where did Ryotsu and the others go?
What the hell is this?
What?
Ryotsu is inside the cockroach-resistant power supply?
Yes.
It's impossible for Ryotsu to escape from there.
If he's not there, there's no need to panic.
He was a little angry and flew too far.
Ryotsu!
How can something like this stick to me?
Amazing!
It made the impossible possible!
It's exactly the same physical strength as cockroaches.
It's a wonderful physical strength.
Chief!
The prediction is at a high pace.
At this rate, it seems that a considerable number of people will reach the goal in 30 minutes.
What?
That's why I told you.
What are you going to do with the prize money?
Currently, we don't have the time to give out the prize money.
Hmm.
I can't believe we're going to use this.
It's late.
What?
Run away!
Ryotsu!
What kind of athleticism is this?
Did you see the power of the robot arm?
It's still too early to be surprised.
The chopsticks are in the way!
I can't stand this.
But thanks to you, I was able to get the chopsticks.
Ryotsu!
Huh?
What?
Were you there, too?
Yes.
I was suddenly attacked and ran into this place.
I couldn't get out.
Damn.
One million yen.
I can't waste it here.
All right.
Let's all jump out at the same time.
Huh?
The opponent is a machine.
I can't move fast.
While someone is being sacrificed,
the others can move on.
Interesting.
Huh?
Listen.
No matter who is killed, there is no grudge.
Yeah.
Go now!
What?
All right.
While they're being attacked.
I knew it.
Huh?
You're all cheating!
Which one is cheating?
All right.
Now.
Damn.
I can't do it alone.
Don't do it!
You're so cruel, Senpai.
Sorry to bother you.
You're no match for me.
How is it?
You don't like to fight, do you?
Ryotsu!
Is the chief alive?
I won't forgive you.
Damn.
Wow.
It's like a real cockroach.
I'll get rid of you one by one.
All right.
Give it to me.
No.
It won't reach this far.
Don't follow me.
You're always imitating me.
You're the one who imitates me.
You're cowardly.
Senpai was finally defeated.
He went to a good place.
He came out of that place.
It's a real cockroach.
The chief is pretty good, too.
Chief!
It's a present!
I'll get a million yen with this.
There's nowhere to hide from now on.
The goalkeeper is tough.
I can't get close to him.
I'll get a million yen with this.
You're cowardly.
No.
Chief.
I won't forgive you.
Calm down.
It's a small voice.
What's this, Chief?
I've found it!
Damn it! I was just about to reach the goal!
I can't believe I got beaten up this far!
Alright, this is it!
Ah, that felt bad! I'm going to make you fall!
I can't believe I fell!
The captain has been crushed.
The two of them have been crushed?
Hey, captain!
I'm not done yet!
One million yen!
I'm going to make you fall!
What kind of trick is that?
I'm going to take this!
No!
No! I'm going to be beaten up like this forever!
I'm going to reach the goal!
That felt bad!
Damn it! I'm going to make you fall!
I did it!
I got one million yen!
Captain, didn't I tell you?
It's no use paying money and going to an athletic club.
Aren't you going to change?
I liked it, so I got it as a souvenir.
I'm going to live as a cockroach for the rest of my life.
Hey, Ryo-san, you did it!
Congratulations!
I knew you were going to do it!
And then, as promised...
Ah, the Komuro family is over there!
Hey, if you can do it, try it!
You can't lose to anyone with your physical strength!
Hey, I got one million yen!
Damn it!
I did it!
Hey!
Hey! Wait for me! I got one million yen!
Ah, this?
What's wrong?
Please look at it.
Recently, a witness who saw a giant cockroach on the island of dreams had appeared.
And finally, we, the investigation team, were able to capture it on camera.
A cockroach?
Then, please look at the shocking VTR.
One million yen...
My one million yen...
Damn it! Where did it go?
My one million yen!
To be continued...
What should I do?
I failed to capture the important photo that the chief asked me to capture!
This is bad! This is bad! This is bad!
If I get caught, I'm sorry!
I have to do something!
Next time, we will recreate the Gekisha trip to Kyoto!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!