One-Shot at Big Bucks The Lottery Guy
Thank you very much.
See you next time.
On this precious day,
I spent 20,000 yen in 5 hours.
What's the point of having one cup noodle?
Even though it's free of charge.
Damn it.
Hey!
This guy's good at acting in the summer.
Here's your change.
Thank you.
You don't need it, do you?
I'll send it to the police.
This is the common sense of Japan.
If you come to the police station later,
I'll give you a favor.
I'll give you one noodle.
You don't need it, do you?
That was close.
I'm a survivor before my pay.
Even one cup noodle is a precious food.
That's a shame, too.
It's a shame.
Hey, what are you doing?
Yeah.
We're looking for the treasure.
We bought 40 pieces for four people.
Huh?
You've done something stupid during the break.
Let's talk about the world sometimes.
Like a Japanese soldier with a dirty belly.
A dirty belly?
Don't you know, sir?
Yugo has split up.
If you say that, you'll lose to the boss.
Huh?
You're always playing the gamble.
There's no way you can escape.
The treasure is not gambling.
Gambling is your own power.
You have to win with your own power.
That's gambling.
You're so persuasive.
It's naive to bet money on a book like that.
If you want to play, you have to spend time and money.
Leave him alone and investigate.
That's right.
There are four pieces left.
Oh, this is...
You're wrong.
You're thinking wrong.
Work according to your expectations.
Ignore it.
They're all missing.
Of course.
There's no one like you.
The goddess of good luck is smiling.
That's right.
Maybe the same treasure was left last year.
Why don't you investigate?
There should be a year-end lottery number in this book.
That's right.
I don't like the treasure because the winner hides it.
The first prize is no good.
The second prize is no good.
The third prize is no good.
I won 3 million yen.
In Japan, we don't announce the winner in front of the mass media.
It's the Japanese's fault.
Isn't that right?
It's not good to be silent when you win.
That's right.
If you go there, it's good to play pachinko and horse racing.
Even if you win or lose, your emotions will be honest.
You lost the pachinko today.
Shut up.
It's a matter of time.
Chief.
How was the treasure?
That's right.
Let's stop talking about the treasure and talk about Bosnia and Herzegovina.
Chief.
Are you hiding something?
A letter?
Is that so?
The winner's action pattern is...
The first prize is no good when you win.
The second prize is no good when you talk about the treasure.
Chief.
Please show me the ticket.
It's a failure.
If it's a failure, can I see it?
No, no.
Shut up.
I'm more suspicious when it's a failure.
It's not a failure.
I'm saying it's a failure because it's a failure.
I'm sure because he said it.
I think it's a failure.
No.
Then please break it at this place.
What?
It's a failure.
If it's a failure, can I break it?
No, I'm collecting failures.
When did you start doing that?
Your eyes are lying.
Show me.
What are you doing?
Hey, you can break it.
Why?
Stop it.
Ryo-chan, are you okay?
Senpai.
What you're doing right now is not about 100,000 or 200,000.
It's a lot of money.
Terai, give me that book.
Yes.
Which is the owner's share?
It's the same as this year's.
This is it.
You read the prize money from the bottom.
Yes.
50,000 yen for five.
Wrong.
1,000,000 yen for four.
This is also wrong.
Next.
3,000,000 yen for three.
I got it.
It's 3,000,000 yen.
Wrong.
You're a fool like me.
It's 3,000,000 yen.
Wrong.
It's wrong.
It's hard to check the prize money for more than 1 million yen.
The limit is today.
If you don't go today, you'll be out of luck.
What?
Chief.
Let's go for a drink today.
Until 0 o'clock in the morning.
I'm sorry.
Actually, it's 3,000,000 yen.
You did it, Chief.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
You don't have to hide it.
That's right.
Next.
It's a bad habit of Japanese people who don't say anything.
Really.
You should be happy like a foreigner.
Like this.
Happy.
I won the lottery.
I'm so happy.
I got it.
Give me chocolate.
I want you to express your happiness like this.
Do you understand?
I'm not a foreigner like that.
Let's call the office and let everyone know.
Hey.
I checked it by chance, so I think I got it right.
It's the same as the golf hole-in-one.
It's common sense to have a party and celebrate it with everyone.
But...
Or were you going to enjoy 3 million yen alone?
I didn't mean that.
Then leave it to me.
This is Ryotsu, the head of the park.
Prepare a special shabu-shabu for 200 people tonight.
Shabu-shabu?
Hey.
I'll go to the office to inform them directly.
Ryotsu.
I was lucky to win the lottery.
It was unlucky that Ryo-chan was there.
Chief, do you have a day off today?
It's been like this since the day after that.
It's about time to recover.
I was shocked.
Senpai, You're doing too much.
You should stop doing shabu-shabu.
You have to set it up until 8 o'clock.
Chief is on his way.
Good morning.
I'm sorry to bother you.
How much did you spend on the party?
I didn't have any money left.
I'm sorry, but don't talk about that anymore.
I'm getting hot again.
More importantly, Chief.
Since then, Senpai have been addicted to lottery.
What?
It's the lottery in America.
What's that?
You have to choose 6 numbers from 1 to 51 to win.
The prize money is 5.5 billion yen.
5.5 billion yen!
I understand that why he is addicted to lottery.
But is it that easy to win?
Ryo-chan said there might be a trick.
He collected the data from the past five years.
He is going to the math teacher.
He's going to study the combination of the numbers.
He's a hard worker.
Hello.
Chief, did you finally come out?
Damn it!
Even though you made a fool of the lottery,
you seem to be buying lottary a lot.
Don't say that.
It's 5.5 billion yen.
Ryo-san, there's a latters from overseas.
I'll keep giving you until you win.
Chief, would you like to have a bite of the dream of 5.5 billion yen?
No, it's okay.
You just have to finish your little dream in Japan.
Did I get it right?
What was the previous winning number?
2, 16, 17.
I got it right up to here.
The next one is 23.
2, 34.
I got it right!
No, it'll keep you happy until here.
It is  going to disappoint you later.
I knew it.
If I had chosen it, it would have been a 4-5 curve.
Why did I choose 4-5 instead of 45?
4-5?
Could it be...
45?
I got it right.
It's 5.5 billion yen.
It's amazing that you will get it right.
The winning number is 5.5 billion yen.
Right, Ryotsu?
What is it?
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Did I have a fever?
What about lottary?
What are you talking about?
You were looking for the winning number of lottary, weren't you?
I'm surprised.
Anyway, why don't we talk about the cost of food?
What do you think?
I think the winning number will change the topic and stop talking about the lottery.
What happened to lottary, Ryotsu?
That's...
That's none of your business.
I'm on duty.
Please don't talk to me for a while.
If you talk to me for a while, you'll suddenly become silent.
I don't like it.
I don't like to talk.
I got it right.
What are you talking about?
Don't play around. You got it right.
What is it?
You got it right, the lottary .
You got it right for 5.5 billion yen.
I got it right.
You got it right.
It's the same number as the number you chose.
Hey, Nakagawa!
You have a bad eye.
You're dirty.
We were thinking about winning together.
Stop it, Ryocchan.
You got it right.
5.5 billion yen.
Really?
You got it right.
Yes.
What is it?
You always say that people are noisy like foreigners.
You're the representative of the common people.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm going to be noisy like a foreigner from now on.
I'm going.
I got it right.
5.5 billion yen.
Give me a dance.
It's not a good dance for 5.5 billion yen.
Look at him.
He's totally out of it.
I got it right.
5.5 billion yen.
Give me a dance.
It's rare to see someone who hides something like this.
It would be nice if he was happy.
I'll let the press know about it.
I'm not going to be noisy like a foreigner from now on.
You said you would let everyone know about it, didn't you, Ryocchan?
That's right.
I want people all over Japan to know about it.
Hello?
This is the police station in front of Kameari Park.
This is going to be a big deal from tomorrow.
Yes.
Ryocchan!
Senpai, you're popular at night.
Damn it.
He always thinks it's a piece of cake.
I got this letter.
What?
From Mr. M.K. who lives in Chiba Prefecture.
5.5 billion yen.
You bastard.
You can't use it.
Why don't you go to hell?
Because...
Don't mess with me.
Get out of the way.
Naoko Komachi.
Ryocchan, marry me.
I've always wanted to marry you.
Ryocchan?
What?
Ryocchan, I thought you were going to do something big.
I've always wanted to marry you.
Wait a minute, Komachi.
Naoko, listen up.
I'm the one who's going to marry Ryo.
Until yesterday, Ryocchan was the number one man I didn't want to marry.
Shut up!
If I'm going to marry you, it's better to throw away 5.5 billion yen.
What did you say?
I'm going to marry you.
Ryocchan, do something.
Chief.
Fujiwara, if you don't get out of here, this panic will be over.
This guy and that guy.
Hurry up and go home.
I haven't got 5.5 billion yen yet, so no comment.
But...
Don't make excuses.
I'll tell you everything when I get the money.
I'll tell you how to use it.
So go home today.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
What?
Okay.
I got it.
What's wrong?
There was an investment from America.
The investment was 5.5 billion yen.
That's a lot.
They're going to report it to the press.
They're going to report it to the press?
Of course.
Anyway, I'm going to get it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
We are here.
Please come in, Master.
Thank you.
How are the civil servants doing?
What's with that outfit?
I ordered it for 3 million yen.
It's a brand product.
Master, it's not a brand product.
It's a branded product.
I'm here.
I'm sorry.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Sato, and I'm going to work as a sheep.
I'm Sato.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Hello, I'm Nakagawa.
I'm Reiko.
I'm the chief, Ohara.
By the way, you always take care of Mr. Nakagawa and Mr. Reiko.
Please take care of them.
This much?
Is it really okay to get it?
Of course.
Ryo, Ryo-tsu.
Don't use it so much.
Give me some money.
I'm sorry.
I'll give the director something in return.
What is it?
I spent 3 million yen at the party the other day.
Please take it as an apology.
Is it really okay to get it?
Please.
Oh, right.
Let's do that.
I'll give him 3 million yen.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
What is it?
I wanted to try it once when I became rich.
I can't stand this interpretation.
Please give me some money.
I can't stand it.
Idiot.
How can you do that?
You're rich.
It's a good time to spend money.
That house?
Ryo-tsu.
Have you decided how to use it?
Yes.
I ordered it on the day I got it.
It was suppose to be delivered today.
It seems, it have arrived.
What did he order?
It's a real combat helicopter.
And it's gold.
Idiot.
If it's real, it'll cost more than 100 billion yen.
Are you surprised?
Of course, you can't buy the real one.
This is a one-fifth scale radio-con helicopter.
It looks like the real one.
And it's made of gold.
It costs 500 billion yen.
Idiot.
Chief.
Did you order that?
Yes, I did.
All right.
Let's start the first flight.
Please wait a moment.
It's really flying.
What are you going to do?
Senpai, I can't help it.
It's like driving a real helicopter.
If it's going to cost 500 billion yen anyway.
It's better for me to spend money.
All right.
Let's spread it out in the park.
It looks like it's going to cost a lot of money.
Dear citizens of Chodai.
I'm Kikichi Yotsu, who has been given 500 billion yen.
It's my pleasure to make this good fortune by myself.
So I'm going to share it with you.
Thank you very much.
It's a treasure chest.
But it looks like it's going to cost a lot of money.
It's going to cost 500 billion yen anyway.
500 billion yen?
Let's spread it out.
By the way, where is this?
It's fun.
By the way, this one too.
By the way, bring this one too.
Oh, no.
The controller...
The controller is gone.
The pilot...
Oh, no.
My helicoptere...
My 500 billion yen helicopter...
Excuse me.
Where is my money?
Ryo-san, you're in trouble.
The United States is going to make you pay a 30% tax on the lottery.
What?
They're going to make you pay a 30% tax of 500 billion yen as a tax.
A 30% tax of 500 billion yen?
What?
1.65 billion yen?
A tax?
They're going to make you pay a 5.5 billion yen tax.
They're going to use it in no time.
And they're going to make a tax of 1.65 billion yen.
What a stupid man.