Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Ah!
The southern wind blows
Nagisa-de!
Ureborii!
Hugely popular! Flying food stalls
The Big Rebellion
The Sky-Flying Yatai
What's this?
A wish for a long-distance relationship?
You're going to quit, senpai?
I don't like it, chief!
Please call it a wish for a vacation!
A wish for a vacation!
Idiot!
You're an adult and you don't even write kanji!
You're going to quit, senpai?
Are you going to go out with me?
No way.
I'll write the reason in detail.
Reason?
The reason for the Tameyari Fireworks Festival?
I've never seen a firework festival since I was a kid.
Idiot!
Do you know what kind of job you're doing?
Of course! I'm a police officer!
Do you think it's okay for a police officer to take a vacation at a firework festival?
The firework festival is held every year by amazing people.
I want to borrow a cat's hand as a guard.
It can't be helped. I'll pay for it.
If you do that, you'll be fired right away!
It's a joke! It's a joke!
The firework festival is held every year by amazing people.
The head of the department store is using the firework festival every day.
It would be great if I rode him and saw the fireworks.
Damn!
There's no way I can rest well.
Hey, Ryo!
Yes?
Hey!
What?
I just thought I'd pay you back.
I can't pay you back.
Is it that expensive?
Yes.
If Ryo pays me back, I'll have to pay for the firework festival.
This is a step ahead of us.
There are big apartments all over the place.
Aren't there more people eating ramen?
In a high-rise apartment, you can't even hear the sound of the firework festival.
You should pay me back.
I have a cell phone.
No, I can't.
I'm alone.
I can't ride the elevator while pulling the bar.
It takes too much money to pay with a helicopter.
And the engine is noisy.
It's easier.
The firework festival
Hey, Kazushika Balloon Club!
Hey, Ryo.
Are you nervous about the firework festival?
Yes, I borrowed money.
Where's the old guy?
He's in the warehouse.
If you don't mind, could you lend him to me?
He has a friend who's interested in it.
Yes.
It's a great honor for us to have more friends.
I don't mind.
The firework festival
Are we going to ride this and go out?
We can use propane gas for fuel.
Are we going to make ramen in this?
What do you think?
Oh, no.
He seems to like it.
He said he wanted to ride it.
Oh, please.
Let's try it.
It's inflating.
Remember the procedure.
What?
We'll drive it on the show.
You're not asking him to do it?
Do you think he'll be happy to do it?
Besides, in Japan, it's not allowed to fly at night.
What if the bearded man knows about this plan?
Beards are scary when they get angry.
They might bite you to death.
Ryo, get in the car.
Okay.
Calm down.
It's flying.
You're a pro.
The basic movement of the hot air balloon is adjusted with this burner.
It can fly high.
It doesn't have to fly that high.
It can fly as high as a high-rise apartment.
What?
It can also release the heat when it is fast.
Releasing the heat?
You're enthusiastic.
What?
It's a business.
No.
I want to be a professional in the hot air balloon.
I want to do business flying in the sky in elementary school.
That's what you wrote, right?
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
We're running out of time.
It's a hassle to go to the convenience store.
What's that?
What?
It says ramen.
No way.
The phone number is also written.
I'll try calling it.
Yes, it's an emergency ramen.
Are you on your way?
Can I have two ramen, please?
Yes.
Two ramen, please.
Which one do you want?
No. 8, 3011, Yamada.
30 times, right?
Every time.
I was able to order it properly.
But how do I deliver it?
It's getting closer.
I'm scared.
It's delicious.
You're Yamada, right?
Yes.
I got it.
You're fast.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's 1,000 yen.
It's an emergency ramen.
Hello.
Three ramen, please.
4023, Beat.
All right.
It's that room.
I got it.
I'm on my way.
Here's your ramen.
It's 700 yen.
Five ramen, please.
I got it.
I'm busy.
Ryo-san.
Someone called the police.
What should we do?
It's an emergency.
Formation.
Where is it?
It's dark.
It's too dark to see.
It's a plan to destroy the world.
That's why I painted the ground black.
I'm not good at it.
If you get caught,
your business will go up.
I didn't think it would go up so much.
If you do it like this,
I'll do it on purpose.
I'm not good at it.
Good.
But is it okay for the police to do part-time jobs?
Is it okay?
I'm a police officer.
I have a duty to help people in need.
If there are people hungry at night,
it's the way to help people.
A suspicious situation
has been witnessed in the neighborhood
of a high-rise apartment in the city.
It's likely to appear tonight.
It's a big deal.
Enhance the night patrol
and work on the discovery.
Do you understand?
But I don't think it will appear tonight.
Why do you understand that?
That's what he said.
I'm a police officer.
Did you know
that you were a police officer?
What?
What do you want to bet?
1,000 yen.
Idiot!
Do you think it's okay
to do part-time jobs?
Sir, how about this?
If Ryo-chan
gets a clue about a suspicious situation,
he can make the fireworks day
a holiday.
I see.
What do you think, Ryo-tsu?
Is it okay?
That's right.
Whatever.
I want to
sing and dance
in the summer.
Thank you for your hard work.
Senpai.
It's up there.
What?
What are you doing?
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
Can you see a woman?
Well, please take a look.
A bird?
What?
It's a bird.
It's so dark
that I can see it clearly.
It's a starlight scope
used by the U.S. military.
If you look at it with this,
you can immediately
find the black, suspicious balloon.
That's not good.
Oh, no.
I got something amazing.
Senpai, why don't you
find the balloon together
and get a reward?
I'll give it to you.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Oh, Ryo-san.
Well, Ryo-san always
let me make a living,
so I thought I'd deliver a late-night meal.
Idiot!
What if I get caught
and get suspicious?
Oh, a ramen shop?
I was just hungry.
Oh, it's my first time
eating ramen at a ramen shop,
so I'd like to try it.
It smells delicious.
What?
Is a ramen shop
like this?
Huh?
Yes, it's a ramen shop
run by a police officer
in Onzo City, Nakagawa District.
I don't eat ramen often.
That's not a hobby.
You sell ramen, don't you?
Huh?
The phone is ringing.
Oh, hello.
Yes, hello.
Kikyu Ramen...
No, it's just a ramen shop.
Huh?
Just a ramen shop?
It's a Kikyu Ramen shop, isn't it?
What time do you come here tonight?
Oh, sorry.
I'm off today.
Oh, yes.
Nice to meet you.
You're closed
because you're closed, aren't you?
Oh, no.
I was going to get up early
tonight.
Hey, Ryo-san.
Don't ask me.
I don't know anything.
That's right.
Kikyu Ramen
Cat.
Air gun.
Triangle.
Oh, Ryo-san.
I'll open it now.
What's with that luggage?
You can make a profit
just by eating ramen.
The theory of business
is to develop it
according to the needs of the times.
Oh.
It's called
the flying convenience store.
Everyone,
sorry to keep you waiting.
Kikyu Ramen is here.
Hi, Kikyu Ramen.
Oh, hi.
Three char siu noodles, please.
Can I have a rice ball, too?
Sure.
The idol hell limited edition
set, please.
Oh, I wanted this.
Hey, can I have a cigarette?
Sure.
Oh, you have everything.
I want chocolate.
I'll have yakisoba with oolong tea.
Thank you.
I'll have coffee when I'm sleepy.
Please go home.
Hey, melon and strawberry milk.
Which one would you like?
Oh, thank you.
Oh, by the way, can I get two or three weekly magazines?
Sure.
Oh, I'm in a hurry.
This is a big profit.
Oh, look.
It's Kikyu.
It's here.
Okay, I'll go after it.
This is Naoko.
I found it.
Okay.
Kei, please prepare the starlight scope.
It was worth it.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
It's sold out today.
Let's go.
Ryo, it's a mini-pato.
What?
That's for Kobachi and Naoko.
Okay.
It's a mini-pato for formation.
It's gone.
It's okay.
I can see it with the moonlight.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
This is my strategy.
I'm working hard.
I can't see the moon.
I just need to see the smoke.
But I can't see the road.
It's gone.
Damn it.
I can't see anything.
It's gone.
I thought I was going to die.
Damn it.
Kikyu seems to be heading this way.
I can't see it at all.
It's okay even in the dark.
That telescope.
It should be perfect
until a few kilometers away.
Oh, Kei.
This lens.
What's wrong?
This is a black pen.
Who did this?
If you say so.
I don't want to be caught so easily.
I'm sorry, Ryo.
I helped you until the last minute.
I can pay you back in a little while.
Where is the other person?
Hey, it's a convenience store ramen.
I'd like to ask for your number.
This voice.
After all, Ryo-chan.
I'm sorry, Ryo-chan.
Today is the last day.
Good night.
That's right, Reiko.
Why did you give me this phone number?
There is no doubt.
Because the suspicious Kikyu
always appears when Ryo-chan is not around.
If this is the case.
I was caught by that woman.
You're a good woman.
I think it's better to open it soon.
Even though I'm in a good mood.
It's okay.
I have to clean up this stock market.
Let's make a lot of money at the end.
If it goes well.
You can also be popular at the store.
How can you be so popular?
Use the fireworks competition.
Fireworks competition?
But Ryo-san, can you rest on that day?
Can you rest on that day?
It's unfortunate to have relatives.
If you make excuses, you can rest.
I have a lot of relatives who are older than me.
Chief, actually...
I know.
It's about the holiday.
I'm listening to the report.
You seem to be looking for the suspicious Kikyu
until the last day.
You seem to be looking for the suspicious Kikyu.
I'm impressed with you.
Tomorrow's fireworks competition is a special holiday.
Please continue to investigate.
Yes.
What?
You don't seem to be very happy.
It's nothing.
I was looking forward to the fireworks competition.
The wild guy's enthusiasm.
Hey,
isn't it strange?
Those two have been there for a while.
Don't you move while standing still at the window?
I'm not going to let Reiko get in the way of my business.
Ryo-san,
it's finally time to decorate the finale.
Yes.
The last Kikyu Ramen at the convenience store.
I'll make it more exciting like fireworks.
Thank you for waiting.
The Kikyu Ramen has arrived at the convenience store
that is familiar to everyone.
The beer that you drink while looking at the fireworks
is the best in Japan.
What is the best?
The first-class seat at the fireworks exhibition.
Everyone in the high-rise apartment.
Beer, snacks, shaved ice.
The convenience store that has everything
is going to sell you happiness.
Yes, everyone,
together.
Let's go.
Hey, give me beer.
Give me shaved ice.
Yes, I'm coming.
I knew it.
I got beaten up.
Ryo-san,
if you keep this up, you're going to break everything.
This is a great joke.
Hey.
What is it? What's wrong?
The burner is not in a good condition.
It's old.
I can't stop.
Hey, what is the Kikyu?
I have an illusion.
This is no doubt.
I was good at it,
wasn't I?
Idiot!
I'm going to the fireworks exhibition.
What?
What!
I'm going to the fireworks exhibition.
He seems to be involved in the shock wave and doing a dutch roll.
He's a crazy guy.
Ryo-chan!
Is it over?
No, there should be a 15th ball left at the end.
15th ball?
It's 300 meters straight, so if he gets involved...
If he gets involved?
It's the end of the system!
It's a miserable end for an idiot.
What?
Hey, money is falling from the fireworks!
It's a great service!
Ryo-san, the money...
It can't be helped.
I was able to see the fireworks of the 15th ball up close.
I'll give it to everyone as a gift.
Gege!
The foreign lottery has won 5.5 billion yen!
It's 5.5 billion yen!
I'll return the money and buy a plastic model.
I'll make an eel steak.
I can't use it all!
Next time, we'll do a one-time lottery lottery!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!