The Battle of Edokkogase
You're doing great, Junpei-kun, Kappei-kun!
Oh, it's the girls from Nippon-tachi!
You girls are doing great too!
Yeah, leave it to us!
There's a lot of Amikoshi, it's really lively!
It's natural that the festival is lively, right?
It's going to be more lively from now on!
Oh, Reiko-san!
The main event of the festival is from now on!
There's a lot of Amikoshi!
That's right!
After competing with the shrines up ahead,
we're going to decide who's going to be the main event of the festival!
It's the main event of today's festival!
Oh, he's here!
This way!
You're late, Ryo-san!
Sorry, sorry!
I was so worried that you wouldn't come!
It's true!
After all, thanks to Ryo-san, our festival is three years in a row!
Right now, Ryo-san seems to be the main event of Edokkogase!
Is that so?
That's right!
Edokkogase of Edokkogase!
Ryo-san, Edokkogase No.1!
Super Edokkogase, Ryo-san!
Yo!
The best Edokkogase in the universe!
It feels good when you're told the truth!
That guy is Edokkogase?
Huh?
You're making me laugh!
He seems to be happy that he's being teased!
I can't say that he's the real Edokkogase!
What?
You're a face that can't be seen!
Where are you from?
This guy is the real Edokkogase in Edokkogase, Kin-san.
He's a spy in our town!
What did you say?
Every year, every year, I can't let you big guys do it!
You fake Edokkogase!
I'll skin you!
It's fun!
Don't make me laugh!
Yuriyo!
Amazing!
He's a guy with no manners!
You're really an Edokkogase!
You're the real Edokkogase!
I'm not a real Edokkogase!
You're really an Edokkogase!
You can't win over anyone!
You have to look around from the top of the tree!
This is the real Edokkogase!
If you let me say it...
Hey, Ryo-san!
If you're an Edokkogase, you have to stand on the top of the tree!
If you're sitting on the top of the tree,
you're a real Edokkogase!
Yeah!
You're a real Edokkogase!
So that's why you're here!
This is a good idea!
I don't know this guy, so I can't be an Edokkogase!
I'm not going to stand on the top of the tree!
I'm not an Edokkogase!
What?
This is the real Edokkogase!
No, this is the real Edokkogase!
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
You're getting better at this!
Ryo-san, you're getting better at this!
That's right!
We're going to win!
Shut up!
If that's the case, I have no choice.
Let's go!
We're going to lose!
This is great!
That's dirty!
Don't follow us!
You're running in front of us!
Damn it!
You're beating us up!
We're going to lose!
Speed up!
Don't run away!
Hurry!
En Blessed!
We're the only ones left!
We'll be the number 1 chance of你是场上的囚犯!
I'll kill him, so you will die here with him.
Here, take this!
Idiot! Slow down!
You'll crash into a ginger!
You can't stop me now!
I can't stop you!
I forgot!
The
Damn you, idiot!
Are you okay, Senior?
Damn!
I'll miss the four consecutive wins,
I'll be scolded for breaking the shrine and the shrine maiden,
I'll get wet in the mud!
It's all because of that bastard!
Damn!
Damn it!
It's all because of him!
Do you want to get in this bath too?
I'll do it myself!
Senior!
Get out of here!
You can't get in!
I don't feel like giving up at all!
Damn it!
Dad!
I'm here!
Well,
Ryo-san, you're a fisherman, aren't you?
I got one!
It's 370 yen, so...
Well...
Dad!
I don't need fishing today!
What?
I knew it!
You're the best!
I'll get you!
I'm the best!
Senior, what was that scream?
Scream?
I didn't hear a scream.
It's your imagination, right?
But...
It's your imagination!
Um...
Senior, aren't you going to get in the first bath?
What?
I was just thinking about getting in right now.
Oh, this way too!
Don't shake it!
The water is going to leak!
That's right!
Nakagawa!
Help me with the boilers!
If it's this wet, I'll catch a cold!
What?
You're going to raise the temperature?
Yeah, it's still wet.
That's strange.
I thought it was going to be pretty hot.
It seems to have warmed up a little.
If it warms up to this point,
I'll make you laugh.
It's still very wet.
Nakagawa!
It's not warming up at all!
You have to warm it up more!
It's still wet?
It's hot!
It's over 60 degrees!
It's not the temperature that humans can enter!
I said it's wet, so it's wet!
I don't know if it's 60 degrees or something.
It's still like ice water in Edo.
Hurry up and go back to the boilers!
I understand.
It's unfair!
I'm going to get a nosebleed!
Nakagawa, do something!
Y-Yes!
Who are you?!
This is the enamel paste that is used in the Nakagawa ice iron mine.
At a stretch of 10,000 degrees, this can be heated up!
I see...
This bubble is good.
After all, if I don't see the water boiling like this, I don't feel like I'm in the bath.
You bastard.
Don't make a fuss just because the water is boiling.
It's still wet.
It's dangerous!
Senpai!
Are you okay?
If it didn't explode, I wouldn't be an Edo girl.
I'm not that bad.
I'm home!
Ryo-chan, are you awake?
No, not yet.
I bought sushi for you.
What? Sushi?
Senpai, are you awake?
Yes, I woke up because of the word sushi.
Edo girls don't have eyes for sushi.
As expected of Senpai. You're so mean.
It doesn't matter, but you should wear your pants before eating.
There's no delicacy.
There's no such word in my dictionary.
Let's eat!
What's wrong, Senpai?
What's this sushi?
It's an avocado roll.
Avocado?
It's a sushi from the west coast of America.
It's healthy and very popular.
The west coast of America?
Healthy?
Are you kidding me?
Do you know why they call sushi Edo-mae?
Edo-mae.
In other words, it's made of fish caught in the Tokyo Bay.
That's why it's called Edo-mae sushi.
This is not real sushi.
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
It's not that, Senpai.
You bought it for Senpai.
That's right.
I can't eat sushi other than Edo-mae sushi.
Then let me eat what the real Edo-mae sushi is.
What's the difference between the real Edo-mae sushi and the sushi I bought?
If I don't compare them, I can't understand Ryo-chan's attitude.
Edo-mae Sushi
I got it.
You can take it with you.
Take it with you.
What kind of Edo-mae sushi do you want me to eat?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's the first time Senpai is treating me.
Damn it.
I can't believe it.
Let's go over there.
Senpai, how far are you going?
Just a little further.
It's not the sushi restaurant over there, is it?
I thought it was someone else, but it's the real Edo-mae sushi.
You're from Hiromaru!
What?
Ryo-chan's fighting partner?
Was it a sushi restaurant?
It's been 500 years since I went to Edo-mae sushi.
When Toyotomi Hideyoshi was still in Hiriyoshi-maru,
I often went there.
Tokugawa Ieyasu-ko also went there.
It's a very important sushi restaurant.
Let's go, Reiko Nakagawa.
If you fight with someone like this, your brain will rot.
Hey, hey.
You're not going to join that sushi restaurant, are you?
I'm the one who's going to join it.
Damn it.
Tokuko also fell to the ground.
She went to the sushi restaurant to feed her juniors.
Hey, senpai.
Isn't it that restaurant?
It's not that restaurant.
I'm going to join this restaurant.
I'm sure you'll satisfy us enough.
Sushi restaurant.
Let's eat.
This is the real pleasure.
Well, what are you going to do?
This kind of restaurant is very expensive.
I'm going to make it as cheap as possible.
There's a delicious sea urchin in it, miss.
Then I'll take that.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
What do you want me to do?
You have a good taste, customer.
Then I'll take it.
Hey, hey.
Dad.
Why?
Are you worried about the contents of your wallet?
It's obvious.
Real Edo people don't have enough money.
Don't talk nonsense.
I...
Where's the toilet?
Over there.
Even that sea urchin and tuna cost 5,000 yen.
Even if I order cheap ingredients from now on,
20,000 yen will be a little over.
I think I should do something about it and pull it up.
Hey, wait.
I was surprised.
This guy.
He's just going on about expensive things again.
If this is the case...
Dad, I'd like to order a roll of kanpyo.
Yes.
A roll of kanpyo.
I'm looking forward to the cheapest roll of kanpyo in the story.
Special move.
How many tricks are you going to use?
What's this?
What? It's a roll of kanpyo.
Oh, this is a roll of kanpyo?
The seaweed is shining, and there's only one kanpyo in it.
Do you think Edo people can eat such a small fish?
I've been listening to that for 500 years.
This is the real Edo rice sushi.
Let's go, Reiko Nagagawa.
Yes.
Where's the money?
There's no need to pay fake Edo rice sushi.
Operation successful.
Wait a minute, Giku.
That roll of kanpyo is just an appetizer.
This is the real one.
It's a roll of kanpyo.
That's right.
The Edo rice roll of kanpyo is this big.
I'm glad you said that.
It's not easy.
I'll make you do what you want.
What are you going to do next?
That's right.
I'm going to eat the sea urchin too.
Hey!
The sea urchin roll of kanpyo.
No.
You can't do it?
Why not?
There's something I can't do.
Wait a minute.
Um...
Space battleship...
This is it!
Hey, you!
What do you think?
The sea urchin roll of kanpyo.
What's this?
It's a roll of kanpyo.
Isn't it cool?
You fool!
There's no way the sea urchin roll of kanpyo is the same.
This is the sea urchin roll of kanpyo.
That's a bit wrong.
There aren't many people who ask for the sea urchin roll of kanpyo.
This is the truth.
The sea urchin roll of kanpyo.
This is it.
I don't think I've been to a sushi restaurant unless I eat this.
As expected of Edokko.
Then I'll eat it in one bite.
What?
If it's Edokko, I'll eat it in one bite.
Of course.
What's next?
That's right.
I'll get some snacks.
There's nothing I can't do.
That's right.
I'm aiming for a bonito.
Aiming for a bonito?
Aiming for a bonito.
A sea urchin sushi roll of kanpyo.
A roll of kanpyo.
Curry rice.
A rice ball with salmon and salmon roe.
Here it is.
Making a tuna rice ball.
It's completely a piece of art.
It's like watching a child.
What should I do next?
I still have a lot to do.
That's right.
Then I'll get some octopus.
It's alive.
Octopus is dancing in the air.
This is exactly octopus dance.
I'll eat it in a fresh house.
This is it.
I have to eat this once in Edokko.
Oh, thank you.
It seems to have a good breath.
I'll eat it if I get it.
Don't make a fuss about the octopus in Edokko.
Senpai, are you okay?
I got it.
I ate it.
Then it's over.
2 million yen.
Is it expensive?
It's not expensive.
I was surprised that it was so cheap.
Of course you're fine with the payment.
After all, it's Edokko.
I'll get the money.
Wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
I'm sorry.
Unfortunately, I only have small ones.
Can you count them?
I'm happy.
I wanted small ones.
Lucky.
I thought you would say that.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
Your eyes are not laughing at all.
I want you to make Edokko more generous.
The End
What is it?
Why is it that Reiko and I are connected by hand?
What?
There's no key?
Then, then, Reiko and I are going to live in this state for the rest of our lives?
I don't like that.
Next time, don't tell me that Ryotsu and Reiko are...
Nice to meet you.
Let's smile at any time.
Even if something ridiculous happens.
Smile cutely.
You can go out with a face that's nothing.
Hey, smile at me.
You're not bad.
You're always smiling.
A woman who is deeply in love is not beautiful.
You should smile right away.
If you're not a child, then,