Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
The Great Explosion!
In the city, especially in our area, there is a traffic accident.
So, next week, the traffic safety training course will be held in this area.
On that day, the students of this training center will also participate as a guide, so they will be able to understand the idea of a guide that is easy for children to understand.
There are a lot of accidents, so it's troublesome, Ryo-tsu.
That's right.
Like someone who breaks the speed with a bicycle.
I don't like it.
Someone who ignores the traffic light because it's a bicycle.
I don't like that either.
Someone who goes into the shop with a bicycle and destroys the shop.
It's stupid.
Someone who makes plastic and doesn't listen to people.
It's ridiculous.
Idiot! It's about you, about you!
I'm listening!
I'm making plastic for mental health!
Don't make fun of me!
Do you think I'm going to go through such a helix?
It's just like tea!
Don't make plastic and tea together!
What about traffic safety?
Darn it.
Anyway, think of an idea to prevent traffic accidents by the end of the course!
I'm not kidding.
An idea to prevent accidents?
It's easy.
Everyone has to get in the car.
I'm busy making plastic.
Darn it.
Excuse me.
Yes?
What can I do for you?
Um...
Is Ryo-tsu-senpai here?
It's you!
Long time no see.
Ryo-chan's junior?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Honda from the traffic control team.
Actually, I'm going to join the same company as you.
So I'd like to say hello to you today.
Wow, it looks delicious.
I baked chocolate cake.
Look at this.
Surara-chan's face is cute, isn't it?
Surara-chan?
The main character of the anime.
Surara, the girl of light source, is quite popular now.
Surara-chan's voice is so cute.
Don't do that today.
But...
Darn it!
I'm going to beat you up!
This is a riot!
Stop! Stop!
I can't stop!
Stop!
I'm scared!
I'm scared! I'm scared of the riot!
It's going wild.
Are they chasing Komachi and Naoko?
It's a cool mini-pato!
The performance of the machine is different!
I can't catch up!
Stop!
Honda!
Hey!
You came by bike today, didn't you?
Yes.
I always come by bike.
Okay, Honda!
You follow me!
I'm scared.
I'm not good at that.
Just get on the bike!
I have to.
If you're here, you can do it.
It's impossible for you, Honda.
I can't do it!
Just get on the bike!
Stop it, Ryo-chan!
I feel sorry for you, Honda.
Just get on the bike!
I can't do it!
Alright!
Let's go!
Who is he?
I'm Honda.
I'm Kouki's Honda!
The bike technique is amazing!
Are you ready, Ryo-chan's husband?
Yes!
Let's go!
Go!
What is he doing?
He looks like a different person.
Wait!
Hey!
I can't see him anymore.
What was that?
It looked like a white horse.
The sound of the exoskeleton that shakes the soul of Ibuki Gin.
And the sound of his heart beating fast.
His heart is beating fast.
Look!
The cockroaches are chasing him.
Oh, no!
It's a white horse!
Do you think you can get away from me?
Stop it, you bastard!
Oh, no!
What is this?
What happened?
You're late, girls.
That's what this Honda did to you.
So cool!
What is this?
Don't tell me...
This is...
Honda's...
Yes, that's right!
Honda used to be a bandit.
Now he's a police officer.
But his personality changes when he rides a motorcycle.
He's a man who is feared as a two-wheeled devil.
A two-wheeled...
Devil?
The engine has warmed up.
Do you want to race again?
Yes!
Let's race!
A two-wheeled devil...
No way!
The signal was red just now, wasn't it?
You don't know?
It's not a crime if you don't find it.
If you don't find it...
I found it!
He's the one who made the signal in front of Honda.
He's a coward.
Hey, you!
Don't you have to stop?
I have to stop.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to destroy the universe.
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
You ignored the signal.
Yes.
Is this the end?
Move the car as fast as you can.
But the engine...
What?
Is it my fault?
No, it's...
Don't you have a problem?
Idiot!
Even though you're a criminal,
you destroyed three bikes and one passenger car,
and caused a huge traffic jam.
What kind of person are you?
I'm sorry.
It's a big deal.
Well, well, well, chief.
Honda is also reflecting on itself.
Today, we have a lot of things to do.
You're the one who made Honda disappear, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I don't have a female driver.
I just want to drive this guy.
Didn't Ryotsu-senpai tell you to go?
You don't like it, do you, Honda?
When did I say that?
Oh, so you're the one who died.
No, that's...
No more questions!
Ryotsu!
I'll give you a high-speed safety poison hundred-shot set!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Poison all of them by the end of this week!
What?
Are you going to read all of this?
It's done.
1750 horsepower, two-speed, three-speed, high-speed engine,
with a great output engine,
it's a masterpiece made by Germany,
who ran through the big sky of Europe.
Junkers Yumo 213H,
another name is Tank 152.
Hey, are you studying traffic safety?
If you don't read it, the chief will scold you again.
How can I read something like this?
By the way, you're not playing with dolls, are you?
I'm not playing.
I'm making it because the chief asked me to.
I'm going to use it at the traffic safety workshop tomorrow.
I'm going to hit a doll that looks like Ryo-chan in the car
and do an experiment on a traffic accident.
What? Hit in the car?
A doll that looks like me?
I won't let you do that.
That's what the chief would think.
You're going to turn your daily grudge into a doll.
Who's the chief?
The chief is the chief.
No, no, no.
I want to eat human tonight.
I'm sorry, but it's boring.
Anyway, I'm fine.
You promised to read a hundred books
on traffic safety until the workshop tomorrow, didn't you?
That's right.
I'm definitely coming tomorrow.
Of course.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
I wonder if I'll be able to sleep tonight.
I'm going to make you do a lot of work.
What's with that creepy laugh?
Is Ryo-chan still not here?
Did he run away?
I think he's coming.
Even if he complains or complains,
he's a person who can't resist what the chief says.
It's about him.
Even if he's late, he walks around with a calm face.
Maybe he's skipping.
Hello, hello.
While saying that, he's definitely coming.
I don't like his attitude.
Why are you so...
I'm sorry I'm late, chief.
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
What do you think you're doing?
The alarm suddenly stopped.
It's not my fault.
Besides, the bicycle will puncture and the bus won't come.
I ran all the way here.
It's true.
Idiot.
Don't blame anyone.
Chief, the general public is watching.
I see.
It can't be helped.
The alarm broke and the bus was late.
Ryo-chan, you've learned how to drive, haven't you?
Of course.
From the tip of my head to the tip of my toes,
I'm full of traffic safety.
He's picking up.
Don't mess with me.
Chief, look ahead.
It's not a good idea to make a joke
about a difficult traffic pattern
and teach it to everyone.
It's okay.
You have your own role.
What are you doing, chief?
I'm going to help you.
It's scary.
It's going to be a traffic safety issue.
I wonder if it's going to be okay.
We are working day and night
to protect everyone from traffic accidents and crimes.
However, traffic safety...
I thought it was over when I was late.
I'm going to start the next operation.
Honda, can you hear me?
I can't do that.
Besides, I'm on patrol.
I'm a little lazy.
Are you listening to me?
I understand.
I'm going.
Okay.
It can't be helped.
I'm going.
Wait for me.
Please use this opportunity
to prevent traffic accidents.
I don't have an old man's body.
How long do I have to hold the microphone?
Chief Ryosu.
What is it?
Please prepare for the good kids' corner.
Good kids.
You are small,
so it's hard to see from the driver's point of view.
Please be careful.
Yes.
Okay.
Chief Ryosu,
I'm hungry to enjoy myself.
When you cross the road,
raise your hand and cross it.
Yes.
It's dangerous.
I don't know when the car will come out,
so be careful.
Okay.
Next,
it's a bicycle accident
that often happens between elementary school students.
It's often a traffic accident
caused by a truck.
Let's recreate that scene here.
Let's do it.
Damn it.
It's ridiculous.
Why should I be sad
when I have to dress like this?
Hey,
elementary school students shouldn't call me that.
Kankichi-kun.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
In the case of left-hand traffic,
please be careful
especially for large trucks.
At such an intersection,
when a large truck turns,
this boy,
may get involved.
I'm going to use this boy
to practice,
so please keep an eye on him.
Chief,
don't beat around the bush.
I'm not a chief.
I'm a driver of a large truck.
You have to practice hard,
elementary school students.
It's good, everyone.
Please pay attention to this guy.
Let's practice.
When the car turns,
the rear tire
comes out inside,
and in this case,
that boy will be pulled out.
Damn it.
I'm going to get involved
in the chief's trap.
Please watch.
The rear tire comes out here,
and the boy...
He dodged it on purpose.
At this rate,
my position will be...
I'm sorry,
Ryotsume.
What about now?
If you run away like this,
you might be saved.
But if you think
you can run away every time,
you're mistaken.
Next.
Next is the real game.
Watch, Ryotsu.
I won't miss this time.
This is the end of the game.
I'll run away as many times as I can.
I won't let the chief
do what he wants.
Here we go.
In this way,
you need to be careful
when you run
parallel to the truck.
Hey,
the bicycle
runs faster than the truck.
It's to survive
in a sudden battle.
In this way,
the truck
will never come
parallel to the truck.
Please be careful.
Everyone,
be careful.
Damn it.
The truck jumps,
spins,
and comes in.
How can it be parallel?
That's right.
It's like
a child's fight.
I don't think
it's a good idea
to have traffic safety.
Protect the rules
of the traffic war
that you don't know what will happen.
Yes.
Don't you know
what will happen?
Don't tell me.
I'll tell you
the meaning
of that word,
chief.
Next,
is the accident
of a 50cc bike
that often happens
to women.
It's a 50cc scooter,
but the speed
is quite high,
so please
keep in mind
how to ride it.
Thank you for waiting.
What?
Chief,
please show me
how to drive safely.
I got it.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Now,
get in.
Get in.
What the hell
are you planning?
First,
bend while standing.
Of course,
don't forget to wear a helmet.
Before
you bend,
make sure
that you turn well.
Ouch!
What's going on?
I started running on my own.
I can't even
use the brake.
Everyone,
this is a bad omen.
This scooter
is modified
so that I can
control this radio.
What's going on?
What's going on with this scooter?
Now,
get in,
radio.
I'm going to drive safely today.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'll show you.
What the hell
are you doing?
Please don't
ride like this.
No one is listening.
What are you
doing?
Look at Honda.
Idiot!
Honda,
please be careful.
Now,
let's try
a more dangerous car
with this
ugly doll.
Damn it.
The chief
is going to
make fun of me.
As you can see,
this doll
is not only
20kg,
but also
a lot of damage.
Now,
let's speed up
and see
how long
this doll can last.
Poor
Ryo-chan doll.
It looks like
the real me
is being hurt.
Mr. Ryotsu,
can you
just shut up?
No,
I'm not
a man
who
will
show my shame.
Now,
let's try
with 60kg
at once.
Will
that doll
be able to
last?
Even though
it's a doll,
I'm a little
worried.
I don't care.
Come on.
I finally
made it.
Hey,
the bike
is coming from the sky.
I don't know
what's going to happen.
It's a traffic
war,
isn't it?
Damn it.
You're
going to
get in the way
if you don't
hurry up.
Yes.
What are you
doing?
Can't you catch up?
No,
the bike
is more advantageous
if it's narrow.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and
move on.
No,
there's oil
on the road.
I can't
move on
because
of the
oil.
Look at
the traffic
war.
It's
scary.
Oil is
suddenly
on the
road.
Damn
Ryotsu's
vacation.
All right,
I'll
take care of you
at once.
Is it really
good?
Ryotsu's
boss.
What are you
afraid of?
If you do it,
do it
thoroughly.
Okay,
I'll do it
thoroughly.
What are
they?
Ryotsu.
Hey,
is this
possible?
It's
hard to see.
Let's go.
It's
cool.
How
Thank you for your hard work during this time.
We will now begin the last practice session.
The two policemen who are prepared to die will compete in the shock test of the two cars.
Please don't try this at home.
Do it, Nakanoa!
Do it with all your might!
Are you sure?
Do it, Kamawa!
Chief!
Please help me!
Chief! I'm sorry!
Stop it!
I'm not a dummy doll!
We did it!
Tomorrow we'll have a party at Nakagawa's house!
It's like the birthday party of the prince of the Kingdom of Hondara!
It's at Nakagawa's house!
The food will definitely come out like a mountain!
Alright!
I won't eat anything from now on, and I'll make you hungry!
Next time on Nakagawa-kun no Otaku Haiken
Thank you for watching!