Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Sumo to the max!
There! Go, Takanoyama!
There, there! Go fast!
Alright! Alright!
There, there! Use your left hand!
Takanoyama!
We did it! We did it!
It was really powerful!
Takanoyama of Konbashi is the president without any complaints.
I don't want to miss the best part of Yokozuna Takanoyama.
Even if you watch it on TV, you won't understand the real fun of Osmo.
So have you ever seen the real thing?
If it's a real sumo wrestler, I sometimes see him walking in his yukata.
Even I watch it!
Why don't you come to see the real thing?
It's not that easy to get Osmo's tips.
Oh, really? I didn't know that.
You can't get Osmo's tips if you're not good enough to be a member of the national team.
It's my dream to see Osmo in the national team.
The dream is to be a member of the national team.
By the way, it's the Fukubiki of Shoten-Gai.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to patrol.
It's rare for Ryo-chan to leave the soup.
This is the Fukubiki of Kamiwari Shoten-Gai.
This is Osmo's ticket.
It's right in front of the town hall.
He hasn't left yet.
Support ticket, support ticket.
It's pretty low.
This is bad.
Ryo-san is trying to do the Fukubiki.
Oh, no.
I'm going to die today.
What's wrong with Ryo-san?
Don't you know?
He's a very lucky man.
He went on a trip to Hokkaido the other day.
Last year, he went on a trip to Guam for four days.
He's got a copy of a computer.
What are you doing?
All right, let's go.
Gold-colored stone sword.
I hit it again.
You did it.
You're back already?
Yeah.
You've just been wandering around, haven't you?
Can I say that?
Oh, no.
I dropped my support ticket.
What?
What's wrong with that?
I have a big face, too.
Ryo-chan, you're amazing.
No, I'm not.
Well, that's...
Well, how about it?
Who wants to buy this ticket?
Sumo is a Japanese traditional martial art.
Flowers are sakura, mountains are Fuji.
You have to watch sumo to be a Japanese.
Oh, right.
Don't you forget the Japanese spirit soon?
But...
This is a ticket to Masseki and Seishuraku.
It's not something you can buy with a salaryman's salary.
Is he gone?
I don't think so.
I don't know. Let's go to Nagagawa.
Let's go see it together.
Yes.
There's only one person left.
Oh, right.
I forgot the important person.
I have to invite my father to the ramen shop.
Senpai, you're doing too much.
That's right.
I'm not good at it.
It's a joke.
You don't have to invite your boss.
Boss, you're going too, right?
Well, if you invite me, I'd like to see it.
That's right, boss.
You had a high-class brandy, didn't you?
The one you were proud of.
No, that's...
The brandy you drink in Masseki is delicious.
You can bring it to me.
All right, it's decided.
Let's get back to work.
That's a lot of work.
I can't help it.
I'm excited.
You're a great person.
You're right.
And you have a big sense of patriotism.
That's because I'm a patriot in Japan.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're a great person.
This is no problem.
I have no problem.
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
A lot of foreigners are coming to see you.
The popularity of Osmo is quite international.
You can see Osmo in Masseki in a great mood.
Well, well, who is it?
By the way, someone gave you a ticket to Masseki at Fukubiki in Shoten-gai the other day.
Giku.
That's right.
I heard you were in uniform.
What?
What do you mean?
If you're not satisfied with the ticket, you can go home.
It doesn't matter whether it's Fukubiki or something else.
I'm really grateful to you.
Well, let's go.
Did you all get the ticket?
Yes.
All right.
Don't be late after me.
My ticket!
Wait!
Idiot!
The wind in Ryogoku is so nice.
Now we can see each other slowly.
Leave him alone.
Let's go.
Yes.
Wait!
The flow of Sumida River was great.
Did you jump into the Sumida River?
Of course.
I'm going to lose the ticket.
I can't believe it.
He's doing it.
The flow of the river is great.
This way.
It's quite small.
But it's close to the ticket.
It's great.
What's that?
It's snacks and sake.
You're so considerate.
It's great.
I heard you can get souvenirs on your way home.
There's also a manager's brandy.
It's going to be a grand banquet.
I'm not here for a banquet.
I'm here for Sumo Kansen.
It's a great view.
It's a product of Kansen.
You're smart.
Let me see.
Wait, I'll go first.
Who did this for?
You again?
Okay, I'll show you.
Thank you.
You don't eat much.
It's the blonde girl.
If you don't want to see Sumo, give it back.
It's fine.
That's not the problem.
Let's have a toast.
I forgot.
Cheers!
Did you forget something?
What?
You should be thankful to Mr. Ryotsu.
What are you talking about?
Really?
Wait a minute.
He's in a bad mood.
Okay, I'll say it.
Thank you to Mr. Ryotsu.
Cheers!
This is Takanoyama.
Look!
It's Takanoyama.
You can tell by looking at it.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's right.
What will you show us?
I'm looking forward to it.
I see.
This is Makunochi bento.
Why don't you calm down and look at Sumo?
I've already eaten.
Can I eat sushi for Reiko?
Sure.
Sorry.
Senpai is eating silently.
It's okay.
It's better to give food quietly.
The East Sea
The Sea of Plum Blossoms
The Sea of Plum Blossoms is full of energy.
Unlike TV, it's full of energy.
It's a good shot!
Shut up!
Can I eat this yakitori?
Don't call me like that.
It's over!
The Sea of Plum Blossoms
It's amazing!
Thank you!
It's my first time seeing it.
Idiot!
You didn't see the match.
You'll get angry if I eat silently.
I won't get angry because of that.
It's not a big deal.
What did you say?
That's enough.
I'm going to the toilet.
What a guy!
He's making a fuss because he missed the first match.
That's right.
I was looking forward to the first match of the Sea of Plum Blossoms.
Why don't you watch it on TV?
Then you don't know why you came.
Thanks to who?
Don't say that.
You're the one who got lucky.
You're late.
You're lost somewhere.
I'm the one who's in trouble.
Who are you?
Are you all right?
There's been a lot of damage recently.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
Really?
I'm really sorry.
What?
That's strange.
I thought you were coming from here.
I'm in trouble.
It looks the same from any entrance.
Did something happen?
I don't know.
I don't know where my seat is.
Sir!
This way!
Ryosuke!
I just got a call.
Is that so?
There's been a lot of damage in the ship today.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help.
I almost got lost.
Let's go back.
Ryotsu!
We're in front of the store.
Let's buy some souvenirs.
Hurry up.
It's almost the second half.
What should we buy?
I have an idea.
Takanoyama is really big.
This isn't bad.
We can sell it to the women in the department store.
It's well made.
I'll buy one as a souvenir.
How much is this?
What?
What's wrong?
I don't have a wallet.
That's strange.
I don't like this.
Didn't you forget your wallet at home?
I bought a ticket and got on the train.
I'll lend you my wallet.
I'll give you the money.
What?
That's not my wallet.
That's my wallet.
Wait a minute.
It's a woman's wallet.
It's Sully.
No, it's not.
Where is Sully?
This is Sully.
I said no.
Let's run away.
Stop.
Why do I have to run away?
Ryotsu, what's going on?
I don't know.
That's right.
That woman is guilty of Sully.
Damn it.
Where is she?
She should be in that room.
Ryotsu, explain yourself.
Stop.
If this continues, we will both be arrested.
Please be a little victim for the sake of justice.
What?
That's the board.
Where?
I'm sorry.
Wait.
You two are late.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you're lost together.
Those two are scary.
I'm going to look for them.
All right.
I'll be back in a while.
I'm going to eat lunch now.
That's right.
Hey.
Ryotsu.
What are you doing?
Go away.
Typhoon.
Excuse me.
I'm going.
All right.
This is Sully.
No.
That's not it.
But it's not different from a friend.
That's why I...
I don't know.
Where is it?
Where is that blonde?
I sacrificed my head.
I'll definitely catch you no matter where you are.
There it is.
Sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes.
It's Sully.
That's Sully.
Oh my God.
Arrest him.
Wait.
Senpai.
Help.
Wait.
What are you going to do?
I caught you, Sully.
I won't let you get away.
No.
You bastard.
Get your dirty hands off me.
Shut up.
You were arrested by me for Sully's crime.
Be quiet.
What are you talking about?
You're Sully.
Let her go.
Sully is this blonde woman.
You're not Sully.
You're a villain.
Don't judge me by my face.
He's not Sully.
He was trying to save me.
Sully is that woman.
That's right.
But...
What?
What's wrong with you?
Damn it.
Wait.
What are you doing?
That's my mouth.
Ryotsu.
You abandoned me.
Well, well, well.
For the sake of the criminal,
you can't give up a little sacrifice.
And if you run that much,
you can get rid of your shortcomings.
What?
No way.
You put so many things in my jacket.
I'll do it with a cute face.
That's my wallet.
I didn't have time to be careless.
Even if I told you.
What?
You always make trouble.
I don't think so.
I may be a man who makes trouble,
but I'm a doji who can at least take my wallet.
Can you say that?
You put your wallet in your pocket.
What did you say?
Ouch.
My pants are broken.
Hurry up.
There's only one knot left.
It's a final match between Yokosuna and Ryotsu.
It's hard.
At least I have to see that.
Ryotsu.
I'll talk to you later.
Hurry up.
We have to do something.
I'll do anything.
You came to see me with my ticket.
I'll forget everything.
I got it.
How did you do it?
If I had seen this match, I would have come to the museum.
Go.
There it is.
What?
I can't see anything.
Senpai.
Here it is.
I can't see anything.
Let me go.
It's a big match.
What happened?
It's over.
I can't see anything.
It's a big match.
It's a waste.
As of now, the winner is Takanoyama.
Ryotsu.
What do you have against me?
You're just saying useless things.
What?
Young lady.
How dare you.
What did you say?
You're useless.
I'll cut your head off.
You're saying too much.
Shut up.
Of course I'm useless.
What did you say?
What is this?
The match has started.
I can't see anything.
What are you doing?
I can't help it.
I have to wait until it's over.
But...
I shouldn't have come.
I'm going to die now.
Red is stopped.
Blue is recommended.
Let's raise our hands and cross the road.
What?
That's common sense.
Are you guys following that common sense?
Alright.
I'll guide you through the traffic safety.
Next time, we're going to have a blast.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.