Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
PURi PURi PURi
PURi PURi PURi PURi PURi
The wind blows from south
With the Nagisa
Purr Purr
More!
Visit to Nakagawa-kun's house
Everyone, I'm going to order lunch.
What would you like?
I'd like char siu noodles and gyoza.
I'd like stir-fried lebanese.
I'd like fried rice.
What about you, Ryo-chan?
Oh, it's before payday, so I'd like ramen rice.
What are you doing, Ryo-chan?
Are you on a diet?
I don't think Ryo-chan is on a diet.
I don't think I'm on a diet.
I'm working out hard like this and I'm hungry.
Oh, so you're not hungry?
No, I'm not.
There's a party at Nakagawa's house today.
Oh, I see.
So there's going to be a lot of food at tonight's party, right?
Yes.
I'm going to make it with the help of the best chefs.
I don't think I can eat that kind of food.
That's why you're hungry.
I'm not bragging, but I haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
Idiot.
You can't work if you're hungry.
Why don't you eat lunch?
I'm sorry, but I don't have the right to order food for my subordinates.
By the way, can I eat char siu noodles and gyoza?
I can't eat it at the party.
That's right.
Reigo-kun, gyoza is fine.
Just make me char siu noodles.
Yes, sir.
I'll stop eating lebanese noodles and ramen.
Nakagawa, what kind of party is Party Party?
It's the birthday party of the prince of the Kingdom of Hondara.
Kingdom of Hondara?
It's a small country, so I don't think you'll know.
The king and my father have been friends for a long time.
They always stay at my house when they come to Japan.
It's the first time I've been in a wide Ferrari like this.
I asked the president of Ferrari to make it a wide body.
But isn't this a traffic jam?
It's okay.
This is the C U road in Nakagawa.
What did you say?
There was an entrance to Nakagawa that went down earlier.
Maybe Mr. Nakagawa's Nakagawa?
Nakagawa's Nakagawa?
But maybe Mr. Nakagawa's Nakagawa?
Yes.
He made it for my house.
Are you still tired of that?
I'm so hungry that I'm going to die.
No, I'm already tired.
What?
I can't see anything.
The peace is just going on.
The other side of the peace is my house.
What?
Ninth District
How much is the common place?
I think it's 100 times bigger than Disneyland.
What?
If it's that big,
we have to put the door here and there, right?
There are 12 gates in total.
We are heading to the closest gate, the Gate of the Land.
The Gate of the Land?
There are other gates, like the Gate of Youth, the Gate of the World, and the Gate of the Land.
Here we go!
Here we are! Let's go!
Huh?
What's wrong?
I think I got lost on the road.
Don't get lost on your own!
I'll navigate right away.
Please confirm your destination.
I can't get there without using the navigation system in the Land of the Land.
I can finally see the house.
It's the same as the chief's house.
It's small, isn't it?
It's too small for a house with a lot of land.
What?
Isn't it a great house?
Excuse me, is that a dog house?
So the chief has been paying the loan for 20 years for the same house as the dog house?
Mr. Yoh!
You laughed too much.
What?
Is this your house?
Yes.
To be exact, it's a room.
My parents live in the house over there.
And over there is my younger sister's house.
It's a small, private house.
Please come in.
Is this the living room?
Oh, that's...
It's an old-fashioned invader game.
And it's black and white.
It's a cellophane body.
Wow!
It's amazing!
It even has a pool.
No, this is a bath.
The pool is over here.
The bath house is moving.
It's moving.
No, it's not.
The whole room is moving.
This room?
It's just the face of the pool in the amusement park.
It's a golf course.
It's an airport.
We did it!
We got 50,000 yen!
Did you see that?
Mr. Ryo's great house!
Let's leave him alone.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Ryo's House
May I come in?
Yes, come in.
Ms. Reiko, you look great.
Thank you very much.
We have to dress up like this.
We have invited some famous people.
Please be patient.
But Ryo, you look the same even in a taxi.
Thank you very much.
What's going on?
Calm down, everyone.
We have to be calm and calm in any situation.
Senpai, it's not an earthquake.
This is an elevator.
What?
The whole room is an elevator?
I don't live in a house that is smaller than an elevator.
Welcome.
He's a great man.
Look, look.
Mr. Hashimoto is here too.
Over there, there are celebrities like Sala Takaoka and Sabu Kitahima.
Sign here later.
Here you go.
Stupid.
More importantly, the food.
Senpai, please wait.
What is it?
I'm going to introduce you to Prince Hondara.
Hey, please, Hondara.
Okay.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I thought Prince Hondara was cooler, but he's just a fat kid.
Ryo-chan.
What is it?
Prince, I'm going to introduce you to my colleagues.
This is my boss, Chief Ohara.
Nice to meet you.
And this is my senpai, Ryotsu-san.
Hello, hello.
What are you talking about, old man?
The prince speaks Japanese fluently.
Idiot, why didn't you say that first?
I'm going to be the man who will lead the future of Japan!
Ryotsu Kankichi!
This gorilla is really annoying.
I was told by a pig.
What do you mean by a pig?
Well, it's my birthday party, so let's get along.
If you're done greeting me, I'm going to go.
Don't worry about the prince.
He's just a fool.
What a stupid gorilla.
Yoita-san, please grab 10 pieces of tuna and sea urchin.
I'm sorry.
The prince told me not to grab until the candle of the cake is out.
I haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
Please!
Don't grab it.
Prince.
I'll forgive you.
Don't grab it.
You're a good guy.
What's wrong?
Keiichi-senpai told me to grab a special delicious sushi.
You'll be a good prince.
Then grab it quickly.
Yes.
Here you are.
It looks delicious.
I can do it.
Wasabi!
I got caught.
It's my fault.
Now, please turn off the candle for the prince.
Prince, please come to the stage.
Yes.
I don't remember.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Congratulations!
Prince!
Now!
I failed.
What did you do to the prince?
It's a joke.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
Prince, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Is there something suspicious in this mansion?
It seems to be the work of the people of the Hontara Kingdom.
That means...
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
It's a big problem.
The terrorists have invaded the mansion.
What?
Alright.
Now, I'll teach you Chinese food.
This one.
I think this is enough.
I'm hungry.
You bastard!
Get up!
I'm so hungry that I can't run.
Aim at them.
I know.
Let's find the terrorists.
What about Ryo?
He won't help us.
First, we have to protect the guests.
I was faster.
You're rude to the prince.
The prince is not inferior to you.
This is mine.
I won!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Everyone!
It's dangerous.
Please be careful.
The terrorists have invaded the mansion.
My meat...
Damn it, we failed again.
We have no choice.
We have to go inside and find the prince.
What's going on?
What's this?
Please calm down.
The central part of this room is moving to the basement.
It's okay now.
The food!
I'm not kidding.
I haven't eaten anything yet.
Ryo-chan!
Senpai!
Ryo-chan, come down!
Let go of me!
The terrorists are after the prince.
If we let the prince escape...
Prince!
This is the worst situation.
Let go of me!
I won't let you eat me!
You idiot! Stop it!
One last piece!
How about this?
Wait for me!
Senpai! Prince!
Please leave the room immediately!
That's not enough!
My favorite chicken ball!
What?
You can't find it before me!
Idiot!
This isn't the time for that!
The terrorists are coming!
They're here!
Raise your hands!
You idiot!
I told you this isn't the time for that!
You did it!
Don't ignore us!
The chicken ball!
Damn it!
Wait!
It's mine!
You idiot!
You're so annoying!
Prince!
It's mine!
Where did the chicken ball go?
Now!
What's going on?
It's a timing gas.
It should be fine now.
Alright, let's arrest them!
The chicken ball!
Where did it go?
Prince!
The chicken ball!
Do you remember them?
Chief!
What a shame!
Don't move!
Everyone, drop your guns and raise your hands!
This is the end.
Prince, please go back to that world.
Prince, it's alright.
I just need you to put in that switch.
It's gone!
Where's the chicken ball?
Where's my chicken ball?
Chicken ball, chicken ball!
They're probably looking for a big chicken ball.
No way.
What are you talking about?
Are you praying?
Die as you wish!
I got it!
Chicken ball!
I'm going to eat it!
We did it!
Senior!
What happened?
We did it!
Senior put the switch in the pit.
Ryo?
The chicken ball...
Where did the chicken ball go?
I found it!
You did it, Ryo-chan!
It's from the Chief!
Thanks to you, I was saved.
Thank you, Ryo-san.
Well, that's how it is.
What's this?
That's...
Everyone, help me!
It looks like they pushed the emergency self-destruct switch.
Here, it's from the Chief of Katsushika.
You did a good job, Ryo-chan.
I don't want that.
I want to eat the chicken ball, the sushi, and the food!
They were shocked that they couldn't eat the party's food.
Hey, wait!
Who are you?
Thank you for saving me.
Last night was really fun.
Eat it for me.
The Prince!
He's so considerate.
Wasabi!
I got you again!
You're such a fool!
You brat!
To be continued...
Teyandee!
I, Ryotsu Kankichi, am an edokko!
Edokkos don't have eyes for fighting and eating sushi!
Can you put edokkos in such a lukewarm bath?
Make it hotter!
It's not hot at all!
Next time, it's a fierce edokkoga battle!
See you!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for your viewing.