The XX Cop Ryotsu Appears!?
He's coming!
He's here!
You're so excited, Ryousa!
I'm late!
I can't believe he's parking at a place like this.
What kind of sense does he have?
Don't get in the way!
Move
Ryousa...
Wait!
What's wrong with him?
Ryotsu Kankichi...
He's so clumsy, he's so strong, and he's a real man!
Police officer, wait!
We are coming!
You think you can catch me, Ryotsu Kankichi?
I'm 30km per hour!
40km per hour!
50km per hour!
60km per hour!
70km per hour!
80km per hour!
The tachometer is entering the red zone!
Hang on, 90 degrees!
This is terrible!
I did it!
I made it in time!
I made it in time! I made it in time!
I'm so glad that I did it!
That's not good, Ryousa!
You broke the glass, and chief will get mad at you again!
Hey, Ryousa!
I watered that flower every day, and it finally bloomed!
I won't forgive you if you touch it again!
She's as noisy as ever.
What?
The chief isn't here yet?
He's not here yet.
Usually people who stand on top of people have to come 30 minutes earlier.
Ryousa!
What's wrong Tera..?
Chief!
You came early today, too.
It's great that you come two and a half hours every day from the countryside.
Chief, you're the mirror of the entire police force.
You idiot!
It doesn't have to be loud, right?
I didn't get late today, so I'm going to slide in a minute.
You idiot!
No matter how many times you do it, it's the same as the neighborhood police officer!
I feel like I've written a few letters of resignation.
Are you going to sign up for the Guinness Book of Records?
That's why you don't have a wife.
Live your life to the fullest!
There's a song like this in my favorite Suizenji Kiyoko's song.
One day, one step.
Three steps in three days.
Three steps forward, two steps back.
Donkuna!
Yes, yes, yes!
Chief, you are really good in Suizenji Kiyoko.
That's right, that's right.
Three steps forward in life, two steps back.
It's the same if you take a step forward and rest.
You idiot!
I was a fool to try to teach you the modesty of life.
My head hurts.
It's finally over.
The second word is stupid.
I won't remember one of those stupid things.
Chief!
Did you forget something?
That's right.
Today was payday.
I don't want to do it for you, but I can't help it.
Listen, Ryotsu.
You can't use it right away because you have money.
Think about the future.
Try to use it strategically.
Yes, sir.
I'll add another radio.
What are you doing?
Chief!
My one month's sweat and tears are going to be paid off!
Door and glass.
And a bicycle compensation bill.
You're so stubborn.
Well, as long as I have this.
We'll be back on Sunday!
What?
I'm here to receive the compensation.
Everyone of the shopping district is here.
Damn it. What if this happens?
Run away!
Chief!
Terai, hold Ryotsu's legs!
Yes, sir!
Let me go! Let me go!
Terai, Let me go!
Now, everyone, please take it.
Let me go!
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
I'll take the Game Sock and the Plamodive for 38,000 yen.
I'll take it.
Plamodive for 32,000 yen.
Beer and whiskey for 28,000 yen.
Let's get some money.
How much is it?
It's 18,000 yen.
3,000 yen for the fishing pole.
My money!
150 yen.
Am I going to spend this much this month?
You're self-sufficient.
That's why I'm telling you that you have to live a real life.
Chief!
You can't be greedy!
Try to live a month just like a man.
No way!
Terai, Reiko, It's not good to lend money to Ryo-tsu.
There's a house loan in the house.
It's okay.
Ryo-chan can live on that alone.
That's right.
You can't be greedy for Ryo-tsu.
Chief!
You don't have to say that.
50,000 yen, no, 30,000 yen is fine.
Then, 20,000 yen.
10,000 yen.
At least 1,000 yen.
No!
All right!
I won't cry to anyone anymore.
If you're going to cry to these cold guys,
it's better to starve to death.
You said it.
Don't forget that word.
I don't care if you're hungry and crying.
I'll give you a luxurious life with 150 yen.
It's a child's fight.
You're right.
My stomach clock is really accurate.
It's closed.
Reiko isn't here.
I wonder if I can get a lunch box in the meantime.
Ouch!
Ryo-chan, if you're going to cry to these cold guys,
it's better to starve to death.
You said it. Isn't it?
Damn it.
I was reading the pattern of action.
Give me your lunch.
No! I won't.
This is mine!
Ryo-chan,
stealing is a crime.
Shut up!
Is there a name on the rice grain?
Give it to me.
Ryo-chan, stop it.
No! No!
Hehehe.
Reiko,
okay,
this is good.
It's great to talk about food.
Damn it.
Ouch!
I'll make you a roll of eri next time.
I'm hungry.
Is there anything to eat?
I found it.
It's a mochi.
There must be something to eat.
I'll add a little bit of ponzu.
I put too much.
This is too much.
I'll add some salt.
I put too much.
I'll add some sugar.
It's okay.
It's like this.
I'll season it with pork cutlet sauce.
Ryo-san's pot is ready.
I still have the mochi from the New Year.
What?
Isn't that the one that you chewed?
You're an idiot.
Mushrooms are also a kind of hair.
It contains the leaves of mackerel,
and it's well balanced.
Eating the leaves of mackerel...
It's about the taste of mackerel,
so it must be delicious.
The color is not good.
Ryo-san, that's Reiko-san's...
The color is important in cooking.
I'll eat it.
Ryo-chan, what are you doing?
I told you not to touch it again.
You're an idiot.
Damn it.
I'll leave it for a while.
I'm hungry.
This is...
Over there!
Isn't that Junpei and Kappei from the tofu shop?
Good luck, Junpei-chan!
You're doing well, everyone.
You're doing well.
It looks delicious.
What do you think, Junpei?
Do you want to compete with me?
With Ryo-san?
That's right.
It's a one-on-one game.
If I win, I'll get this takoyaki.
What if Ryo-san loses?
I'll give you whatever you like,
whether it's my collection of plastic models or game software.
What? Plastic models?
What do you think? Do you want to do it, Junpei?
Yeah!
Good luck, Junpei!
That was easy.
Oh, Ryo-san.
I did it!
You got 980 points out of 1000.
You're pretty good.
Alright, it's my turn next.
Start!
I won't give up!
It's over!
I'm in the lead!
He won!
Amazing!
How was it?
I lost.
You should have stopped, Onii-chan.
As promised, I'll get the takoyaki.
Junpei!
You bastard!
Are you alright?
Ryo-san, I got it!
Leave it to me!
Wait!
This is bad!
Your bike's going to break!
Ultra Power Turbo, on!
Ryo-san!
Oh no! He's chasing us with his bike!
I won't let him to catch me!
You'll get me if I let you!
Are you serious?
I won't let you get away!
You bastard!
Alright, it's my turn!
Missile Jump!
Damn! There's a shortcut!
Oh no! I made a wrong turn!
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
Damn!
I will come back to you.
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
I am on a chase
Wait for me!
He's still chasing us!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
He's so stubborn!
Don't underestimate me!
He's chasing us at 80 km per hour!
Hurry up!
Move, you idiot!
Looks like he finally gave up.
No way!
Wait for me, you bastard!
He's a monster!
He's not following us anymore.
You did it, Ken-chan.
What do you mean?
Yes! It's an exit!
The culprit has been arrested, Ryo-san.
Well done!
You bastard!
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Give me back my takoyaki!
It's takoyaki, takoyaki!
You did it, Ryo-chan.
It's been eight years since the culprit was arrested.
Congratulations!
Well, it's because Nowaru Taka has been hiding his takoyaki for a while.
Nowaru Taka hides his takoyaki, right?
It doesn't suit you, Ryo-chan.
Ryo-san!
Hey, Jumpei.
Are your legs okay now?
This isn't a big deal!
Ryo-san, I'm going to win the game this time!
Yeah, yeah.
You should practice hard, Jumpei.
Come to think of it, I haven't eaten anything yet.
Oh, right.
I heard that the driver's license was a two-month traffic violation.
This is probably a special award and a gold medal.
A gold medal!
I did it!
I'm going to be saved this month!
Are you ready?
Huh?
Yes!
I'm here to arrest, Kameyari's excellent police officer, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
You're going to give me a gold medal, right?
Idiot!
Look outside!
Ryo-tsu!
I heard that you caused trouble to your neighbors again.
I'll pay you back next month!
No way!
Please forgive me! Chief