Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Ryotsu! Mecha-Pote Sengen!
It's going to be cold today.
Nothing's going to happen tonight.
Let's stop patrolling and go home.
Chief!
Isn't this the girls' dormitory of the Katsushika school?
How dare you!
Nakago, turn around.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Where are you? Where are you?
Where are you?
You, underwear thief!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
I'm a police officer! Hey!
It's me!
I'm Ryotsu Kankichi, the first officer of the park!
Oh, you're right.
I'm Ryotsu Kankichi!
I'm Ryotsu Kankichi, the first officer of the park!
If you're Ryotsu Kankichi, then you're the underwear thief!
I'm not the next one!
Ryotsu!
I'm going to arrest you!
I'm going to arrest you for being the underwear thief!
Don't make fun of me!
I'm not an underwear thief!
Then what's that thing you're holding in your hand?
Huh?
That's proof that you can't move!
N-No!
I just grabbed it when I fell!
I came in here because I heard a scream!
Do you think that excuse makes sense?
It's true!
There's another one here!
No, there isn't!
Mr. Nakagawa!
Ryutsu!
It's a misunderstanding.
We heard a scream that we were the underwear thief and came in here.
It's no use. I said that too.
Oh, is that so?
No!
If you say that, I'll misunderstand you.
I'm sorry.
Speaking of which, we were doing a special training for the underwear thief.
I heard a scream.
Hey, you guys!
You're saying the same thing, but you don't believe what I'm saying.
Don't you doubt what Nakagawa is saying?
Oh, that's natural.
Of course.
What kind of people do you judge people based on?
Of course, it's the face!
You can't trust what a man with such a hot face with eyebrows says.
That's right. On top of that, he's short.
He's tall.
He's hot.
He's short, but he's tall.
On top of that, he has smelly feet.
You guys!
Stop it!
Let go of me!
That sound...
Stop it, you idiot! Stop it!
Mr. Ryo...
No, it was a misunderstanding.
Mr. Nakagawa, you tried to steal the underwear, didn't you?
I said no!
Stop it!
I'm innocent!
That was a disaster, Ryo-tsu.
But it's your fault for having such a bad dream.
You should reflect on yourself.
Reflecting is a joke.
Women these days think men are nothing.
I don't understand what you're saying.
It's true that women these days are beyond my understanding.
Even before this...
You're so mean!
Right?
That's why you look so pitiful.
Please go out with me.
No, what are you talking about?
Even though you don't have a boyfriend?
Hey, old man!
What are you looking at?
No, I'm not looking at anything.
You bastard!
I'm done with him.
He's clearly an alien.
I've decided!
What are you doing, senpai?
I'm done with her.
I'm not going to see her again.
Really?
Then you're not going to work?
No.
Excuse me.
Which way is the station?
No, no!
What?
Don't come in from that line!
What did you say?
What?
You're the security guard, aren't you?
Yes, it's the station.
The station is...
You...
You idiot!
No matter what anyone says,
I'm never going to see a woman again!
What a shame!
I could have arrested Ryo-tsu a little earlier.
You're right.
Huh?
In front of Ryo?
Hey!
Why is there a maruto in the garden?
Naoko!
You're in trouble!
Hey!
What's with this maruto?
You're Naoko Seisho, aren't you?
Congratulations on winning the lottery.
Yes.
I see!
Look!
That's the winner!
That magazine's verification!
I applied for it with a light heart,
but I didn't think I'd really win.
But Ryo's garden is spacious,
so it's fine, right?
That's right.
Look at Ryo's best!
It's wonderful!
Well then,
the investigation has been completed,
so this is the summary video of the log-out assembly.
Well then, please do your best to assemble it!
What?
We're going to make it?
What should we do?
We can't assemble something like this.
Don't you know anyone who's good at this?
There he is!
But...
He's definitely not going to do it.
That's right!
There's a good way!
Wait a minute!
Gather everyone tomorrow.
This is bad, Ryo-san!
Look at this!
This month's log-out survey!
You don't know that!
He's always doing boring projects every month.
That's clearly Sekwafara.
He's making a fool of men.
What?
Ryo's number one again?
That means V7 has finally been completed.
What's wrong?
This is...
The number one that Katsushika Shofukei asked for,
doesn't have Senpai's name on it!
What?
By the way,
Ryo-san is number one in the log-out survey.
This is...
The number one in the log-out survey, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The number one I want to make my girlfriend, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
The number one I want to marry, Ryo-tsu Kankichi.
He's always in the top three with Nakagawa.
Isn't that some kind of misprint?
I don't think so.
It doesn't matter if it's 5 o'clock or 6 o'clock.
That means...
You!
You've been acting like a coward again.
Why would I do that?
Chief,
I don't think Senpai would do something that doesn't make money.
Hmm?
That's true.
But you're number one all of a sudden from the beginning.
That's strange.
It's not strange!
The modern women have finally realized.
The true manliness.
They're starting to choose the number one.
Ryo-tsu Senpai.
The number one in the log-out survey.
Congratulations!
Congratulations Ichi!
Congratulations Ryo-tsu!
We've been misunderstanding Ryo-tsu Senpai.
That's right.
We've finally realized the charm of Ryo-tsu Senpai.
He's popular.
I can't believe it.
Hmph.
I'm going to lose.
Didn't you choose Senno as your girlfriend?
Huh?
You're so insolent.
Don't cross that line!
Huh?
I've decided not to go out with a woman.
Don't say that.
Shut up!
Get out!
Senpai!
Get out of here!
What's with that attitude?
Calm down.
The first step is complete.
That idiot shouldn't have come to feed us.
How is it?
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Here it comes.
Next is Rai-Rai-Gen.
Is he trying to disguise himself with that?
It's Rai-Rai-Gen.
I thought it was ramen.
Ryo-tsu Senpai's charm is his manliness, isn't it?
That's right.
He's not like the other men.
He's more like a master.
His eyebrows are sharp.
That's right.
A good man is more delicate than his appearance.
But it's sad.
He can't accept our passion.
We don't like men.
That's right.
Ryo-sama!
But he's not popular.
We don't like men.
Women's hearts are complicated.
Hey, you two!
Ryo-tsu Senpai!
Senpai!
You didn't accept our bouquet.
Naoko was very sad.
I'm sorry about that.
Coffee?
That's nice.
On a cold day like this.
Give me a bite.
What?
Me?
Naoko!
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's good.
Here, have some.
What?
Don't hold back.
But...
I'm happy, Ryo-tsu Senpai.
Why did I do that?
Good job, Naoko.
Good job.
I won't let your precious sacrifice go to waste.
I'll do that for you.
Hey, Ryo-tsu Senpai!
Are you free tonight?
How is it?
Do you want to go out for a drink?
I thought it was someone else, but it's you.
What's with that outfit?
I have an appointment tonight.
Sorry, but I don't have time to go out with you.
Appointment?
Ryo-san, I heard you're being invited to the girls' dorm tonight.
To the girls' dorm?
You must be jealous.
I can't take you there.
I'm the only one who's being invited.
Women these days know the budget of men very well.
It's totally different from what I usually say.
Girls' dorm!
Good evening!
I'm sure you know this place.
This place is actually for men.
Only Ryo-tsu Senpai is here.
It's special.
I'm impressed.
This is great.
Naoko.
Ryo-tsu Senpai, the moon is so beautiful.
Let's go see it.
It was cloudy earlier.
It's okay.
Okay, now.
Roger.
Oh!
Isn't this an illusion?
What's that?
That's a log house kit.
All the log materials are here.
Just put them together.
The gas and the water are one-touch.
If we put it in the garden, it'll be a good place for everyone.
But there's no log builder.
We can't build that.
Isn't there a strong and talented man?
No, no.
Men these days are all satisfied.
A man who works with sweat on his forehead is wonderful.
That's right.
The recent trend is a man who smells like sweat.
I don't know if it's a trend or something,
but don't you guys forget someone?
What?
A man who is strong, talented, and reliable.
Eh?
Who?
Are you talking about Ryo-tsu Senpai?
No.
I can't ask Ryo-tsu Senpai to do that.
Why not?
Because Ryo-tsu Senpai has already decided on a suit.
Right?
This is my true form.
Wonderful!
And this is my army.
Even though it's an emergency...
It's forced.
Shut up!
Don't talk nonsense!
First of all, the basic construction.
You guys know that, don't you?
Attack!
Hey!
Don't do it like that!
Hey, what's with that face?
Men aren't that simple.
Hey, Sasato and Hagomi!
Eiji, let those two do what they want.
Everyone!
It's lunch time!
This is our homemade lunch.
The cookies are homemade too.
Wow, amazing.
It looks delicious.
Terai-san and Honda-san, thank you.
Please do your best.
I'm counting on you.
Honda-san is more talented than he looks.
Is that so?
Terai-san's thick arms seem to have power.
No, it's almost all of it.
You guys go home!
Eh?
Oh no.
Oh, but we came all the way here.
It would be better if everyone cooperated.
This is enough for me alone.
Come on, let's go home.
It's not done yet.
It was a bit of a strategy.
It was impossible to do it alone.
I can't ask them to do it now.
After all, the pace is slow.
If this is the case, you have to praise it,
praise it, put it on, and make it work.
Okay.
Ryoko-san, do your best.
Huh?
The way you work is wonderful.
It's cool.
Is that so?
I'm surprised.
It's very powerful.
What is this?
It's wonderful.
It's manly.
Is that so?
Kyosuke-san!
It's like a trip.
It's easy to handle.
At this rate, let's continue to switch for 24 hours.
Kyosuke-san!
It's manly.
Ryotsu-senpai, you're the best!
Ryotsu-san, do your best!
It seems that only 1000 yen is not enough.
We need to use one can full.
Ryotsu-san, are you okay?
I'm a little tired.
I'll give you a massage.
Do your best.
Make our log house as soon as possible.
Of course, Tomoe.
Revival!
We did it!
Let's do it!
Here's your lunch.
See you.
Are you leaving already?
I'm on a business trip.
Another convenience store lunch?
It used to be a handmade lunch box.
The completion rate of the house and the grade of the lunch box are decreasing.
This again?
The days of bread and butter continue.
Recently, no one has come to 1000 yen.
It seems that they are forced to work.
If this continues, I'll break my body.
I feel like my seniors are being manipulated by their girlfriends.
Nakagawa-kun, I know how you feel about being taken away by me.
I'm jealous, but I don't want you to have a strange feeling.
I don't think I'm too jealous.
I don't think so.
But I'm really tired.
Senpai! Ryo-tsu-senpai!
Ryo-tsu-senpai! Senpai!
It seems that Ryo-tsu hasn't come yet.
It's a mess.
It's a little more, but it's useless.
When will it be completed?
I'm tired of making fun of it.
I did my best to get first place in the survey.
Just a little more.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to be mean.
What's wrong? Did you say something?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
I'll do my best.
I'm glad I didn't hear it.
I'm glad I was really stupid.
I can hear you.
Look at this.
Amazing!
It's finally completed.
Our villa.
Amazing!
It smells good.
It's a curtain window.
The bath is bigger than I thought.
Let's stay here tonight.
Yes!
I'll teach you how to get angry at me.
Let's go.
It smells good.
I feel like I'm in a hot spring in the mountains.
But he's good at making such a great log house.
I agree.
He did his best.
I've seen it again.
Komachi.
What?
You fell in love with Ryotsukan.
I'm not kidding.
It's red.
It's not.
Everyone.
Be quiet.
The special seat is 5,000 yen.
The camera is 5,000 yen.
Let's go.
Did you see that?
This is the real job of a man.
What are you doing?
You bastard.
It's too hot.
The mini bath is too hot.
I can't stand it.
I'm not done yet.
Don't bully a weak woman.
I can't stand it.
Where are you weak?
Wait.
He's going to be number one again.
To be continued.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
The sun is calling outside the door.