Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Nobaya Rebuild Plan
It's so rusty.
Do you want some hot soba?
Sounds good.
It wasn't a very popular restaurant before.
It's about time we could go in.
Hey, you!
You're in danger!
You bastard!
Senpai!
This guy...
He's been on TV a lot lately.
He's a food critic.
It's you, Chogoro.
This taste...
It's not ordinary.
There's a restaurant that's not ordinary as usual.
Is the owner here?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, this is for you, Sensei.
Please come in.
Hey, hey!
This is for you, you bastard!
Oh, well, Senpai.
Here you go.
It's not ordinary.
It's like a hand-made dish.
You're so generous.
We've been waiting for three hours under the cold sky.
I'm hungry.
This soba is not ordinary.
Thank you very much!
There's a restaurant that's not ordinary as usual.
As I thought, the soba here is top-notch.
It doesn't matter if it's just soba or not.
When the winter is over, hurry up and open the seats.
Master, I want to show my acquaintance
that this is not just soba.
Please give me 200 people.
200 people is more than 100,000 yen.
Master, am I a Japanese food critic?
It's you, Cho Goro.
Of course, I don't need an offer.
Please enjoy your meal.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you very much.
It's finally gone.
Well, it's our turn next.
What?
Hey, old man.
What's going on?
We wanted to eat warm soba,
so we waited for three hours under this cold sky.
It's you.
Master took all the soba.
What?
No way.
I want to cry here.
You shouldn't have put it on a magazine like this.
Damn it.
I see.
Because it was introduced in this magazine,
the number of customers suddenly increased.
He put this on and ate it.
He's ridiculous.
Damn it.
It doesn't matter if it's just soba or not.
Hey, isn't there a restaurant to eat warm soba?
Master, how about this soba restaurant?
What?
Sorry.
It's like there's no sign of customers.
It's dangerous here.
Why?
You don't know?
It's not normal that it's not popular here.
If you eat a lot of soba,
you can't eat warm soba.
Are you a customer?
I was going to say that.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Actually, you are the fifth customer.
The fifth today?
I guess so.
No, I'm the fifth customer since I started the restaurant.
What?
Wait.
When did you start the restaurant?
Three years ago.
Three years ago?
I'll make it right away.
What are you going to do?
Actually, my stomach is getting weird all of a sudden.
Senior, I feel sorry for you.
Let's eat it.
If you eat soba here and your stomach gets weird,
what are you going to do?
If something happens,
I'll do something with the medical team of Nakagawa Corp.
I'll be the fifth customer.
Please.
Okay, okay.
I'll be the fifth customer.
Thank you for waiting.
This soba looks bad.
Let's eat it and go back to the restaurant.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
You're worried about the customer's reaction, aren't you?
Yes.
I'll tell you what I think after I finish eating.
So go over there while I'm eating.
Yes.
It's a normal soba.
It's not that bad that I can't eat it.
This is...
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
Master, I have something to ask you.
Yes, what is it?
Are you using the soba that was made at the Yamada Farm?
Yes, that's right.
What is the Yamada Farm?
People who know know.
It's the farm of the master of making soba, Mr. Yamada Dengoro.
The soba made here is said to be the best in Japan,
but it's difficult to get it.
Even in the cooking department of the Nakagawa Group,
only a small part of the shop is used.
I've been close to Mr. Yamada for a long time,
so he makes it cheaply at home.
I see.
And the soy sauce used for the soup.
Isn't this made with sugar syrup?
Yes.
The sugar syrup is made from handmade soy sauce.
It is said to be the birthplace of soy sauce,
and it has the traditional taste of Kishu.
The soy sauce made here is called soy sauce in soy sauce.
No, not only soy sauce.
Katsuobushi and kelp.
It is a must-have ingredient to make this rich soup stock.
The leek is well-sealed and used for a glossy and wonderful thing.
And seven-spice chili.
The seven flavors create an exquisite harmony.
It works well on the body,
and it is no doubt that it uses a very well-chosen material.
Hey, hey.
How can you use such a great ingredient
to make such a normal soba?
Normal?
Senpai, please look at your bowl.
Huh?
Huh? When did you say that?
That's what a really delicious thing is.
It naturally enters the body.
Hey, dad.
One more cup, please.
Y-Yes.
Hmm.
It is certainly quite delicious if you taste it carefully.
Isn't it?
It has this much flavor.
Please promote it more.
I'm not very good at flashy things.
Besides, it's strange.
If it has this much flavor,
it's likely that customers will come.
But there is a deep reason why customers don't come.
A deep reason?
Three years ago, I didn't even forget.
On the day I went to Koiki,
I opened this store.
I was nervous,
and I was waiting for the first customer to come.
Then...
Sorry.
What?
Omaeda?
Did Omaeda-sensei come to eat on purpose?
No.
I came to borrow the toilet.
Hmm.
So this is a soba restaurant.
I didn't notice it because it was too simple,
but it's just right.
Let's eat here for lunch.
Yes. I'll make it right away.
After all, it was my first customer,
so I put a lot of effort into it.
Please.
Omaeda
How was it?
It's a simple dish,
but it has a unique taste.
I see.
Excuse me.
It will be 700 yen.
Master,
I don't think anyone knows who I am.
I'm Omaeda Chogoro, a gourmet philosopher.
Yes.
So it will be 700 yen for a bowl of soba.
I'm Omaeda Chogoro, a gourmet philosopher in Japan.
Unfortunately, I don't have any cash.
Please forgive me.
It should be about 20,000 to 30,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Master, what's the name of this restaurant?
It's Tanaka Soba.
Tanaka Soba.
I'll remember it.
In the end, the dining room was a fake.
It's a big story.
I was surprised a week later.
I was very upset about my restaurant.
It's not a human food.
Even if the world forgives me, I won't forgive you.
Minus seven stars.
That's terrible.
Don't say that.
But my restaurant is being introduced.
It's only a negative image.
It's a terrible article.
It's just a criticism.
It's because I couldn't eat it.
I can't forgive you for taking my soba.
It's strange that a person who doesn't know the taste is a gourmet philosopher.
If you make me angry, I'll let you know what will happen.
Okay, master?
Yes, if I can do it.
Leave it to me.
I have a good idea.
Wash your head and wait.
Omaeda Chogoro.
In order to make Omaeda say it, you need to make a sacrifice.
Are you ready?
Yes.
From now on, Omaeda Chogoro will make you say it.
What are you doing?
It's not good to be treated like a gourmet philosopher.
You need to be taught a lesson.
I see.
You're trying to make me feel like I've been suffering for years.
That's right.
This bowl should be a little lively.
Myeden!
You're a gourmet philosopher.
Do you have any help?
I'm fine with anything.
Use anything that can make you feel traditional and distant.
Okay.
Next...
Ryo-san, what are you doing?
Oh, I came to a good place.
I remember you said that you made a bowl of rice during the time you were at school.
Yeah, but it's covered in dust, and it also contains shrimp.
It's more convenient this way.
Bring it here.
Lend it to your friends.
Okay, Ryo-san.
You're here.
The World's Greatest Museum
I came back from the World's Greatest Museum.
All of them tell the history of mankind.
Good, good.
Excuse me.
I think it's unnatural to have something like this in a simple soba restaurant.
It's okay.
It's better to have something like this.
That's right.
Let's make this a celebration from Cleopatra.
It's a mess.
Something like this, huh?
All right.
By the way, I'll take one of the pillars.
Please stop.
If you cut this, the building itself will break.
That's true.
Ryo-san!
I brought it!
All right, all right.
It's perfect.
Now the restaurant is okay.
All that's left is...
No, no way!
Please stop!
That's all!
I'm the owner of the restaurant.
Oh, come on.
Stop it!
Don't make a bad voice!
Huh?
That bike is...
You're being naughty again, Kankichi!
Hey!
Mr. Nakagawa!
It's over.
Come on.
But...
Why are you embarrassed?
You're being naughty again.
I'll tell Chief Ohara.
Hey!
I'm a pervert.
Are you that happy?
He's lamenting my misfortune.
Now the stage is ready.
Nakagawa, prepare the cherry blossoms.
Yes, sir.
All that's left is to chase after the prey.
Is there really a good soba restaurant that can line up like this?
Yes.
According to the information from the viewers,
they can line up two kilos of food every day.
Isn't that it?
That's amazing.
Soba restaurants are all lined up like this?
Today, I'm going to interview
Ohmaeda Chogoro, the best gourmet philosopher in Japan,
and the owner of this fantastic soba restaurant.
I'm Ohmaeda Chogoro.
Who are you guys?
Mr. Ohmaeda is going to interview this restaurant.
Would you like to come with us?
Yes.
Make sure you don't get in the way.
Sir,
what's your first impression of the restaurant?
Hey, do you know?
Mr. Ohmaeda,
this restaurant has been running for 20 generations since its opening.
Yes.
It's said that it's the most important cultural asset in the country.
Most important in the country?
Yes.
This restaurant probably has been running since its opening.
This wound must have been caused by a fierce battle
between the Ishin army and the Baku army
in front of this restaurant during Meiji Isshin.
Even though it's a wound made by your senior.
It's easy to be fooled, isn't it?
This Meira has been left behind.
It's one of the best restaurants in the world.
This restaurant isn't just any ordinary restaurant.
The restaurant isn't just any ordinary restaurant.
I can't wait to see it.
Excuse me.
You idiot, get out of here.
This restaurant has only one chili pepper.
And you're going to use it twice.
Please tell the manager.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Are you really going to wear this costume?
Of course.
Get ready.
Because of the article he wrote,
only five people have been here for three years.
Only five customers came.
Remember that.
Go.
I'm sorry, manager.
The one who doesn't follow the rules of the restaurant
is a customer.
Don't come here again.
Amazing.
It's a restaurant for craftsmen.
What do you think, Mr. Omaeda?
With the current situation,
the people of the British royal room have been kicked out, haven't they?
Yes.
But now that they're back,
they're going to eat at Buckingham Palace every week.
The British royal room.
He's just trying to protect the taste of soba.
And look at this angel.
He's wearing a traditional geta,
but he's actively taking the Western style
that doesn't fit the tradition.
He's in a very warm and friendly posture.
The owner of the restaurant.
He's not an ordinary person.
He's not an ordinary person again.
Why, why, you guys?
Don't you know me?
I'm Omaeda Chogoro, a gourmet critic.
We're here to interview you.
What?
Interview me?
Idiot!
Don't interview me.
If you interview me on TV,
people who don't know the taste of soba will come to you.
If there are more customers,
I'll be busy and it won't work.
Come on.
Don't shoot me.
The customers are the customers.
We just serve the soba as usual.
Yes, sir.
Wonderful!
I've eaten all kinds of food in the world,
but I've never had so delicious soba before.
I'll put the money here.
As expected, the president of the United Nations is just a regular customer.
People who say this is bad are not human.
The president of the United Nations.
I'll wait for you.
Well, how about the taste of the important soba?
The texture of the soba, the way to take the soup stock,
the way to cut the leek,
and this artistic bowl.
I made it.
It doesn't matter which one you take.
It's not just anything.
I'll give you the seven stars,
which is not just anything.
You must be happy, too.
Hey, you!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Shut up!
Look at this!
Tanaka Soba?
Even if you look at this, you can't remember it.
This store is...
You finally remember it.
Yes, it's Tanaka Soba,
which you put the minus seven stars three years ago.
What's going on?
Nothing has changed here since three years ago.
They've been using high-quality materials
to make the best soba since long ago.
Is that so?
It seems that you confessed yourself.
You really don't know the taste of soba.
Oh, no!
You're not the kind of guy who can name food critics.
The truth is just a taste test.
Mr. Tanaka!
Is what you said true?
Please explain it to me, sir!
No comment!
Mr. Tanaka!
The plan was a great success!
The magical soba shop was a success,
but Ohmaeda was a taste test.
Tanaka's soba shop seems to be in a good shape since then.
Yeah.
But since then, Ohmaeda has been
not listening to the news at all.
What?
What's wrong?
A mysterious family food critic has appeared.
Recently, a person who calls himself a family food critic
has entered the city,
and is eating with him.
This is Ohmaeda, isn't it?
He's a cool guy.
He's not an ordinary person.
The End
I don't care about real studies.
I just want to remember.
Life is meaningful when it's useful.
I'll teach you how to enjoy your life
and how to study in a practical way.
Next time,
the test method of the quantum formula.
See you next time!
The End
Even if it rains,
tomorrow will be sunny.
Bye-bye!
Shake hands!
Say goodbye to the unpleasant things.
Oh yeah!
Let's live the way we like.
There are good things.
Outside the door,
the sun is calling.