Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Everybody can do!
I don't want to say it even if it sticks out a little.
I want to give up the noisy.
A strong and high-pitched voice.
Gekisha! Recreation of Kyoto Travel
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Do you know him?
Yes.
He's the security guard at the station over there, right?
He's good. He's young.
The two of them are here again.
Good morning, Ryo-chan.
Good morning.
I think the driver is missing.
I don't have time to answer.
Ryo-san.
It's a newspaper article published by Aoshingo.
The other day, I went to the principal's office.
By the way, my hair is broken.
I'll ask for a little softer hair from now on.
What are you doing?
I'm going to take the newspaper that we made with all our might.
Don-Kan! Yabanchin!
You're going too far, Ryo-san.
No, it's a valid recycling.
Carbohydrate!
Bacteria, viruses, etc.
Shut up!
If you have time to make such a useless newspaper,
take one of the illegal vaccines.
You, drug thief!
The Katsushika Women's Police Department is disbanded!
Announcement of the result of the investigation!
The number one man who doesn't want to get married, Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
What?
The number one man who doesn't want to date, Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
Why?
The worst man, number one!
The animal man, number one!
The man who can't be saved, etc.
The top 17 in the worst ranking!
No. 1!
Ryo Tsukan-kichi has been in the top 6 years in a row!
Congratulations!
Please look forward to the results of this survey.
Stop the survey!
Stop it, Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
By the way, the number one man who was hugged was Mr. Nakagawa.
The number one man who was hugged by my brother was Mr. Terai.
Really?
Damn it!
I'm so proud of you.
The wall for the interview.
The man who can't be saved, Ryo Tsukan-kichi!
I'll go to Patron.
The wall for the interview.
That's right.
Anyway, there are no illegal shots.
Do you remember?
Senpai, what are you going to do?
I'm going to help you with the interview.
I'm going to make you stupid and show you everything about me.
Here, there, and here.
And here, too.
If you do that, you'll be the worst man, senpai.
That's right.
You don't understand my feelings.
Senpai.
I'm going to show you everything about me.
Show me.
What?
Hurry up. They're coming.
Well, I'm going to go.
Yes, cheese.
Damn it! Don't underestimate me.
I don't have to worry about falling anymore.
I have to think about something.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You're welcome.
Are you done with the interview?
Yes.
Mr. Nakagawa, Mr. Deiko, thank you for coming.
Here's an important camera.
Don't forget it.
That's not ours.
What?
Whose camera is that?
Ohara director, thank you for your hard work.
Don't tell me the director...
Oh, that's my camera, Ryo.
Did you forget about it?
I was looking for it.
Senpai.
Ryo, what are you going to do?
I'm going to take a break.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Mr. Nakagawa, Mr. Deiko.
It's going to be a long time.
It's only five or ten years.
Ryo-tsu!
Ryo-tsu, are you there?
Director, what's wrong?
Ryo-tsu, where are you going?
I'm going to patrol.
You idiot!
Go wherever you want.
Don't ever show your face again.
You're fired.
I don't need an arrogant person like you.
No, director.
This is a deep conversation.
Director, it's a joke, right?
It's not a joke.
You're fired.
No way.
Nakagawa, explain to Ryo-tsu.
Goodbye.
Nakagawa, Reiko.
You betrayed me.
Terai.
Hey, open it.
If you open it and break it,
what will happen if you don't make me angry?
This cake that Reiko made is delicious.
If you like, there are still more.
Ryo-san.
Let's take a break.
Let's go home.
Wait for me.
I'll definitely pay you next time.
If you're fired, the bonus is...
Nakagawa, Reiko.
Help me.
Oh, you're here, Ryo-tsu.
That's my camera.
Give it back.
This is a good camera.
It's a Micon F50.
I wanted it too.
As expected, you have a good eye.
It's a camera I'm not used to.
I don't know how to use it,
but I forgot to bring it.
Is that so?
I'm glad.
I thought it was a mistake,
but I forgot it in the delivery room.
If you find out, you'll be in trouble.
Will that do?
Give it back to Genzo.
Genzo is a little...
Shut up, Ryo-tsu.
It's a joke, isn't it?
It's not a joke.
You're fired.
Wait a minute.
Where are you going to put it?
It's a camera in the shopping district.
No, not there.
In this day and age,
even if you take a 20-yen print,
you're underestimating consumers.
Is there a cheaper store?
Yes.
I know a store with a 0-yen print.
Don't lie.
Will it be a deal with 0 yen?
It will.
A 24-priced Genzo is 600 yen.
The highest price is
about 30% of 180 yen.
Even if you take a 40%
of human rights,
about 30% of 180 yen
will be used as a profit.
I understand.
I'll give you that photo tomorrow
at the bus station.
I'll order it by 10 o'clock in the morning.
Leave it to me.
I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
It's not that difficult
to use a Genzo kit like this.
Just cut the part
where I'm in the picture.
Excuse me.
Please take the ball.
What are you doing, you brat?
I failed.
Anyway, my photo
disappeared, so it's a success.
But what are you going to do
with the photo?
Did you say it was in Kyoto?
What?
In the next newspaper,
you said you were going to post a photo
of the Kyoto trip to Ohara.
Really?
I did.
I can imagine.
Anyway,
I took a lot of pictures
without people in Kyoto.
I don't remember what I took.
I'll use a copy of the picture.
I wonder if it will work.
It's okay.
This is Kamewari Park.
Ryotsu, are you there?
Yes, what is it?
Ryotsu?
I forgot to tell you,
but please print it carefully.
I took it with my best friend Maiko.
Did you take it?
A bonus picture was taken.
It may be in the newspaper.
It's an important picture.
Please print it carefully.
Yes, please leave it to me.
I'm the head.
I won't let you cheat.
If you don't do it well,
you'll be ruined soon.
It's your fault.
I have nothing to do with it.
This is what happened
because you took my picture.
But you...
When I become the head,
you will be the same.
It was a short life.
I understand.
Boss!
Let's go to Kyoto.
I'm working.
If you want to get off,
go ahead.
Do you remember the picture
you took with the chief?
It's from last week.
Please make it clear.
Yes, sir.
How is it?
I sent all the data
about the chief.
All that's left is the bag.
That's right.
I think it was
a brown line and a tie.
Yes, sir.
That's it.
What's the color?
It's clear.
The color is...
That's it.
Let's go.
Tomorrow,
our staff will be waiting.
I'm sure it will work.
We're finally here.
Chief!
When did you get here?
Sir.
It's a doll
I made with the data
you sent me.
A doll?
It would be perfect
if you lied to me.
The color
and the touch of your skin
are perfect.
It's a form latex
I use for special effects.
You can't see it unless you're close.
Look at this face.
The chief gets nervous
when he sees this face.
But why did you make this?
Don't listen to him.
But...
Sir,
we have a staff
who will help us.
Let's go!
Are they all here?
Yes.
Sir.
I think this is
Mr. Maiko.
Welcome.
It's been a week.
Oh, it's you.
All right. Let's start shooting.
What do you think?
This is what
a ray looks like.
All right.
Let's start shooting.
Here we go.
Next,
Kamogawa.
Recently,
our special effects staff
has been working on
countermeasures for both
the ray and the ray.
Are you going to shoot a movie?
Yes.
I think we can go home
before it's too late.
Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy your meal.
I thought it was a movie,
but there's even a food truck.
It's common in America.
This is delicious.
Yes. He used to work at Sheraton in Hong Kong.
He used to work as a general manager.
I pulled him out.
Where should we put the chief?
No.
Chief Ohara took a picture of a turtle,
so he won't go into the river.
Hurry up and say that.
I don't have a chief.
I think the turtle is flying.
It's a turtle. Let the turtle fly.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I think he's drowning.
He's drowning.
I thought it was a turtle.
It's a turtle.
It's impossible.
I don't think it was a turtle.
Hurry up.
Don't you remember clearly?
If you attack so much,
you won't remember what you remember.
It's love.
There are three loves.
Get ready.
How is it?
Yes. It seems to be okay.
All right.
Let the rain fall.
It's the wind.
The chief flew.
All right. One more.
It's easy.
Excuse me.
Don't move.
Push the shutter.
At that time,
the cherry blossoms in the back were in full bloom.
Make the cherry blossoms in full bloom.
Yes.
There are 50 people on the old man's tour.
50 people on the old man's tour.
Yes.
It's a sunset.
It was a sunset.
Don't say that.
Excuse me.
Can you see the sunset?
I'm afraid you can't see it in this darkness.
Let's do something.
This is it! This is the sunset of that day!
Hurry up and turn off the shutter!
Yes.
We managed to finish it safely.
Yeah.
You did a great job too.
Good job!
You didn't have to kick anything off.
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
Even though it's a doll, if you think there are two of them, you'll be disappointed.
12th Line, No. 21, 34th Street, No. 304, Nozomi Street, Tokyo.
We managed to make it to the last bullet train.
We'll be at Tokyo Station by 12 o'clock.
When we get home, we'll be in a good mood.
What is it?
There's another picture.
What?
I forgot the most important picture of the Buddhist temple.
Wait, wait, wait!
Yes, yes.
I understand.
It's no good.
The movie crew is about to leave for Alaska.
Where's the helicopter?
The engine is broken.
It's in Tachiojo in Nagoya.
It won't be able to fly for a couple of hours.
Darn it.
I guess I have no choice but to take a picture of it.
Senpai!
Are you there?
Darn it.
How much longer are you going to make me suffer?
Senpai!
Are you okay?
Open it!
Show me the Buddha statue!
Hey!
This Buddha statue looks like a Buddha statue.
This isn't just a Buddha statue.
It was released once every 1,000 years for only three minutes.
It's a very high-class Buddha statue.
Show me the Buddha statue!
What do you want at this hour?
Show me this Buddha statue!
I only show it once every 1,000 years.
Don't say such things!
I'm going to take a punishment!
Are you okay?
Darn it.
Darn it!
If this happens, I'm going to beat you up!
Senpai, this is bad.
This is illegal.
Is this the time to say that?
Who's there?
Senpai!
Let's run away!
Anyway, let's run away!
It's impossible to keep the guards in check.
Do you want us to give up after coming all this way?
No.
But the next time I see you, it's after 1,000 years.
Did you come up with a good idea?
I see.
I have an idea.
Yes.
What is it?
Huh?
It's kidding.
Yuck, why do we have to do such a thing?
Awesome!
So you are the same.
Sure?
Time up!
Come on, who's up?
Let's take a picture!
Yes. First, turn your back, put your body in front of you, and turn your face this way.
The right arm goes from the back of the neck to the left cheek, and the finger goes into the mouth.
It looks like this!
If you look closely, you can see that only the thumb of the one leg with the front of the seat is standing.
The left arm goes from the inside of the leg with the front of the seat to the nose.
The right eye looks to the north, and the left eye looks to the south.
Hurry up and take a picture!
I'm going to take a picture.
What are you doing?
Ryo-chan won't come back.
That's right.
Ryo, is Ryo-tsu here?
T-that's...
What?
Did you get the camera wrong?
That's right.
I put the film in, but I completely forgot that I put the camera in before I went out because it was heavy.
Is that so?
Chief!
I did it!
Chief, I took a picture.
You're Ryo-tsu?
Ryo-chan?
Why are you dressed like that?
Look, it's a picture of the chief.
A picture?
This is...
There are two of us.
What's going on?
The pose and everything is exactly the same.
But the details are a little different.
What do you mean?
You're up to something again, aren't you, Ryo-tsu?
No, Chief!
I did it!
I took a decisive picture!
Please look forward to the next O-Shingo!
Damn you!
This is bad!
Now, let's hear the story slowly, Ryo-tsu.
Chief, please wait!
There's a deep reason for this!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The food critic, Omaeda Chouhoro!
I can't count the stores that were crushed by his ferocious criticism!
The grudge of the food is terrible!
Next is my opponent!
Come at me!
Next time, on Soba-ya's Reconstruction Plan!
Looking forward to it!
Let's fly, let's live
Even if today
is a rainy day
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye-bye!
Let's wave our hands
Goodbye to the bad things
Oh yeah
Let's live the way we want
There's something good
Outside the door
The sun is calling
To be continued