Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Poop-poop-poop-poop-poop-poop-poop.
The South Wind blows.
Eggplant salad!
Poop-poop-poop-poop-poop-poop.
Poop-poop-poop-poop!
One more?
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
A new soldier from the sky!
What a nice weather!
Something good is going to happen on a day like this...
It's too quiet.
That means...
Ryouku is late again!
Huh?
Ryou... Ryouku is working!
He came two hours before the time to go to work.
He's been like that all the time.
I thought he'd take a shower even if it rained.
We were just talking.
I'm very moved right now.
I've been working at the police station for 30 years.
I've never been this happy!
Ryouku.
You're so moved.
Ryouku finally woke up from work.
He's been working so hard.
Yes! I did it!
Good job, Ryouku!
I thought you'd do it someday.
By the way, what documents did you write?
What?
I don't like it.
Did you forget, chief?
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
I told you to submit the finished paper.
The finished paper?
I wrote everything.
My hands are frozen.
Idiot!
Who are you?
Chief, are you okay?
I'm sorry, but I need medicine.
Okay.
Did you drink too much, chief?
I'm old enough.
I need to take care of myself.
What did you say?
It's all your fault!
Calm down, chief.
If you get too angry, your blood vessels will break.
I have no choice but to give up because I have such a bad subordinate.
I remembered it as a subordinate.
Is Nakagawa-kun still here?
Mr. Nakagawa?
He's a newcomer who's going to be in this police station from today.
What kind of guy is he?
Oh, he's pretty handsome.
He grew up in New York until he was 16 years old.
He's the same age as Reiko-san.
Yes.
His car has a permanent license.
He also has a boat and a plane license.
He's also good at sports and can speak Japanese.
He's so good at shooting that he can blow a needle's head off a kilometer away.
Who is Mr. Nakagawa?
He's the son of Nakagawa-zaibatsu.
Nakagawa-zaibatsu?
Is he the Nakagawa-zaibatsu that can be found anywhere in the world?
That's right.
What is that Nakagawa-zaibatsu?
Is it a piece of wood?
It's not a piece of wood. It's a piece of wood.
It's a piece of consul.
Is it a piece of konnyaku?
No, it's not.
Reiko-kun, don't talk like that.
Don't talk.
You're going to hurt your stomach like me.
Yes.
You're not going to get a hard job as a police officer.
You're going to have to go to kindergarten and study hard.
Ryo-tsu!
You're going to have to teach Nakagawa-zaibatsu not to do that.
What?
Okay, now.
Let's go.
How is it? Isn't it amazing?
It's the American helicopter Black Hawk combat rescue type.
I'm tired of it.
Is that what you were doing yesterday?
Well, yes.
The chief will definitely be tired of it.
That's strange.
What is the prop?
What's with that locker?
That's right. I remember now.
When did you get that?
Huh? You didn't know?
It's completely deformed.
Good, good.
Here we go.
Good, good boy.
Besides, how did you get this?
You could have used this passion for work.
I'm always using it.
Sorry, sorry.
Ryo-chan!
Ryo-san?
What's going on?
Are you okay, Ryo-san?
I thought I was going to die.
By the way, where's the helicopter?
Helicopter?
It flew out.
It's worth 300,000 yen!
If it's gone, I'll have to pay for it.
I'm not joking.
Ryo-chan is the one who's to blame.
Darn it. Where did it go?
Huh?
Oh, it's an excellent helicopter.
It came out of nowhere.
Damn it! How dare you use my helicopter!
What's going on?
I-I think the helicopter is coming this way.
W-What?
What's that?
I don't know. Who is it?
It's a blast.
Oh, no, no.
Hooray!
It's too late, everyone.
From today, I will be working at the launch site.
I'm Keiichi Nakagawa.
Nice to meet you.
You bastard!
How dare you destroy my helicopter!
Huh?
Oh?
It's a Walther MPL submachine gun.
Do you know?
I'm so happy.
By the way, this is the gun.
Oh!
It's the same as Dirty Harry.
That movie was great, wasn't it?
Oh, if you don't mind,
I'd like to give you an apology for destroying the helicopter.
Really?
I'm sorry about that.
No.
I have a lot more at home.
Would you like to come and see it next time?
I'll go.
Idiot!
What are you thinking about?
Revenge! Revenge!
So this is no good either?
Of course.
Terai.
Collect them.
Yes, sir.
My stomach is killing me again.
I'm going to the doctor.
Reiko.
I'll leave the rest to you.
You're a pretty attractive guy.
I'm Ryotsu.
Nice to meet you.
Oh.
You're the super famous Ryotsu?
I am.
I'm Ryotsu.
Nice to meet you, too.
You two are the bad guys.
You two seem to be happy.
Is that helicopter for the next time?
You're rich for the konnyaku shop.
Konnyaku shop?
By the way, why did you become a police officer?
Well,
I've lived in New York for a long time.
I've always wanted to be a police officer who would risk his life for the citizens.
And you're wearing a shabby uniform.
What?
That's right.
I think it's more problematic than a gun.
Is that so?
The uniform of the police in Japan is not good.
So I made an order in Armani.
It was about 1 million yen.
1 million yen?
I don't think I can afford such a cheap uniform.
I don't know how you feel about spending 300,000 yen on a radio.
I'll do it with you.
Yes, yes.
By the way,
I haven't been going to the police recently, but I've been trying to forgive you for that kind of uniform.
Well, I was told it was no good, but I changed my clothes on the helicopter.
I'll do that.
The chief should be in pain, too.
I'll go to the patrol.
Ryo-chan, tell Mr. Nakagawa.
See you later.
So what should I do?
I'll tell you.
You're the one who teaches me.
I'll go to the patrol, too.
Hey.
Damn it.
Well, I...
Stand in front of me and show me the way.
Yes, sir.
Are you Mr. Omawari?
Yes, I am.
Oh, good.
I'd like to ask you the way.
Yes, please.
Senpai, please wake up.
What is it?
I was sleeping well.
I was asked the way, but I don't know anything about this area.
What?
Show me the map and let me look for it.
That's the old man who came back to Japan for the first time in 50 years.
He says he doesn't know where this is.
Well, it can't be helped.
So, where do you want to go?
A restaurant.
What kind of restaurant?
I forgot the name of the restaurant, but I have a clue.
What?
It's a restaurant like this.
Oh, that's a bad picture.
Did you draw it?
When I was a student, it was more than 50 years ago.
What? 50 years ago?
So, what's the address of the restaurant?
That's the downtown of Tokyo.
That's all?
Yes.
No, no.
The downtown is big.
I don't understand.
Give up.
That's no good.
Because it's my first job.
Do whatever you want.
If you let me look for it, I would like to thank you.
What?
Why don't you say that first?
I'll ask you about the details in the back.
Hey, Nakagawa.
Order coffee and cake for breakfast.
What?
Just go.
Yes.
I see.
When I was a high school student, I went to that restaurant several times.
High school?
Yes.
It's Tokyo Art University now.
I was always busy because I had a day off.
What?
That means it's near the art college.
Yes.
I walked for about 15 minutes.
The art college is on the upper floor.
If you don't mind, I'll have this.
Sorry.
Let's look for it near the art college.
Can you find it in about two hours?
If it's on the upper floor, it'll take 20 to 30 minutes by car.
Actually, I have to go back to Paris by the 1 o'clock flight to Narita.
If it's on the upper floor, it'll take about an hour in Tokyo.
What?
Get a taxi.
I'll call you right away.
It's me.
Bring the car to the airport right away.
Well...
How about my car?
Thank you very much.
Here it is.
Ferrari F40.
Here you are.
But this is for two people.
I've remodeled it into a new one, so it's okay.
Please get in.
Reiko, I'm back at a good place.
Ryo-chan.
I need help.
I need a taxi.
What?
See you later.
I think I saw him somewhere.
I'm back at the airport.
Damn it.
I don't have time for this.
Hey, Nakagawa.
Turn around.
Senpai, it's impossible.
Is it the exit of the one-way street?
Idiot!
Don't you want to make a good old man's wish come true?
Well...
Go back.
Then there's no problem.
No way.
I understand.
Senpai, let's go back.
What's going on?
Idiot!
I don't know.
Ryoji Kankichi.
He's back at it again.
It's nice to ride such a lovely car.
It's not the time to be impressed.
I'll arrest you this time.
Turn left.
Stop.
Senpai, what should we do?
When you're busy...
Come on!
I'll show you the power of Ferrari.
Yes, sir.
It's too fast.
It's Ryoji Kankichi again.
If there's a problem, I'll fix it.
Turn right.
Yes, sir.
Turn left.
But Ryoji is so busy.
I can see it well.
I've been playing around here since I was a kid.
It's like a garden.
It's impossible to go any further.
Idiot!
It's your first job.
Policemen always finish their tasks.
Senpai.
I made a mistake.
All right.
It's getting darker.
Don't worry.
I can get through.
I've been here before.
It's not a bicycle.
All right.
As expected of Senpai.
What is this place?
Can you stop for a moment?
It's nostalgic.
I've lived in Paris for decades.
I often remember Japan.
It was when I was a student at a beautiful art school.
I was surrounded by good friends.
I was painting all day long.
Ueno is a forest of art.
I went to the art museum every day.
I had a good time with my friends.
At that time, I fell in love with the girl at the cafeteria that my friend took me to.
It was my first love.
That's the cafeteria in that painting.
When was that?
I think it was close to graduation.
It was when I caught a cold and went to bed.
She came to the dormitory.
She took care of me.
When I got better, I tried to thank her.
At that time, I was poor and had no money to give her a present.
So I drew her portrait with all my heart.
And I gave her that picture.
The happy face of that girl at that time is still burning in my eyes.
So what is that girl?
I went to study in Paris at the same time as graduation.
I didn't say I liked her.
It's a long time ago.
It's not the time to be upset.
There's only an hour left.
Let's find the cafeteria.
How is it, old man?
Do you remember the scenery around here?
This area has changed a lot since 50 years ago.
An hour left?
It's impossible.
I decided to bring back my memories to Paris as a memory.
There are still 10 minutes left.
I won't give up.
I can't find one or two of them.
I'm going to be a police officer.
Damn it!
I've been thinking about you for 50 years.
I wanted to see you for the first time.
It's okay.
This is also fate.
That tree...
I found it!
Look at this place.
It's the same as before.
It hasn't changed at all.
Let's go see the first love.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong, old man?
He's married and has a family.
I don't want to ask him all of a sudden.
What are you talking about?
Let's go inside.
But...
If you don't open it, I'll open it.
Come on.
Open it.
Hurry up and open it.
Ms. Isumi.
Mr. Taki.
It's Mr. Taki, right?
Yes.
It's been a long time.
No, it's true.
That painting is still in the store.
You've been taking good care of it.
This painting is my treasure.
Thank you, Ms. Isumi.
Senpai, look at that happy face.
We police officers work hard for the people's smiles.
Police officers have a great job.
By the way, how much will you give me?
Senpai.
No, thanks to you, I made a good memory.
Please accept this as a thank you.
Thank you.
Then I'll take care of it.
Goodbye.
Let's go home.
Are you going again?
There's nothing to be happy about.
I got such a bad painting.
Hey, idiot.
I'll do this painting.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Go.
Taki, Jotaro.
Did the Ferrari just break down?
No, it didn't.
We still have a lot of cars.
Do you have that much money?
Well, it's about 400 million yen.
400 million yen?
Nakagawa, let's get along.
Ryo-chan.
There was an old man in the Ferrari, right?
Yes, that old man.
No way.
He was a famous painter all over the world.
It's that old man, right?
Is he such a famous painter?
One painting costs at least 100 million yen.
100 million yen?
I won.
You're good.
I'll give you a lot of money.
My 100 million yen.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I've come up with an amazing idea.
I'm going to sell ramen on a balloon.
I mean, a convenience store.
What do you think?
No one can come up with such a great idea.
I'm a genius.
Next time, on Sky Jumping Store.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, smile at me
You're not bad
You're doing great
Smile at me all the time
A serious woman is not beautiful
You should smile right away
If you're not a child