Fresh Spring Patrol Karuta!
It's strange, isn't it?
No, it's weird.
Alright, it's done.
Thank you for your hard work on the New Year's work.
We'll take over the rest.
Thank you for your hard work.
I heard that you've been working since New Year's Eve.
Of course.
Unlike Nakagawa and Reiko, I put my life on my work.
During the New Year, I was on a hot mission to protect the safety of the people.
What's wrong with you?
Riy-san, stop joking around.
What?
I know.
Last year, we had a summer vacation.
So, we had a meeting on New Year's Eve.
You knew that, didn't you?
Alright, let's go home.
Ryo-san, what are you going to do from now on?
I'm just going to sleep.
We don't have a New Year's party at the chief's house this year.
That's strange.
I met Terai at Hatsumode yesterday.
He told me that he was going to the chief's house to celebrate New Year's Eve.
That's a mistake.
The chief told me that he was going on a family trip with his family.
A New Year's party?
Yes, it's a New Year's party at the chief's house.
When are you going to do it next year?
Next year, I'll cancel it.
I was looking forward to New Year's Eve when I ate at the chief's house.
Ryo-chan, you're exaggerating.
Don't be so disappointed.
It's been a long time since the three of us went on a trip to the hot spring.
Are you taking care of your family more than your subordinates?
Don't say that.
Hiromi is also old.
I can't go on a trip without seeing my parents.
Well, that's what it is.
Everyone, the New Year's party is next year.
Yes.
Really? That's too bad.
Now that I think about it, I feel like everyone was out of their minds.
Maybe I wasn't the only one who wasn't invited.
All right.
Are you Mr. Terai's otaku?
I'm Ryotsu.
Congratulations.
By the way, I have something to do at Terai.
What?
You did it for me.
That actor director.
You made me an outcast.
Damn it.
Then I'll eat anything.
I'll eat your food.
I won't forgive you.
Ryo-san, he didn't have a chainsaw just now.
This is a blood test.
Happy New Year.
Thank you for coming.
I look forward to working with you again this year.
Hiromi-chan, you're cute.
Reiko-san looks good on you, too.
Thank you.
Huh?
Senpai haven't come yet?
You know, dad.
Hiromi.
I don't want to remember anything like that from the New Year.
Anyway, Nakagawa.
Did you park the car in front of the house?
Yes.
Come on.
It's a small place, but come in.
Huh?
Director.
Why are you closing the window in the middle of the day?
It's a devil's curse.
Devil's curse?
Senpai, please forgive me.
I'm going to Hatsumode with my sister from now on.
You can always go to Hatsumode.
But the director's New Year's party is only today.
That's ridiculous.
Don't you regret it?
You're not invited to the New Year's party.
Of course.
I'm a white-collar and I'm not a department team.
Don't say that.
I'm your best friend.
You can take me to the director's house.
You're a tough guy.
I got it.
Let's get on the bike.
Let's go!
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Nakagawa?
Isn't that Honda's CBX engine?
Maybe Senpai's here, too.
What?
I can't believe it.
The devil's curse doesn't work.
Listen, no matter what happens,
don't say anything or come out on the street.
Damn it.
You've made up your mind.
I thought you went on a family trip.
It's not like that.
Look at that.
What's that?
You're using your dirty hands to cover it with a sheet.
It's a Ferrari F50.
It's different from the one I always ride,
but it's definitely a Nakagawa Ferrari.
Is that so?
Maybe the neighbors' cars are cars, too.
Look around.
Where the hell do people live?
Look at the license plate.
It's a Shonan license plate.
Nakagawa lives in Tokyo,
but he's dressed up to make all the cars his Shonan license plate.
Ohara-san?
It's a delivery.
Please send it to me.
Ohara-san, please come out.
Ryo-chan is so mischievous.
I don't know what to do.
Damn it.
Are you going to pass through the house?
The windows and curtains of the house are closed.
I'm going on a long trip.
The enemy is still inside.
Look at this.
Isn't this just an electric meter?
Look at the meter.
If it's a house, it should only work with a refrigerator and a phone.
The meter doesn't work like this.
I see.
Everyone, would you like some sukiyaki?
Sounds good.
I'm tired for the food.
I'll help you.
Chief!
I know you're inside.
He's stubborn.
Put us inside as soon as possible.
Dad, I feel sorry for you.
Please put us inside.
No.
You may not know, but every time I went on a trip, he made my house a mess.
If I do something to him, he will destroy my precious bonsai.
If I do something to him, he will destroy my tatami.
If I do something to him, he will paint ink on my face.
He made my room black.
I will never let him stay in my house again.
I don't know how to make you a scarecrow.
You are completely surrounded.
Give up and come out.
Ignore him.
He doesn't react at all.
Damn it.
If that's what you're going to do, I'll do it with the back of my hand.
Back of your hand?
It's quiet now.
It seems that he gave up.
No.
When it comes to food, he'll show you a terrible end.
I can't rest assured.
Is it a power outage?
There is no electricity in the New Year.
The gas in the kitchen suddenly stopped.
What?
Damn it.
It's all Ryotsu's doing.
Senpai.
Let's stop here.
Shut up.
If this is the case, I'll eat you.
Anyway, it's tough.
It's good to make these guys panic by reversing the waterway and the waterway.
Let's break the door faster.
Senpai.
It's a mess.
Honda, it's okay.
Don't worry.
For the time being, only the minimum is scary.
I can't rest assured.
Let's go.
Ryotsu.
Chief, please don't open the door.
The life expectancy has been reduced.
I was the one who reduced the life expectancy.
Senpai, what are you doing here with a chain saw?
The door...
Well, the chief asked me to take care of the farm.
Liar.
I don't remember asking you to do that.
I hate it.
When I get older, I forget it.
Right, Honda?
Yes.
No, no, no.
Anyway, Chief.
Didn't you go on a trip to the hot spring?
Yes.
That's...
I couldn't get a ticket because of the difference in the travel agency.
So I decided to stay at home.
Then why are you in Nakagawa?
Well...
I suddenly got bored, so I called Nakagawa and Reiko.
Of course, I contacted Niconico, too.
I'm sorry.
Of course.
I've been working in the hot spring for a long time.
Is that so?
I was surprised.
Well, it's a coincidence.
Let's get closer, Honda.
Chief, of course you don't mind, do you?
I'm glad, Honda.
You came all the way to Chiba to take care of the farm.
Well, then, let's have a meal.
Oh, before that...
Thank you for waiting.
I'm glad you came to take care of the farm.
I brought it so that you don't have to worry about this kind of thing.
Honda, it's a little rude to dress like that.
Well, whatever.
It's the chief's house.
Ryotsu, remember what to do.
Ryotsu, Honda.
Happy New Year.
Come on, sit down.
Thank you.
Happy New Year, everyone.
Happy New Year.
Terai, You look good in Japanese clothes.
Why do you say that?
If you wear such good clothes and come to the New Year's party,
why don't you say a few words to me?
Honda, I'm really happy to have a good colleague.
Senpai.
Ryotsu, don't be so mean as if you've got something in your teeth.
What?
Well, it's New Year's Eve, so let's have fun.
I'm tired of New Year's food, so I'm going to make sukiyaki.
How about you guys?
What kind of stupid thing are you doing?
We eat New Year's food.
This is the common sense of the Japanese.
Chief.
But...
It's not that there's no New Year's food.
It's the wisdom of the Japanese from the old days
that we put in a lot of things that make us feel like we're going to take a break from work on New Year's.
But it's not like you're going to take a break from work on New Year's.
Even if it's about New Year's food,
I'm happy with the omumaki.
Black beans work for beans.
Shrimp is an act.
There's a meaning to it.
What are you thinking about from New Year's to sukiyaki?
New Year's in Japan is of course New Year's.
It looks like the New Year's is coming, so it's better to give it out.
It seems so.
Mom.
There's still some osechi.
Give it out.
Yes.
Yay!
Osechi is here!
We're going to make sukiyaki here.
Ryosu, you can eat the osechi there.
Huh?
It's an imposter again.
Well, as long as the osechi comes.
Oh, here it comes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What?
Um, I can't see Kinton or Kazunoko.
I ate that one.
All that's left is there.
What?
Black beans?
Omumaki?
Kamaboko?
So the best three of the unpopular osechi are supposed to be left.
Osechi cooking without the main character is not good.
It looks delicious.
All right, it's boiling.
Excuse me, boss.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
Excuse me, boss.
What is it?
If you don't mind, can you help me with the sukiyaki over there?
I made the osechi dish for you.
Ryosu, I'll leave the sukiyaki to you until you finish eating the osechi.
All right.
I can eat the osechi, right?
Of course.
I'm glad.
I was wondering how to get rid of the rest of the osechi.
It's just right to get rid of it.
Ryosu's stomach is as big as a bug.
That's right.
I'll introduce it to you even if it hurts a little.
Anyway, Ryosu, you'd better eat the meat before you finish eating the osechi.
All right.
I can finally eat the sukiyaki.
Let's eat.
There's only one piece of meat.
What?
What a shame.
I was faster.
No, I was faster.
Honda, right?
Honda, you'll tell us the truth.
I don't want to.
It's better to avoid meat than to get old.
You're the one who ate so much of the osechi, so don't do it.
You bastard.
It's not good to put a wisp on the meat.
I can see your despicable ways.
You two are not children.
That's right.
Let's decide who wins the game.
Game?
How about we settle it with karta like ginger?
That sounds interesting.
All right.
I think there was a police karta.
Police karta?
I did it with my sister yesterday.
If you walk around, you'll get into an accident.
Be careful, you'll get hurt.
That's good, isn't it?
It's not interesting to have a karta like that.
What do you think?
Let's do it with my karta.
Did you bring the karta?
Yes.
I made it when I was working on New Year's day.
You bastard.
Are you going to do the karta game?
Are you not going to do it?
Let's do it.
I won't let you eat meat.
I'm the one who eats meat at the end.
I'll eat it.
Then I'll go.
What's wrong?
Hurry up and read it.
I can't read it.
Mr. Nakagawa, please change.
What?
It doesn't matter who it is.
Hurry up and read it.
I understand.
Reiko's big pie that will someday fall.
What did you say?
No, I...
Yes.
Chief, you're going to pray first, aren't you?
What are you writing?
Idiot.
I'll go next.
The last one is definitely the chief, Ryotsu Kankichi.
What?
I'll take it.
You like this card the most, don't you?
I just made it.
It's a weird karta.
I'm hungry.
Chief Ohara is soaked.
What is it?
I'm sorry I met you a long time ago.
My home.
Terai-kun of Lone Hell.
Not yet.
I found it.
You're naive, Chief.
You don't seem to be my enemy.
You made this karta.
You made it yourself, so you're better than me.
Are you trying to make fun of me for losing?
That's not it.
It's hard to read because the words are dirty.
You're the only one who knows it's not fair.
Chief, where are you going with that picture book?
I'm making it fair.
Don't make it messy.
Are you going to spread it all over the house?
This is fair.
Okay, this is good.
We'll find out what Nakagawa is reading here.
When we find it, we'll bring it to Nakagawa.
That sounds fun.
Okay, let's get started.
Nakagawa-kun is doing it for fun.
What is it?
Okay, I found it.
Damn it.
Yotsu, Kankichi, Kameyari Ichi's good man.
Honda-kun, who is more impolite than Tora-san.
I did it, Ryo-san.
Pachinko Dai Fever.
Chief, raise the salary rather than raising the blood pressure.
Ryo-chan has 20 sheets.
Chief has 19 sheets.
There are only two sheets left.
I can't lose to Yotsu.
I remember.
This is the second-floor library school.
I told you not to eat only Aisai bento.
Toilet.
Damn it.
I found it.
This is my victory.
This is a tie.
You're a dirty handler.
Then I'll go to the last sheet.
I'll definitely turn it over.
This year.
It's not 4, it's 1.
This is my victory.
What?
It won't open.
You're naive, Ryo-chan.
I put the key in the book just in case.
Damn it.
After all, the last thing to laugh at is...
There's no key.
That's strange.
That means you can't get in.
Alright.
Sorry.
Both of them are late.
They went outside.
Huh?
I knew it.
What's that sound?
Inside here?
What's going on?
Damn it.
My book.
You're a little late.
It's my victory.
You did a good job.
Next year's New Year's party.
You're the only one who can't get in.
Damn it.
I knew it.
This year's New Year's party is going to be like this.
Watch this year's New Year's party.
This is Katsushikaku.
Kameyari Park.