Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Everybody can do!
I don't want to say it even if it sticks out a little.
I want to hug the noisy Kouki.
Strongly and high, Lollipop!
Well, everyone.
Over the past few years,
we have been troubled by a certain person.
That is this man!
The leader of history,
every year at this time,
made all possible measures to challenge this man.
However...
There was a loose end to everything,
and only a strong sense of defeat remained.
The commitments were just one step away.
I will never forget the humiliation I felt two years ago.
When I think of this man,
I feel depressed and can't sleep at night.
But that will end this year!
Because I am the leader.
Yeah, but that's over this year, too!
I'm going to be the leader, so I'm going to make sure to...
This year, I'm going to get a debt from Ryotsu Kankichi!
Um, it's just a simple pillow, but I think it's time for you to go inside.
I know.
So, everyone, let's start the 21st Ryotsu Kankichi Bonus Consultation Battle.
Oh, good, good, good, good. It'll be over soon.
Kikuchi-san!
You know, it'll be a problem if you bring a baby to an important meeting.
It can't be helped.
His wife is a man who can't even take out a debt.
He left the house.
I... I'm not paying Ryosu Kankichi for his debt.
But in fact, I don't think Ryosu Kankichi can do anything to him.
What are you talking about?
He's your father.
He was the president of the 8th shopping district, and he risked his life to get his debt.
Yeah, he was passionate about everything.
He was also the one who started the sports meeting.
But thanks to that, he got out of it.
Sorry, but that was a masterpiece.
Yeah, right.
So, this time, I prepared a new weapon to take away Ryosu Kankichi's bonus.
A new weapon?
I've been living in Plamoya for 30 years.
I've put all my technology into it, and I've developed it over 90% of the shopping district and three months.
This is Ryosu Kankichi's navigation system.
In other words, Ryonavi.
I'm ready.
All I have to do is catch Ryosu Kankichi and take away his bonus.
The name of the operation is the Sky Eye Operation.
Ryosu-san, Ryosu Kankichi, the district secretary.
Yes.
Ryosu-san.
Here's the bonus for this time.
Yahoo!
It's been 180 days and two and a half.
I've been going to the office every day, even in the darkness of the chief.
Everything is for you, this cute bonus.
Ryosu-san, what are you going to use this year's bonus for?
Actually, I've reserved a one-twelveth model of NASA's special Radicon Space Shuttle for the limited release.
You're always like that.
Well, let's go to the bank right away.
If you don't put in the money today, it will be canceled.
It's late.
There are 30 people.
They are more careful than usual.
What's more?
It's late.
It's about time for them to come out.
I think they've already left.
Yes.
Those who are good at disguising with sunglasses are not good at all.
Oh, my bonus.
Hello, miss.
I dropped this.
Oh, thank you very much.
No problem.
What?
What is it?
I felt like it was similar to my wife who ran away.
I feel like it's similar to my wife who ran away.
If you look closely, you'll see that she's more beautiful than her husband.
Oh, I'm scared.
Well then.
Be careful.
That was close.
But their eyes are so strange.
Hey, Ryosu-san.
What?
I forgot half of it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What?
Oh, no.
It's Ryosu-san.
Return my bonus.
My pay.
What?
I thought something like this would happen.
Take this, Nippo.
Oh, you bastard.
Over there.
Well then.
I'll take the bonus.
Oh, it's Ramiya's camera.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Over there.
When did this happen?
Damn it.
I'm done for.
Ozaki-san, please respond.
This is Katsushika Shomae.
The ambush was a failure.
Ryo-san ran away.
The emergency operation has begun.
Roger.
Ozaki-san, are you all right?
At this stage, it is expected that Ryo-san will be able to escape.
This is the real story of the Sky Eye Operation.
Navigation computers are installed on Ryo-san's belt.
The artificial satellite catches that signal and always knows where it is.
It's kind of exciting.
Is this really going to work?
It's a system used by the US Army.
It's more than 200% reliable.
But I can't trust a new machine.
Yes, yes.
This time, you just have to watch it.
Start navigation.
What is this shining spot?
This is Ryo-san's current location.
The target is heading to the Kamewari Association Bank through the back road.
Go around and ambush them.
Roger.
Ryo-san, it's no use trying to escape.
Your location is being monitored from the sky.
Welcome.
Ryo-san, wait.
Please go to the Kamewari Association Bank for the bonus.
Oh no, I'm in the way.
Okay, Street Riders, go!
Start navigation.
Damn it.
I'll show you the skills of a motorcycle that I've been training for a long time.
You've even prepared a motorcycle.
Then...
What?
You're ten years too early.
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
I used to be a professional racer.
I've been told that you're ready to listen to me.
Hello?
Street Riders, annihilated.
They're going to the neighboring town across the Nakagawa River.
Ryo-san is heading to the neighboring town.
Use the center of the bridge to ambush them.
Damn it.
They're not going to be in a good mood this year.
It's safer to get away from the town and go to the neighboring bank.
We're not going in here, Ryo-san.
That's ridiculous.
How did you know we were going through here?
Ryo-san, there's no way out.
What the hell is going on?
We're going to give you a bonus.
Ryo-san, give us a bonus.
Everyone, give us a bonus.
Bonus, bonus.
Let's go.
They're not going to jump into the river.
They're running away.
Wait up.
Let go of me.
We're not humans.
We're going to die if they jump into the river.
Let go of me.
What are you doing?
Did you drop this misbo-like gate ball?
Or Nagashima Shigeo's sign ball?
Nagashima's sign ball.
Of course it's a gate ball.
I'm going to change the fire.
Damn it.
How do you know where I'm going?
What's this code?
A battery in a hand-held case?
You were monitoring me with a navigation system?
That's a good idea.
But I'm not going to get caught like that.
I'm not going to get caught.
I have an important mission.
I'm going to the bank today.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
It's not as fragile as it's broken into the river.
The hot pot I made.
Is this really showing where Ryo-san is?
I can't believe it.
Hey, Ohara-san.
How is it?
Did Ryo-tsu get caught?
It's a matter of time.
This is only possible if Ohara-san's help is available.
It's cheap enough to replace Ryo-tsu's belt.
Ohara-san
I'm not going to bother you with him anymore.
No, no.
Please feel free to get on the boat.
Thank you.
Mr. Osaki.
What is it, old lady?
It's been a while since it moved, but it's broken, isn't it?
It can't be.
It's closed.
It seems to be running away and taking a break.
Ohara-san.
I'm going to see Ryo-san for the last time.
Oh, finally.
Please get on.
Yes, sir.
It's coming. It's coming.
Ryo-san is currently staying at the Kamewari Hybrid Hotel.
We're going to have a match here.
From now on, the overseas operation will enter the final stage.
Everyone, head to the hotel.
It's coming.
Is Ryo-san really here?
Believe in the latest news.
This option CD-ROM is in sync with the radio transmission from the satellite.
Find out where Ryo-san is in the hotel while standing.
This room.
To all.
Ryo-san is a veranda in room 817.
Room A is a veranda in room 816.
Room B is a veranda in room 818.
Room C and D are in the inside of room 817.
The existence of the Kamewari Hotel is in this battle.
Everyone, head to the hotel.
Be sure to win.
Yuki.
It's finally the two of us.
Let's go.
Room B is in position.
Room B, go ahead.
Room B, room 818 is in position in the veranda.
Room C and D.
Room C and D are in position.
Understood.
Countdown, start.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Go!
You bastard.
Report.
Did you successfully capture the target?
It's a crow.
A crow?
The one on the veranda is not Ryo-san.
It's a crow with Ryo-san's belt on it.
It can't be.
I can't believe the strategy to use it is broken.
That's why I said I couldn't trust the machine.
I won again this year.
Now, let's wash the money.
Ah, the money is falling.
Money?
Money, money, money, money.
I found it.
I got it.
Children's bank?
What?
Damn it!
You tricked me, you coward!
Right?
Even if you didn't use the machine, you could easily capture it.
That's right.
This is the best way for Ryo-san.
As expected of Toshinoko.
How pitiful.
What was the trouble I've had so far?
Come on, come on.
Line up, line up.
Is that okay, Mr. Ohara?
Please, please.
Please take it.
I'm sorry, Ryo-san.
I'll take it.
What's wrong?
Isn't it a bad omen?
No, it's worse not to pay for it.
Please take it without hesitation.
Is that so?
You're in a bad mood when I say it lightly, aren't you?
I'm sorry, Sachiko.
It's going to be a long way to go to pick you up.
Who is that girl?
Sachiko, my sister.
I'm Sachiko.
Sachiko works in a cold place in the north where her limbs are numb and her bones are stiff.
What?
You're still a child, aren't you?
Why?
It's a long story.
I won't forget it.
Sachiko was born on a cold night full of snow.
Her parents were happy.
They wished for her to grow up to be a happy child.
They named her Sachiko.
However...
A sudden accident happened to her parents.
The insurance money that was supposed to come in was deceived by a bad broker.
The house collapsed as if it were being chased away.
Her parents died.
They failed the class and found out that they had 2 billion yen in debt.
Sachiko was taken away by a relative who was in charge of the debt.
However...
That relative is actually the president of a bad-for-nothing construction company.
He forced her to work even as a child.
He didn't even let her eat.
I tried to get Sachiko out of it.
However...
Every time I tried to get her out of it, she gave me 2 billion yen.
And then I made up my mind.
If I didn't earn enough, I wouldn't be able to get Sachiko out of it.
My salary and my bonus would all go to the debtor.
I don't care how much people in the world hate me for that.
But my brother was wrong.
Even though you were a bad-for-nothing,
you caused so much trouble to so many people.
My brother is a bad-for-nothing human.
Is that so?
Please forgive me for making you a bad-for-nothing human.
It's all right.
Everyone, you may have done it wrong.
However, he was trying to live as a human being.
Please forgive me for making you a bad-for-nothing human.
Please forgive me.
I didn't even think about Ryo's situation.
I was just trying to get a bonus.
Ryo, this is your bonus.
Please give it to your sister.
But this is...
I don't care about the debt.
Compared to Ryo, I'm a million times happier.
Don't lose!
I will never forget your kindness.
I'm sure your sister will be happy.
Hello, everyone.
What's going on?
What's this?
That's Ryo's sister, Sachiko.
That's strange.
This is a news report.
And your sister is not here.
It's impossible for Ryo to steal my bonus.
Thank you very much.
I'll just go to the bank tomorrow.
What's this?
Who did this?
According to past data,
you will have a 95% chance of defeating us.
You will win at this cafe.
As I thought.
I was waiting for you.
What's this?
This is a debt-taking weapon.
Shaking X.
It's Shaking X.
I was secretly developing it for the next year's bonus fight.
But it's always 80% complete.
I'm sure I can beat you.
Are you going to the bank?
Ryo is good at connecting with this Shaking X.
I got it.
This is not good.
Electric Shock.
Are you going to kill me?
Don't worry.
I'll consider your physical strength.
I'll give you a voltage that won't kill you.
I'm sure you'll faint.
Electric Shock.
Shock.
This is my bonus.
I don't want to do this.
I don't want you to pay the debt.
I'll take the bonus.
What's wrong?
I was so close.
Now you know.
It's impossible for you to take my bonus.
Even if the director forgives you, God will not forgive you.
God is also...
Wait.
Don't come too close.
Let go of me.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Even if you lose money, you can exchange it in the bank.
I'm sorry.
If you want to pay the debt, you can help me.
Don't talk to me.
I'm focused.
This is my bonus.
I'll take the bonus next year.
Thank you.
I did it.
I was selected as the number one exchange student.
Men are not face and body.
It's heart.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
Even if it rains today
Tomorrow will be sunny
Bye bye
I wave my hand
Goodbye to unpleasant things
Oh yeah
Let's live as we like
There is a good thing
Outside the door
The sun is calling