Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Everybody can do!
I don't want to say it even if it sticks out a little.
Don't worry about the noise.
A strong and high-pitched voice.
Like Zou-san!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Well, I'm going to work until 10.30.
No, wait.
I'm going to work until 11.
What have you been doing for a while?
What, Nakagawa?
I thought you were the head of Ohara.
I'm free tomorrow.
I'm going to set up a tight schedule and have a meaningful day.
It's really a valuable day outside of work.
Of course.
There are few days off for work days.
I also want 5 days off for work days.
2 days off for work days.
I'm working hard for the safety of the citizens.
It's a natural demand.
Ryo-chan is always on 7 days off.
However, if you do all these tight schedules, you need a lot of stamina.
Yes?
This is Kamayari.
What?
What is it?
I'll take a break here and have lunch and talk.
It's a big problem.
What?
What's going on?
It's dangerous.
Please go down.
Please don't go in.
It's dangerous. Please go down.
Okay?
If you get in trouble, you'll get in trouble.
Get out of the way.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Nakagawa.
Is there anyone injured?
No.
Where is the elephant?
It's in the warehouse in the back.
Hurry up and catch it.
That's right.
You're used to it, aren't you?
I'm not used to it, elephant.
I'll go with you.
Mr. Nakagawa is dangerous.
What's that?
It's discrimination.
Hurry up and go.
Here you are.
I don't want it anymore.
It's a little elephant.
Come on, elephant.
It's okay.
It's quiet.
Is it okay?
Senior.
It's dangerous, Mr. Nakagawa.
Let go of me.
Nakagawa.
Bring milk and a bottle of milk.
What?
Hurry up.
Yes.
Mr. Nakagawa.
I'm glad you're okay.
Excuse me.
Do you have milk and a bottle of milk?
What?
It's okay.
Nakagawa, you're still not good at this.
I'm done.
Do you drink milk?
Milk is the basic of dairy.
Here's milk.
Please forgive me, my father.
Here.
Like this.
Try drinking it.
Here.
He drank it.
Good boy.
Don't touch it.
The elephant will be surprised.
Here.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
He's getting used to the farmland.
It's the same wild animal.
It's big, but it's still a child.
If you don't excite it, it'll be quiet.
But where did this elephant come from?
I don't think it was a pet.
I don't think it swam from Africa to the sea.
If that's the case, it's probably from the zoo.
I see.
Then, take care of it here until it comes back.
I'm going home, Nakagawa.
Please forgive me, Mr. Omari.
Nakagawa!
It's no good, Senpai.
We can't leave.
The wild animal and the elephant.
They're the best couple.
Why is the elephant here?
It's lost.
Ryo-chan picked it up.
Why is it in the excretory?
It's connected to the surface.
If you trample it even if you're drunk, it'll be a problem.
We can't leave it here until morning.
Ryo-chan was kind to it, and it seems to have gotten used to it.
Ryo-tsu likes it other than humans.
Look.
It's real. It's big.
I'll put it on if you give me 100 yen.
Really?
Ryo-tsu!
It's a joke.
Try it on.
Put it on.
I can't help it.
It's amazing.
It's expensive.
Brother, it's rotten.
It's true.
Did you get the search request?
I reported it to the head of the department.
There's nothing yet.
If it's difficult, let me drink milk again.
Don't tell me it's a frog.
Ryo-tsu!
Why?
Don't look at me like that.
My work hours are over.
I'll be free until tomorrow.
You'll be sleeping all day long.
Why don't you take care of him until he comes to pick you up?
No.
What is it?
It's your schedule for tomorrow.
I have a lot of plans.
9 o'clock, 3 o'clock, breakfast, 9 o'clock, 30 minutes,
10 o'clock, lunch, 10 o'clock, meter, 12 o'clock,
You're responsible!
If you're here, you should act more posteriorly.
Yes, Ryo-chan.
This isn't my constellation.
Did he follow us?
This is your vacation.
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
Good work!
See you later!
Hey, I'm definitely going home!
I'm going home no matter what you say!
Let me go! Let me go!
I'm not going to let you get away with this!
I'll take you with me, Ryo-chan!
Don't be stupid!
Do as you wish, Ryo-tsu!
This is an order from the chief!
Wh-what is it, Ryo-san? What's that big thing?
It's an order from the chief!
If you have any complaints, tell it to Chief Ohara!
I just cleaned the floor!
I don't want to walk on dirty feet!
That's enough!
I'm sorry, Tokura!
What are you doing, Ryo-san?
Don't put that in the bath!
It's an order from the chief!
If you have any complaints, tell it to the chief!
Ah!
Okay, the other side!
Okay, now the back!
Okay, it's clean now!
Listen, you stay here and wait quietly!
This guy seems to know only what's good for me!
I don't get it at all, Ryo-san!
I'm asking you, so stop asking me for a favor!
What's wrong?
T-that's...
As much as you want!
This is my food!
What are you going to do with our breakfast?
This is what happens when Ryo-san brings in an elephant!
If you're the owner, take responsibility!
That's why this isn't my elephant!
Please do something, Ryo-san!
Listen!
Don't say anything!
Bring him here right now!
But there's no sign that the elephant is gone yet!
Then where did he come from?
Is he from Norazo?
Then contact the health center!
Anyway, I'll contact you as soon as I get any information!
So please do until then!
This guy and that guy...
They're all following my good personality!
To be continued...
Look at this!
It's 9.30 a.m.!
Ryo-san!
That guy is coming in!
Yeah!
It's Douglas A-1 Skyray from Mologram!
This is it! I've been wanting this for so long!
8,000 yen, right?
I forgot my wallet!
Don't say that again!
No, it's true!
I'll bring the money next time!
Ryo-san!
He's already here!
This is the back door!
Oops!
You can't go in there, Ryo-san!
Ryo-san, there are two other people who are asking for money.
If you want it, bring the money.
That's not fair!
I'll definitely pay for it, so please don't sell it!
Please!
No!
I'm going to get caught!
You're a cop!
Why do I have to go on a date with an elephant during this time of the day?
Don't do it!
You're not going to die!
I'm thirsty after running around.
Huh?
Damn it!
If I have 10 yen left...
10 yen left...
Oh, there's a grain of grape!
A grain of grape...
A grain of...
10 yen...
Ah...
In the case of a small grain,
it's difficult to identify the owner even if it's sent to the police station.
I'll just have to return it when I get back to the station.
Alright, alright.
Good job.
Good job, good job.
Then, a grain of grape...
Ah!
I spilled the juice!
I can't drink juice when my throat is dry!
Give me back the 100 yen, you bastard!
Huh?
Two more?
If it's the case, give me another one!
Ah...
My throat is getting dry.
It's troublesome to go back to pick up my wallet.
The 10 o'clock check-in is cancelled.
Thanks to you, I can eat breakfast.
And the long-awaited scheduled dinner is a bar!
Ah!
What should I do now?
Did you pick it up again?
Ah!
It's my wallet!
And it's really heavy!
Ah!
It's a big one!
Oh, that wallet...
I was looking for it.
No, thank you.
You saved me.
Is this your wallet? What's the proof?
I think it's a picture I took with my granddaughter.
Unfortunately, it's the only thing I can prove.
I don't really care about the atmosphere.
Thank you.
I'll be careful.
But it's a rare pet.
I've heard that in Asia, there are few countries that value elephants as gods.
God?
This one?
Oh, it's a small one, but it's the second food for this elephant.
What?
This much?
I'm sure it's a good deal to give thanks.
Well, have a nice day.
I have 30,000 yen.
It seems to have come with me.
In that case, the afternoon schedule will continue again.
Come with me firmly, God!
How much is the elephant's ticket?
There is no elephant ticket.
Then it's free.
It's free.
What?
You ate too much and gained too much weight.
If you can't get through, you have to say goodbye here.
If you're upset, try jumping.
Hey, customer!
The train will arrive shortly on the second line.
Hurry up!
The train is coming!
The first one to get off is the first one.
Excuse me.
Please slow down a little.
It's coming!
Damn it!
What is it?
It's not coming at all.
What is it, God?
That old man said he would pay attention.
It's the last 1,000 yen.
If I take this off, I'll be able to walk back to Kameyari.
It's 20 times more than 47.
However, there is also a line called 36.
The person behind you is waiting.
Please line up again after you decide.
The sixth train will depart shortly.
This is the second train that connects to the next train.
It's the second train.
It's the first train.
No, it's not the first train. It's the second train.
The next person.
No, it's not like that.
37, 38, 100 yen.
It's the second train.
I've never heard of it.
What?
Both of them are old-timers.
They're so far away.
This old man.
God damn it.
No way.
I got it.
I got it!
I got the 100 yen!
It's good.
I got it!
You're going to be rich!
Here you go, Mr. Ryo.
Here, it's a new train.
I'm sorry.
It was a great elephant.
Okay, I'll treat you to anything for the sake of Manba.
I wonder where Ryo went with the elephant.
Yes.
This is the Kameyari Park.
What?
I saw an elephant.
I feel like I can be a good friend with you.
It's cold.
You're really something.
I'm sorry.
You look cute when you look at me.
Tonto!
Tonto?
Ryo!
Boss!
What do you want to do with the elephant?
I got a message from the zoo that they were looking for an elephant.
But Ryo is missing.
Anyway, I'm glad the elephant and Senpai are safe.
Thank you for the trouble.
Tonto's mother died yesterday.
What?
We took care of Tonto's mother.
He was lonely and escaped from the cage.
Tonto helped us a lot.
What?
What are you talking about?
Hey!
What do you want to do with my elephant?
Ryo!
What are you doing?
Let me go.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
What are you going to do?
Let me go.
Boss!
He's gone too.
I'll take care of him.
Idiot!
Nakagawa!
Come here!
Yes!
Let me go!
Senpai!
Don't let Nakagawa go!
It's dangerous.
Let me go!
Yes!
Please help us!
Let me go!
Yes!
Ready!
Go!
Stop!
Let me go!
Do you understand now?
Tonto is my elephant!
I'll never forget your kindness even when I return to the zoo, Tonto.
Tonto!
Wait for me, Tonto!
Wait for me!
Tonto!
Senpai!
Ryo-chan, you're so kind even though you look like that.
Tonto!
Tell me!
What's going to happen to the next elephant show?
I want him to win with me at the zoo.
Tonto!
If the elephant show doesn't work, I won't give up!
What's going to happen to the derby?
Did you fall in love with Megumi-chan from Aijo bento?
Good job!
You did well, Honda!
Get it on the second episode of the show!
I, a nice middle-class guy, who has a lot of experience, will teach you the points of a date!
Next time, on Fasile Honda, for the sake of love!
The End
Let's live the way we want
There's something good
Outside the door, the sun is calling