Shaved Ice and Ski Ski!
I can't do this in the morning.
Kaki-gori, give me some strawberries.
Sure.
Huh? When did you start doing this?
I've been doing it since this year.
It's easier to do it in the morning, and it's easier to do it in the evening.
That's true.
Yeah, I thought I am going to throw that away.
Throw it away? What a waste.
You can still use this kaki-gori.
Well, it's the flow of the times.
Here you go.
If you don't want it, I'll take it.
Yeah, sure.
Grandma!
Huh?
Give me some strawberries.
I'll have some lemons.
Sure.
You guys, if you don't study and wait for the money, I'll get mad at you.
Ryo-san, is it okay for you to be selling oil in a place like this?
I'm not selling oil. I'm eating ice.
I don't want to talk like a boss to a kid like this anymore.
I ate it.
If you eat something cold, you'll get a stomachache and go to sleep.
You won't even know if you get a stomachache and puke.
Then I'll take it.
Sure.
Hey, you, working-class workers.
Ryo-chan, what's that?
It's an ice-picking machine. I got it from a candy shop.
An ice-picking machine?
You can get anything you want, senpai.
What are you going to do with that?
Huh?
I'm going to make shaved ice.
Winter is the season of the year. Summer is the season of the year.
I can't do anything with this.
Senpai, if it's an ice-picking machine...
Ryo-chan bought it at the supermarket last week.
There's a pen-kichi-kun like this one, right?
Hey!
You can't be like that toy!
In this day and age, shaved ice has to be real.
Is there a real shaved ice?
Sometimes it changes depending on the place.
I showed you this shaved ice machine last week.
I'm going to make it right away.
But Ryo-chan, if it's real, you won't use the ice in the refrigerator, right?
Huh?
If it's real, you'll have to use the ice in Mont Blanc or the ice in the South Pole.
The ice in the South Pole...
There's a branch of the Nakagawa Continent in Greenland.
The ice in the North Pole should be fine, but...
That's it!
Huh?
Gourmet shaved ice is more in the North Pole than the South Pole.
I will buy that ice.
Give it to me right away.
Okay, but...
Listen, right away.
I hate waiting.
I understand.
Then I'll take a break and come back.
I'm going to throw up right away.
What?
It's so noisy that I can't sleep.
Senior, the shaved ice has arrived at the North Pole.
Huh?
Hurry up! The shaved ice is here!
It's here!
Where's the shaved ice?
Hurry up!
Huh?
There's only one shaved ice!
I did it!
All of these are mine!
Here, take it for the ice.
This way!
A little bit more!
There's no space!
I'm going to throw up right away.
It's so hot!
It's the worst when the cooler breaks at a time like this.
I feel like I'm going to get wet even with the snow.
I know.
Huh?
What's that?
It's the mountain!
The lights are different after all.
Ryo-chan, can you give me some too?
No.
Why not?
Just a little bit.
Shaving ice is a very important thing.
You can't just get it for free.
No matter what you say, I've already paid 10,000 yen in Nakagawa.
The ice is all mine.
The ice in the refrigerator suits you, Tenkichi-kun.
What a terrible sound.
Compared to that, it's a wonderful sound.
It's like the sound of a bug.
This is Japan's traditional shaved ice.
I'll put some syrup on it.
It's done!
The ice is as delicate and beautiful as the snow.
I'll have a bite first.
It's good!
The real one is different after all.
And it's also pleasant.
The smell of water and the smell of the refrigerator is mixed together.
It's really pleasant.
Mmm...
This is so good.
It's full of the romance of Taiko.
It has to come from the beautiful ice.
It's the best shaved ice in the world.
No, actually, this should be called shaved ice.
The ice I shaved in the refrigerator is no longer shaved ice.
You ate the best shaved ice I made yesterday.
That's right.
I'll make it with milk this time.
Huh?
Hey, what?!
Don't steal it!
I'll arrest you!
Just a little bit is fine.
Thanks to this shaved ice, the heat is getting through.
Look, the car is moving.
Hurry up and get to work.
Oh, Keiichi.
Mmm...
It's beautiful.
It's really delicious!
It's just like a gourmet shaved ice!
Oh, I want you guys to eat it too.
I'm really satisfied with shaved ice like that.
It's really refreshing.
The brilliance of this elegant ice and the softness of the milk.
The sound of the ice popping is the elegance of Venus's whisper, which woke up from a sleep of millions of years.
Fantastic!
This is the color of the rose and the color of shaved ice!
I'm going to eat it all!
The inside of my mouth is cold and numb.
I'm going to eat it all! But when it comes to the 70th cup, it's a little...
Aren't you tired of it? It's about time.
What?
That's not true!
Is this the ice?
It's cold.
It's dangerous, so move away from here.
It feels good.
Damn it!
Eat this! It's my shaved ice!
Don't make it your own!
I paid for it and bought it.
It's my meal for a week!
It's delicious!
It tastes like strawberry and has milk topping.
I ate it all and my head is numb.
Are you okay, Senpai?
Don't push yourself too hard.
I gave it to a neighbor.
What is this?
If you think this is just water, you can drink as much as you want!
It's water for two-thirds of the human body.
There are still so many people left.
All right, it's a special service for you guys.
I'll give you this full-fledged meal shaved ice.
I've already eaten it, so it's okay.
That's right. I don't need it.
Ryo-chan, take responsibility.
All right, I'll eat it all.
I'll eat it all.
What are you going to do?
It's decided.
I'm going to eat it.
I only have strawberry flavor and milk flavor, so I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to put cola on this side and change it with ketchup sauce.
I'm going to put eggs and natto on this side.
I'm going to eat it with vitamin drinks.
Doesn't it look delicious?
Are you really going to eat it?
Of course.
It's getting cold.
I'll drink tea and warm up.
All right, it's warm.
I can't eat any more.
What are you going to do with the rest?
I'm going to make rice balls and eat them later.
What is this?
Ryotsu, is it your doing again?
What is it?
I didn't do anything.
Come on.
My ears are stretching.
What is this?
That phone is useless.
This is a stage device I prepared for the chief.
For me?
That's right.
I'm going to have Ryuhyo Nagaretabi, the chief's specialty, sing in karaoke in this ice mountain bag.
Don't fool me.
This is the ice from the North Pole that was imported directly from Greenland.
Ryo-chan bought it for 10,000 yen from Kei-chan.
Ryotsu.
How about a cup of tea, chief?
I don't need it.
Put an end to this ice.
Listen to me.
Even if you say that,
Shut up.
If this ice doesn't disappear until tomorrow,
You will be sent to the North Pole.
North Pole?
Is there such a place?
I'll make it especially for you.
Do you understand, Ryotsu?
There is still a lot of ice.
There is no way I can eat all of this today.
This is it.
The ice mountain that Ryo-san bought.
This is the ice mountain of the North Pole.
If you stand out this much,
it will be a rumor.
What are you going to do?
I thought I'd shave all of this and eat it.
If you make this much ice into shaved ice,
you can ski.
That's it.
I like this hot summer, I am going to do ski.
I'm going to take this.
Rental skiing and rental snowboarding.
I don't mind if I think about it.
I can make money and clean up the ice.
It's exactly the same.
Okay, let's get started.
What is this?
Even if this hand is mine...
Senpai, what are you going to start again?
I'm sure it's about money.
Ryo-chan's power is all about money.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning, Ryo-san.
Please carry the rest.
Next is the seat.
Okay.
It's a woman's morning meal.
Now the road is clear.
Kankichi, what are you doing with the ice?
I did a lot.
Ryo-san, I brought ski and snowboarding.
Please put it there.
Okay.
Okay, now I'm ready.
I did pretty well.
Welcome, welcome.
Ryo-tsu Snowland.
I'm back.
What is Ryo-tsu Snowland?
Welcome, welcome.
It's snowing in the middle of summer.
It's a small town like a desert.
In the middle of summer, you can enjoy skiing, snowboarding,
and even bobsleigh.
That's it.
Let's go in.
Yeah, that sounds fun.
Me too.
The traffic jam has been resolved, but there's still a lot to do.
Yes, yes.
This is the snowboard.
You can't bring it in.
Yes, the company is 10% off.
How about that snowboard?
Yes, yes.
Welcome, welcome.
Thank you.
I think this will be a few million yen.
That's right.
Snowboard
Come on, come on.
When you're hungry,
it's snowland specialty, kourizushi.
It's a fish that makes your parents cry.
It's a favorite egg for children.
If you don't eat this,
you won't get anything.
Then grab one.
I want an egg.
Okay, one egg.
Wait.
The rice is frozen.
That's right, It's frozen.
It's cold, so it lasts a long time.
How do you eat it?
You eat it with jam.
It's refreshing.
Let's eat it with jam.
If you don't like raw food,
how about ice curry?
Welcome.
Even curry is ice?
I want that.
Curry.
I can still eat it.
If you hit it,
you'll get a car and an egg.
If you throw it,
you'll be happy.
Uncle, give it to me.
Me too.
Don't push it.
The egg is 200 yen here.
Me too.
I can't do this anymore.
What?
Wait, What?
Ryo-tsu?
He made a snow land in the park.
He rents skis and snowboards
and earns money.
What a guy.
If you make so much money,
do you want to buy another mountain?
Ryo-tsu.
What is it, chief?
You make this in the park
and earn money?
No way.
I don't just make ice.
I want to make a place
for the local residents.
I want the people of Kameyari
to be happy.
What is this?
What is it?
Ryo-tsu!
I know you have money behind your back.
Give it back to everyone!
No way!
Wait!
Time out!
It went well.
What?
Ryo-tsu!
I got it.
I have an egg.
Wasabi!
Wait!
What?
Damn it!
No way!
It's an earthquake!
Wait!
Ouch!
Watch out!
Damn it!
It's mine!
I won't give it to anyone!
Come on!
Get ready, Ryo-tsu!
What?
I won't do that!
You're naive!
It's collapsing!
It's so heavy!
What is that?
Where did everyone go?
It's time to retreat.
Ryo-tsu!
It's strange.
No one is here.
Chief!
Help me!
I protected you.
Give this money back to everyone.
No!
It's mine!
Good for you.
You used up all the ice.
I'm a stingy man.
I use up all my money.
I wonder if my instinct makes me do that.
Shut up!
I'm done for!
If I make Reiko angry,
I'll be in big trouble!
I'll throw away the high-speed cars!
I'll run the high-speed roads backwards!
Then I won't have a wife!
Next time, on Reiko,
I'll chase after her with anger!
Let's do this!