Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Reiko, the Great Pursuer of Anger!
Move, move!
The speedometer is entering the red zone of 1 million revolutions!
Power up to 2 million revolutions!
Hand on the rescue curve!
This is scary! It's dangerous!
Stop at the corner.
Look right, look left, and check your safety.
Got it?
Let's go!
Don't jump out!
Are you okay?
If we're late for the shift, Ryo-chan will be so noisy!
Reiko!
Hello, how's the old man's cold?
His fever has gone down, so he'll be able to go out in a couple of days.
It's hard being all alone, but take care of yourself.
Take care!
Old man!
I'm grateful to Reiko-chan for always taking care of me.
It's business, but bring it.
Um, I was told it was 12 o'clock, but I'm completely late.
Here.
Thank you very much!
You're a good girl, Reiko-chan.
There aren't many good girls like her these days.
She's strong, and she's also beautiful.
I wonder if she can be replaced by my wife.
Really?
Wait a minute!
Let's cross, old lady.
Oh, yes.
If we take a detour, there's a pedestrian bridge.
There are a lot of cars coming this way.
There will be a traffic light soon, so please be patient.
Hurry up!
Please wait a moment.
Yes, yes.
What is it?
That old lady waited a long time to cross this bridge.
Wait a moment.
If you hold on for about 30 seconds...
Yes.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
No, be careful.
I'm glad.
Reiko-san, can you come here for a moment?
It's been here every day for a while.
It's in front of the kindergarten, and the child is in the shade of the car, so it's dangerous.
I'm warning you many times, but you don't listen to me.
It's in the middle of the pedestrian crossing, Tsuzushi.
Please move the car number that is parked in front of the kindergarten immediately.
By the way, I'm waiting for you.
I'm at the repair factory in the neighborhood.
You're coming, aren't you?
These people said the same thing yesterday.
It's all a lie.
Here's the study book.
Please forgive me.
I don't have any points anymore.
You're so cute.
I won't give you a license.
Don't even move.
I won't move.
Then I'll move it for you.
What's that?
It's supposed to be a pump for jack-up.
If you raise the level to the maximum, it will swell up to anywhere.
Hey, you idiot, stop it.
I don't know how to stop it.
It's my first time using it.
Damn it.
What?
Hey!
You bastard, get out of the way.
It's a colorful foot.
It's a terrible foot.
I can't move on like this.
Of course.
Pay the fine properly.
Oh, no.
Welcome back.
You're late.
I'm sorry, Ryo-chan.
The transfer time is 12 o'clock in the afternoon.
It's past 1 o'clock.
I'm in a bad mood.
Patroll and my life.
Which one is more important?
Even if you say it's a transfer,
you're still there in the middle of the day.
Chief Ohara won't come today.
So I'll be like that all the time.
I'm going to Patroll.
By the way, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
You won't come back no matter how long it takes.
I couldn't go out for lunch.
Hey, don't boil the noodles too much.
Add a lot of green onions.
I didn't forget the transfer time.
It was hard.
That's it.
Next time, next time.
Hey, Reiko.
What's wrong, Ryo-chan?
Take the newspaper there.
Isn't it faster to take the newspaper there?
There's a vicious criminal.
Even if you say it's a car accident,
it doesn't work at all.
You think you're a criminal,
but you're licking it from the head.
By the way,
press my back.
It's lower.
Lower.
Not there.
Press it.
Like this?
No, it doesn't work at all.
It doesn't work at all.
That's why you're licking it.
It has nothing to do with it.
What you need to control
is the power of the face.
Your face doesn't have the power of the face.
It's itchy.
Please write it down there.
Here?
Hey, is the ramen okay?
Don't add too much.
Oh, it's itchy again.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
The last one is the power of the face.
Oh, it's itchy.
I'll hit you if you want.
I'll run away if you want.
What's that?
It's a special pillow for Ryo-chan.
It's handmade.
What?
Ouch!
How is it?
Don't let your guard down.
Start the counterattack!
Think of the power of a man!
You bastard!
Are you done?
The game starts now.
If you can't do it,
use your own power.
Ouch!
I got it!
I'll kill you!
Not yet!
You're so obsessive.
Yes?
I saw the poster.
Who did this?
Reiko, right?
Who are you?
Please go on a date with me.
What's wrong with this number?
It was written on the poster.
What's wrong?
I don't know what's wrong with the poster.
Hello?
Are you Reiko?
Who are you?
I'll go to the beach with you.
I won't go.
Then go ahead.
Go alone.
What's this?
A date?
I'll lend it to you.
Reiko?
Yes?
Are you asking for a date?
I'll give you 5,000 yen as an introduction fee.
Ouch!
If you say something stupid,
I'll arrest you.
Reiko!
There's a lot of this on the table.
What's this?
To Be Continued
The people just now
called because they saw this.
It's a bad photo.
Who is this?
I took it off a lot,
but it's still stuck on the side of the road.
It's a bad guy.
Reiko, what do you think?
It's obvious.
This is Naoko.
Please respond.
We found a suspicious large dump.
We are currently tracking
and heading north in the direction of Kameari.
Please support us.
The driver
was hanging around
Reiko's poster.
Roger.
I'll lock you up.
It's terrible.
It's Reiko's large dump.
Ugh.
Both of them
are checking the signal.
Reiko,
the dump was pulled away.
Can't you see it?
Is that it?
Reiko,
hurry up!
What?
Hey!
It's dangerous!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm glad.
Look!
I turned my back!
Ouch!
I hit my back.
I won't forgive you!
Reiko,
ouch!
Hurry up!
Put your seatbelt on!
I have an announcement.
We are currently tracking
and heading north in the direction of Kameari.
The driver
was hanging around Reiko's poster.
Roger.
I'll lock you up.
Put your seatbelt on!
Ouch!
I won't let you get away!
I found it!
Take this chance!
It's the same scene as the rumor.
What happened, Reiko?
Listen up, you guys.
You were about to pull the kids away.
Besides,
what did I do wrong?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Then why did you hang around the city?
Reiko!
Look over there!
It's them!
They?
I found them!
They were coming.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Hurry up!
This is the car
that was parked at the kindergarten.
They're the bad guys.
What a bad car.
It's like a natural monument.
What are you doing?
Don't drive so fast!
Shut up!
Hey!
Don't let them get away!
If you're going to do that,
do it faster!
You're so stubborn!
Hey!
What are you doing?
You're the bad guy!
You broke my car!
Let's go back to the school.
That's right!
Stop it!
Wait!
Calm down, Reiko!
I know how you feel,
but Mini Pat is only a 550 cc light car.
You can't catch up with the 2000 cc guys!
Hey, they're still following us!
They're not just bad guys.
It's not easy to go that far with a light car.
Let's go at high speed.
We can't go that fast with that car.
They're going at high speed.
We can't catch up with them with this car.
This is Reiko.
This is Kameyari Park.
Kei, I have a favor to ask you.
I can't see anymore.
Hey, Reiko!
Oh, no!
Hurry up and stop!
Here we are!
It's the Audi Quattro!
Sorry for being late.
I just got here yesterday.
This is the car that won the Monte Carlo Rally.
I couldn't make it.
The collector gave it to me.
Well, I'm going to borrow it.
They weren't here before,
but something strange is following us instead of Mini Pat.
Hey, could it be them?
Hey, Nikusama!
Huh?
What's going on?
It's like a gas station.
I'm so frustrated!
What's going on, Nakagawa?
Just fill it up with gas.
There's no gas at high speed.
I found gasoline!
Reiko, slow down.
I'll get it from the tank car behind you.
What?
Oh, no!
What are they doing?
Damn it!
I'm so tired that I can't get out.
One liter is 100 yen.
45 liters is 4,500 yen.
Reiko, buy me 4,500 yen.
It's not bad.
It's not bad?
Does that mean you don't need it?
Okay, I'll pay for it.
I'll pay for it.
What is this?
Give me my money!
Reiko, hurry up!
Here it comes again.
Oh, no!
Damn it!
My money!
It's sweet!
Are you running away?
Reiko, go!
I'll forgive you!
Wait a minute!
Don't go on the highway!
You've gone too far, Reiko!
Damn it!
We can't go on the highway!
How far can we go by that car?
Calm down, Reiko!
I sent out two Audi cars,
but their car was blown up!
It's too much!
Is it a dream?
I'm sorry!
Help me!
It's scary!
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
Help me!
It's scary!
It's scary when you look at a woman like that.
You must not let her turn into an enemy.
I don't mind if she climbs up, but I wonder what she's up to.
Good morning.
I forgot my wax.
Thank you for your hard work.
What's wrong with those two?
They fell in love with Reiko's driving technique and decided to get into the car on their own.
It's been a long time since I've had such a scary feeling.
You guys should be careful of Reiko, okay?
Ryo-chan, did you call me?
Here, have some tea.
Reiko-san, thank you for the delicious tea you always make.
Thank you.
The weather is nice.
Be careful.
I know.
Oh, the old lady from before.
You're so kind.
You're welcome.
Reiko-chan.
Oh, old lady, what's wrong?
Actually, Reiko-chan has an affair.
What?
You're also an old lady, aren't you?
Old lady.
Hey.
If you marry her, you'll have a lot of money.
This year is the year of the Olympics.
The year of the Olympics.
Speaking of the Olympics, it's the day life.
The day life is when you wake up once every four years.
But this guy has a lot of superpowers.
Next time, on Waking Up, Police Officer Tomi.
Thank you.
To be continued.